Chapter 113 – Casually Dungeoning

This time, the Vampire Knight didn’t have a set fodder. However, the previous fodder didn’t expire. Fortunately, after this cycle, the effects had somewhat decreased.

But it didn’t matter if the effects decreased. With the BOSS’s percent lifesteal, there was no way they could let him have his way. Ye Xiu, Tang Rou, and Su Mucheng rushed forward after the bats transformed back into the Vampire Knight. They continued to surround and attack him, while Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon continued to watch as spectators.

After a few cycles, the Vampire Knight’s life finally dropped to 10%. However, no one was worried about his Red Blood status. This was because when the Vampire Knight turned Enraged after dropping to Red Blood, it would set new fodder without replacing the old fodder. In theory, this meant that all five players could become fodder, which meant that no matter who fought it, they would have their life stolen.

But with Ye Xiu’s and Su Mucheng’s level of skill, the Vampire Knight’s bat transformation was already an empty threat. They didn’t need to care about such a change.

The Red Blood Vampire Knight screeched as he struggled until finally, he died under the three player’s attacks. After falling to the ground, all of the items that could be dropped had already all dropped. Ye Xiu looked over them. He didn’t see that scarlet Vampiric Lightsaber, but wasn’t too disappointed.

This was an Orange equipment, a type of equipment that heavily depended on your luck. If you didn’t have the right mindset towards it, then it would be easy for you to curse your luck and cause you to lose all hope in yourself.

“Wow! Two Purple eggs!!” Su Mucheng cried out in astonishment.

Ye Xiu stared blankly. Two Purple eggs was a saying in Glory. It meant that two Purple equipment dropped when the monster died. To raise one and infer three, two Blue eggs, three Purple eggs, four Orange eggs could all be said as long as you actually encountered such a situation.

The probability of two purple eggs obviously wasn’t high. However, of the equipment that the Vampire Knight dropped, the only item Ye Xiu wanted was the Vampiric Lightsaber. As for rest, even if eight purple eggs came out, he still wouldn’t care.

“It’s the Shield and Cloak.” Seven Fields looked over them and said.

After changing classes, the Shield could only be used by a Knight. Shields had two main attributes. The first was increased defense and the second was damage absorption. They were both important in increasing the Knight’s survivability. The Shield dropped from the Vampire Knight was his Vampiric Shield. It increased defense by 20% and and had 12% damage absorption. Besides this, it also had an additional effect: all damage done would have 2% Life Return.

“Not bad.” Ye Xiu praised, “Then give it to whoever can use it!” Ye Xiu was talking about Seven Field’s friends. Drifting Water was a Knight, while Sunset Clouds was a Blade Master. Except Ye Xiu already forgot which one was the knight and could only say “whoever it was”.

“There’s also the Vampire Cloak. Vitality +15, Strength +15, 2% Lifesteal for Melee Attacks.” Seven Fields said. “Lifesteal” and that shield’s “Life Return” were antonyms. Lifesteal was damage done to the target would change into the user’s health. Life Return meant that when the user was attacked, the damage done to the user would change into the user’s health.

The Cloak was an accessory type equipment. Usually, they had this type of additional base stats and an additional effect. The current five players were all physical damage type classes, so everyone could use the Cloak. However, Seven Fields didn’t really do anything in the battle against the Vampire Knight. How could he shamelessly ask for it? So he directly renounced it. As for Sleeping Moon, after becoming fodder, he let the three experts attack the BOSS with ease, so his impact in the battle wasn’t small. However, this contribution was quite shameful to be considered as one, so he also renounced it.

Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist was long-ranged, so that 2% Lifesteal for Melee Attacks was completely wasted on her, so she also renounced it.

In the end, only Ye Xiu and Tang Rou remained. How could Ye Xiu care about these low-level equipment? He also renounced it. Up until finally, Tang Rou was extremely puzzled: “Why did everyone renounce it?”

“I’m long-ranged!” Su Mucheng was the most justified.

“Cough cough……” Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon didn’t utter a word. If no one wanted it, it wasn’t as if they weren’t going to roll for it.

“You use it!” Ye Xiu said.

“Can’t you guys all use it too?” Although Tang Rou was a noob, she knew that physical classes needed strength, while magic classes needed intelligence. How could she not have understood this sort of basic knowledge by now? This Cloak could clearly be used by everyone, but they all renounced it. The strong-headed Tang Rou didn’t want to take it so conveniently.

“Roll for it!” Tang Rou said.

“Okay, okay. Roll, roll. Everyone come and roll. Whoever rolls for it gets it.” It was just a small matter. Ye Xiu didn’t want to get caught up with it.

Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon still wanted to decline, but Ye Xiu’s hands were quicker. They had previously renounced it, so they no longer had the button for rolling. As a result, they had to give the command for rolling in the chat box. In the end, Ye Xiu rolled a beautiful 100 and completely decimated his opponents.

“Oh…….”

“Then it’s yours.” Tang Rou had also renounced it before, so the Cloak was just lying on the ground.

Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon’s cheeks streamed with tears. They had wanted to decline it. And if the everyone insisted, then they would reluctantly roll for it! But he deserved to be called brother expert! Everything he did was extraordinary. He never gave others a chance……

“Then it’s mine.” Ye Xiu said this and had Lord Grim pick up the Cloak. Although it was a low-leveled equipment, even if he didn’t care, it’s not like he wouldn’t turn his back on it. After picking it up, he put it on at once. This Vampire’s clothing and the Cloak were pretty much the same. From the back, Lord Grim looked exactly the same as the Vampire Knight.

Ye Xiu opened his character profile and casually looked at his model. He didn’t care too much. In so many years, what dress up hadn’t he been in?

“Continue, continue.” Ye Xiu yelled. The party continued forward. Because of the hidden BOSS, setting a record this run had already become like floating clouds. Everyone had run this dungeon before, so no one was a stranger to it. They casually rolled through it.

Without resting, they continued on for their second run. This time, no hidden BOSS appeared, so everyone immediately moved forward with a record-setting mindset. Ye Xiu instructed them, seeking after zero mistakes and good coordination. However, Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon’s skill and equipment were all a degree lower. There were always times when the situation was beyond their ability. The current record was set with great effort by Level 27s. Breaking it meant that they couldn’t afford to be sloppy.

In the two following runs, Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon each nervously made their own large and small mistakes. In the end, the difference between their time and the record was only off by a hair. This was too much of a hit to them. The two all knew that if they had made a fewer mistakes, then they would have broken the record long ago.

“Sigh…… brother expert. It seems like us two aren’t good enough. Do you want to switch players to set it?” Seven Fields said in embarrassment. Boneyard could be run four times everyday. Right now, the five players could still run it one more time.

On the side, Sleeping Moon was unwilling to accept it. But no choice, it was a fact that he and Seven Fields weren’t able to keep up. But if the party lowered their tempo to let them relax a bit, then they wouldn’t be able to set a new record.

“Switch players? Weren’t you the one that wanted to set a record?” Ye Xiu asked Seven Fields.

Seven Field’s cheeks streamed with tears. Only then did he recall, in the beginning, when he asked whether or not they could set a new record. In the end, he was the one who gave up and made himself look like he had no resolve. Even Sleeping Moon chose the opportunity to look down on him: “Yeah, Seven Fields, you really have no future.”

“F*ck!” Seven Fields cursed, “We’ll definitely have it this time.”

The two players summoned up their spirits and entered the dungeon their final run. Focused and concentrating with all of their might, adding on to their previous experiences, their performance was finally smooth the entire way through. The two were extremely happy with themselves. In the blink of an eye, they reached the final BOSS. Here, the two player’s tasks were easy. It was the part where making mistakes was harder than not making mistakes. Finally, the BOSS fell and a system announcement popped up: Congratulations to players: Lord Grim, Seven Fields, Sleeping Moon, Soft Mist, Cleansing Mist, for breaking the Boneyard clear record, time: 23:54:71.

This record wasn’t much better than the previous Tyrannical Ambition’s record. But in the eyes of the two carried Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon. Being able to improve the record by a minute was already extremely good for their current party setup. Currently, in the competition between the big guilds, they were only improving the records by a few seconds.

Breaking the Boneyard record wasn’t anything rare, but having Lord Grim’s famous name appear was a completely different matter. The first reactions of each of the big guild’s leaders was: which guild invited him to set a new record? Blue Brook Guild’s Blue River and Tyrannical Ambition’s Cold Night even directly asked him.

And in the end, Ye Xiu gave them the reply: I was just leveling and casually dungeoning.

The two guild leader’s cheeks streamed with tears! This casual dungeoning had broken their records. If this wasn’t him showing his strength, then what was it?

Outside of this, there was still Liu Hao. His Hateful Sword never went offline. What was he doing? He was in the Arena playing with Steamed Bun Invasion.

Liu Hao had wanted to whisper to him with Hateful Sword, but knowing that Steamed Bun was playing in the Arena again, he was suddenly hit with a bright idea. He ran to the Arena and fought with Steamed Bun Invasion. He wasn’t able to get anything out of directly contacting Ye Qiu, so wouldn’t it be better to begin with the players close to him? Liu Hao felt that this wasn’t a bad idea.

Fighting with Steamed Bun Invasion was quite exhausting for Liu Hao. He had to hide his strength! But he also couldn’t hide too much. As a result, he had to make every battle extremely close. Steamed Bun Invasion wasn’t weak either. The battle wasn’t easy to control, so it was very demanding for Liu Hao. While carefully fighting, he also had to use every possible means to get information out of Steamed Bun Invasion.

If Steamed Bun Invasion knew anything, it wasn’t as if he wouldn’t say it. The problem was that he himself didn’t know anything. He wasn’t even familiar with the game Glory itself, so his descriptions of his dungeoning weren’t clear. He couldn’t even name what skills the other players used. And in the end, he began describing how great his own strength was.

Liu Hao was trying hard to decipher the information that was coming out from the noob’s mouth. After quite a long time, he was still unable to understand anything. Suddenly, a system announcement popped up and that extremely sensitive name caught his eye.

How???

Liu Hao was astonished. Could it be that this Steamed Bun Invasion wasn’t a member of Ye Qiu’s main force? Why wasn’t he called over to set this record? Liu Hao went to look for Steamed Bun Invasion to play. A part of this reason: to get familiar with Steamed Bun Invasion and take the opportunity to become a member of the main force.

“This…… Why didn’t God call you over to set a record?” Liu hao asked Steamed Bun Invasion.

“Remember this well. In the Arena, if you want to obtain victory, the the first thing you have to do is concentrate. You. You’re not focused enough.” Steamed Bun Invasion lectured.

“F*CK!!!” Liu Hao turned furious. Who does this guy think he is! How dare he lecture ME!

Chapter 114 – Control Over Records

That was the last straw for Liu Hao. This time, he didn’t hold back and flattened Steamed Bun Invasion back into dough.

“You fought really well.” Steamed Bun Invasion said, “It looks like what I said aroused your spirit. Okay, then I won’t say anything more.”

“I’m out!” Liu Hao directly let Hateful Sword leave the Arena. If he continued playing, then he felt that he’d smash his newly replaced keyboard into pieces again.

“God, you set another record! Congratulations.” Liu Hao sent Lord Grim his felicitations.

“I was just casually dungeoning.” Ye Xiu’’s reply was the same as his reply to the guild leaders.

“To be able to break a record while casually dungeoning, that’s too amazing.” Liu Hao falsely flattered, while his mouth was actually cursing non-stop.

“It was just a fluke. It took a few times before we set it.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh, then do you have a space now?” Liu Hao asked.

“So sorry…….” Ye Xiu said.

“Then I’ll be going off first.” Liu Hao grinded his teeth and left.

“See you later.”

For Ye Xiu and the others, after breaking the record, there was a 100% chance of receiving a Purple equipment as a reward. In the end, they were rewarded with a Level 25 Leather Armor. Of the five players, only Soft Mist’s Battle Mage was proficient with Leather Armor. Seven Fields, Sleeping Moon, and Cleansing Mist naturally chose to renounce it. Lord Grim’s unspecialized character class wasn’t proficient in anything, but after expressing that the Leather Armor’s defense was beneath him, this Leather Armor was given to Soft Mist to wear.

With regards to armor, it was quite miserable for unspecialized characters. They weren’t proficient in any, so they didn’t get any additional effects.

After splitting the equipment, the five players went to run Frost Forest for experience. On the way there, a message popped up in the world channel claiming that Full Moon Guild was responsible for Boneyard’s record.

“Full Moon Guild? That sounds a little familiar!” Ye Xiu mumbled to the five players.

“Never heard of them.” Su Mucheng said.

“I don’t understand.” Tang Rou said.

“Our guild……” Seven Field’s and Sleeping Moon’s faces were burning hot and were promptly roared at in their guild channel. The guild members hadn’t given them any prior warning. After seeing their two names in the record-setting party, they inexplicably tried to get publicity. Full Moon Guild was just a normal guild. They weren’t like Blue Brook Guild and the others with a Club behind them. Their strength was far off from the big guilds’ strength by a large margin. To rely on their own strength to set a record was something that they had never even thought of.

“Woah, in any case, it’s your two names up there. All this yelling is just a joke to you two.” Full Moon Guild’s players all smiled mischievously at the two of them.

“Exactly, exactly. Speaking of this, it seems like you guys are close to Lord Grim? When are you going to let him help our guild set a record? Let us be in the spotlight too.” Everyone in the guild channel was jeering.

Jealousy! This was plain jealousy! Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon angrily thought. These guys saw that they had mixed in with brother expert quite a few times and appeared on TV. They had appeared on so many leaderboards and now that they had mingled onto one again, their jealousy exploded out, so they deliberately mocked them. This sort of behavior was quite petty. The two didn’t know how to explain it to brother expert. The guild wouldn’t listen to anything they said. These guys were still incessantly typing in the world channel that the record was set by them.

Ye Xiu also quickly received messages secretly from the guild leaders. Full Moon Guild was so insignificant that Blue River and Cold Night had never even heard of them. They just asked what the situation was.

Ye Xiu was helpless. He could only say it was just friends joking around.

The two guild leaders heaved a sigh of relief. Because the subject happened to be on this, Cold Night took advantage to conveniently ask Ye Xiu whether he would be hired by two guilds simultaneously and then break his own record.

“That isn’t good!” Ye Xiu replied, “For the records I set, I can’t guarantee that others won’t be able to beat it. But I definitely won’t break my own again.”

“Then this current record doesn’t count, right?” Cold Night said.

“Of course this doesn’t count…….” Ye Xiu replied.

“How much better can the record be?” Cold Night asked.

“This…… With a better party setup, three minutes!” Ye Xiu said.

Three minutes! Cold Night sucked in a cold breath. If the current record was improved by three minutes, then it would break the fastest record in all ten servers. This was clearly another height that normal players had no way of reaching. If it was this type of achievement, then as no one invited similar-level experts to substitute in, then it was practically unbeatable!

“Then, what if we waited until you were Level 27?” Cold Night asked.

“The difference between setting it at Level 27 and Level 25 isn’t actually too big. Of course, there is still a small difference. I should be able to set it within the 20 minute mark!” Ye Xiu replied.

“Oh, then currently, how many guilds are you in contact with?” Cold Night asked a relatively sensitive subject.

“Not many…….” Ye Xiu looked at his chat box. Besides Cold Night, there was only Blue Brook Guild’s Blue River. The other big guilds hadn’t contacted him, which was clearly because the current competition for the records was both chaotic and high-end. Each of the big guilds were all already in a wait-and-see state.

This type of situation wasn’t one that Ye Xiu wanted to see. He clearly knew where the problem was: he had lost control over the fastest record.

In the competition for Frost Forest’s record, from a short-term perspective, he took control two times, one after another. But the final record still fell into Excellent Dynasty’s hands. On the surface, Ye Xiu looked as if he was indifferent. But in his heart, he clearly understood what a heavy blow this was to him.

It was all because of the existence of this that all of those guilds sunk into a wait-and-see state. Because of this, Lord Grim was no longer a guarantee for the fastest dungeon record. Even if his record was far higher than the normal record, there were outside players that could still break his record in the tenth server. If the situation stayed the same, then obviously no one would look for him to break the record.

Currently, Blue Brook Guild and Tyrannical Ambition’s players still looked for him all because these two guilds had cooperated with him before and had personally seen his skill. This was why they still held confidence in him. But Ye Xiu was afraid that Frost Forest’s record had already sown a seed of doubt into these two’s hearts. The following competition for Boneyard became another test for him. If this time, he broke the record, but was still unable to hold the spot for fastest record. Then even though he could still obtain the rewards, in the next dungeon, he was afraid that even these two guilds wouldn’t look for him.

If he could improve the Frost Forest’s record again, then it would be a powerful counter attack. However, the current record made Ye Xiu feel a bit helpless. Just like what he once said, this was only a low-leveled dungeon. No matter if it was him or Liu Hao’s party, their skill was way above the dungeon. Thus, against this dungeon, tactics, skill and so on couldn’t make too much of a difference. As a result, once Liu Hao went all out, the record set by his more optimal party made Ye Xiu feel somewhat helpless.

Moreover, he didn’t have too many players he could choose from to create the most optimal party. On the other hand, Excellent Dynasty could provide the necessary accounts for the required party set-up. As a pro-player, besides their most proficient class, they also had some understanding of all the other classes. If they switched classes, even if they couldn’t display the greatest strength, it was still a low-leveled dungeon and nothing more. Pro-players simply didn’t need their complete strength…..

Ye Xiu was thinking while running the Frost Forest dungeon with the other four players. In the process, he was not only fighting monsters, but he was also carefully observing the dungeon. He wanted to see if there was any sort of way to break through the record. In the end, after clearing the dungeon four times, he hadn’t come up with anything. After finishing the dungeon runs, Su Mucheng was the first to log-out. Tang Rou and the others were prepared to continue power leveling. Ye Xiu didn’t follow them and logged out of the game.

“Why’d you stop playing?” Tang Rou got up and moved around. She went for a walk and went to greet Ye Xiu.

“Oh. I’m going to do some research for the next dungeon.” Ye Xiu said.

“The next dungeon?”

“Boneyard!” Ye Xiu was currently gathering a large amount of information.

“What about Frost Forest?” Tang Rou cared quite a bit about the fact that their Frost Forest record had been broken.

“That…… unless we had better equipment, it’ll be very hard to break it.” Ye Xiu said. Just before, when he ran the four dungeons, he was completely stumped. However, Ye Xiu still had some hope for Boneyard.

Tang Rou was silent. Although she wasn’t willing to accept it, she knew that she didn’t really have the right to speak. Her ability to judge was still far off from Ye Xiu’s by a large margin.

“What’s wrong with fighting Boneyard in the same way we do now?” Tang Rou tried hard to learn.

“There isn’t a problem……. However, our goal is to set a record that no one else will be able to break!” Ye Xiu said.

“Yeah, yeah! That’s good!” Tang Rou liked this type of goal.

Tang Rou went back to continue playing, while Ye Xiu continued to look for info.

“There’s got to be a newer strategy…….” Ye Xiu looked at the info and felt his heart shake. He hadn’t discovered anything surprising from all the info. Rather, he discovered that all of the info was quite old-fashioned. Clearly, this was because this was a low-leveled dungeon. As a result, besides the players who researched it in the beginning stages of the game, all of the later players followed the guides that were previously written. There would occasionally be a few changes in the particulars, but the general strategy never changed. After all, for this type of low-end dungeon, in the stage of the game where players would flash by it, there simply wasn’t much value in conducting further research.

Looking at the info, checking the data, racking his brains, and recalling these past few days of running the dungeon, a new strategy gradually formed in Ye Xiu’s mind.

“Good, tomorrow we’ll try it.” Ye Xiu straightened out his line of thinking again. He even wrote down a few of the important points and then nodded his head. Soon after, he logged into the game. Tang Rou immediately sent a message: “How is it?”

“I’ve got a general idea. We’ll try it tomorrow.”

“Okay.”

The two players each minded their own business and leveled, without a word the whole night.

In Club Excellent Era, the next day, Liu Hao got a call from Chen Yehui early in the morning.

“Liu, Ye Qiu set the record for Boneyard.” Chen Yehui said.

“I know. I was there yesterday night!” Liu Hao replied.

“Oh……. I had something to do last night, so I wasn’t there. I just found out. But it looks like the record this time isn’t anything amazing.” Chen Yehui said.

“Yeah, he definitely wasn’t using everything he had, so there’s no need to come out yet.” Liu Hao said.

“RIght, I have info from Tyrannical Ambition and Blue Brook Guild. Ye Qiu received pay from them when he helped them set a record.

“Received pay? Ha ha ha, so he was originally selling himself! God Ye must be hard pressed for money. How much money for one dungeon? Perhaps I’ll buy him to do our labor!” Liu Hao was extremely happy.

“Oh, he’s not taking money. He wanted several specific uncommon material.” Chen Yehui said.

“He wants uncommon material!!” Liu Hao suddenly thought of something.

Chapter 115 – Going All Out

Uncommon materials, self-made equipment!!

Liu Hao quickly thought of these two things and then immediately understood Ye Xiu’s purpose. He suddenly laughed wildly: “HA HA HA HA HA, so this is his plan.”

On the other line, Chen Yehui almost threw out his phone in surprise. After steadying himself, he carefully asked: “What do you mean?”

“Hmm, it’s too bad. He’s already been completely seen through by me. With his current state, how does he plan on fighting me? Is he going to start over and try again? Dream on!!” Liu Hao was already talking to himself. Chen Yehui heard this while saying helplessly: “Liu, if there’s nothing else to attend to, then I’m going to hang up!”

“Okay, go back and prepare accounts to use for Boneyard. I need a Spellblade, Sharpshooter, Striker, Blade Master, and a Witch.” Liu Hao ordered.

“Okay.” Chen Yehui replied. Hearing these five classes, he was secretly startled. For the previous record, Liu Hao had only picked three classes. This time, he had picked five classes. Could it be that he was going to bring out five pro-players to set the record for Boneyard? What exactly has he discovered? He was actually starting to put even more energy on this dungeon.

In Happy Internet Cafe, Ye Xiu and Tang Rou continued to level and weren’t doing anything out of the ordinary. Chen Guo had already become numb to it. That morning, after waking up, Ye Xiu unexpectedly went over to look for her.

“Boss, lend me your account for me to play with!” Ye Xiu had come over to borrow her account card.

“What are you planning on doing?” Chen Guo asked.

“Clearing a low-leveled dungeon.” Ye Xiu said.

“Clearing a low-leveled dungeon?” Chen Guo stared blankly. She handed over her Chasing Haze while following along to see what he was planning on doing.

Chasing Haze was an account that had already entered the Heavenly Domain. But that didn’t mean she couldn’t leave the Heavenly Domain. After Ye Xiu had Chasing Haze leave the Heavenly Domain, he immediately rushed over to the low-leveled dungeon Boneyard.

The Boneyard in the old server naturally wasn’t as lively as the tenth server’s Boneyard, but there were still a few players there. Seeing a Level 70 character appear, players immediately filled the screen with messages of “Sister, please carry me.” Quite a few parties had already sent out party invites. This was the benefit of playing in an old server! When comparing leveling speed, leveling in the old server was absolutely faster than leveling in the new server. Even if you didn’t know any friends, there were quite a few high-leveled accounts that specially came to sell their services to carry low-leveled accounts.

Ye Xiu obviously ignored these players. He immediately had Chasing Haze enter the dungeon. A Level 70 account wouldn’t have any problems clearing this low-leveled dungeon, not to mention that Ye Xiu was the one controlling it. But after entering the dungeon, Ye Xiu wasn’t in a hurry to fight. He had Chasing Haze run this way and that until eventually, a mob of monsters followed behind her butt. It looked as if he were flirting with these monsters.

“What are you doing?” Chen Guo didn’t understand.

“Oh, I’m just looking at this dungeon. My account doesn’t have any entries left.” Ye Xiu explained, while playing. Chasing Haze unleashed a few skills and the mob of monsters were wiped clean. Following after, Ye Xiu fished out a notebook from his pocket.

Chen Guo was familiar with this notebook. If you took a left turn after leaving the Internet Cafe, there was a shop that sold these for 3 RMB each. Once the notebook was flipped open, Chen Guo looked at it and saw that there were already a few notes messily written in the first few pages. On them, there were even a few indistinguishable things drawn on. Ye Xiu flipped to the last page and then immediately began scribbling.

“You’re taking notes?” Chen Guo felt refreshed.

“I’m researching it in preparation for setting a new dungeon record.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo stared blankly and didn’t know what to say. Ye Xiu’s concentration and seriousness made her feel moved. She also liked Glory. She was also a considerably loyal fan. But for Ye Xiu, she could tell that he had a completely different attitude towards the game. She was playing the game, but for Ye Xiu, Chen Guo suddenly felt that the word “playing” couldn’t be used to describe him.

Chen Guo couldn’t help but think of nine years ago when she took the Internet Cafe under her care. She was completely surrounded by gazes that doubted her, though it was true that she knew nothing. From that day onwards, she soaked in the Internet Cafe and little by little paid attention to her customer’s needs. She continuously improved the Internet Cafe’s environment and tried out all sorts of methods to draw in more customers. Every night, she calculated that day’s customer flow and looked for patterns.

The her at that time was similar to the current Ye Xiu: concentrated, serious, and spared no efforts. It was extremely exhausting, but when she saw how her Internet Cafe was doing better and better every day, she felt that much more satisfied. The current Internet Cafe had a steady customer flow and the income that came in far exceeded the income at that time. But how long had it been since she had felt that sort of satisfaction?

Chen Guo was somewhat envious of Ye Xiu. But besides envy, there was also some sympathy. To put so much effort into the game, yet to be kicked out of the pro-scene, how sad! Chen Guo suddenly felt her heart ache. She couldn’t help but think of the recently retired Ye Qiu. At the time of his retirement, the person suffering the most had to be the person himself, no? It truly was a cruel word.

The pen tip scribbled across the notebook. Ye Xiu didn’t notice the change in Chen Guo behind him. Chen Guo didn’t disturb him any further and silently walked away in grief.

Ye Xiu continued to use Chasing Haze to explore Boneyard. A high-leveled account brought along with it a lot of conveniences that low-leveled accounts didn’t have. The notes written on the notebook increased more and more. Unwittingly, the run had been completed. Ye Xiu didn’t stop. He had Chasing Haze enter the dungeon again. Except this time, he spent more time playing and less time taking notes.

After three runs, Chasing Haze’s entries had all been used up. Ye Xiu harvested quite a bit from this. He logged out of the game in satisfaction and returned the account card to Chen Guo.

“How was it?” Chen Guo asked.

“Pretty good.” Ye Xiu smiled.

“Okay, you can do it!” Chen Guo said.

“What?” Ye Xiu didn’t hear her clearly.

“You can do it.” Chen Guo repeated.

“I didn’t hear wrong did I?” Ye Xiu widened his eyes. He had put so much effort in the low-leveled dungeon. Wasn’t she supposed to look down on him? She was cheering him on right now. Moreover, her tone seemed a little…….gentle? Thinking of this word, Ye Xiu couldn’t help but shiver. This word seemed a little wrong to describe Chen Guo.

“Get lost, go to sleep!!” Chen Guo was furious. This guy truly didn’t know good from bad.

Ye Xiu immediately relaxed. This was the Chen Guo he was used to. He wasn’t talking to the wrong person.

Nothing exciting happened during the day. At night, when Chen Guo was getting ready to go to bed, Ye Xiu and Tang Rou turned on their computers in glowing spirits and began their day.

In game, after Ye Xiu went online, he whispered to Steamed Bun Invasion and told him to come to dungeon with him at midnight. In the end, Steamed Bun Invasion recommended him that Hateful Sword. He said that after fighting him in the Arena for the past two days, that Hateful Sword’s skill improved by a lot.

“Really? Then when the time comes, bring him with you.” Ye Xiu laughed and then ignored the rest of Steamed Bun Invasion’s boasting. In any case, besides the four main players in their party, there was still an empty position. It didn’t matter who came.

“Okay, come along with us tonight to dungeon.” Steamed Bun Invasion told Hateful Sword, who was in the Arena with him.

“Really? That’s great.” Liu Hao really was happy. Except even though he was happy on the outside, he was dark on the inside.

“Let me tell you this. When you meet God, you have to be polite. If he can instruct you on anything, it’ll be the gift of a lifetime!” Steamed Bun Invasion said heartfeltly.

F*ck his instructions!! Liu Hao cursed inwardly. Fortunately, after being with Steamed Bun Invasion for two days, his tolerance towards the noob’s babbling nonsense had clearly improved. In the end, he still embodied his pro-level inner qualities and adaptability. Although he was furiously cursing in his heart, he was smiling on the outside: “Of course.”

At midnight 0 o’clock, the party gathered. Steamed Bun Invasion and Hateful Sword arrived from the Arena at the same time. Ye Xiu and Tang Rou were already together and they casually greeted him. Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist was the last to arrive and also greeted the newcomer.

“Is she Su Mucheng?” Liu Hao guessed. She had only said a short greeting, so he wasn’t able to tell.

However, but whether or not she was Su Mucheng wasn’t Liu Hao’s main focus. He stayed low and cautious and followed the party into the dungeon.

“This time, we’re going to be practicing the strategy for setting Boneyard’s record. It’s currently still in the testing stage, so there might be a few overlooked places. Everyone, be careful.” Ye Xiu said after entering the dungeon.

“Did you hear what he was saying? I’m talking to you!” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“Who?” Liu Hao answered. They were all characters in the game, so there wasn’t any contact between them. There was no way to tell who Steamed Bun Invasion was talking to. Noobs were noobs.

“You! Besides you, we’ve all been teammates before.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

Liu Hao slapped himself. He only had himself to blame! Why’d he have to be partners with this rotten Steamed Bun!

“Huh? What was that sound? I thought I heard a “slap” sound. Did you hear that?” Steamed Bun Invasion yelled.

Liu Hao started sweating. He really couldn’t be careless! They had even heard that.

“I heard it. Let’s begin.” Ye Xiu didn’t use any skill to change topics. Steamed Bun Invasion didn’t move or speak. No one knew whether or not this guy was trying to listen for a second “slap”.

“The most important point in setting the Boneyard record is your pathing. By using good pathing, you use the most ideal movements to alarm the least amount of monsters underneath the ground. Our strategy will be using this line of thinking. Everyone pay attention. Do your best to make sure that you don’t make a single wrong step. Hateful Sword….. come back first.” Ye Xiu said.

“Ah?” Liu Hao stared blankly.

“What ah! We just started and you’ve already began randomly running around. We won’t be bringing you!!” Steamed Bun Invasion solemnly criticized Hateful Sword.

“What’s wrong?” Liu Hao still didn’t understand.

“It looks like you know the strategy?” Ye Xiu said. If they weren’t rushing for the record, there was no need to save time. If they had more monsters to fight, then there would even be a bit more experience for them. That’s why Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion had no clue on the strategy for record-setting.

“I know it…… In the beginning, I thought that there wasn’t much to pay attention to?” Liu Hao said.

“Ha ha, we’re going to be using a new strategy.” Ye Xiu said.

“Did you not hear it? New strategy. It’s not that outdated strategy you know of.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“New strategy?” Liu Hao was in a daze.

“Right, everyone pay attention to how I move. I’ll talk while I move.” Ye Xiu said. He had already let his Lord Grim rush forward. In the blink of an eye, the earth that met his body opened up and four undead monsters began climbing up.

“What’s different about this strategy?” Liu Hao was at a loss. The four monsters in the beginning couldn’t be avoided, which was why they would swarm around them and kill them off. Right now, what was so special about Lord Grim’s pathing? Didn’t it also alarm four monsters?

Chapter 116 – An All-New Strategy

Chapter 116: An All

An All-New Strategy

After the four monsters rushed out, they immediately headed towards Lord Grim. In the next second, the four monster grouped together.

To be more accurate, they weren’t together. But they were all heading towards the same target and just happened to meet up at the same place.

Although Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion had skill, they were still beginners in terms of knowledge and experience and were completely indifferent to the current situation. However, Su Mucheng and Liu Hao quickly saw through it.

This was gathering the monsters in one move. Just by relying on his pathing, he was able to perfectly gather up the monsters in one move.

This gathering calculated for the monsters’ positions, the monsters’ movement speed, pursuit path as well as how they chose to change directions. Afterwards, by controlling the character’s movements and pathing, in the blink of an eye, the monsters would move into the necessary position.

This was a strategy that needed them to pay extreme attention to the details!

However, although this method of gathering monsters was beautiful and flawless, killing off these four monsters in this way wouldn’t improve the time by much, right? If everyone just swarmed them and forcefully attacked the four monsters separately, they could also instantly gather the monsters and they might even be a bit faster.

Su Mucheng and Liu Hao both had the same doubts in their heart.

Lord Grim, however, had already started moving.

Shadow Clone Technique!

Lord Grim’s fake body was left in his original position while his real body had already instantly flashed over to the other side. However, the monsters were still headed towards his original position. Players could rely on experience to determine the real body in Shadow Clone Technique, but monsters couldn’t. This skill had a 100% chance to trick monsters. The four monsters continued to charge towards the fake body.

Falling Flower Palm!

The real Lord Grim immediately unleashed a blast. The four monsters smashed into each other and flew out. One of them wasn’t hit strong enough. It looked as if it were about to fall, when Lord Grim stabbed out with his lance and the monster flew high up into sky. A Dragon Tooth thrust forth and this monster flew forward farther than rest.

The four monsters were hit onto a stone wall. Dungeons! Most of them had a closed off space, whether it be a mountain, a forest, a precipice, or a wall. There was always some sort of barrier that led players towards a certain direction. They couldn’t let you just casually go around the monsters.

The four monsters smashed into the wall. Lord Grim’s quickly rushed up. Steamed Bun Invasion roared and was about to go up too to battle when Ye Xiu yelled: “Watch first.”

Steamed Bun Invasion immediately halted. He spun around in his original position and said to Hateful Sword: “Don’t move! Watch carefully.”

Liu Hao had already learned well. He definitely wouldn’t reply back to Steamed Bun Invasion.

Lord Grim rushed up. One player versus four monsters, which were easily suppressed. Originally, there was a small, narrow crack in the stone wall. Lord Grim’s previous Falling Flower had blown a monster into it and his following Dragon Tooth knocked another one into it. After rushing up and using two or three moves, the monsters were stuffed into the crack. Although it was a 1v4, it was more like a 1v1.

“This…… it could be considered a pretty good method for clearing the dungeon. But for setting a record, how will this save time?” Liu Hao was puzzled, extremely puzzled. But he didn’t say anything and only silently watched.

One of the monsters fell. The second one stepped out of the crack. In a short moment, it was killed and then also fell. The third monster stepped out, was killed, and then fell. And then afterwards……. afterwards there was no more!

Besides Ye Xiu, the other four players all looked at their screen with wide eyes. They had all seen in awe that the fourth monster, a zombie, was stuck in the stone wall. Although it bore its fangs and brandished its claws, no matter how it struggled, it couldn’t get out.

What was jamming it were the broken bones of the previous three skeletons. After the skeletons in the Boneyard were killed, they would immediately turn into a pile of bones and merge with the ground into a solid chunk like a scar. At this moment, the three skeletons were killed by Lord Grim on the same spot in the stone crack. The three piles of bones built on each other and the pile couldn’t be considered very tall. However, the clumsy zombie couldn’t get out no matter how hard it tried. It could only spin around in circles.

D*mn! So it could be done like this!!! Liu Hao was dumbstruck. Like this, when they pulled four monsters, they could kill one less, which would definitely save a lot of time.

However, to do this, he would have to do a lot more movements. Although he would save time from killing one monster less, would that time be wasted on those extra movements? Liu Hao was currently pondering over this issue, when he heard Ye Xiu say: “It’ll be done like this. However, as a record-setting party, we have to coordinate together and use the shortest amount of time to complete these moves. I’ve roughly calculated it. If the coordination is smooth, then we’ll be faster than normal parties by at least 10 seconds.”

10 seconds. This didn’t seem very amazing. But throughout the dungeon, if there were six of these ten seconds, then there would be a 1 minute advantage.

1 minute. If another party didn’t know of such a method, then it’d be extremely difficult for them to make up for it in other areas. Besides better equipment to increase their damage, there was no other method.

A chill arose in Liu Hao’s heart. He believed that situations similar to this definitely wouldn’t arise just this one time in the beginning.

Just as expected, whether it be similar or different situations, there were always a few excess movements that utilized the dungeon details. And in the end, they all went around monsters that couldn’t be avoided with the original methods.

With the original methods, if there were no mistakes, then a party could avoid fighting a total of 12 monsters.

With the new method, if there were no mistakes, then a party could avoid fighting a total of 21 monsters.

Using the previously calculated 10 seconds for each monster, then the new method had an advantage of a minute and a half.

Liu Hao was both astonished and extremely pleased. Although it was true that the new method was superior, he had already seen it all. For a pro-player like him, he didn’t need to learn all of the details perfectly. He just needed to understand the general line of thinking and then rely on his skill level to work it out. But right now, he didn’t even need to spend the effort doing that. This was because after their first run, the following three runs were for practicing their coordination. And Liu Hao was one of the five……

‘Soft Mist, you execute this Falling Flower. Go here, good……”

“Steamed Bun, your pathing. Use Brick to hit that one.”

“Anti-Tank Missile!!”

“Use Gore Cross and then Colliding Stab.”

“Hateful Sword’s skill isn’t bad!” Ye Xiu praised the new player quite a few times.

“How could that be. God, when the time comes for you to set a record, bring me along!!” Liu Hao actively requested it.

“Oh? Are you in a guild?” Ye Xiu asked.

“No.”

“When the time comes, you’re going to need to temporarily join a guild. Is that okay?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Oh, so you’re doing work for a guild? How much money can you make?” Liu Hao’s seemingly normal question actually held sinister intents. He knew what Ye Xiu’s demands to the guilds were, but right now, he was bringing a party. After receiving the rewards, would he split them with the party? If he was splitting them, then upgrading his Silver weapon would be even more difficult. If he wasn’t splitting them, then Liu Hao would bring up this issue among them at once.

Ye Xiu hadn’t yet replied, when Steamed Bun Invasion said in extreme disdain: “Money? What money? That’s for going up on TV. It’s for glory. Hateful Sword, you really have no future! I look down on you as a representative of Aquarius!”

“Ah……” Liu Hao’s tone was somewhat terrified. In his heart, he was cursing: Steamed Bun, you dumb*ss. Don’t you know that you’re doing free labor? No wonder he brought along such an idiot!!!

And the other two players didn’t react in the slightest. Liu Hao couldn’t count on Cleansing Mist. It was 80% likely that this player was Su Mucheng. She breathed the same air as Ye Qiu. How could a little bit of money cause a fight. But what about this other girl? Why didn’t she have any reaction, who was she?

That girl hadn’t yet reacted when Liu Hao heard Ye Xiu say: “Oh, there are rewards. All of these are a few uncommon materials, but they’re all things I need. What would you like?”

“I don’t need anything….. I was just asking.” Liu Hao said. Of course he didn’t want anything. He only wanted to ask this question and use unfair distribution as a way to cause strife among the party. But now that he looked at it, it seemed he had failed. There was no point talking about the player that was likely Su Mucheng. It looked like the other girl didn’t get the signal at all. And as for Steamed Bun, that f*cker was an idiot. However, even if he was an idiot, if he really wanted to sow seeds of doubt into that guy, then it wouldn’t be too hard.

“The materials I ask for are all things I urgently need. As for the items dropped in the dungeon, those are given to everyone else to split. I don’t need those. That shouldn’t be too big of a problem, right?” Ye Xiu said.

Liu Hao recalled. In the previous two runs, it seemed like Lord Grim really didn’t take anything, whether it be Green equipment dropped from monsters or Blue equipment dropped from BOSSes, he directly renounced those. If he really did it like this every time they ran a dungeon, then there truly wasn’t anything to complain about.

“Oh oh. It’s nothing. I was just curious, so I just randomly asked that’s all.” Liu Hao hurriedly said, “I can join a guild or whatever. Why don’t you bring me along? I also want to go up on TV.”

“Okay, I’ll tell the guild when the time comes…… All in all, we’re helping them set the dungeon record, so if no one from their guild comes along, then it won’t look very good for them. Let’s see what they say! If they don’t care, then I’ll bring you along.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay, thank you, thank you.” Liu Hao said. Following the party, he could completely grasp their final strategy for setting the record. Moreover, as a member of their party, he could make a few mistakes to waste time without exposing himself. Right now, he was already hiding his true strength. As a result, he could act like he had difficulty doing a few actions in a few places as if he wasn’t skilled enough. And when it was time for him to truly set the record, he could completely go all out. Like this, using the same method, he would be able to set a better record.

Even if he wasn’t able to become a member when the time came, he felt that he could still suppress this party by a chunk relying on his pro-level coordination and skill.

Liu Hao was already extremely clear on these few player’s strength. Ye Qiu’s Lord Grim naturally didn’t need to be talked about. That Cleansing Mist’s performance wasn’t particularly noteworthy. However, as a teammate, Liu Hao saw through a few of her habits, especially her tacit understanding with Lord Grim. Although he couldn’t directly confirm it, Liu Hao was already certain that this player was Su Mucheng.

As for the other two, with Liu Hao’s skill, he could completely tell that these two were new players. He didn’t know how their mechanical skill was so remarkable, but these types of players still couldn’t be compared with pro-players.

Gazing at Lord Grim on his screen, Liu Hao seemed to have trouble doing a few actions while wearing an extremely pleased smile on his face.

Chapter 117 – Specially Substituting In

“It looks like you’re afraid of me!” Liu Hao said gleefully and constantly thought this in his heart.

He was already clear what Ye Xiu’s plans were. Getting hired, setting records, being rewarded with uncommon materials, upgrading his Silver weapon, the steps were just that simple. But if he wanted to continue doing it like this, then he had to take the highest record for each dungeon. Ye Xiu understood this point, Liu Hao as well.

For Frost Forest’s dungeon record, Liu Hao had specially come out because he knew Lord Grim was Ye Qiu, so he wanted to step down on him. But now that he understood how important this record was. He would spare no efforts and planned on gathering five pro-players to set the Boneyard record.

As for Ye Xiu, he had thought hard with all his might in order to come up a new strategy for this record. This was clearly because he knew that his opponent was Liu Hao, whose strength was powerful. If he contested with the usual strategy, then he would certainly lose just like how he did in Frost Forest.

“I’ve said so long ago. Your era is over. It’s my era now!” Liu Hao continued to dungeon with everyone else, but was already no longer as attentive as before. After all, the class combination he was planning on using was completely different from this party, so there was no way he could completely copy the strategy word-for-word. He already knew what he needed to know. What he needed now was to practice it. Fortunately, his party members were all pro-players. With their pro-level inner qualities, getting to this level of coordination definitely wouldn’t be as difficult to do as Ye Qiu’s inferior party.

“Tsk tsk tsk, how pitiful!” In game, Ye Xiu constantly reminded Tang Rou, Steamed Bun Invasion, and Hateful Sword to pay attention to this and that. Hearing all this, Liu Hao was extremely satisfied. Before, it wasn’t as if he had never been instructed like this. However, this was his first time feeling happy about it. Thinking of this, Liu Hao’s hand slipped and he made another pathing mistake. Just as expected, Ye Xiu immediately instructed anxiously: “Hateful Sword, move back two steps. You went too far.”

“Okay!” Liu Hao answered. In his heart, he was secretly laughing as he moved back two steps. He had the impulse to make a movement that would destroy the entire strategy, but in order to stay in the group for the long-term, he tried hard to endure. As long as he maintained Steamed Bun’s level of playing, he would be fine.

These four runs were finally completed. Because the new strategy had too many details, to players lacking experience and knowledge like Tang Rou and Steamed Bun, it could only be learned by learning it mechanically, making it seem extremely difficult. Liu Hao had grasped it long ago. But in order to keep up the act, after running the dungeon four times, he also said with lament: “So difficult!”

“That’s why you have to try harder. Got it?” In the end, he was once again lectured by Steamed Bun Invasion.

“We’ll practice again tomorrow!” Ye Xiu sighed. He wasn’t very satisfied with today. As expected, complicated strategies completely exposed the weaknesses of Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion, these types of new players.

“Are we going to go to Frost Forest?” Liu Hao asked. He was incomparably happy right now.

“Not right now!” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay, then I’ll be going off now. See you tomorrow!” Liu Hao said goodbye to everyone and then went offline. He swiped his account card and ran to Boneyard. Taking advantage of the fact that the strategy was still fresh in his mind, he went in to review it. Based on their class combination, he also did his own homework.

“It’s a little troublesome, right?” In Happy Internet Cafe, carrying her tea cup, Tang Rou went to the reception desk to look for Ye Xiu.

“Yeah…….” Ye Xiu admitted.

“Practice for a few more days?” Tang Rou asked.

“If time drags on for too long, then the record won’t be worth anything anymore.” Ye Xiu said helplessly.

“Is there any other way to practice?” Tang Rou was more eager to face difficulties than anyone else. Having a limit of four runs every day didn’t make her feel good.

“There is!!” This question reminded Ye Xiu of something and he immediately thought of a place.

“Steamed Bun, Steamed Bun.” Ye Xiu called in the game.

“Here!” Steamed Bun Invasion replied.

“Come here. We’re going to keep practicing.” Ye Xiu said.

“I don’t have any entries left!”

“We’re going to practice somewhere else.” Ye Xiu said.

“Where?”

“Skeleton Graveyard.” Ye Xiu said.

Skeleton Graveyard, a beginner village dungeon, was obviously different than Boneyard. However, there were definitely a few similarities between them. More importantly, there was no entry limit, so they could practice however many times they wanted to.

“Buy a random low-leveled weapon in beginner village. We’re going to practice slowly.” Ye Xiu sent Steamed Bun Invasion a message while saying it to Tang Rou.

“Cleansing Mist and Hateful Sword aren’t on anymore!” After meeting up with everyone, Tang Rou noted.

“It doesn’t matter. We’ll practice first.” Ye Xiu led the two into the dungeon. He himself obviously didn’t have any problems using the strategy. The most important part was getting the other player’s coordination up to par. Right now, Tang Rou, Steamed Bun Invasion, and Hateful Sword made too many mistakes. Although they weren’t fatal, they were definitely enough to stop them from setting a record.

Skeleton Graveyard’s and Boneyard’s terrain were different, but the monster models and spawn points were very similar. In Skeleton Graveyard, the monsters were randomly distributed, so occasionally, they would be distributed similarly to their arrangement in Boneyard. Plus, with Ye Xiu’s ability to control monsters, it really made the scenario extremely similar.

The three spent the night soaking in Skeleton Graveyard. It didn’t need to be said that Tang Rou silently and stubbornly worked hard. Steamed Bun Invasion, on the other hand, talked a lot. He would talk for awhile and then another while. His mouth just kept on moving like a train. However, he also worked hard and practiced with the other two. This was all because of love. An idiot’s deep love for the game.

They had to practice, but their levels couldn’t fall too far behind. After a few days, Lord Grim was the first to reach Level 27. He didn’t know how often this Blue River checked his level. But less than a minute after he hit Level 27, Blue River sent a message: “Boneyard, Boneyard. I’m not too late, right???”

“No…….” Ye XIu said.

“Oh, what do you want this time?” Blue River asked. This was a question that he was quite concerned about.

“Vampiric Lightsaber.” Ye Xiu said.

“What a coincidence!” Blue River’s cheeks streamed with tears.

“Hm?”

“I’m using a Vampiric Lightsaber right now.” Blue River cried.

“Aren’t you almost Level 30?” Ye Xiu said.

“It’s an Orange weapon, brother. There’s no need to switch weapons at Level 30.” Blue River said.

“It doesn’t matter if it’s Orange, it’s still a low-leveled weapon. It’s just like floating clouds.” Ye Xiu comforted.

“What else do you need?” Blue River was aware that his demands couldn’t be as simple as just a single Vampiric Lightsaber.

“Eight Bone Spines!” Ye Xiu said. This was an uncommon material from Boneyard’s hidden BOSS Rotten Skeleton Sheep.

“Okay….. but no more!” Blue River replied.

“Okay. But setting the record for Boneyard is going to be a bit difficult. This time, I want to directly bring a party of five members. We’ll then play for your guild, after joining it. Is that okay?” Ye Xiu said.

“This….. that won’t look too good for us, no?” Blue River hesitated.

“The fight for dungeon records is very intense right now!” I have to do everything I can.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay then……” After thinking for a bit, Blue River agreed.

“We’ll start tomorrow!”

“Okay.”

Their conversation had already ended, when Cold Night sent his message: “Boneyard!!!”

“Blue Brook Guild…….” Ye Xiu’s message was very simple.

“F*ck! When did you get to Level 27?” Cold Night asked.

“Five minutes ago!” Ye Xiu said.

“Sigh, sigh, sigh. Then I pray for your success.” Cold Night showed his grace.

“Brother…….” Blue River sent another message at this time.

“What?” Ye Xiu replied.

“Are you planning on doing things like this, substituting in and setting records, for the long-term?” Blue River asked.

“That’s what I’m planning on doing for now……” Ye Xiu said.

“Then if it’s like this, if you keep on pulling along your party, then I’m afraid you won’t be able to continue doing this for more than a few times, no?” Blue River said.

Ye Xiu sighed. How could he not know what Blue River was talking about? Although he could join a guild and then hang the guild’s name up on the record, if he kept on bringing along a fixed party with the same set of players, then if it was today Tyrannical Ambition and tomorrow Blue Brook Guild, everyone would see eventually see through it. Although the dungeon record was technically the guild’s, everyone would know what their party was doing: it meant that this record was bought with money. For guilds, records were supposed to be a way to advertise themselves and represent a guild’s strength. However, in this way, that would no longer hold any meaning.

In the beginning, Ye Xiu hadn’t thought of pulling along a set party. He had originally wanted to rely on his own strength and mix in with others to set a record, similar to how he had cooperated with Blue River and his guild members the first time. He had led them through One Wave Rush, which was already more than enough to surpass normal players. Their identity was relatively forgettable, so when he left the party in the end, it wasn’t too noticeable. However, because Liu Hao came out and substituted in for Excellent Dynasty, a pro-level record was set. As a result, Ye Xiu had no choice but to pull along a somewhat elite party to resolve the situation.

In fact, actual substitution should have been like how Liu Hao was doing it. He would use the other side’s provided account, which wouldn’t expose his identity. Ye Xiu directly using Lord Grim and making a reputation for himself already couldn’t be considered as substitution.

“Let’s discuss this later!” There was nothing he could do right now. “ “Brother, why not just join our guild for the long term? We’ll reward you according to your needs. How about specially substituting in for our guild?” Blue River said his true intentions.

“Sell out!” Ye Xiu laughed.

“You wouldn’t lose out in any way, no? If you’re not happy, you can just leave. We won’t stop you.” Blue River said.

“This…. Let me think about it!” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay, let’s talk about this after you’ve finished setting a record for Boneyard.” Blue River said.

Ye Xiu laughed. As expected, Boneyard really was a test for him. Blue River also needed to see whether his record would be beaten by someone else.

The next day. Everyone depended on the next day. Ye Xiu silently thought. He rushed over to Boneyard and did a final practice for the final day.

They had already successfully worn in, so they emphasized the details today. They couldn’t have any mistakes. They couldn’t be careless when they went for the record-setting run. Between Level 27 and 28, Even though they could keep practicing for a few more days if they only went to Boneyard, then they might find it difficult to concentrate when carrying this casual, stress-free attitude into the record-setting run. In this area, what they all needed was Tang Rou’s spirit! If they were going to do it, then they had to do it until they were the best.

At midnight the next day, the five players gathered together in front of Boneyard. Ye Xiu once again stressed this sort of spirit. Afterwards, he ran to the side and prayed silently to himself. He prayed that no customer would come to him with a problem while he was dungeoning.

Chapter 118 – Mid-Air Coordination

Start!

Lord Grim led the way forward. He was the main force for pulling monsters. At the start, the four monsters were pulled in the same way. Except this time, once Lord Grim alarmed the four monsters, Soft Mist immediately went up. She quickly rushed towards the position Ye Xiu indicated for her to go to. A Falling Flower Palm into a knock-up into a Dragon Tooth and the four monsters flew backwards all together.

Lord Grim used a Shadow Clone Technique. This time, he didn't head towards Soft Mist's position. Instead, he directly flashed over to where the four monsters flew to. Cleansing Mist, Steamed Bun Invasion, and Hateful Sword had already rushed towards that direction when Lord Grim was pulling the monsters. They swiftly hit the monsters into the stone crack. The zombie was in the very back and the three skeletons were in the front. Sword, lance, cannon, brick, all wildly greeted them.

In a short moment, the first monster at the head was killed and the second skeleton went up. When killing the first skeleton, all of their AoE skills were sent out. So when the second skeleton came out, its life wasn't full. After a few rounds of attacks, it also fell. The third skeleton went up and came out even weaker than the second. In just one round of the five players' combined attacks, the skeleton was blasted into a pile of shattered bones.

The three piles of shattered bones piled on top of each other and the fourth zombie monster bore its teeth and brandished its claws, trying to tear them apart. But the five players had already ran off and vanished.

Ye Xiu's so-called new strategy built upon the basis of going around monsters by increasing the number of stuck monsters.

Under normal circumstances, the stuck monster were there in order to pursue dependability. But strategies that pursued safety couldn't be considered when pursuing efficiency. Ye Xiu's method of getting a monster stuck in Boneyard directly trapped it so that they wouldn't need to kill it. This naturally saved a lot of time.

But for a record-setting party, they couldn't slowly and unhurriedly keep trying to trap it. They had to use the shortest amount of time to trap it on their first try.

For the first wave of four monsters, Ye Xiu's Lord Grim could successfully trap one by himself. However, it would be far slower than the five of them coordinating together. In terms of damage output, they were even more incomparable.

Perfect and careful coordination, perhaps wasn't necessary for success, but it was necessary for efficiency.

However, there was one place where they needed coordination to succeed. This was also one of the difficult parts of the strategy. Over the course of the five player's practice, they had always made mistakes over the course of their practice. To this day, not a single perfect run had been achieved.

When Liu Hao compared the old and new strategy, he calculated that the new strategy would be able to avoid a total of 21 monsters, while the old strategy avoided only 12 monsters, a difference of 9 monsters.

However, the monsters weren't the only ones that could be avoided. In reality, with Ye Xiu's researched strategy, they could even avoid a BOSS.

The second BOSS, Zombie Bailey.

Zombie Bailey moved slowly, but had matchless strength. Players hit by it had an extremely high chance of being hit back and being infected by the Zombie Virus. Moreover, this Zombie Virus could be transmitted between players.

It sounded scary, but in reality, this BOSS wasn't difficult to beat. The infection speed of the Zombie Virus wasn't fast and it didn't do a lot of damage. If a party had a Cleric with decent equipment, as long as the party knew who had the Virus, the Cleric could stop the infection. For top-tier experts like Ye Xiu, who didn't need Clerics, they were confident that they wouldn't be hit by the slow-moving BOSS.

Although Zombie Bailey was easy to deal with, it had high health, so they would need a lot of time to beat it. For monsters like these, record-setting parties could only go all out in their damage output to save time. However, Ye Xiu had researched a method to directly trap Zombie Bailey.

But this method was extremely difficult. They had been stumped by it up until now. Although the party had been successful before, they had never succeeded on their first try.

However, if they succeeded. They'd be able to save a lot of time. Under normal circumstances, where the party would just go all out with their damage, it would take at least two minutes to kill it. But if they completed the method Ye Xiu had thought of on their first try, they wouldn't even need 20 seconds to kill it.

This exceedingly difficult method sounded very simple. It was to send Zombie Bailey into a crack in the wall not too far high up. Once it was trapped in the crack, it would no longer have any way of climbing out.

The hard part was actually doing it.

There was a quite a bit of distance between the ground and the crack in the stone wall. The strategy required all five players to chain knock-up skills and continuously lift Zombie Bailey into the air, until it was finally sent into it.

When they first tried to do it, the five players had knocked Zombie Bailey up into the air until it was dead, yet never succeeded once. This was all because the requirements for their coordination and hand speed was too high. Every time a player knocked it up, there was a very short interval to link the next player's skill. If anyone made even the slightest of errors, it would cause them to fail. Moreover, this all required on the individual to grasp the timing. By the time Ye Xiu reminded them, it was already too late.

Only by succeeding on the first try would they be able to set the fastest record.

However, no one had much confidence in doing this on the first try. But even if they succeeded on their second try or third try, they'd still be able to win a lot of time. It was an advantage that no normal party could surpass.

Liu Hao liked this. With his Hateful Sword here, there was no way he would let Ye Qiu's party succeed on their first try. In this party, anyone had the possibility of making a mistake. But switched with a party of pro-players, wanting to succeed in this difficult part wasn't a challenge at all.

Seeing that they were about to reach Zombie Bailey, Liu Hao secretly plotted.

"We're almost at Zombie Bailey! We can do it!" Ye Xiu said at this moment.

"We can do it!" Steamed Bun Invasion yelled.

"Let's try to succeed by the second try!" Ye XIu said.

"Succeed on the first try!" Tang Rou was even harsher.

Ye Xiu laughed bitterly. He hoped to succeed on the first try, but such a thing really was too difficult for them.

"Everyone focus!!" After clearing away all of the monsters in front of Zombie Bailey, Ye Xiu shouted out.

Everyone immediately went into their position.

Because Zombie Bailey moved slowly, it would take quite a bit of time for it to reach the stone wall, which was why it required the players to help push it faster.

"Begin!!" Ye Xiu's Lord Grim rushed up to pull it. He knocked it up and unleashed a Falling Flower Palm. Zombie Bailey went flying.

Soft Mist stabbed forward. Taking advantage of the flying Zombie Bailey, she used a Sky Strike and then another Falling Flower Palm.

Steamed Bun Invasion and Hateful Sword carried out their relay roles. From beginning to end, Zombie Bailey never fell and was sent over. This process was simple. No mistake had been made yet. The pitiful Zombie Bailey was only the second BOSS. It wasn't like Frost Forest's Frost Thain. It didn't have any method of getting out of chain knock-ups.

The final player to receive it was Su Mucheng. She kicked Zombie Bailey up and fired consecutively with a machine gun, the skill BBQ. Zombie Bailey tumbled in the air under fire.

If Delivery Gun could be used, then there would be a higher chance of succeeding on their first try. Unfortunately, after testing it multiple times with Chasing Haze, he found that there was no way of directly Delivering Zombie Bailey from the air into the crack due to the terrain. The firing angle wasn't enough.

Regretfully, they could only use this sort of five player chain knock-up method.

After BBQ finished, Zombie Bailey dropped from midair when Steamed Bun Invasion rushed forward and followed up with an Uppercut.

Zombie Bailey was once again hit, but Ye Xiu sighed in regret.

Failed.... In the first move, Steamed Bun Invasion had already failed. Because the party had used trash equipment to practice this so many times, after Steamed Bun Invasion punched and then observed, he also went "Uh oh" and was aware of his failure.

"Don't stop, continue." Ye Xiu yelled.

If they couldn't succeed on the first try, then hopefully they'd succeed on the second try.

Hateful Sword moved up and used a Back Slash. The slashed Zombie Bailey smashed into the wall like a bullet and then rebounded.

Perfectly executed!

With Steamed Bun Invasion's mistake, Liu Hao didn't need to deliberately mess up. This was because he already knew that this already wasn't a perfect record.

Su Mucheng's Cleansing Mist leaped up. She swung with her hand cannon, using the Launcher knock-up skill "Swing". Zombie Bailey was hit up a bit higher.

Tang Rou's Soft Mist had already rushed to her position. She leaped up into the air and then used a Sky Strike. Her lance tip hit Zombie Bailey right when it began to fall. This move didn't cause Zombie Bailey to continue rising, but made it stay at the same height.

Steamed Bun Invasion, who had just made the mistake, had already leaped high into the air. He followed up with a Hook. Zombie Bailey rose higher up again and reached a height where normal jumps could no longer reach.

A figure flashed above where Steamed Bun Invasion had jumped.

Lord Grim.

Leaping up, he stepped on the stone wall, turned around, and jumped again. This move allowed his character to leap up higher.

The previous four players hadn't made any mistakes. Success or failure now all depended on Ye Xiu.

Lord Grim's lance steadily stabbed out. After piercing Zombie Bailey, the lance flew in a circular arc and delivered Zombie Bailey into the crack in the stone wall.

"Success!!" Steamed Bun Invasion yelled.

"Continue! Don't be careless." Ye Xiu's voice was still calm. After landing onto the ground, the party continued onto the remaining ⅓ of the dungeon.

At this moment, Liu Hao suddenly felt a bit regretful.

Even though this level wasn't perfect, it wasn't far from it. The only time lost was from Steamed Bun Invasion's single mistake. How long was that? Three seconds? Four seconds?

But could his party succeed on the first try? Previously, Liu Hao had never doubted it, after all, they were all genuine pro-players. But after finding out that the gap was only by three or four seconds, he suddenly felt a little worried.

"No! How could the distance from perfection only be three or four seconds? In the entire dungeon, I've always been holding back my strength. If I went all-out, then I'd definitely be able to steal back 15 seconds. Adding on to my more perfect and coordinated pro-team, we should at least be able to beat the time by 30 seconds. Oh, I forgot, we even have Orange weapons!! This time, our party has two players with Orange weapons... the damage output is definitely greater than Lord Grim's party, who only has a Silver weapon." Liu Hao carefully calculated. After determining his party's overall advantage, he finally relaxed and gave up on intentionally making a mistake in this run.

Boneyard's final BOSS finally fell. The last ⅓ of the dungeon could be considered perfectly done. The system announcement also came out: Congratulations to Blue Brook Guild's players: Lord Grim, Cleansing Mist, Steamed Bun Invasion, Soft Mist, Hateful Sword for breaking the Boneyard clear record, time: 17:22:17.

Chapter 119 – I Forgot

The world was at a loss. Each of the big guilds were shocked.

17:22:17. All of the Glory veterans began murmuring about this record. If they hadn’t gone mad yet, they were close.

It was another fastest record in all ten servers. After the tenth server opened, these towering records that stood tall for many years became like crumpled paper. Fortunately, the new server had a lot of new players, so they didn’t understand. If this was in an old server, then the players would certainly begin discussing which God had descended down into the mortal plane. But even if it was the tenth server, sooner or later, there would be controversy too. Right now, because the server had just opened, the other servers’ players didn’t pay much attention to the circumstances in the tenth server. Even more so, this was still just a low-leveled dungeon, so the amount of attention onto it was even more limited.

But the content of the controversy wasn’t wrong. This really was a which God had descended down into the mortal plane issue.

“Amazing, too amazing!! I don’t think anyone can beat this record.” Blue River sent a message at the first open moment.

“Ha ha, that might not be true.” Ye Xiu replied.

“F*ck, if someone can break this record, then I’ll eat my keyboard.” Blue River said.

“You’re too confident.” Ye Xiu said.

“It’s not like we don’t understand. This record is too amazing. How did you do it? Did you record it?” Blue River asked.

“I didn’t.” Ye Xiu said.

“Tsk tsk, amazing, too amazing.” Blue River could only praise him. In reality, he didn’t care how he had set it. As long as he had the record, he was fine. It was just Boneyard, even Blue River wouldn’t put so much effort into researching it.

“Don’t leave the guild yet! Please consider our proposal yesterday.” Blue River hurriedly sent a message. Before, Lord Grim would promptly leave the guild after setting the record. He left so fast that he didn’t have time to say anything to him.

“Okay.” Ye Xiu answered.

“Where are you? I need to give you the items.” Blue River said.

After receiving his coordinates, Blue River rushed over. The Vampiric Lightsaber was originally in his hands, so he unequipped it. Along with the eight Bone Spines, the Lightsaber was sent to Lord Grim.

“Thanks for your trouble everyone.” Blue River expressed his amiability to everyone.

“Are we still going to continue?” Tang Rou asked Ye Xiu. Because of Steamed Bun Invasion’s mistake, the record was still a little off in Tang Rou’s eyes, making her care very much.

“Let’s level!” Ye Xiu said.

“The record still isn’t at the limit!!” Tang Rou said.

“It’s pretty much there.” Ye Xiu rejected the notion.

Aside, Liu Hao snuck a laugh. This girl still wanted to hit the limit? With me here, give it a rest. The limit? You’ll all see it soon.

Afterwards, they ran the dungeon another three times. Everyone played through it like they were leveling. They obviously didn’t fight the second BOSS Zombie Bailey with that method. BOSSes were experience and equipment. How could a leveling party want to trap it and not kill it?

After running the dungeon three times, Hateful Sword took his leave first. Liu Hao had wanted to leave long ago. He didn’t want to waste anymore time. He actually had quite a few times where he had the impulse to reveal his identity, but was always able to stop himself in the end. He even kept up his act and finished running the the dungeon three more times with everyone. Patiently enduring. Liu Hao always felt that he was patiently enduring.

After going offline, he immediately went to rest. Early the next morning, after finding the account cards that Chen Yehui had given him, he promptly gathered his troops.

Wang Ze and Fang Fengran were subs in the current roster and were very young; Zhang Jiaxing and Shen Jian were players in the current roster and were extremely close to Liu Hao. Liu Hao had called for the four of them awhile ago. Moreover, along with Ye Qiu’s practice session in the past few days, he had also brought the four of them to do a few test runs. He felt that there weren’t any big problems, so he felt very confident. In those runs, he hadn’t used the account cards Chen Yehui had provided him until now because he was afraid that he would accidentally break the record in their practice runs.……

After all, they were all pro-players. Their comprehension ability was much greater than Tang Rou’s and Steamed Bun Invasion’s. After Liu Hao had explained it once, everyone already understood what they were supposed to do. They weren’t like Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion, who needed Ye Xiu to constantly remind them. Breaking in naturally went by extremely quickly. Now that he had the suitable account cards, Liu Hao felt certain that they’d be able to set the record within four runs.

“We’re setting the record now?” The four players had all come to the practice room and all knew why they were here.

“Yeah.”

“We have a match tonight!” Shen Jian said.

“What match?” Liu Hao asked.

The four were greatly alarmed. Liu Hao, their vice-captain, had actually forgotten the day of their matches?

“We have a match versus Blue Rain tonight!” Shen Jian reminded him.

“Really?” Liu Hao looked at the calendar. Sure enough, the match was today. In these past few days, he had been extremely busy in the new server. So busy that he had even forgotten such an important event. Recently, he hadn’t practiced as much either. After calculating it, he found that he had actually practiced with Steamed Bun Invasion in the Arena the longest.

F*ck! Thinking of that guy, Liu Hao felt a burst of sinister anger explode.

“Oh…… then let’s wait until after the match to do it!” Liu Hao hesitated for a bit. It was still better to put the more important things first. It wasn’t appropriate to spend time on the Boneyard record. Although Liu Hao was extremely confident, he also knew that taking down the current record wasn’t going to be easy. High levels of concentration were a must.

“Okay, tonight then!” After they heard Liu Hao’s decision, they let out a sigh of relief. Needless to say, Zhang Jiaxing and Shen Jian were going to be playing in the match today. As for Wang Ze and Fang Fengran, even though they probably weren’t going to go on stage, it still wouldn’t be good if they went to play the game on match day. If the Club knew of it, they would definitely punish them.

“What maps are we playing on tonight?” Just as they were about to leave, Liu Hao suddenly asked this question.

Zhang Jiaxing almost crashed to the floor. He hastily supported himself with a chair. The vice-captain didn’t even know what maps they were going to be playing on. Just how distracted was he!

That night, Glory League’s 21st Match began. The home Team Excellent Era faced against the visiting Team Blue Rain. As before, it became competition night in Happy Internet Cafe and business boomed.

Team Blue Rain couldn’t be compared to 301. Blue Rain was currently in second place. Their spot in the playoffs didn’t need to be worried about; they were one of the most popular contestants for the Champion title. Compared to the second to last place Excellent Era, the difference between them was simply like heaven and earth. Excellent Era had changed their rosters. And in their second match with a new roster, they would face against such a strong opponent. It would be a big challenge for them.

Chen Guo was once again sitting in her usual spot, while Ye Xiu was once again leaning on the door and smoking. And Tang Rou, who now took Glory seriously, specially ran over to watch the highest level of play in Glory, a pro match.

As before, the match was split into three parts: individual, group and team competition.

Excellent Era was the home team. Utilizing their advantage of knowing the maps, Excellent Era won two of the three individual matches. Happy Internet Cafe jumped about in joy.

Next up was the Group Arena. This time, unlike 301, Blue Rain wouldn’t be so hesitant against Sun Xiang and One Autumn Leaf. Blue River’s trump card was Huang Shaotian. He didn’t lose to Sun Xiang in skill and was more experienced than Sun Xiang. In addition, his character Troubling Rain was on the same level as the Battle God One Autumn Leaf.

In the end, in this Group Arena, both teams put their trump cards in the third position as the anchor. Relying on their home team advantage, Excellent Era started off well and stayed ahead all the way until Blue Rain’s Huang Shaotian came out. Then, the situation reversed. After slashing down two of Excellent Era’s pro players, still with ⅘ of his health, he met Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf head-on. In the end, he still obtained victory. In the Group Arena, Team Blue Rain won 2 points. Happy Internet Cafe fell into silence.

“In this Group Arena, both teams played well, but in the end, Huang Shaotian was still better and took advantage of every opening there was.” In the broadcast, the host and the honored guest brilliantly commentated on the highlight reel in the Group Arena.

Finally, the team competition began. Excellent Era took the initiative and had a good opening. The situation looked good, and the spectators at the Internet Cafe jumped in joy.

“Uh oh, a mistake…… this is a very serious mistake!!” The host suddenly yelled.

“Yeah…… Liu Hao, his performance today has been very poor!” The honored guest said.

“He also lost in the first match of the individual competition.” The host said.

“But this mistake shouldn’t have happened. Liu Hao is completely out of it today.” The honored guest shook his head.

“We haven’t even finished talking about the first one and he makes yet another one……. that move……. ugh…….” The host was clearly a little speechless. He couldn’t find the right words to describe the situation.

“As a pro-player, that move was a little amateurish…….” The honored guest politely criticized.

“The situation had been reversed…….”

“How could Huang Shaotian let go of such a hole. Nice! Formless Phantom Sword, beautiful! The timing of Formless Phantom Sword was too good.” The honored guest shouted.

“Sun Xiang’s current momentum isn’t bad. But he’s still not as efficient and ruthless as Huang Shaotian!”

“However, we can still look forward to his growth.”

“This competition……. how unfortunate for Excellent Era…….”

“Yeah, from the looks of it, unless Blue Rain makes several major mistakes in a row like how Liu Hao did, I don’t see a way.” The honored guest said.

“Yeah…….” The host once again had no words to say. Clearly, he wasn’t convinced of such a possibility.

“Okay……. in the end, Blue Rain won.” Finally, the host announced the victor.

“What a pity, what a pity……..” The honored guest sighed on behalf of Excellent Era.

Happy Internet Cafe was a sheet of silence. After a short moment, curses began to be thrown around. Right now, in the Happy Internet Cafe, Liu Hao was Glory’s unrivalled number one. He got the “special treatment”. Everyone, old and young, “paid their respects” to him. His huge mistakes caused them to lose the team competition, which was enough to make the overwhelming majority of his fans to lose all reason. Some even went outside to pick up bricks, ready to revolt against Club Excellent Era across street from them.

“F*ck that piece of sh*t!!” Even Chen Guo looked down on him. At this moment, no one respected Liu Hao. Even his most faithful fans couldn’t justify him. His mistakes were just too ridiculous.

As before, Ye Xiu was still leaning on the door and puffing out clouds of smoke. Without a word, he watched as customers left in rage. Quite a few people really did run over to Club Excellent Era’s door and protest.

Club Excellent Era.

After the competition ended, all of the pro-players silently sat in the resting room. No one said anything. Sun Xiang’s face was ashen. After savagely glaring at Liu Hao, he slammed the door and left.

The other pro-players gazed at each other in speechless dismay. They stealthily examined Liu Hao’s expression.

Liu Hao’s face was deathly pale. He obviously knew how serious his mistakes were. He even knew why those extremely serious mistakes were made. In the past few days, he truly was too unfocused. He spent way too much time on that Level 20 Berserker and wasn’t in the right mindset coming into the match. In the end, he had carried along a mindset of playing against Steamed Bun Invasion in the Arena as well as the Boneyard record coming into the match. How could he have done well?

“Liu, are we still setting the record for that whatever dungeon?” Shen Jian was also ready to leave. Only, he took the opportunity to quietly ask him when he passed by Liu Hao.

“Set!” Liu Hao’s tone was fierce and determined. If he didn’t set it now, then there was nowhere else for his pent-up anger to explode.

Chapter 120 – Who Taught You How to Play?

The majority of Happy Internet Cafe’s customers left. This match wasn’t as good as the last’s. Last time, even though they only obtained three points, the 1v3 in the Group Arena made everyone extremely excited and hopeful. But this time, everyone could only silently watch as their chances at victory were destroyed by mistakes that shouldn’t have happened. The majority of the customers were no longer in the mood to play games and all left.

The Internet Cafe turned quieted down a lot. Chen Guo instructed the employees to clean up and was also gloomy. Tang Rou wasn’t affected by the loss. She didn’t care who won or lost. She only saw that Chen Guo wasn’t happy, so she accompanied her. The two beauties whispered in each other’s ears. Once the Internet Cafe was cleaned up, Chen Guo’s mood turned better. After showing her concern for the two all-nighters, she went back to her room to sleep.

“When are we going to break another record?” Tang Rou asked Ye Xiu. To Tang Rou, setting these types of records made her extremely happy. She liked this type of challenge.

“Tonight!” Ye Xiu said.

“Tonight? What dungeon?” Tang Rou was puzzled.

“Boneyard!” Ye Xiu said.

“Boneyard, that dungeon…….. Didn’t you say we were close enough?” Tang Rou didn’t understand.

“Yesterday was close enough. But who knows about today?” Ye Xiu laughed.

At this moment, it was already 11 o’clock. After the other employees finished cleaning up, they all went back home. More than half of the customers, the ones who weren’t going to stay up all-night, also left. In the Internet Cafe, besides the tapping of keyboards and clicking of mice, were the voices of players playing Glory. There were laughs and there were curses. Suddenly, someone yelled out in surprise: “D*mn, the dungeon record was broken again! Who the h*ll are playing in the tenth server!!!”

After hearing this, Tang Rou was stunned. She looked at Ye Xiu. This cry also alarmed quite a few players in the Internet Cafe. Several tenth server players began discussing it with their in-game friends or with other players in the Internet Cafe. Tang Rou around to investigate and then went back to report to Ye Xiu: “It’s the Boneyard record. It’s that Excellent Dynasty again.”

“Oh? How much faster?”

“16:56:78.” Tang Rou was quite sensitive towards records. After seeing it, she remembered it.

“Oh, not bad!” Ye Xiu said.

“What now?” Tang Rou asked.

“We’re going to set it again tonight.” Ye Xiu said.

“But, 20 seconds…… what are we going to do?” Tang Rou only knew that their record only had Steamed Bun Invasion’s mistake. But even if that mistake wasn’t there, the record would have only been faster by three or four seconds. Right now, the records was 20 seconds faster. Tang Rou didn’t know where they could improve on.

“Don’t worry about it!” Ye Xiu seemed as if he knew what to do.

Tang Rou was about to ask again when suddenly, a figure appeared outside the Internet Cafe. The figure’s hands were in his or her pockets and the person wore a hoody. The figure looked as if he or she were scrunched up in a ball. The mysterious figure looked stealthily left and right towards the Internet Cafe and looked like one of those people who was about to commit a crime. Tang Rou immediately stopped herself from speaking, gesturing at Ye Xiu to look at the suspicious figure. In the end, when her gaze shifted over, that person saw her, turned around and then immediately ran off.

“Who was that?” Tang Rou was quite brave. She went out the door and looked. She saw the figure running in the distance still with his or her head facing towards her. When the figure saw Tang Rou rush out, the figure immediately turned around and ran off.

“Cough, what was that?” Ye Xiu asked.

“That guy was weird.” Tang Rou said.

“Did the guy run?”

“Yeah.”

“Then, let’s just ignore him. You go log-in to the game and call for Steamed Bun.”

“Okay.” Tang Rou replied. She then went to her usual all-nighter spot.

Ye Xiu continued to keep watch at the reception desk. He didn’t enter the game and appeared to be waiting for something. After quite a long while, that suspicious figure paced back and forth outside of the Internet Cafe entrance again until the figure saw Ye Xiu at the reception desk. After Ye Xiu nodded his head, the figure let out a sigh and then entered. The figure was still extremely alert and kept his or her head hidden deep in his or her coat. Stealthily looking around, the figure carefully walked towards the reception desk.

“Are you by yourself?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Do you think I’d pull along the entire team?” The person said.

“Sneaking around here and there, you look like a thief.” Ye Xiu said.

“How can I not be careful. This is an Internet Cafe. It’s so dangerous. I’m not like you. I have a lot of fans. I was almost recognized just now. Luckily, I ran away pretty quickly.” The person said.

“Come on. That girl is from the Internet Cafe. She thought you were a thief. Even if you came here normally, she still wouldn’t recognize you.” Ye Xiu said.

“Really?” The person doubted him.

“Would you like me to call her over?”

“It’s fine, it’s fine! Lay low! Lay low!” The person said.

“Area A Number 1. There’s no one in that area. You should go sit over there!” Ye Xiu said.

“And you?” The person asked.

“I have to keep watch here! I’m on the night shift!” Ye Xiu said.

“Why do you have to be so hard on yourself? It’s not like your skill dropped after retiring, no? Oh and speaking of that, why’d you suddenly retire?” The asked.

“First help me set this record and then we’ll chat.” Ye Xiu said.

“F*ck, I get a couple hundred thousand for every match. And now I’m helping people set a record for Boneyard. Don’t tell anyone! If you tell, I’ll kill you.” The person grumbled.

“Area A Number 1. It’s over there.” Ye Xiu gave him the directions.

“Can I have something to eat? I haven’t eaten all night.” The person said.

“Come, here’s some Zha cai for you to eat!” Ye Xiu threw a bag of food at him.

“F*ck that!” The person refused to eat it.

“Ham sausage?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Forget about it.” The picky-eater went off to Area A.

The smoking area was usually more lively late at night. The other non-smokers were mostly placed in Area C and Area A wasn’t usually open late at night. The lights weren’t even on there. After running over, this person discovered that it was so dark that he wasn’t able to find the power button for the computer. Grumbling, he ran back to Ye Xiu to complain.

Ye Xiu took a flashlight and went over to look for his computer.

After the person sat down, the person looked around left and right. This area really was unoccupied. The person stretched. The person didn’t need to be so careful and hidden. The computer turned on and the light shone off of the person’s face. If any Glory fan saw the person’s face, they would immediately recognize the person: Glory’s top-tier Blade Master, Huang Shaotian.

Swiping his card, he immediately entered the tenth server. He was using a Level 27 account. After sending Lord Grim an invite, he began to complain again: “Helping you set a record, fine. But you didn’t even have an account to give me. You even needed me to go find one myself.”

“It should be easy for you to find an account.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Level 27 Blade Master……. After using it, I won’t be using it again. I can’t leave any proof. It’s shameful, too shameful.” Huang Shaotian messaged.

“You first go play for a bit. We don’t have any entries left here. I’ll call you over at 12.” Ye Xiu said.

“Play, what the f*ck is there to play here?” Huang Shaotian replied.

In the end, Ye Xiu didn’t reply. Huang Shaotian took his Level 27 Blade Master and strolled around, not knowing what to do. He checked the new server’s dungeon record and was startled. Frost Forest was already astonishing, but this Boneyard was too ridiculous! This record. He didn’t even know if his Blue Rain’s main team could set it.

He immediately sent a message to Lord Grim: “F*ck me, how did you set this record??? Why is it so high?”

“New strategy.” Ye Xiu replied.

“New strategy? What new strategy?” Huang Shaotian asked.

“Boneyard’s new strategy.”

“There’s a new strategy for this? Who’d be so bored to research a new strategy?”

“…….”

“Ha ha ha ha, it wasn’t you right?”

“…….”

“You’ve fallen! You’ve completely fallen! You ran to the new server to do records and you even need to research new strategies? How bored are you!?”

“You really talk a lot.”

“Ai ai ai, I am safe here right? Will there still be other customers coming here at night? Right now I’m afraid that someone’s going to recognize me. If someone found out that I was setting a record for Boneyard, what would happen if that got out?” Huang Shaotian replied extremely quickly. Pro-player, his hand speed was even faster than his mouth. Using messages to chat was even faster than talking with his mouth.

In the end, Ye Xiu didn’t reply once again. Ye Xiu was busy too! Right when he was online, Blue River sent a message expressing that his inability to understand how the new record was possible. He truly couldn’t imagine that such an amazing record could be beaten by over 20 seconds.

“I’m going to set it back.” Lord Grim replied, which made Blue River crumble even further. How, how could the record be even faster?

On the other side, Liu Hao, who had been impatiently waiting for Lord Grim to come online, once again put on an act with his Hateful Sword. He contained his happiness and sent a message to Lord Grim: “God, our record got broken, did you see it?”

“I saw it.”

“Wasn’t our record already really high? How could it be broken again!”

“You don’t know?”

“I don’t know!”

“Because you weren’t going all out!”

Liu Hao stared blankly. In this moment, he felt as if a surge of electricity shocked him, from his toes to his head.

“I tried my hardest……” Liu Hao typed out this message with difficulty.

“Ha ha, using a Berserker. You think that you can hide from me by hiding your strength? Liu Hao, did you forget who taught you how to play?”

“F*CK!!!!!!”

Broken! The keyboard that he had just replaced had been broken again. It was once again smashed into a slope. At the same time, Liu Hao almost broke his teeth. He utterly couldn’t believe that this was happening.

Spending so much effort, putting on an act, leveling his Level 24 account to Level 27, distracting him so much that he even forgot about the official match. He had originally been waiting for the day when he would reveal his identity. He was waiting to see Ye Qiu’s shock and anger. He was waiting to see this guy stamped so hard under his foot that he would never be able to get back up.

But in the end…… he had already known about it? When did he find out? How did he know? Liu Hao really wanted to know. But he couldn’t get the words out. Lord Grim’s message rigidly stopped right there. There was nothing else after it.

But, even so, how was he going to improve the record? What other methods did he have to improve the time? Liu Hao felt that there wasn’t any other method. He was also a pro-player. For this dungeon, he had also done quite a bit of the research himself, except he hadn’t been able to come up with anything new. From his view, this new strategy was already the limit. He couldn’t think of any other way to improve the strategy. In order to improve the record, besides skill, there was only equipment.

In the new server, equipment wasn’t something that could be improved upon in one or two days. As for skill……. Liu Hao’s team of pro-players was at the limit! They had even succeeded in trapping Zombie Bailey on the first try. Even if Ye Xiu could duplicate their performance, it would still be extremely close. Where did he have the confidence that he’d definitely beat his record?

Chapter 121 – Godly Skill

The clock hit midnight. Liu Hao sat there like a log of wood in front of his computer. He didn’t move. He didn’t speak. Lord Grim’s message hung there staring at him.

“How is he going to break my record?” This question kept playing over and over again in Liu Hao’s head. He tossed and turned, but even so, he was still unable to come up with an answer.

Meanwhile, at Happy Internet Cafe, right when the clock hit midnight, Ye Xiu called Huang Shaotian over: “First come with me for a run. I’ll show you how the strategy works.”

“Hurrying.” Huang Shaotian was extremely bored.

Outside of Boneyard were Lord Grim, Cleansing Mist, Soft Mist, Steamed Bun Invasion, and Huang Shaotian’s Level 27 Blade Master: Flowing Tree.

“Use this sword for now.” Ye Xiu traded with Flowing Tree and gave him the Vampiric Lightsaber that Blue River had given him yesterday.

“Trash.” Huang Shaotian muttered as he received the Level 25 Orange equipment. In the eyes of a top-tier God in the pro-scene like him, Orange weapons were worthless, let alone a Level 25 one. Of course, it would be trash.

“Stop chattering so much. Hurry up and join the party.” Ye Xiu sent over an invite.

Flowing Tree joined the party.

“Head out.” Ye Xiu declared. Lord Grim entered the dungeon, while Flowing Tree followed behind. The other three stared blankly. They hadn’t yet reacted to this Flowing Tree joining the party. They were still waiting for Hateful Sword to appear!

“We have a new player. This run is mostly to let this new player understood the strategy.” After the five players entered together, Ye Xiu said.

“What about Hateful Sword?” Steamed Bun Invasion had the spirit of loyalty. He cared a lot about his good friend, who sent him quite a few Arena points, “I sent him a message, why didn’t he reply?”

“He has something on his mind, so he can’t come.” Ye Xiu said.

“Really, he has no prospects for the future.” Steamed Bun Invasion disdained.

“Let’s start, let’s start. Let me see your new strategy.” Huang Shaotian said, making everyone who heard know that he was very familiar with Ye Xiu.

“Who is he?” Su Mucheng asked.

“Shaotian.” Ye Xiu said.

“F*ck, don’t reveal my identity!!” Huang Shaotian panicked.

“Who are you yelling at! Who recognizes you?” Ye Xiu only told Su Mucheng. He was sure that Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion didn’t know who he was.

Sure enough, Tang Rou only dully said: “Oh? Your friend!”

“Yeah.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Don’t reveal my identity? I like secrets, are you a Scorpio?” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“Pretty close.” Ye Xiu said.

“Shameful! I’m a Leo.” Huang Shaotian said.

Steamed Bun Invasion immediately singing: “If you’re born at the end of July, you’re a Leo; if you’re born at the beginning of August, you’re a Leo!”

“F*CK!” Huang Shaotian yelled.

Steamed Bun Invasion still continued: “When we met, if it was an accident; when you left, why couldn’t I let ~~ it ~~ go!” In the end, he asked: “Right?”

“What’s right?” Huang Shaotian was sucked in.

“Nice singing.” Cleansing Mist applauded.

Steamed Bun Invasion was overjoyed: “I’ll sing another two verses for everyone.”

“Enough, Steamed Bun. I need to explain the dungeon. You can sing for us again later when there’s time.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay.” Steamed Bun Invasion could only agree with difficulty.

“Watch me!” Ye Xiu began controlling Lord Grim. He gave a demonstration just like how he did in the very beginning.

Huang Shaotian deserved to be called a famed blabbermouth in the pro-scene. Following along with Ye Xiu’s playing, he began chattering: “Woah, nice pathing! Shadow Clone Technique? Falling Flower Palm? D*mn, what class are you? Unspecialized? What are you doing? Woah! How’d your weapon transform? It did transform right? Did it transform? Woah! Did you guys see that? His weapon transformed back.”

“You’re so noisy!!” Su Mucheng yelled.

Of course, Huang Shaotian had already guessed that this Cleansing Mist was Su Mucheng. He laughed out loud and then whispered to Cleansing Mist: “You played really well tonight. Even though you guys lost, it wasn’t your fault. It was all on that idiot Liu Hao. Woah, there’s a crack here?” Huang Shaotian said while watching Lord Grim send the four monsters into the crack in the stone wall. He immediately shifted his viewpoint and began commentating like a TV anchor.

“What are you trying to do here?” Huang Shaotian asked.

“The three skeletons layer on top of each other when they die, so the zombie won’t be able to come out.” Ye Xiu said.

“Really?” Huang Shaotian said. His Blade Master Flowing Tree rushed forward. While running, his sword flashed out and a Sword Draw accurately cut the outermost skeleton. Following this, he didn’t use any skills, just normal attacks: stab, slash, scrape, chop, cut.

But these few normal attacks beautifully flowed together to create a melodic harmony. Even if Tang Rou didn’t have insight into anything else, she still had some towards mechanical skill. After a short while, she discovered that this player’s playing was quite smooth and skilled. Every attack was extremely quick and accurate like a precise machine.

“This player is amazing!” Tang Rou’s Soft Mist walked over to Cleansing Mist.

“He is!” Su Mucheng said.

“I’m coming too!!” It looked like Steamed Bun Invasion couldn’t see it. WIth a loud shout, he rushed up too to help. After a short moment, the first skeleton died. Ye Xiu said that the skeletons had to overlap and naturally, Huang Shaotian understood what to do. Coordinating together, they killed the second and third monsters. The three piles of skeleton bones piled on top of each other. Huang Shaotian looked at the zombie and sure enough, it was trapped inside blindly scratching: “Wow, it really isn’t able to come out? You’re really amazing, so there’s such a method. Like this, we should be able to save around ten seconds!”

“Yup.” Ye Xiu said.

“How many of these can be done in this dungeon?”

“Nine.” Ye Xiu said.

“Nine, a minute and a half! That can’t be right! Right now, the current record is much faster than just this. What else is there?” Huang Shaotian asked. This was a pro God’s ability to judge. From the time, he could already determine that just relying on this wasn’t enough to set such a record even by a pro-team.

“The second BOSS can be trapped too.” Ye Xiu said.

“That can be trapped too? How do you do it? Hurry up, hurry up. Let me see.” Huang Shaotian said, while letting his Flowing Tree rush forward. After running for a few steps, he stopped. He turned around on the spot for two full circles and then asked: “How do we do this part?”

“Watch me!” Ye Xiu didn’t laugh at him. As a top-tier God, he could calculate the approximate clear time for Boneyard, but the details were a bit blurry. When Ye Xiu was playing in the beginner village dungeons, he was also going through them using guides.

After demonstrating the strategy along the way, they gradually reached the second BOSS. Tang Rou took note of the time. Even though they were teaching while clearing, their speed was still so quick. When the time came to officially set the record, chasing down those 20 seconds wasn’t a problem at all! However, the second BOSS was still going to be very troublesome!

“So here, we’ll be fighting like this……” Ye Xiu was at that stone wall explaining while moving and jumping around. Huang Shaotian’s Flowing Tree looked around left and right and also tried jumping around. In the end, he replied: “You’re right. It can only be done this way.”

“Soft Mist, you pull.” Ye Xiu instructed.

“I pull? If I pull, then I won’t be able to rush back in time. I don’t have Shadow Clone Technique!” Tang Rou said.

“You don’t need to rush back. You just have to send the BOSS over, that’s all. There’s a different strategy this time.” Ye Xiu laughed.

“What strategy?” Tang Rou asked.

“I’ll record it and then show you when the time comes.” Ye Xiu said. If Soft Mist pulled the monster, she wouldn’t have enough time to rush back to her position, so she wouldn’t be able to see the whole picture.

“Okay.” Tang Rou replied and then didn’t say anything further. She ran over to pull Zombie Bailey. She knocked it into the sky and then blasted it over. Steamed Bun Invasion was next up. He played quite well and gave the mid-air Zombie Bailey a Knee Attack in the back. Next was Su Mucheng. An Anti-Tank Missile helped push Zombie Bailey farther. This pitiful BOSS directly flew over. Huang Shaotian’s Flowing Tree was already in place. Right when Zombie Bailey was about to land on the ground, a sword light flashed out. The angle and timing were absolutely perfect. The flying Zombie Bailey was slashed and then redirected. It suddenly stopped for a short time in midair. Flowing Tree had already stepped forward to meet it and used an Upward Slash to lift Zombie Bailey into the air.

Over there, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had already jumped onto the stone wall and hit the midair Zombie Bailey in front of him. The Thousand Chance Umbrella swooshed out and a chain of bullets flew out. It was unexpectedly the Launcher skill BBQ in midair.

Lord Grim had already begun to fall, but under Ye Xiu’s quick movements, the BBQ bullets all hit the necessary position. Zombie Bailey rolled about in the air until it finally rolled into the crack in the stone wall.

“Beautiful!!” Huang Shaotian yelled, “You deserve to be called the father of Delivery Gun! You’re still the best with that skill. I don’t even think Zhou Zekai could do that mid air Delivery Gun. That guy only knows how to be handsome. Who would actually let him shoot you to high heavens in actual combat?”

“Oh? It’s not bad!” After Lord Grim landed, Ye Xiu looked up and confirmed that Zombie Bailey was stuck up there and unable to climb out. This set-up made sure that they would succeed on the first try.

If this was a normal Delivery Gun, there truly wasn’t enough of an angle to complete it. However, when Lord Grim jumped up in this way, the character would reach a certain height, making enough room to use Delivery Gun. However, this angle could only be made with a very short hop. The timing had to be accurately grasped in order to deliver Zombie Bailey into the crack.

Su Mucheng wasn’t quite skilled enough to do this. Only Ye Xiu could do it.

As for Huang Shaotian’s Flowing Tree, his role was also extremely important. A normal upward cut had no way of lifting Zombie Bailey to Ye Xiu’s desired position. That was why Sword Draw had to stop Zombie Bailey from flying and then use an Upward Slash to send Zombie Bailey up.

In order to send it into the desired position, Sword Draw’s timing and the following uppercut had be executed accurately. Fortunately, such timing wasn’t difficult for Huang Shaotian. The harder task was still on Ye Xiu’s instant midair Delivery Gun, that was a true godly skill.

Seeing Lord Grim and Flowing Tree return, Tang Rou said in amazement: “Done?”

“Done.” Ye Xiu said.

“How did you do it?”

“I’ll show you later. Let’s keep going for now.” Ye Xiu said.

The following parts were normal. Who knew how many times faster Huang Shaotian picked things up than Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion. He only needed a few random instructions and then he would know what to do.

The only annoying part was that this guy really did talk too much. The teacher lectured, but the student talked even more than the teacher. Was such a situation normal?

Chapter 122 – Liu Hao the Helper

After this run of Boneyard finished, Huang Shaotian took a look at Excellent Dynasty’s record and then immediately said with certainty: “Yeah, we should be able to improve the record by around 30 seconds if we use this strategy.”

“However, for their record, they had to have used this strategy to set it. Wasn’t this an original strategy by you? How did they get it?” Huang Shaotian said.

Huang Shaotian really was a keen-witted guy. In the Glory pro-scene, he was famous for his astonishing decision-making and ability to take advantage of openings. He was amazing at Interrupts and a paragon opportunist. Taking the final opportunity was something he loved to do.

This was extremely obvious in the team competition. He might appear weak like he was invisible on the field or might make you feel like his condition was extremely bad. But once an opening appeared, he would immediately seize the opportunity to kill you. Cold-blooded and ruthless, characteristics of a true killer.

If you only looked at his style, you would think he was a cold and cruel character. But Huang Shaotian’s acting was extremely poor. This was because he loved to talk. When he battled, it might seem like he wasn’t there. However, his extremely quick hand speed and his love for the mic always made him shine like a star in the chat box.

Commentating on Huang Shaotian was always the most relaxing for the TV hosts. If they ran out of things to say, then they just had to read what was being typed in the chat box…… Who knew how many analysts and experts pointed out that if he could fix his habit of spending so much time and energy on typing, then he’d be even more terrifying. But this person would never change. Just for him, the Alliance created a special competition rule: in the team competition, dead players were prohibited from sending out messages.

Dead players could no longer play, so players like him could concentrate on typing out messages……. When rule came out to avoid that, the entire Alliance cheered.

At this moment, Huang Shaotian felt that Excellent Dynasty’s record was extremely irregular. Players like Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion, who didn’t have any perception, couldn’t tell this. Even the pro-level Su Mucheng hadn’t noticed it. Now that she heard Huang Shaotian bring it up, she also felt that something wasn’t right: “You’re right, how could that be?”

“That Hateful Sword is Liu Hao.” Ye Xiu said.

“Ah?” Su Mucheng stared blankly.

“What’s Hateful Sword?” Huang Shaotian asked.

“Who’s Liu Hao?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked.

Soft Mist had hid to the side. She didn’t come over to join in on the conversation. Tang Rou saw that Cleansing Mist and Ye Xiu weren’t ordinary friends. And this newcomer Flowing Tree seemed to be the same. She didn’t really understand the things they talked about. Tang Rou also didn’t know whether it was convenient for her to listen, so she politely stepped out.

“Hateful Sword learned our strategy from here. Later, he went to help Excellent Dynasty set the record.” Ye Xiu first explained it to Steamed Bun Invasion.

“Woah, he’s really studious!” Steamed Bun Invasion gasped in praise. After three seconds, he put two and two together: “D*mn, that guy was a spy.”

“…….” Everyone was speechless.

“I’m going to scold him!!” Steamed Bun Invasion declared.

“Stay low, only private message him.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh……. okay!” Steamed Bun Invasion had wanted to type it out on the world channel. But hearing God’s commands, he changed his plans and sent the online Hateful Sword a pile of messages. He used every type of hateful word he could think of.

Only then did Ye Xiu give Huang Shaotian an explanation: “Liu Hao opened up a low-level account. He’s been following along with us these past few days.”

“You figured it out a long time ago?” Su Mucheng asked.

“Yup!” Ye Xiu said.

“Then, why’d you keep bringing him?” Su Mucheng asked.

“Pro-level player! How could I reject such a player!” Ye Xiu said.

“How terrible!!” Huang Shaotian said, “You dragged him along to dungeon, so his condition would be all messed up. Did you see today’s match? That guy looked like an idiot. It looked to me like he saw the team competition as Boneyard. Sister Su, did you guys hold a meeting to criticize him?”

“I didn’t drag him. He was the one actively followed along. I just let him do what he wanted.” Ye Xiu said.

“And then this punk deliberately held back when you guys were setting the record and then went all out with his team. You really do have a lot of confidence! How were you so confident that you’d be able to break their record?” Huang Shaotian said.

“We have you, no?”

“How did you know……..” Huang Shaotian stopped mid sentence.

“Ha ha, the Alliance had already set it up half a year ago. How could I not know you were coming here today?” Ye Xiu said.

“D*mn, you actually calculated that I’d come here so long ago!!” Huang Shaotian said.

“Actually, whether or not you came wasn’t the important point. It’s not like you can’t play if you’re not here!” Ye Xiu said.

‘But…….” Su Mucheng hesitated, “In this dungeon, Shaotian and Liu Hao are around the same. Even if you two can coordinate to use Delivery Gun to send Zombie Bailey over……. there’s only so much time that can save!”

“It was originally around the same, but after Liu Hao helped us set the record, things changed.” Ye Xiu said.

“What changed?”

“We have an extra Vampiric Lightsaber!” Ye Xiu said.

“F*ck, so this was why I was so important!” Huang Shaotian’s cheeks streamed with tears. They had originally looked for him to fully use that Orange weapon’s power. An Orange weapon meant that their damage output would increase. Adding that in over the course of the dungeon, the effects were obvious. Plus now that they could do a mid-air Delivery Gun for that Zombie Bailey part, they’d have to be cursed to not break the record.

“I pity Liu Hao. I don’t want to help you anymore.” Right when Huang Shaotian said this, he suddenly received a guild invite. Huang Shaotian saw that it was Blue Brook Guild and jumped in surprise. Of course he knew that this was the guild that their Club backed. How did he suddenly get a message from them? Was his identity exposed? But after looking at it, he saw that it was unexpectedly from Lord Grim.

“See, look. I’m actually helping you guys by setting the record. If I didn’t look for you, who else would I look for?” Ye Xiu said.

“Is my identity exposed?”

“Of course not.” Ye Xiu asked Blue River for the ability to temporarily invite members to the guild in preparation for pulling Huang Shaotian’s Flowing Tree in.

“Okay, we’re going to officially start now. Everyone concentrate.” Ye Xiu announced.

“I thought I said I wasn’t going to help you guys?” Huang Shaotian asked Su Mucheng.

“Really? I didn’t hear it. You must have imagined it!” Su Mucheng said.

“F*ck, you two!” Huang Shaotian was helpless.

“We’re officially starting. Let’s try to get it on our first try.” Ye Xiu gathered everyone and then entered the dungeon.

They officially started. Even though Huang Shaotian was constantly complaining, his performance was flawless. After they completed a third of the dungeon, Ye Xiu couldn’t bear it any longer: “Steamed Bun, didn’t you want to sing? Please sing!”

“Really? Okay then. Everyone, I’m going to be singing a song about astrological signs!!” Steamed Bun Invasion said and then immediately began singing.

All of a sudden, the dungeon was filled with sounds of chattering, singing, and the cries of undead monsters. It became much more lively than in the beginning.

“Does it have to be like this?” The two girls were almost unable to bear it any longer.

“If I’m dying, you’re all coming with me.” Ye Xiu dully said.

Extremely noisy, yet flawless play.

Huang Shaotian and Steamed Bun Invasion could be considered extraordinary in this area. As a result, they wholeheartedly played without being distracted. They were so good that when they got to Zombie Bailey, with one of them singing and one of them talking, they were able to successfully send Zombie Bailey up into the crack on their first try.

In the last third of the dungeon, the situation stayed the same. And when the final BOSS fell, the two girls immediately got up. One yelled “I’m going to get water”, the other yelled “I’m going to use the restroom” and then disappeared in a flash. They were even faster than the system announcement.

System Announcement: Congratulations to Blue Brook Guild’s players: Lord Grim, Cleansing Mist, Soft Mist, Steamed Bun Invasion, and Flowing Tree for breaking the Boneyard dungeon record, time: 16:24:67.

They beat the record by 32 seconds. Huang Shaotian’s prediction was correct. Excellent Dynasty’s record was already extremely close to the limit. To be able to beat it by 30 seconds wasn’t easy.

“32 seconds…….. 32 seconds……..” Liu Hao hadn’t moved a muscle since Lord Grim’s message. He hadn’t even seen the pile of messages Steamed Bun Invasion had sent him. He had been staring at the system announcements the entire time. He had kept on telling himself that there was no way his record could be beaten, yet he had still waited there staring.

It finally arrived. A 32 second improvement. Liu Hao had absolutely no idea how that was possible.

Flowing Tree? Who was this?

Hateful Sword was still in Blue Brook Guild. He immediately opened up the guild roster and then searched for Flowing Tree. Level 27, Blade Master.

To be able to beat his record, this player’s skill couldn’t be low. However, because this Boneyard was a completely new strategy, if it was someone like Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion, then they’d need a lot of practice. But this player had joined tonight and then immediately went to break the record. Was this someone Ye Qiu had prepared long ago? Or was it another pro-level player that could quickly grasp the strategy?

Looking at the time, this was their second run after 12 o’clock. With their 32 second improvement, even if they had made a few mistakes with Zombie Bailey, it was still enough to take down Excellent Dynasty’s record. But they hadn’t the first time, which meant the first run was very slow. It was a test run. It was for learning.

To be able to completely grasp the strategy in one run. This sort of quality meant he had to be a pro-player.

A pro-player…….. Blade Master……. Then thinking of tonight’s match……. Huang Shaotian.

Liu Hao almost coughed up blood.

Who would believe him? That his Boneyard Dungeon had actually been set by Ye Qiu and Huang Shaotian. Could this still be called setting a f*cking record? They’re holding an all-star event!!

However, even if he was Huang Shaotian, it still shouldn’t be by 32 seconds right? Although he was an amazing top-tier player, it was only Boneyard. No matter how amazing, there was still a limit. Any pro-player could reach that limit. Could it be that there was some hidden strategy? There shouldn’t be one! He didn’t see anywhere that could be improved on!

Liu Hao’s soul left his body. He could only feel anguish swamp his heart. He left the room and wanted to walk around, when he accidentally bumped into Su Mucheng.

“Hi!” Su Mucheng greeted Liu Hao. This was unprecedented. Su Mucheng never gave face to the people who had driven out Ye Qiu. She was never polite to them.

“Thanks for your help!” Su Mucheng smiled and then swiftly walked away.

Help…… what does that mean? What help! How did I help!! Liu Hao’s face fell deathly pale. He clenched his fists so hard that his bones almost popped out.

“You……. halt.” Liu Hao growled fiercely.

Chapter 123 – Talking to Himself

“Oh, is there something you need?” Su Mucheng turned her head and smiled sweetly, the complete opposite of Liu Hao’s cold and fierce expression.

The two looked at each other. Each with fire in their eyes.

Even though she was smiling, Su Mucheng’s eyes displayed an even colder gaze than Liu Hao’s.

In their eyes, Su Mucheng was always a warm girl and was very kind to everyone. However, she stayed around Ye Qiu’s left and right most of the time as if she never had her own opinion. This sort of girl seemed very easy to bully.

Liu Hao fiendishly roared for Su Mucheng to halt. But now that they looked into each other’s eyes, he was the one who felt unconfident.

“If you have nothing to say, then I’ll be leaving first.” Su Mucheng laughed, turned her body around, and left.

Liu Hao watched as Su Mucheng gradually walked farther and farther away. Gradually, he calmed down. After sucking in a deep breath, he returned back to his room.

Taking his cellphone, Liu Hao gave Excellent Dynasty’s guild leader Chen Yehui a call.

“Hello, Liu…….” The voice on the other side was a bit hesitant as if he didn’t know what he should say.

“You deal with the dungeons yourself for now! It’s a bit troublesome for me to come out right now.” Liu Hao said.

“Oh…….”

“The tenth server…… if no pro-player meddles with it, then the records will definitely be ruled by Ye Qiu. The standoff between the different guilds have already shifted to this. Right now, it’s basically who can win over Ye Qiu’s help.” Liu Hao said.

“That’s…… not convenient for us, no?” Chen Yehui said.

“You can try contact him and see what his attitude towards us is. If it’s no good, then still pay attention to him. See if there are any openings. There is one important thing I need you to find out.”

“What is it?”

“Ye Qiu’s price. After each collaboration with a guild, tell me what rewards he gets! That’s something I hope you find out for me.”

“Do you want me to find players to oppose him? He’s lacking manpower right now.” Chen Yehui said.

“This……. you can try it, but don’t send out players from our guild. Don’t let other guilds find out. Right now, Lord Grim is a very important player to them. Who knows whether he’ll join a big guild to protect himself.” Liu Hao said.

“Okay, then I’ll figure it out from here!” Chen Yehui expressed.

“Yeah, I’ll come visit the tenth server when I have time. Let’s keep in contact.” Liu Hao said.

“Okay.”

After hanging up the phone, Liu Hao sucked in a deep breath. He couldn’t move on impulse again. These past few days, he’d been too excited, which was why he made so many mistakes. Destroying Ye Qiu’s record was a failure and he had even been reversed duped by Ye Qiu. Even though it made him extremely angry, in the end, he was the only one to blame and was suffering because of it.

The one mistake he truly shouldn’t have been made was in tonight’s match, where he made several mistakes in a row that caused them to lose.

Even though they only won three points last match, Sun Xiang had at least done a 1v3, which gave fans hope.

This time, they were the home team against the visiting second place team Blue Rain. If they had won a few more points, then it would have a beautiful turn around for them. In the team competition, Excellent Era really did hold more of an advantage. However, their vice-captain’s several amateurish mistakes cost them the competition.

Now, even though everyone was unhappy, they still temporarily regarded it as a mistake that he made because of his poor condition. But, if Excellent Era’s record continued to stumble and never rise, then when reviewing the season, what could have originally been Excellent Era’s comeback was completely ruined all because of Liu Hao’s mistake. His mistakes wasn’t a mere mistake, it was an extremely heavy mistake.

This mistake was enough to affect his future. Right now, if he didn’t deal with the situation and still privately distracted himself by tangling with the retired Ye Qiu, then everything really would be over for him.

Ye Qiu…… I know you’re still unwilling to give up. But things have only just started. Let’s see just how capable you are. I’ll be watching!

Liu Hao gnashed his teeth. He did one final snarl at the mirror and then fiercely rubbed his face. After putting down his hands, a harmless smile appeared on his face. It was as if he had performed some sort of magical shape-shifting spell.

Liu Hao pulled open the door and then walked out once again. His gaze shifted to his neighbor’s room. A small glimmer of light shone through the crack between the door and the wall.

“Cough.” Liu Hao coughed and then lightly knocked on the door: “Sun, did you rest?”

“The door’s not locked.”The reply from the person in the room was extremely cool, but his tone revealed that he clearly wasn’t in a good mood.

Liu Hao adjusted his expression one final time and smiled: “Then I’m coming in!” He pushed open the door and entered.

In the Happy Internet Cafe, after they ran the dungeon twice, the record was broken; the two girls too. Tang Rou really did go to get some water. But carrying her teacup, she refused to leave from the reception desk and talked with Ye Xiu about this and that. All the way until Ye Xiu saw Cleansing Mist take the initiative to go offline and rest, before exclaiming: “No more dungeoning, right?”

Ye Xiu laughed bitterly in helplessness: “Up to you!”

“I remember there’s a quest that I hadn’t finished yet.” Tang Rou mumbled to herself and then left. Ye Xiu was speechless. This girl usually hated to do quests, especially those delivery, mushroom gathering, turnip digging, search ones, etc etc. The difficulty for these were extremely low. They didn’t have combat in them, so Tang Rou regarded them as a waste of time and hated them to the extreme. She had to grind her teeth while doing them because Ye Xiu had reminded her that they were must-do quests, which rewarded attributes or skill points.

To make Tang Rou prefer doing her most hated quests rather than such a fun activity like dungeoning, that made Ye Xiu gasp in admiration: Huang Shaotian deserved to be called the one who changed the Alliance’s rules.

“What happened? What happened? Where’d everyone go? Why is no one responding.”

Actually, Ye Xiu wasn’t so tough either. He also took off his headphones and rested for a bit. Right when he put his headphones back on, those crying sounds immediately popped up again. Huang Shaotian was still scared of having his identity exposed. He nested in the darkness of Area A and lowered his voice when speaking, but even so, he still talked non-stop, his spirit excellent.

“Okay, we’ve set the record. We don’t need to keep dungeoning.” Ye Xiu said, while bracing himself.

“Did you hear what I was saying before?’ Huang Shaotian clearly didn’t know that Ye Xiu had taken off his headphones. People like him who loved to talk incidentally also carried a “talk to himself” attribute. Otherwise, there would often be times where there would be nothing to talk about. Talking to himself meant that he didn’t need to hear other’s replies, so he was never aware that other people weren’t listening.

“Oh, it wasn’t too clear, what did you say?” Ye XIu asked.

“What’s with your weapon?”

“Self-made, Thousand Chance Umbrella.” Ye Xiu said.

“You made it? When did you make it? How come I never heard about it?” Huang Shaotian asked.

“It was from a long time ago, when you were still stealing BOSSes back then.” Ye Xiu said.

“D*MN D*MN D*MN!! Don’t remind me of those terrible times!!” Huang Shaotian panicked. At that time, he was still just a normal player. But his ability to take advantage of openings had already been completed. He was an expert at stealing BOSSes. In the early days of Glory, the rules were very different than now.

“It was at that time that me and my friend made it together.” Ye Xiu said.

“This weapon……. it looks like it’s specially made for unspecialized characters?” Huang Shaotian said.

“Correct.” Ye Xiu said.

“But when the third server opened, the level cap increased. Class Awakening Quests were introduced and unspecialized characters disappeared.”

Ye Xiu didn’t reply. He didn’t need to reply because of Huang Shaotian’s ability to “talk to himself.”

“So your weapon lost its value until the fifth server opened and the Heavenly Domain was introduced. Unspecialized characters that couldn’t awaken could gain experience and continue leveling in the Heavenly Domain, however at that time the level cap had increased to Level 60. Even though the Heavenly Domain Duel Challenge has no level limit, it had a Level 60 difficulty. And the series of quests had to be done individually, so no one could help you which was why the trend of unspecialized characters never resurrected. And at that time you were already using One Autumn Leaf in the pro-scene. The title Battle God had already been given to you, so you never turned back to it.” Sure enough, Huang Shaotian voluntarily said a whole bunch of stuff.

“Yup!” Ye Xiu replied this time.

“Right now, you’re planning on starting from the bottom up again?” Huang Shaotian asked.

“Yup!”

“Then why’d you retire? You could have asked for a random account already leveled. You give the weapon to the Club to finish, wouldn’t that be faster? I don’t understand. I really don’t understand. Why’d you retire?” Huang Shaotian asked.

“Can you not understand ‘Team performance isn’t good. Team captain takes the blame and resigns’?” Ye Xiu said.

“So? There’s still no need to retire! If we talk about your matches, I’ve seen them all. It’s clearly the team was at fault and you were isolated by them. Was it Liu Hao’s schemes? That guy’s like a hungry wolf. Just one look and you can tell he’s up to no good. You’re way too careless.” Huang Shaotian said.

“When did you learn how to read people’s’ faces?” Ye Xiu said.

“I didn’t say that. That’s what Wang Jiexi said.” Huang Shaotian said.

“How could he judge other people’s faces with his uneven face?” Ye Xiu said.

“Stop talking!! That guy really does know some magic! Last time…….” Huang Shaotian blabbered on. On the side, Steamed Bun Invasion hadn’t left yet. He also didn’t understand what the two were talking about and was pitifully waiting on the side.

“Steamed Bun, there’s nothing else for today! If you want to go to the Arena or the dungeon, go ahead!” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay.” Steamed Bun Invasion left.

“Oh right! Let’s go for a round. I want to see just how great your weapon is!” Huang Shaotian said.

“And you’re going to use this account?” Ye Xiu laughed.

“What’s wrong with this account? It’s a Level 27 one like yours. The weapon is a bit lacking, but it’ll make do!” Huang Shaotian said.

“This account’s an unspecialized account though.” Ye Xiu said.

Players who didn’t understand wouldn’t understand what he meant. But when Huang Shaotian heard this, he was immediately startled. Right, if it was an unspecialized account, even though they were at the same level, he had a big advantage. Why? Because at Level 27, no matter what class the account was, it would only have access to 7 sub-class only skills. But unspecialized players? At Level 20, they had access to 120 skills. That difference was too great. That was why everyone had put unspecialized characters as kings in the past. They were kings because unspecialized characters were completed extremely early and their advantage in the early game was extremely large, so large that it was almost completely broken. To only use a Blade Master with 7 skills against an unspecialized character, he’d definitely go in and never come out. Huang Shaotian clearly recognized this point.

“Take out your Troubling Rain and let’s try it out. We’ll obviously be fighting in the Fixed Field.” Ye Xiu said.

“How is that okay!?” Huang Shaotian panicked, “That would expose me. If someone saw, how am I supposed to explain it. It’s fine, it’s fine. We’ll battle some other time then! Do you have anything else you need? If there’s nothing else, then I’m going back. Oh right, why’d you retire? And why didn’t you reply to my last question? Ah?”

“You…… hurry up and go back!” Even Ye Xiu was feeling a bit powerless. He really was too noisy……

Chapter 124 – The Crudest Style

Over in the corner, Huang Shaotian closed his computer. He once again scrunched back into a ball, hiding himself. He evilly snuck out from the darkness. Ye Xiu, who was at the reception desk, had been watching him the entire time and had no choice but to watch as the guy carefully prodded over.

“Why did you retire? Why did you retire?” Huang Shaotian was still asking him.

“If I didn’t retire, you think I’d want to stay in the team to be a training partner?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Training partner? Excellent Era really wanted to drive you out!” Huang Shaotian said, “But isn’t directly retiring too impulsive? You should have tried looking for somewhere to transfer to! Even if Excellent Era absolutely refused to let you go, that doesn’t mean that there was zero chance for you to transfer. There might have been a team that would pay a high enough price for Excellent Era to let you go. At the very least, you should have waited until you saw that there was absolutely nowhere to transfer before retiring!”

“If I transferred……. then what about Mucheng?” Ye Xiu said.

Huang Shaotian stared blankly.

They were both god-level players in the pro-scene, how could he not understand this? For popular players like Su Mucheng, some Club owners wouldn’t let her go even if they had to trade off the rest of the team. She was simply a money tree, a money-sucking machine to the owner. Her financial value was far greater than her skill value. Even for Huang Shaotian, even he wasn’t guaranteed that he wouldn’t be transferred to another Club. But for Su Mucheng, most owners would even sacrifice their team standings to keep her.

“If I transferred, then Mucheng would definitely terminate her contract.” Ye Xiu said.

“So it’s like this…… then what about terminating your contract? Hmm…… if you terminated your contract like that, then they wouldn’t let you join another team for at least half a year, but it’d at least be better than you retiring for a minimum one year. But if you did retire, then there’d be no way for you to return to Excellent Era. It’d be the same as you transferring. If you retired for a year, then at the very least you wouldn’t need to pay contract termination fees or maybe you could even buy out the contract right? After a year……. how long does Mucheng’s contract last until?” Huang Shaotian talked to himself a bunch.

“One and a half years.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh…… so then, you’re planning on coming back after a year and a half? A year and a half! You’re too crazy, aren’t you?” Huang Shaotian expressed his astonishment. ESport pro-players had a short career. It was extremely rare for someone 25 years old to be able to play at this level of skill. To still dare to retire for a year and half, that was simply going against the heavens.

“Ha ha, just wait until I come back and destroy you!” Ye Xiu said.

“F*ck, you’re too arrogant, aren’t you?” Huang Shaotian yelled.

“What’s the current record for our duels again?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Ha…… tonight’s weather is pretty good!” Huang Shaotian gaze shifted to the pitch black night outside of the Internet Cafe.

After standing there staring outside for awhile, Huang Shaotian’s gaze returned back. His expression turned serious: “You have to come back.”

“Who need you say that.” Ye Xiu said.

“If you have any difficulties, contact me.” Huang Shaotian said earnestly.

“Give me back my Vampiric Lightsaber and the fee for two hours of Internet.” Ye Xiu said.

“…….” He finally stopped talking for once.

“I’ll give you the Vampiric Lightsaber later!” Huang Shaotian slapped down ten bucks onto the reception desk. He turned around and faded into the night.

“Flowing Tree went off?” Ye Xiu returned to the game and received a message from Tang Rou.

“Yeah.”

“Dungeon?” Tang Rou asked.

Ye Xiu laughed. He immediately gathered everyone and ran to the dungeon.

The record 16:24:67 on the record leaderboards, made Blue River speechless for a long time. Still staring at it, he suddenly received a message. He opened it and saw that it was Lord Grim: “How many keyboards did you eat?”

Blue River’s cheeks streamed with tears. The record, which he swore he’d eat his keyboard if it was broken, was currently number three on the Boneyard record leaderboards. If he did as he had promised, then he’d have to at least eaten a few keyboards.

“Brother, please don’t joke with me.” Blue River said gloomily.

“Ha ha, there shouldn’t be any problem with the record this time.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay, okay.” Blue River replied, but didn’t say too much. Ye Xiu also understood. The record had been broken again and again. The experts in the game, the ones who could be considered as having good judgement, were all at a loss. Blue River still had to pay attention to this. However, the current record really was at the peak. Unless a guild was willing to pay the effort to gather a party with full Orange equipment and also look for experts to substitute in. For the new server, the possibility of that was zero.

The player who even more shocked by this record was naturally Cold Night. Originally, he had celebrated when Lord Grim’s record was broken again by Excellent Dynasty. He felt that the Excellent Dynasty experts that substituted in were even more amazing and felt that Lord Grim wouldn’t be able to handle it this time. Who knew that not long after, Lord Grim set the record back again.

Soft Mist, Steamed Bun Invasion, Cleansing Mist, these were all players Cold Night knew.

But what about last time’s Hateful Sword?

And who was that Flowing Tree from this time?

What the heck was happening in the tenth server? Why were there so many random experts? Was this still the new server?

Cold Night and Blue River were the same. They had lost all confidence in their judgement. They had no idea whether this record could still be broken. They and a bunch of other guilds watched this record all night.

None! There was no other system announcement. Was Boneyard finally stable again? But, it was only today, that’s all. Every big guild watched for it attentively for another day. The record still hadn’t moved. Let alone the number one record, the number three record hadn’t even been touched.

Because Excellent Dynasty showed the strength of players who were at a level higher than them for the last two dungeon records, they received the attention of all the big guilds. Hidden accounts frequently appeared and then mysteriously vanished. But for the previous experts who had played, it was truly too difficult to gather any information of them from just the guild’s channel. Even more so, these were Excellent Era’s players substituting in. Besides the guild leader Chen Yehui, even their own guild members didn’t know that.

Even though everyone suspected that they had relied on their behind-the-scenes Club experts to set it, if the Club experts ran over to play in the dungeon, it would just be an occasional run for fun. But why did it look like they were picking a fight with Lord Grim? As pro-players, did it really make sense for them to go that far?

From another perspective, if Excellent Dynasty had sent out their top pro-players to set it, then who exactly was this Lord Grim who had stepped all over their record?

Lord Grim, Soft Mist, Steamed Bun Invasion, Cleansing Mist…… everyone had already become familiar with these IDs, which had appeared on TV several times. Who knew how many guilds had sent players to investigate these characters.

These players were extremely skilled. No one doubted that. If they weren’t, how could they have set such a record? What these guilds wanted to know was exactly how skilled were they?

After silently noticing these characters, who knew how many eyes were set on them. Under the circumstances where they weren’t confident in their judgement, quite a few guilds had already reported to the Heavenly Domain headquarters and had their experts from over there come. Even if they didn’t come to level, it was still okay for them to observe these few rising figures.

Herb Garden.

They were one of the Three Great Guilds, yet even so, they never made any sort of official contact with Lord Grim.

At this moment, in the tenth server’s guild leader Plantago Seed’s field of view were a few players fighting wild monsters. However, Plantago Seed seemed somewhat out of it. To be precise, he looked terrified.

Right now, he was sitting there, controlling his character. But behind him stood a genuine god-level figure.

Wang Jiexi, Club Tiny Herb’s ace player, last season’s Champion, Tiny Herb’s team captain and last season’s MVP. In the current season, his team was the current leader in points, suppressing Blue Rain as the leading team. Wang Jiexi’s account character Vaccaria was a Witch. Using weird, variable movements and strategies, he was widely known in the pro-scene as the Magician.

Plantago Seed had reported to his guild on the tenth server’s current situation, but who knew he’d alert such a great God and even cause him to personally run over to take a look at these Level 27 characters.

Plantago Seed felt an enormous pressure on him, making his playing extremely unnatural. Plantago Seed suddenly remembered the adorned notebook that was in his grasp. The notebook was a souvenir he bought after Tiny Herb’s championship victory. When Plantago Seed found out that God was coming over personally, he hurriedly brought the notebook with him hoping to get a signature from him.

But after seeing God looking at him with his uneven eyes, Plantago Seed had immediately tensed up and forgotten about it. He was currently moving his character to look for Lord Grim and the others for God to look at and only now did he remember about the signature he wanted.

How do I start……. Plantago Seed was currently thinking about this, when he suddenly heard a voice from behind him: “You’ve got a message.”

“Message?” Plantago Seed had already become so stupid from nervousness that he had even forgotten what that word meant. After a long while, he recovered and saw that his character had received a message. Opening it, he saw that it was a bunch of random chatter. He hastily closed it and settled his view onto Lord Grim and the others.

Lord Grim, Steamed Bun Invasion, Soft Mist.

Right now, these three were at Boneyard leveling. Besides them, there were also Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon. Even Plantago Seed didn’t see these two in his eyes and tried to get them of his view out as much as he could.

At low-levels, there were only a few skills that could be learned and only a single strategy, so determining a player’s skill wasn’t easy. For example, for players like Plantago Seed, they had no way of figuring out exactly how skilled Lord Grim was. But that was different for the God behind him, if even he couldn’t figure it out, then Plantago Seed didn’t know who else could.

“It’s One Autumn Leaf’s combat style.” Wang Jiexi suddenly said, after silently watching for awhile.

“Which one?

“Both of them.” Wang Jiexi said.

In his view, Soft Mist was a Battle Mage and Lord Grim was also using his battle lance to use Battle Mage skills.

“Lord Grim’s an unspecialized character.” Plantago Seed said. After saying this, he regretted it. What nonsense, how could the God Jiexi not see that?

“Yeah.” Wang Jiexi still replied.

“Is there anything special about One Autumn Leaf’s combat style?” Plantago Seed promptly asked him.

“There’s nothing special about it. It’s the crudest style.” Wang Jiexi said.

Plantago Seed immediately paid his respects! To dare say that the Battle God One Autumn Leaf’s combat style was the crudest, exactly how godly was Wang Jiexi?

“What about this Brawler?” Plantago Seed continued asking.

“This Brawler……” Even Wang Jiexi was having trouble finding the right words, “To say it nicely, he’s following his heart’s desire. To say it bluntly, he’s a complete mess.”

Chapter 125 – God Jiexi

“Their mechanics are pretty good, right?” Plantago Seed said.

“Yeah.” Wang Jiexi agreed. To normal players, these three’s mechanical skill really were enough to be considered “good”, even that completely irrational Brawler.

“But we’re only watching them fight against monsters, so there’s not much to be seen.” Wang Jiexi said.

“Then what?” Plantago Seed asked.

“Lend me your account to use for a bit. I’m going to go and say hello to them.” Wang Jiexi said.

“Ah!” Plantago Seed hurriedly got up and let up his seat. This “Ah!” carried a tone of pleasant surprise. He was surprised because God Jiexi would actually personally come out because of these three. And he was pleased because he had the chance to see God Jiexi’s skill in action up-close. It has to be known that even in a pro match, it still wouldn’t be possible to see him in action up-close like this.

Wang Jiexi walked up and sat down. He casually tapped the keyboard and moved the mouse. Plantago Seed knew that pro-players all had their own keyboard and mouse they liked to use. If it was just to casually play, it wouldn’t matter too much to them, but they’d still feel somewhat awkward with it.

Soon after, Wang Jiexi opened up the keyboard settings. He sweeped over it and then went “Oh? It’s the same as mine? Are you learning from me?”

“Yeah. You’re my biggest idol! Could I trouble you with a signature!!” Plantago Seed finally found the opportunity and smoothly asked him. His class was the same as the class Wang Jiexi was most proficient in, the Witch. His keyboard settings were also the exact same as Wang Jiexi’s.

“Is it hard for you?” Wang Jiexi asked.

“It’s……. it’s okay.” Plantago Seed said.

Wang Jiexi didn’t say anything more. He moved the mouse and tapped the keyboard. The in-game Plantago Seed swiftly rushed towards where those five players were leveling at.

Ye Xiu had noticed Plantago Seed peeping at them long ago, but didn’t care. Now that he saw him running towards them, he guessed that it was to discuss about dungeon-related things. Who knew that right when he arrived, he’d use a Witch’s long-ranged attack and suddenly fire a magic missile over.

“What are you doing?” This magic missile’s target was Soft Mist. At this moment, Soft Mist’s back was facing towards Plantago Seed. Only after being hit by it was she able to react. She quickly turned her camera angle, but couldn’t understand what was going on. Tang Rou had never experienced something like PKing in the wilderness.

Ye Xiu was also extremely astonished. Why did Plantago Seed mysteriously start fighting? How astonishing! Then he saw Plantago Seed say: “Let’s compare notes.”

“What’s going on?” Tang Rou was also puzzled. But Plantago Seed had already sent out another magic missile towards her. Now that they were face to face, how could it be so easy to hit Tang Rou. With a quick tap, Tang Rou dodged the missile. She wasn’t so polite either and immediately began counter attacking. Soft Mist carried her battle lance and swiftly dashed towards Plantago Seed.

Plantago Seed didn’t move forward and instead retreated. He continued to leisurely throw out magic missiles. But every time a magic missile was sent out, the character still had to stop for a bit. So after a few casts, Soft Mist was still able to close in on him. Her battle lance leaped and a Sky Strike slashed at him. Plantago Seed flew into the air. Right when Soft Mist was about to continue attacking, she heard a gentle “whoosh” and Plantago Seed continued to fly over her head. A cloud of medicinal powder sprinkled onto Soft Mist’s body.

Tang Rou was startled. For a short while, she didn’t know what to do. However, Plantago Seed had already landed next to her and then “whoosh whoosh” sent two more magic missiles at her. Tang Rou immediately thought of having Soft Mist dodge, but Soft Mist’s movements had already turned sluggish. She dodged the first missile, but the second missile exploded like a flower onto her.

“What? Have you never fought with a Witch before?” Ye Xiu hurriedly asked Tang Rou. She knew that Tang Rou, with her pitiful amount of experience in Glory, still had some experience in the Arena when she fought for Chen Guo. However, Glory had a total of 24 classes. Because Tang Rou had only occasionally fought, it wasn’t anything surprising that she had never fought against some classes.

“Yeah!” Tang Rou answered.

“I’ve seen this class!!” Steamed Bun Invasion had been soaking in the Arena in these past few days. In these short few days, he had already met with all of the classes, “They can ride on a broom to fly. Just now, he threw a Laxative at you. Did you feel that your body turned soft and your movements turned slow?”

Laxative?????

The two revered gods instantly petrified. Who the f*ck came up with such a name? The powder that Plantago Seed had thrown onto Soft Mist was called “Disperse Powder”, a Level 20 Witch skill. If it was successfully sprinkled onto the target’s body, then it would remove a buff and reduce the target’s attack, casting, and movement speed. Even if the opponent didn’t have any buffs on them, the slow effect would still arise for up to ten seconds. It was a CC skill that Witches often used.

This skill didn’t have any nickname or abbreviation, but right now, Steamed Bun Invasion gave it the name “Laxative” and even said that it made your body turn soft and your movements turn slow…… it was true that it caused your movements to turn slow, but where did he get “your body turned soft” from?

The two revered gods were shocked frozen by Steamed Bun Invasion and even more so were Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon. At this moment, they were all astonished on the name “Laxative”. It really did kind of fit.

Who knew when, but Steamed Bun Invasion had quietly snuck up behind Plantago Seed and smashed a Brick over.

But how could Wang Jiexi be compared to Tang Rou. Even though he wasn’t looking behind him, he had noticed Steamed Bun Invasion’s movements long ago. He suddenly crouched and Steamed Bun Invasion’s Brick hit nothing but air. Plantago Seed took advantage and counter-attacked with a “Sweep”. This was A Witch’s lowest-leveled knock-up skill. Its knock-up effect was the worst among all 24 classes. With a Sweep, the character quickly fell to the ground. The knock-up was very slight and was very difficult to see.

But Wang Jiexi’s actions naturally weren’t ordinary. In this slight knock-up, Plantago Seed rode his broom and completed a short flight. Following this sweep, he sweeped Steamed Bun Invasion into the air. After six consecutive sweeps, the two characters flew higher and higher with every sweep. Plantago Seed then finished with a heavy attack, smacking Steamed Bun Invasion to the ground, while he leisurely flew back to the ground on his broom.

To be able to attack like this was naturally because of the passive skill Witches learned after changing classes: Broom Mastery.

Brooms are Witch-only weapons. Only Witches could use it after changing classes. Unspecialized characters could use the majority of weapons, but there were still a few class-specific weapons that unspecialized couldn’t use. A Blade Master’s Lightsaber was one and a Witch’s Broom was another.

The passive skill Broom Master gave Witches the ability to consecutively attack the opponent while flying. Not all classes had this type of skill. With this type of aerial combat ability, Witches were headaches to many classes.

Steamed Bun Invasion’s actions weren’t slow. In the Arena, he had accumulated a bit of PK experience, yet he had still been casually beaten down. After the consecutive broom hits and the final smackdown, Steamed Bun Invasion planned on using a Quick Recover to prevent falling to the ground, but wasn’t able to do it in time. His hands smashed to the ground, creating a hole.

This wasn’t a coincidence. This was all done intentionally by Wang Jiexi in the air. He had controlled how Steamed Bun Invasion was going to fall, making it much harder for Steamed Bun Invasion to use Quick Recover. If his judgement or hand speed wasn’t enough, then he wouldn’t have time to use it. A pro-player’s ability to calculate and meticulous movements were far greater than normal players.

Right when Plantago Seed landed, Soft Mist had rushed forward. With a battle lance, she powerfully swept across like a torrent. But the passive skill Broom Mastery didn’t have any cooldown and could be used anytime soon. Plantago Seed immediately leapt onto his broom and then once again flew away. Tang Rou controlled Soft Mist to run left and right, but was unable to catch him no matter what she did. After Steamed Bun Invasion climbed up from the ground, he rushed up to join Soft Mist without hesitation. But in the end, the two players still danced around in his palms.

If Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon went to Pk, they definitely wouldn’t be able to beat Tang Rou or Steamed Bun Invasion. But as spectators, they would certainly be better than those two. At this moment…….

“Meet my Brick!!” Steamed Bun Invasion hadn’t been able to touch his opponent for a long time. He angrily threw his Brick. In the end, Plantago Seed rode his broom to meet it and then swept at it in midair. The timing of this attack was perfect and he directly interrupted the flying Brick, sending it back towards its owner, Steamed Bun Invasion.

“F*CK!!” Steamed Bun Invasion yelled. Right when he was about to duck and dodge it, a sword light flashed by and the Brick was smashed into pieces in midair. Ye Xiu finally acted. He launched a Sword Draw and accurately hit the Brick into pieces.

Plantago Seed landed and then immediately threw out a magic missile at Lord Grim and then once again went back on his broom, ready to escape. But unexpectedly, Lord Grim ignored this magic missile and directly used a Collapsing Mountain to leap over. This Collapsing Mountain had much higher priority over this magic missile. Even though he was hit by the magic missile, he would only take damage and wouldn’t be interrupted.

Right when it looked like Collapsing Mountain was about to hit, the broom-riding Plantago Seed suddenly leaned forward unexpectedly and the Collapsing Mountain brushed past him.

Plantago Seed followed up with a leap and swept out in 180 degrees angle. But Lord Grim, who had just completed Collapsing Mountain, seemed to flash.

Shadow Clone Technique!!

Even though Wang Jiexi had instantly made the judgement, he knew the situation wasn’t looking good. It wasn’t as if Broom Mastery could be used non-stop flying down. Wang Jiexi, who had just been flying, had already turned and leaped. He was currently in midair and before hitting the ground, he wouldn’t be able to ride on his broom and fly away.

Without anywhere to run, Wang Jiexi swiped his keyboard. Plantago Seed once again turned around 180 degrees. Just as expected, with the Shadow Clone Technqiue, Lord Grim had flashed over to behind him. He stamped down, using the Striker skill “Eagle Stamp”.

Plantago Seed immediately swept and also damaged Lord Grim at the same time. Under the situation where there was no where to dodge, he could only use the strategy where both sides took damage.

But after Lord Grim’s Eagle Stamp, Lord Grim didn’t continue stamping. After the stamp he drew his sword and completed a Guard in midair, blocking Plantago Seed’s horizontal sweep.

Plantago Seed’s owner, the real Plantago Seed, was standing behind Wang Jiexi dumbstruck.

To be able to instantly do such an exchange of blows in midair, the one who lost was actually God Jiexi. Who exactly was this Lord Grim?

Chapter 126 – What Exactly is He Trying to Do?

Plantago Seed was still hopeful.

But right when he saw that Wang Jiexi was about to have Plantago Seed fall to the ground and use Quick Recover, a blade edge once again flashed by. After guarding and flying backwards, Lord Grim had used another Falling Light Blade. The light blade descended down onto Plantago Seed at Quick Recover’s crucial moment. The Quick Recover failed and Plantago Seed ate the attack and rolled sadly onto the ground.

This time, he really had suffered. The situation wasn’t looking good.

Even Wang Jiexi himself felt somewhat helpless, shaking his head and sighing: “Fighting against an unspecialized at Level 27 really is difficult!”

Saying this, he ignored the incoming characters. After getting up, he turned around and flew away. To the Plantago Seed behind him, it practically looked like he just picked up the broom and started flying along the ground. For Witches to ride on their brooms, they had to leap up into the air in order to use the skill. But seeing Wang Jiexi’s extremely quick and skilled movements. Plantago Seed almost couldn’t tell when he had completed the leap.

Flying was somewhat faster than running, so Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion arrived one step too late. But Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon were impressively waiting to welcome Plantago Seed on his flight path.

Wang Jiexi hadn’t put these two characters in his eyes. At this moment, he practically ignored them, too lazy to even move his hands. With one lazy flick, Plantago Seed’s broom flew diagonally over the two’s heads. Seven Fields punched out and Sleeping Moon slashed with his sword. But the two attacks hit air. After turning around, they saw that Plantago Seed had already slipped even farther away.

The two were helpless. They didn’t continue chasing and walked back. Seven Fields yelled regretfully: “Brother expert……”

“No problem.” Ye Xiu didn’t say much. He was the one who had instructed the two to intercept him. But with their skills, intercepting the target was too difficult. Even Steamed Bun Invasion and Tang Rou had been fooled into running around in circles.

A player’s skill in a dungeon was restricted to how difficult the dungeon was. In comparison, PK was a much better representation of a player’s skill. Even if the skills that could be learned at Level 27 were limited, a player’s pathing, decision-making, attack timing, etc. could be seen. Depending on your own skill, you could see just how deep or shallow the opponent’s level was.

“Could it be that guy?” That Witch’s skill could already be considered top among pros. There was no way the person playing on it was the tenth server’s guild leader. Ye Xiu thought to himself as he watched Plantago Seed’s far-away figure.

After Wang Jiexi’s Plantago Seed had run far away, he got up and gave Plantago Seed back to the real Plantago Seed. Plantago Seed looked at God, wanting to hear his verdict. In the end, Wang Jiexi didn’t say a word.

Plantago Seed was fidgeting in his heart. He had seen that Wang Jiexi wasn’t quite Lord Grim’s opponent and had ran away, so he didn’t know whether God was in a bad mood or not.

“Signature. Where do I sign?” Wang Jiexi suddenly said.

“Ah?” Plantago Seed stared blankly. He suddenly recovered and then hastily brought out the warm notebook that he had been embracing. The cover of the notebook was a Witch riding on a broom. There was a single small word written on the side: Vaccaria.

Wang Jiexi took it and smiled. He waited for Plantago Seed fluster around for pen and then asked after taking it: “Is it okay for me to sign the title page?”

“Okay, okay……” Plantago Seed hastily replied.

Wang Jiexi scribbled his practiced signature and then handed it back to Plantago Seed: “I’m going. Bye.”

“Ah……. God…….” Plantago Seed couldn’t help but stop Wang Jiexi, “This…….” He pointed at the screen. He wanted to know Wang Jiexi’s verdict.

“That Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion’s mechanical skill aren’t bad, but they’re still new players. They don’t have enough knowledge or experience. That Lord Grim…… he’s unspecialized so I still can’t tell how deep or shallow his skill is. You also saw. He was suppressing me and not the other way around. I wanted to test him, but I’m afraid he was the one who tested me.” Wang Jiexi said.

“Does he know who you are?” Plantago Seed felt that it was incredibly hard to believe.

“Oh! Maybe. It depends on his perception. Well, he at least knows that you weren’t the one playing.” Wang Jiexi said. He waved his hands at Plantago Seed and left.

What type of monster is he! Plantago Seed went back to this seat, but was still in a daze. After a short while, he recovered and immediately made his Plantago Seed run far far away. Even God Wang Jiexi admitted that he’d been suppressed. If Lord Grim wants to kill me, then even ten of me won’t be enough!

But how do I confront him later?

Plantago Seed suddenly thought of this question. He turned his head, but found that Wang Jiexi had already left. Plantago Seed was gloomy. He had actually forgotten to ask such an important question.

“What’s up with him?” Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion had wanted to continued chasing, but were blocked by Ye Xiu in the end. Tang Rou could only ask this gloomily.

“That guy was Herb Garden’s guild leader?” Seven Fields said.

“The character is……. but not necessarily the person.” Ye Xiu said.

“Then who was that?” Sleeping Moon asked.

“What I’m about to say might scare you to death. If I’m not wrong, I’m pretty sure that was Wang Jiexi.” Ye Xiu said.

“Ha! And I’m f*cking Huang Shaotian!” Sleeping Moon didn’t believe him one bit.

“Who’s Wang Jiexi?” Tang Rou asked.

“You don’t even know this?” Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon gasped, almost at the same time.

“Why do I need to know that? What astrological sign is he?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked.

“Astrological sign?” Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon were actually pondering over this question. For such a celebrity, there really was information on his astrological sign.

“Wang Jiexi is one of Glory’s top players. His class is the same as the one you guys just saw, a Witch. His nickname is Magician. In Glory, there are a lot of these types of titles, Battle God, Sword Saint, Great Gunner, King of Fighting, etc. but most of these are given to the character. Only Wang Jiexi’s title ‘Magician’ is given to the person himself instead of the character.” Ye Xiu said.

“Why?” Tang Rou asked.

“Because the title describes his combat style. This player’s style is strange and always changing, often exceeding expectations. If he wasn’t the one playing, then the character would be called something else entirely. It wouldn’t be called Magician.” Ye Xiu said.

“If it’s like this, then shouldn’t it be really easy to recognize him?” Tang Rou said.

“Yeah, that’s why I said it’s very likely that that was him.” Ye Xiu said.

“The more you talk, the more believable you sound.” Sleeping Moon said in disdain.

“Wang Jiexi is from Club Tiny Herb. Herb Garden is supported by Tiny Herb. If Wang Jiexi wants to use their characters, then it should be easy for him to do.” Ye Xiu deepened his analysis.

“Then why would he run here to stir up trouble? If he wants to fight, then he should go to the Arena!” Steamed Bun Invasion expressed his resentment.

“Maybe he saw how amazing your skill was, so he impatiently went to test you?” Ye Xiu said.

“Really? Then this guy’s eyes aren’t bad.” Steamed Bun Invasion said sadly.

“F*ck!” Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon both cursed. If it was a normal person saying it, then they would have regarded it as a joke or even as a shameless boast. But this was Steamed Bun Invasion, who actually believed it.

“Herb Garden…….. Many of the the guild players seem to have names of Chinese medicine.” Tang Rou said. This unique characteristic of Herb Garden was quite eye-catching.

“Yup, the names of all of their Club’s characters are all names of Chinese medicine. That’s why most of the important characters in their guild also have that type of name.” Ye Xiu finished and then said to Seven Fields: “Seven Fields, are you from Herb Garden?” (TLN: Seven Fields = Panax Notoginseng)

“I’m not……” Seven Fields said gloomily. He had encountered such misunderstandings before, “I wanted to be called Nine Fields at first. But the demons and gods must have been at work and my hands somehow slipped, changing my name to Seven Fields.” (Author Note: This is a real story. A certain author wanted to use Nine Fields at first, but somehow made it into Seven Fields. To the fan who applied for Long Tao, I messed up with Seven Fields. Seven Fields is Nine Fields.) (TLCN: 龙套 Long Tao, small character, usually, web novelists would allow the fans to apply for a “龙套”. For example, if a reader provided the name Nine Fields and “male”, then the guy Nine Fields might appear in the story. Sadly, author mistook the name. lol)

They continued to chat while leveling. And unexpectedly, they didn’t take what had just happened seriously.

Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion were new players, so they didn’t understand. After recovering from their initial surprise, Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon were both still secretly shocked. That was Plantago Seed! He was the tenth server’s guild leader of Herb Garden, one of the Three Great Guilds. If this was on a normal day, they would have been frightened to death if Herb Garden’s guild leader personally came to attack them. But now? With brother expert, the Three Great Guilds were nothing! There wasn’t any pressure at all!

“It should be Wang Jiexi……” Ye Xiu was still thinking about it. He hadn’t finished his analysis, but he was pretty sure that that person was Wang Jiexi. It was just like what Tang Rou said, his style was too unique, a clear indication that it was him.

“What exactly is he trying to do?” Ye Xiu was also worrying over this question.

Meanwhile, in Herb Garden, after God Jiexi left, Plantago Seed was still pacing about back and forth. From time to time, he would take out his notebook and study it. From time to time, he would smile, loving it too much to part with it.

“Guild leader, guild leader.” At this moment, a message was sent over.

“What?” Plantago Seed replied.

“Boss is looking for you. Get on QQ.” The guild member said. The senior he was talking about was Herb Garden’s leader, the one in the Heavenly Domain, Arisaema.

“Boss, what do you want?” Plantago Seed looked for him.

“How many extra empty accounts do you have over there?” Arisaema said.

“Around ten I think. Why?” Plantago Seed answered. When he said empty accounts, he wasn’t talking about those accounts with no equipment and no money. He was talking about accounts with no definite owner. They were accounts that had been leveled using other people to substitute in or were leveled through the guild’s efforts. These accounts wouldn’t be part of the guild and they wouldn’t use Chinese medicine names, obvious indicators that they were Herb Garden’s. In the end, they were often used as spies or for shady business that wouldn’t be convenient for official guild members. Not just Herb Garden, but other big guilds would raise these types of characters. Some people called then free accounts, others called them empty accounts, it depended on the person.

“Take five of them out! A Ghostblade, Sharpshooter, Battle Mage, Assassin, and Witch. Can you gather these five classes?” Arisaema said.

“Let me see! What are they going to be used for?” Plantago Seed couldn’t remember every class he had listed.

“For the gods above.” Arisaema said.

Plantago Seed heard this and froze. This…… Could it be that because God Jiexi had lost to Lord Grim, he wanted to create a party to retaliate?

Chapter 127 – Five Characters

Plantago Seed didn’t continue to rack his brains over it. God Jiexi was widely known for his unpredictable style. There was no way for him to know what God Jiexi was thinking. Regardless, Plantago Seed refused to believe that God was forming a team just for revenge. He couldn’t imagine that God Jiexi would be that petty.

After asking Arisaema when he wanted those accounts cards, Plantago Seed didn’t think anymore of it and then went to look for the requested account cards.

White Night Black Day, Ghostblade, Level 26.

Fallen Angel, Sharpshooter, Level 27.

Cloudy Heavens, Battle Mage, Level 26.

Ashen Moon, Assassin, Level 25.

Weeping Crow, Witch, Level 26.

The next day, Plantago Seed selected five account cards according to the request. They were all Level 25 and above characters. Among the empty accounts, they could already be considered high leveled.

That same day, a small, shy, and thin youth came to retrieve the cards. Plantago Seed didn’t suspect this person’s identity. When he handed over the cards, he also handed his notebook over.

This youth hadn’t yet participated in an official match in the Glory Alliance. However, his reputation wasn’t lower than even some first-string players. To a loyal fan like Plantago Seed, how could he not be recognized.

This youth was called Gao Yingjie and was a part of Tiny Herb’s inner circle. According to reports, he would be the player to inherit Wang Jiexi’s Vaccaria. As a result, the class he practiced with was also a Witch. Plantago Seed had originally thought that the Witch account card was going to be used by God Jiexi, but now from the looks of it, it looked like it was going to be given to Gao Yingjie.

In front of Gao Yingjie, Plantago Seed wasn’t as terrified as when he was in front of Wang Jiexi. On the contrary, Gao Yingjie was the one standing there shyly looking around left and right.

Plantago Seed took the five account cards and handed them over to Gao Yingjie. He then took out his notebook: “Little Jie, can you sign your name here?”

“Oh!” Once Gao Yingjie took the account cards, he looked as if he was about to run away. Hearing Plantago Seed’s request, for a short while, he didn’t know what to do. His face had also reddened. He had clearly never experienced anything like this before.

After taking the pen Plantago Seed had handed over, Gao Yingjie carefully wrote his name Gao Yingjie onto the notebook. When signing it, his hand was a bit shaky, so the end result looked a little deformed.

“Thank you…….” Gao Yingjie hurriedly handed back the notebook and pen to Plantago Seed and then took off. Plantago Seed didn’t know whether this “thank you” was for the account cards or for his support.

Plantago Seed then logged into the game soon afterwards. He had already added these five characters as friends. He even knew where those five characters were located. Right now, he wanted to know what exactly these five characters were going to be used for. After waiting a long while, he found that none of them had appeared. Plantago Seed wasn’t a marathon runner. He had stayed up all-night yesterday and tonight, he had been waiting for Gao Yingjie to retrieve the cards, so he hadn’t slept tonight either. In the end, he gave up waiting and went to sleep.

Currently, in the tenth server, the highest-leveled characters finally stepped into the Level 30 critical point. New skills, new equipment, their strength naturally increased another-fold. In addition, from Level 30 onwards, there was another large change: class sets would begin appearing. Class sets usually raised the levels or power of a few of their respective classes’ skills. Apart from that, when the set was completed, the additional attributes would naturally increase the user’s strength by another level. From Level 30 onwards, weapons would no longer be the sole factor in determining damage. Characters with their respective completed class sets were on another level compared to characters without a complete set.

Although low-leveled equipment would eventually grow outdated too, to big guilds who scrambled for these types of records, at the very least , their elite teams’ DPS had to maintain a certain standard. As a result, these equipment would also be sought after.

Speaking of records, it could be considered the final moments of observing the Boneyard record for each of the big guilds. For Lord Grim’s friends such as Blue River and Cold Night, they all knew that Lord Grim had already leveled to Level 28. There was already no longer a way for Boneyard’s record to broken again. If Excellent Dynasty were hesitant towards Lord Grim and wouldn’t fight against him, then the record would finally be at ease. If they did try and fight, but still weren’t able to break the Boneyard record, then that would at least mean one thing: The substitute experts of Excellent Dynasty were finally beaten by Lord Grim. This meant that the tenth server’s dungeon record really would be ruled by Lord Grim.

Blue River and Cold Night were direct friends of Lord Grim, while the other big guild leaders had their own ways of contacting him. After watching Boneyard for a full day, they saw that the record hadn’t changed. At the early morning hours, when the dungeon entries refreshed, everyone watched one last time for one or two hours. In the end, they confirmed their decision. Lord Grim immediately became the genuine ruler of the records, and they would now begin fighting for him.

Blue River held the advantage here. Not only was he the first one to work together with Lord Grim. Lord Grim’s party was still under the name Blue Brook Guild. Moreover, he had already made the preface long ago. At this moment, he asked clearly and rationally: “Brother, what do you think about the offer I made last time?”

“Let me think about it again!” Ye Xiu replied.

“Ha ha, brother, I’m sure you understand! Right now, all of the big guilds know of your strength. But if you keep selling your services like this, then the leaderboards will all be under your name in the end. This wouldn’t be good for the guild’s honor. In the end, everyone would recognize your Lord Grim and not the guild. This is something no guild wants to see. And for you, brother, I don’t think you came here to make a name either, right?” Blue River had analyzed it quite well.

“Yeah. You’re right. But who says I have to use my own account to substitute in.” Ye Xiu said.

“Ah……..” Blue River stared blankly after hearing this. Not using his own account. That was right. That was true substitution. In fact, when guilds looked for players to substitute in, this was their preferred method. It was obviously very common that players used their own accounts when hired for their services. However, it really hadn’t ever been done like this for setting records. To be honest, each of the big guilds had hired an expert for setting records at one point. But they had never encountered a character like Lord Grim, who could easily beat the record made by their elite teams by a few minutes.

“Brother, you’re planning on…….” Blue River asked, trying to probe him.

“That’s why I said that I’m still thinking about it!” Ye Xiu said.

“Then I need to hear your answer as soon as you’re done……” Blue River was helpless. He didn’t know what to say at this moment.

At the same time, Cold Night had also analyzed something similar to what Blue River had said, except he hadn’t made any preface like Blue River had done. This was why he made an extremely generous offer now, which Ye Xiu also replied with “I’ll think about it”.

Apart from this, there was a whole mess of friend requests, which were all from the big guilds. More than half of the guilds that were backed by the 20 pro-teams had come to negotiate with Ye Xiu. Without exception, Ye Xiu replied with a “I’ll think about it”. However, among this, he never saw anyone from Herb Garden.

What now?

Ye Xiu hesitated. He wasn’t refusing them when he said “I’ll think about it.” He really was thinking about it. Things weren’t going as smoothly as he had originally planned. Even though he had eventually suppressed Liu Hao’s annoyance, the damage had already been done. For example, Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion were also being bombarded right now…….. If Liu Hao hadn’t come out and stirred up so much trouble, how would Ye Xiu need to bring so many players to complete his task.

Because they were being bombarded by messages, their dungeoning was somewhat slow. Now that they were Level 28. They were now running the Level 28-30 dungeon: Desolate Land.

Of course, the new dungeon was also in a new map. The map was naturally called Desolate Land. According to Glory’s description, this place was gathering land of homeless drifters, powerful and unyielding, the strong ruled the lands. In the leveling area, the monsters were made up of all sorts of vagabonds. The dungeon Desolate Land was another gathering place for vagabonds and was said to be a gathering of the strongest gangs and hoodlums.

Desolate Land’s record had just been set anew that morning. The current record holder was Blue Brook Guild. Blue Brook Guild’s elite team was undoubtedly a team with Level 30 Purple weapons and their respective class sets. Seeing this record, Ye Xiu felt that it’d quite difficult for his Level 28 team to beat it. In his current team, Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon were familiar with the dungeon, but their skill was a bit lacking; Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion had skill, but they were completely new to the dungeon and extremely unfamiliar with it.

After two hours, they painfully completed three runs. The dungeon Desolate Land had an entry limit of three per day. The party gathered outside of the dungeon, ready to run Boneyard. Although their levels were higher, the dungeon monsters were still elite monsters. Plus, with the extra rewards for clearing the dungeon, their experience gains from it were faster than directly leveling at the Desolate Land map.

At Boneyard, a five player party had also just finished their record-setting runs at Boneyard. In the party was White Night Black Day, Fallen Angel, Cloudy Heavens, Ashen Moon, Weeping Crow. After running it three times, the five players’ expressions were all quite embarrassed. Let alone the fastest record on the leaderboards, their final time wasn’t even close to the third place record.

Although their characters weren’t at Boneyard’s limit, Level 27, there wasn’t too big of a difference between Level 25 and Level 27. With their pro-level skill, making a time with such a large gap compared to the record really did make them somewhat speechless.

The five players were even a bit terrified. They had already tried their hardest, but they had made such a poor time. Even though their characters weren’t optimally equipped, they all had Level 25 Purple weapons. Because God had wanted these accounts, even though they were normal empty accounts, Plantago Seed still helped them and gave each of them a Purple weapon.

“Captain…….” One of the players turned his head and looked at the person behind him, Tiny Herb’s team captain Wang Jiexi.

“You guys played well.” Wang Jiexi said.

The five players looked at one another. They weren’t sure if their team captain was mocking them.

“We’re so far off from the record…….” Gao Yingjie said, ashamed.

“That’s because your strategy wasn’t correct.” Wang Jiexi said.

The five players looked at one another again. They didn’t make any mistakes anywhere, so where did they mess up?

“There was definitely some sort of new strategy that was used to set that record.” Wang Jiexi said.

“Oh? So then we should go study it?” One player said.

“Are you joking? You’re going to waste your precious time on this?” Wang Jiexi said.

“That……”

“Go find Lord Grim.” Wang Jiexi said.

“And then?”

“Kill him once and then go to bed early. This will be one of your main exercises in the future.” Wang Jiexi said.

Chapter 128 – Rookie

After throwing down these orders, Wang Jiexi left first. With him gone, there was nothing to discuss. Among the five players, Gao Yingjie was the youngest, but the other four players weren’t much older. They were all subs in Club Tiny Herb. Of them, three of the players had come out in an official match as subs.

However, the Alliance had its rules. Players and the characters that would be used had to be reported to the Alliance before the season started. Afterwards, the list could not be changed unless there were transfer deals or waivings. Moreover, the Alliance had to approve the sub in. The rules stated that during the match, players and characters were not allowed to be casually switched around.

For example, if Wang Jiexi wasn’t prepared to go on stage next match and have Gao Yingjie sub in for him, then even though no one was using Vaccaria, Gao Yingjie would not be allowed to use it. Gao Yingjie would only be allowed to use the character that was reported to the Alliance before the season started, a different Witch, Kind Tree.

Gao Yingjie never had any experience in an official match. The other player who had never went out on stage either was called Qiao Yifan, who was currently using the Assassin Ashen Moon. These two were very young. However, Gao Yingjie was already the decided sub for Wang Jiexi and the future successor for Vaccaria. As a result, Qiao Yifan could only be considered a fairly talented new player. Even though he had been signed up to be a part of this match, he was just barely hanging on and might not be in the next match. For new players like him, they had no way of controlling their fate. After all, he was still only a youth and nothing more.

There was a large gap between their statuses, but neither of them thought anything of it. They were actually on extremely good terms and loved to hang around each other. Right when Wang Jiexi left, Qiao Yifan was just about to talk to Gao Yingjie about something when he heard someone yell: “Yifan, go fetch some drinks for us.”

“Oh!” Qiao Yifan helplessly replied. The person who had yelled was called Xiao Yun, coincidentally getting the Battle Mage Cloudy Heavens (Yun Xiao) this time. He was the sub who had come out on stage the most. He could even be considered half-main roster half-sub, so he was naturally the senior among the subs.

However, he didn’t dare order around Gao Yingjie, who would be a part of the main roster in the future. Though he did order around Qiao Yifan very impolitely. This type of situation didn’t only occur in Tiny Herb. All of the Club’s rookies were in a similar situation. Fetching them drinks for the main roster and so on were common occurrences, unless they were important targets of care like Gao Yingjie or a super rookie like the previous year’s Sun Xiang.

“What would you like to drink?” Qiao Yifan said that he would go grab drinks, but didn’t forget to ask his good friend.

In the end, the person he was asking hadn’t yet answered, when the three other players all came up very impolitely.

“Get me a bottle of green tea.” This was Xiao Yun.

“I want Cola.”

“I want Cola too.”

These two were Zhou Yebai and Liu Fei. They were respectively given the Ghostblade White Night Black Day and the Sharpshooter Fallen Angel. These two had been in the Club for two years and were prepared to sub in at any time. Although they couldn’t compare to Xiao Yun as of now, they were still in a much better spot than Qiao Yifan.

“It doesn’t matter for me!” Gao Yingjie said softly at the end.

Qiao Yifan ran to fetch the drinks for everyone. The three veteran subs didn’t say a word of thanks and were already discussing amongst themselves.

“Who is this Lord Grim? How did he offend our captain?” Liu Fei asked. Girls were always slightly more gossipy than guys.

“Who knows.” Xiao Yun wasn’t too interested in discussing that issue. He didn’t dare talk about things behind their team captain’s back.

“Yebai, do you know?” Liu Fei asked Zhou Yebai.

“How would I know!” Zhou Yebai said while drinking his Coca Cola and asked for seemingly no reason: “Didn’t Little Jie get these cards?”

Sure enough, Liu Fei immediately turned her head to ask Gao Yingjie: “Little Jie, do you know?”

“I don’t know either, Sister Liu.” Gao Yingjie hastily said.

“I guess there’s no way Yifan would know?” When she asked Qiao Yifan, her tone was very disdainful.

“Ha ha……” Qiao Yifan could only foolishly laugh. How could he be the first person to know about things regarding the Club!

“It doesn’t matter. Let’s hurry up and kill this guy, so we can go to bed early!” Xiao Yun said.

“Exactly.” Zhou Yebai looked at the time.

“Who’s the guild leader over here?” Xiao Yun asked.

“Plantago Seed.” The person who replied was Gao Yingjie. Even though he and Plantago Seed hadn’t introduced each other, Gao Yingjie had still asked who he was going to meet beforehand.

“Oh, he should be in the friends list! I’ll go ask him.” Xiao Yun said.

To these normal players in the new server, Xiao Yun was even more impolite. He directly asked: “Hello? Do you know where Lord Grim is?”

When Plantago Seed saw these five characters go online, he silently paid attention to them. He quickly read the message, but seeing that it was asking for where Lord Grim was, his heart froze and he immediately replied: “I don’t know!”

“Go find out.” Xiao Yun said.

“Oh……” Plantago Seed had been ordered and immediately had a bad impression of Xiao Yun. Plantago Seed was very familiar with everyone in Team Tiny Herb. He obviously knew which member used a Battle Mage if he was from Tiny Herb. An image of Xiao Yun appeared in his mind, which made him in a somewhat bad mood. However, he could only do as he was ordered to do and tell everyone in the guild to pay attention to Lord Grim’s movements.

“I saw Lord Grim and the others heading towards Boneyard.” Someone in the guild immediately replied. The current guild was growing larger and larger. The members were all at different levels, so they were all spread out in different leveling areas. As long as Lord Grim was online, with such a large scouting range, it was quite easy to find him.

‘How many? Where are they headed towards?” Plantago Seed asked.

“Five players. They should be going to Boneyard I think?” The guild member said.

Plantago Seed immediately reported back to Xiao Yun’s Cloudy Heavens.

Xiao Yun looked and then promptly told everyone else: “Lord Grim is bringing a party to Boneyard. Let’s all separate and intercept him. If they enter the dungeon, then we’ll have to wait a long time.”

“Oh.” The other players replied. The Boneyard dungeon could be considered a cave. But with so many players running the dungeon, the lines would be extremely long if there was only one entrance. Similar to how players could enter the Frost Forest dungeon anywhere around the Forest, Boneyard had several entrances around the circumference. When fighting monsters in the area, accidentally dropping in a hole and into the dungeon was a common occurrence.

Xiao Yun asked clearly where Lord Grim was and then the five players separated and headed towards Desolate Land to intercept. Not long after, Qiao Yifan was the first to find the target: “I’ve found them. Lord Grim, five players!!!”

“Coordinates.” Xiao Yun hastily said.

Qiao Yifan sent the coordinates and the four others immediately headed towards it.

“Go intercept him!” Xiao Yun ordered in fear that their efforts would be wasted if Lord Grim went and entered the dungeon. If it did happen, then they’d have to wait awhile for him to come out.

“I…….” Qiao Yifan stared blankly.

“Hurry up!” Xiao Yun urged.

Qiao Yifan didn’t have much confidence. But under Xiao Yun’s urge, he had his Level 25 Ashen Moon rush forward.

The other side had five players. To be able to enter the pro-scene meant that Qiao Yifan was extremely skilled. In normal circumstances, if he was against five random players, then he wouldn’t be scared at all. But the problem was that these five were the ones that set a record that they couldn’t even come close to. Even though God Jiexi had said that it was due to the difference in strategies, no matter how different the strategy was, it would still need a high level of skill to carry out. These players’ skill levels couldn’t be too different from theirs, right?

After Ashen Moon advanced a bit, Qiao Yifan saw who the other four players were. Two of them were characters on the record leaderboards, though he didn’t recognize the other two. At this moment, Qiao Yifan wasn’t able to plan anything. Ashen Moon rushed up and then a sudden Shining Cut headed straight for Lord Grim.

In these leveling areas, players come and go, so no one was very cautious. Shining Cut was an extremely quick skill. It launched quickly and no one except the user would know where it was aimed at. However, this Lord Grim had unexpectedly reacted in an instant, drawing out his sword, and using a Guard to block this Shining Cut.

This one move already made Qiao Yifan lose confidence. He was a new player through and through and hadn’t had any experience in an official match. He was also unlike Gao Yingjie in the fact that the team captain would occasionally come to spar with him personally. In this sort of environment, everything he did was extremely careful. He hoped not to make any mistakes, but didn’t hope for anything more. At this moment, seeing Lord Grim’s reaction, he immediately felt that this was a difficult opponent. After the Shining Cut, he didn’t execute any other attacks and immediately jumped back in an attempt to widen the distance between them.

A sword light flashed. Lord Grim chased with a Sword Draw.

He had already taken back the Vampiric Lightsaber from Huang Shaotian awhile ago and obviously wasn’t an equipment for Ye Xiu to use. It was used as a material to upgrade the Thousand Chance Umbrella. For the current Thousand Chance Umbrella, in addition to the Lance form, the Sword form was also Level 25. It had an Attack Speed of 5, a Weight of 2.3 kg, a Durability of 23, Physical Attack: 320, Magic Attack: 340, equivalent to a level 35 Purple Tachi. This was why recently, when Ye Xiu battled, besides the Lance form, he would also use the Sword Form frequently. The two forms’ damage was quite scary.

This Sword Draw was extremely quick and accurate just as Ashen Moon was coming down from his leap backwards. Right when it seemed like Ashen Moon would be hit, Ashen Moon suddenly leaped again and dodged to the side, narrowly avoiding the sword.

Air Jump!

This was a level 15 Assassin skill, which allowed the user to jump again in midair. To put it simply, Assassins could double jump.

Relying on this, Ashen Moon dodged the originally unavoidable blade. But because of this, he became even more terrified of Lord Grim. Just as he was figuring out how to stall for more time, Steamed Bun Invasion had already grabbed a Brick and rushed forward, yelling: “Who are you! You’re looking to die!”

Qiao Yifan hastily had Ashen Moon dodge to the side, avoiding this Brick. But on his other side, Soft Mist’s battle lance had already arrived like a viper. Qiao Yifan once again had Ashen Moon dodge and was already somewhat panicked.

Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon felt a bit embarrassed always being spectators. With an opening, they also went to attack. The two rushed forward and each used their respective skills.

Qiao Yifan’s hands were rushed and muddled. He already lost his rhythm was now subconsciously trying to dodge attack after attack now. To him, he was no longer paying attention to whether there was a chance to counterattack and had no idea how to escape.

Gao Yingjie, who was sitting next to him, saw that the situation wasn’t looking good for him and was even panicking on his behalf. He hurriedly yelled: “Hang in there. I’m almost there.”

“What? Yifan’s not a match?” Zhou Yebai and Liu Fei both turned their heads to look at Qiao Yifan’s screen.

Chapter 129 – Vanishing Step

Zhou Yebai and Liu Fei fixed their attention onto Qiao Yifan’s screen. In fact, it wasn’t just them. Xiao Yun also wanted to see, but he was too far away. Between him and Qiao Yifan were Zhou Yebai, Liu Fei, and Gao Yingjie. If he didn’t get up and walk over, there was no way for him to see.

Xiao Yun didn’t say a word. Even if he couldn’t see, he could still ask. A part of why he urged Qiao Yifan to rush forward was to test the waters. But if Qiao Yifan could speculate that Lord Grim’s party wouldn’t be an easy opponent, how couldn’t he have considered it.

“How?” Xiao Yun asked, not in the least concerned.

In the end, she heard Zhou Yebai and Liu Fei laugh.

“Too stupid, Yifan.” Liu Fei laughed out loud. She clearly didn’t put the attacks thrown at Qiao Yifan’s Ashen Moon in her eyes. If it was her, she would have easily escaped. But for Qiao Yifan right now, his hands were a complete mess. A feeling of superiority swelled up in her heart.

“Let’s hurry. If Qiao Yifan actually died here, then we’d look like a huge joke.” Zhou Yebai said.

Even though those words weren’t very pleasant to hear, to be fair, it wasn’t too excessive. In the game, no matter how you said it, these were just normal players. For pro-players, they really shouldn’t be losing to these normal players. If they died to them, that’d be even more ridiculous. Even if they couldn’t defeat them, then they should at least be able to escape.

Even for Gao Yingjie, who was close friends with Qiao Yifan, couldn’t deny this. He could only furiously tap his keyboard and hurry over to help his friend.

But the first person to arrive was Xiao Yun’s Battle Mage Cloudy Heavens.

Xiao Yun didn’t impatiently advance. He wasn’t like the other three, who had seen what the situation was from Qiao Yifan’s screen, so he could only observe for a bit before acting. In addition, his character could see a more all-around and concrete view of the situation compared to Qiao Yifan’s first-person perspective.

In front of his eyes, he could easily tell the difference in skill levels between the four players attacking Qiao Yifan’s Ashen Moon.

That Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion’s were noteworthy, while Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon weren’t worth mentioning.

Seven Fields!!!!

This name made Xiao Yun at a loss for awhile.

Could he be from Herb Garden? This thought flashed by Xiao Yun’s mind. Even if he was from Herb Garden, it didn’t matter. Even if they all ganged up and killed him, they definitely wouldn’t be punished.

Xiao Yun’s line of sight fell outside of the battle onto that Lord Grim.

He was their goal and their main target. Since those other four players were chasing down Qiao Yifan’s Ashen Moon, wasn’t this the perfect opportunity to attack?

Xiao Yun’s Cloudy Heavens had already formed Chasers from fighting the nearby monsters. Besides relying on Dragon Tooth to form Neutral Chasers, Level 26 Battle Mages had a new Level 25 Chaser: an Ice Chaser that was created when Double Stab was used.

After an Ice Chaser attacked, the character have their Physical Defense buffed. The Level 1 Ice Chaser increased Physical Defense by 2%. Battle Mages could only wear Leather armor and thus their defenses weren’t particularly outstanding. As a result, this additional Defense wasn’t very useful. In comparison, the effects from an Ice Chaser attack were much more valuable.

When an Ice Chaser hits a target, it applies a brief Stun, similar to Dragon Tooth. Besides this, Ice Chasers did Ice Magic Damage and had a 50% chance to Slow the target for up to 3 seconds. The higher the Ice Chaser level, the higher the chance and the more obvious the effect.

Even though Level 26 Battle Mages only had one level into Ice Chaser, the effect was still obvious if it hit the target. At least, enough to make Steamed Bun Invasion believe that it was some sort of “Laxative”.

At this moment, not only did Cloudy Heavens have the buffs from the Chasers, he also had seven Ice Chasers revolving around him, all done through killing monsters along the way. Seven was the max and each one lasted for 30 seconds.

Seeing the situation, Xiao Yun finalized his plan. He ignored Qiao Yifan’s Ashen Moon and directly headed straight for Lord Grim.

Dragon Tooth!

Dragon Tooth was quick, had a long range, and could stun. It was a skill that Battle Mages loved to use as an initiator. Xiao Yun was using it as one as well. He rushed forward, his lance directed at Lord Grim.

At this moment, Lord Grim was also holding a battle lance. Cloudy Heaven’s Dragon Tooth stabbed forward. Lord Grim sidestepped it and counter-attacked with his own Dragon Tooth.

Cloudy Heavens dodged and then slashed up with his lance: Sky Strike.

Lord Grim avoided it and then slashed up, a Sky Strike too.

Cloudy Heavens escaped again and then leaned forward, stabbing with his lance, attempting to use Circle Swing to grab him.

However, Lord Grim did the same thing as before. He dodged and then returned with his own Circle Swing.

“F*ck!” Xiao Yun was somewhat angry. He felt as if he were being played with. He hated how his account was only Level 26. He didn’t have many skills and felt as if his hands and feet were tied together. His hand speed immediately quickened. In game, Cloudy Heavens leaped back, dodging the Circle Swing while stabbing out with his lance twice, a Double Stab.

In this way, if his attack was avoided and Lord Grim once again copied his movements, then he wouldn’t be any danger. This was because he had jumped backwards, distancing himself. If Lord Grim dodged his Double Stab, then Lord Grim’s Double Stab wouldn’t be of any threat to him.

In the end, Lord Grim still copied him and leapt backwards while using Double Stab. Just as Xiao Yun was laughing at him for his stupidity, a cold light leapt at him. It wasn’t Double Stab, but rather an arc of light.

Sword Draw!

Sword Draw’s attack range wasn’t just the sword’s reach. It also included the range of the sword’s aura, so the attack range was much greater than Double Stab’s.

Double Stab wouldn’t be able to hit him, but Sword Draw could.

“F*CK!” Xiao Yun really did curse out loud this time. This Sword Draw was too sudden. He was still in mid-air! HIs Cloudy Heavens wasn’t an Assassin, so he didn’t have a Double Jump. How could he dodge this?

Needless to say, this “F*CK” immediately grabbed everyone’s attention. Liu Fei, that talkative girl, glanced over and immediately yelled: “Woah! Xiao Yun, you’ve arrived too!”

Even though they had all seen Qiao Yifan’s screen, even Qiao Yifan himself didn’t know that Xiao Yun had arrived. He was being attacked on all sides by four players. His camera was twirling around and around in chaos. How could he have the energy to see what else was going on.

Everyone turned around their heads to look and all saw Cloudy Heavens flying backwards from Sword Draw. Xiao Yun’s face was extremely gloomy.

After a Quick Recover, Cloudy Heavens immediately got up.

Dragon Tooth, Sky Strike, Double Stab, Falling Flower, Circle Swing……

Level 26 Battle Mages only had these skills too, plus a few normal attacks.

Chasers? Cloudy Heavens carried seven of them, but Chasers weren’t something that could be fired as he pleased. The instant an attack hit its target, the Chaser would automatically fire at that target. Cloudy Heavens exchanged blow after blow with Lord Grim, but was never able to hit him. And in the blink of an eye, 30 seconds passed and the seven Chasers cleanly faded away. Xiao Yun’s face turned extremely ugly as if it had produced an Ice Chaser.

This account’s level is too low. If not…… Xiao Yun complained, while madly tapping his keyboard and clicking his mouse.

The irritated Xiao Yun finally exposed an opening and was hit by Lord Grim’s Dragon Tooth.

Xiao Yun cursed to himself. His Cloudy Heavens had entered a Stunned state. Lord Grim launched a Sky Strike and Cloudy Heavens flew high into the air.

Xiao Yun immediately adjusted his camera angle.

Players weren’t NPCs. A lot of NPCs would be tyrannically oppressed in midair and had no way of escaping. But players could still act in air. Appropriate actions, for example, even a normal attack at the correct moment, could let the player escape from a mid-air predicament. But no matter how it was said, after being hit into the air, the player would be at a disadvantage. Escaping from such a predicament wasn’t easy.

But for pro-players, these were all required courses that they had to learn through intense training. No one could ensure that they wouldn’t be knocked up during a PK battle, which was why players had to practice how to get out of a mid-air predicament.

Xiao Yun’s fundamentals weren’t bad. His camera had already turned and stabilized. However, he was unable to find Lord Grim.

Xiao Yun stared blankly.

Since there were ways to escape from mid-air, of course there were ways to keep the target in the air. Players could still move in the air. However, their movements were extremely limited. For example, the amount the camera angle could be shifted was limited. You want to move your camera angle 720 degrees while in midair? Then your body might as well be a spiraling gyroscope. If someone helped you, then maybe you could pull it off.

At this moment, Xiao Yun turned his camera angle again, but Lord Grim was still nowhere to be seen. He now knew that Lord Grim had already entered his dead angle. Lord Grim was next to him, but was at a place invisible to him!

Only someone with lots of experience and accurate decision-making could do this.

In order to respond to this, the other side had to have lots of experience and accurate decision-making as well.

In an instant, Xiao Yun lost all confidence. Where was his dead angle located? He suddenly lost track. He wasn’t able to make a decision, so he could only blindly make an attack towards a random direction and then pray.

The attack hit nothing but air and Xiao Yun’s prayer was useless.

He received an attack soon afterwards. He basically didn’t know what type of skill he was hit with because his opponent was still invisible, still in his dead angle. Xiao Yun spun and spun until he was almost about to vomit. In the end, besides the blue sky, there was only mother earth. And at most, he would catch a glimpse of Lord Grim’s blood-red Vampire Cloak. But every time Xiao Yun attacked in a direction, all he ever hit was air.

Gao Yingjie finally arrived. Right when he was about to rush forward and rescue his good friend, the scene in front of him made him completely dumbstruck.

Cloudy Heavens was rolling around and around in the sky as if he really was like a flying cloud.

Gao Yingjie could clearly see that Xiao Yun was struggling and what he saw more clearly was Lord Grim’s beautiful pathing. He obviously understood what the purpose of this pathing was. In Glory, this type of pathing had a special term for it: Vanishing Step.

You always knew that your opponent was at your side, but you would never be able to see him. This was Vanishing Step’s purpose.

But for experts, even if they couldn’t see your position, they could still rely on experience and decision-making to deduce your position. As long as you escaped from a mid-air situation, Vanishing Step would naturally stop.

This was a competition between their experience and decision-making. And as for Cloudy Heavens, who was being completely suppressed up in the air, there was clearly a large gap in both experience and decision-making between him and Lord Grim.

Gao Yingjie couldn’t help but stealthily glance towards Xiao Yun.

In his eyes, he saw a fuming Xiao Yun, who was slamming his keyboard and mashing his mouse like crazy.

Chapter 130 – The Opponent Is Extremely Strong

“Ah, Little Jie, you’ve arrived too!!” At this moment, his neighboring player, Liu Fei, exclaimed.

“Ah!” Gao Yingjie replied. He hastily turned his camera. He felt that Xiao Yun didn’t want others to know of his embarrassing situation.

But when Xiao Yun heard this, he quickly turned his head to look at everyone. Unfortunately, he happened to meet eye to eye with Gao Yingjie. The two players awkwardly turned their heads back, avoiding each other.

Gao Yingjie moved out in a hurry. His Witch Weeping Cry swiftly flew over, rushing towards Lord Grim. In comparison, although Qiao Yifan’s Ashen Moon was being attacked on all four sides, he was at least hanging on. But Xiao Yun’s Cloudy Heaven, on the other hand, was already completely helpless.

Gao Yingjie’s Weeping Crow quickly hurried over and threw out a Magic Missile.

Lord Grim moved sideways and dodged it. And unexpectedly, he was still using Vanishing Step.

Gao Yingjie was dripping with sweat. Even though he was considered a talented new player, for moves like Vanishing Step, which required a great amount of experience, he wasn’t much better than Xiao Yun in that aspect. Since he had no way of figuring out how Lord Grim was going to move and attack, he could only fly forward to close in on Lord Grim.

Close in and then steal his positioning. That should be able to break his Vanishing Step right? Gao Yingjie thought like this.

Weeping Crow hastily advanced, when suddenly, Lord Grim’s weapon streaked in a 360 degree circle. The ground beneath him flashed with light.

Rising Emblem!!!

Gao Yingjie was greatly alarmed. But as a recognized talent, Gao Yingjie’s reaction speed and mechanics truly were first-class. He immediately rode his broom and flew away. Rising Emblem’s ring of light ascended, nearly brushing his broom.

Cloudy Heavens was still up in the sky, rolling around.

After dodging the Rising Emblem, Weeping Crow quickly circled back for another try.

A gun sound rang out!

Weeping Crow rolled away and was once again delayed.

How terrible!! Gao Yingjie looked on helplessly as Cloudy Heavens was hit twice in midair.

Climb back up, rush forward again.

This time, Lord Grim didn’t use any methods to prevent him from getting close, but Gao Yingjie immediately felt an ominous premonition.

Lord Grim suddenly leapt backwards towards him. The battle lance in his hands stabbed forward still aimed at the mid-air Cloudy Heavens.

He then turned 180 degrees in mid-air, creating a wide arc.

Circle Swing. Cloudy Heavens was carried around on the head of the tip like a sledgehammer, smashing towards Weeping Crow.

Weeping Crow easily dodged it, but Cloudy Heavens, on the other hand, had smashed into the ground and didn’t stand back up.

Crash!!

Xiao Yun smashed his keyboard and stood up.

Everyone else jumped in their seats and subconsciously glanced at him.

Only Gao Yingjie didn’t. It wasn’t just because he knew what had happened, but more importantly, he already had no time to pay attention to him. At this moment, Lord Grim was his opponent.

Xiao Yun was somewhat angry. It wasn’t just towards Lord Grim but also towards Gao Yingjie.

Gao Yingjie had clearly arrived. Why didn’t he go and help him? Xiao Yun furiously glared at Gao Yingjie. But he saw that Gao Yingjie hadn’t seen him and was staring at the screen tapping his keyboard instead.

F*ck!!! Xiao Yun cursed in his heart.

His neighbor, Zhou Yebai, had already seen his corpse from Xiao Yun’s screen. Zhou Yebai was overwhelmed with shock, but didn’t say anything. Even an idiot could tell Xiao Yun was in a bad mood, an extremely bad mood.

However, even if everyone could tell that Xiao Yun wasn’t happy, saying it out loud was a whole different matter.

Liu Fei saw Xiao Yun’s screen and immediately gaped: “Wow! Xiao Yun, how’d you die?”

This time, even Qiao Yifan, who was running for his life, was astonished. He had been running for so long, but he still hung on. Xiao Yun died? How did he die? Qiao Yifan was extremely baffled.

Extremely busy, he still stole a glance at the four others. He saw that Xiao Yun’s face was flushed with anger, but more importantly, he saw his friend extremely focused.

“Bang!!” In this split second of his distraction, Qiao Yifan’s Ashen Moon was immediately hit by Steamed Bun Invasion’s Brick.

“Ha ha ha ha, you can’t run from me!!!” Steamed Bun Invasion laughed as if his one Brick had killed him.

Qiao Yifan’s attention immediately returned back to his Ashen Moon. His health was already low. He wouldn’t be able to hold on for much longer.

Right at this moment, a hole suddenly appeared in the four player’s encirclement. Big enough that Qiao Yifan was able to immediately recognize it among all the confusion. Without hesitating, Qiao Yifan ran straight out.

In this space, Qiao Yifan was finally able to see the entire situation. He immediately saw Gao Yingjie’s Weeping Crow riding on his broom, quickly fluttering by. Just now, he had helped Qiao Yifan escape from the encirclement. Once he did that, he faced towards Lord Grim, who was currently carrying his weapon, running over to kill him.

“Run!!” Qiao Yifan heard Gao Yingjie yell.

“Run?” Zhou Yebai and Liu Fei looked over, astonished.

“My opponent is extremely strong!” Gao Yingjie said.

Zhou Yebai and Liu Fei looked over at Xiao Yun.

Xiao Yun’s face was still as ugly as before. If this wasn’t a low-leveled account; if this was a Battle Mage with all of the skills…… Xiao Yun kept on thinking of this hypothetical situation, but….. Vanishing Step. There was no way Xiao Yun didn’t know of this move name. He also knew he had died by it. Using Vanishing Step to play around with him, currently, only team captain was able to do it when they practiced. As for in the Alliance, even though there were definitely a few Gods at that level, with Xiao Yun’s status, he had yet to fight against such a God one on one.

As for in the team competition, team members coordinated together, so it was very rare that Vanishing Step could be used.

“Then should we still come over?” Zhou Yebai asked. He and Liu Fei were still a bit too far away to coordinate together. They were still heading over there!

“Let’s regroup first before talking!” Gao Yingjie said.

“Okay.” The two replied. In their hearts, they were both extremely frightened. Killing Xiao Yun, making Gao Yingjie not dare to directly face him, just who exactly was their opponent?

The four reported their coordinates and then chose a spot to group up. Gao Yingjie anxiously waiting, ready for battle at any moment. After everyone grouped together, he turned his head and said, stunned: “Huh? They didn’t come and chase us!”

Zhou Yebai and Liu Fei helplessly looked towards him.

Gao Yingjie’s face flushed with embarrassment: “I thought they would chase us!”

“What about now?” Liu Fei said. She was unexpectedly asking Gao Yingjie. Their group of five had been originally led by Xiao Yun, but now that he was dead, she set up a new leader. This girl was clearly a master of speaking whatever was on her mind. She didn’t have any plan.

“Uh…….” Gao Yingjie had just anxiously led them a few moments ago. Now that there was nothing happening. He once again turned shy, unsure of what to do.

“We go back to kill him?” Qiao Yifan was rather brave on the other hand. Unfortunately, he was destined to be ignored.

“What about Xiao Yun?” Zhou Yebai turned his head to ask. He couldn’t help but ask. Cloudy Heavens was still lying on the ground as a corpse.

“I revived.” Xiao Yun said hatefully.

After reviving, the character would appear at a revival point in a city, so it would take some time for him to reach the leveling area.

“How exactly did you die?” Liu Fei asked.

Xiao Yun’;s face darkened. Losing wasn’t anything humiliating. They were all pro-players. Even God Jiexi couldn’t guarantee that they could go undefeated for an entire season. But the problem was that in the game, as pro-players, they were already considered gods by the normal players.

If a god was killed by a mortal, then what honor did the god have?

“Little Jie, you saw it right?” Liu Fei truly was helpless. Seeing that Xiao Yun didn’t want to say it, she went to ask Gao Yingjie.

Gao Yinjie had been mentioned by name, so he had no choice but to reply: “It looked like Vanishing Step.”

“Vanishing Step?” Zhou Yebai and Liu Fei were extremely astonished. They turned their heads to look at that bitter Xiao Yun.

“To be able to kill Xiao Yun with Vanishing Step, could this guy be at captain’s level?” Liu Fei blurted out.

“What do you know! That player was an unspecialized character with a large variety of skills. He has a huge early game advantage.” Xiao Yun had no choice but to try and justify himself. However, he felt his explanation was lacking. What pro-player didn’t know that Vanishing Step had nothing to do with what skills he had. Vanishing Step was purely based on a player’s experience and decision-making as well as a few accurate movements.

“Could this Lord Grim be captain?” Liu Fei said.

“Bullsh*t.” Zhou Yebai said.

Qiao Yifan silently sat there. In the team, he was always the listener. Besides privately chatting with Gao Yingjie, there was almost never any other chance for him to speak. Right now, he was tapping his keyboard as if none of this was related to him.

“Captain told us to kill this player once!” Zhou Yebai reminded everyone to not forget everyone’s assignment.

“Could it be that captain knew of this guy’s strength and wanted to test us?” Liu Fei said.

Everyone was speechless. No matter how it was said, the reason wasn’t important. What was important was that the captain had given them a task. Right now, Lord Grim wasn’t dead and had actually killed their leader Xiao Yun instead in an extremely infuriating manner too.

“Now we don’t even know where they are.” Zhou Yebai said.

“Go ask Herb Garden’s players!” Liu Fei asked Xiao Yun.

At this moment, Xiao Yun didn’t want to talk to anyone. All he wanted to do was find a sandbag and punch it. Liu Fei, this f*cking girl, had so many questions. Maybe putting her into a sandbag and then beating it up would be more satisfying. Xiao Yun thought.

“Uh oh! It looks like they’ve caught up!!” Qiao Yifan suddenly yelled. Only he wasn’t participating in the discussion, but looking around in-game.

The other three immediately turned their cameras. Sure enough, they saw Lord Grim’s group of five.

“Hm? Those guys look like the ones from before.” On Ye Xiu’s side, a few of them recognized Ashen Moon and Weeping Crow. They still hadn’t had the chance to meet White Day Black Night and Fallen Angel yet.

“There are another two. They’re together, right?” Seven Fields said.

“What are these guys trying to do?” Tang Rou asked. Yesterday, they had been attacked for no reason. And in the end, another similar situation happened again.

Yesterday, the player had run off and today, they still weren’t able to catch one. Seeing that their four’s encirclement wasn’t able to kill off even one, while Ye Xiu had killed one, made Tang Rou feel even worse.

“Everyone, be careful. These guys aren’t so easy.” Ye Xiu said.

“How are they not easy?” Steamed Bun Invasion.

“If you go fight with them, it’ll definitely be more satisfying than fighting in the Arena.” Ye Xiu said.

“Then what are we waiting for!!” Steamed Bun Invasion held sand in his left hand and a Brick in his right, already ready to go up.

Chapter 131 – Cover Strategy

Boneyard could be considered fairly spacious and empty. Looking at the map: gravestones, coffins, and withered trees were the three most prominent scenery.

As pro-players, Tiny Herb’s four players weren’t scared. Seeing that their opponents had chased them, they immediately began seizing the strategic high grounds. Right now, the four were together. But if they still ran away, then it’d be quite difficult to explain.

The four characters each held their own positions. From an overall perspective, their coordination wasn’t bad.

Ye Xiu saw this and immediately blocked Steamed Bun Invasion from advancing: “Don’t rush.”

“My Brick has already been waiting impatiently for too long.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“This is a real team battle.” Ye Xiu said, “Have you watched any of the Pro Alliance’s matches?”

Steamed Bun Invasion obviously said that he hadn’t. Seven Fields said he did. Sleeping Moon said obviously. Tang Rou didn’t say anything. She had watched a total of one, so she didn’t know if that counted as having watched them or not.

“Remember their positions well. We’ll attack them one by one.” Ye Xiu said.

“Brother expert, you should set it up!” Seven Fields made a fist.

“Cross Formation. Steamed Bun Invasion at the front. Seven Fields on the left. Little Moon Moon in the middle. Tang Rou at the back. Myself at the right. Everyone follow me while staying in formation. Don’t break order.” Ye Xiu said.

Sleeping Moon heard “Little Moon Moon”! He didn’t want to cooperate, but he was at the middle. The others all depended on him as the center. The four instantly moved to their front, back, left, right position and he had no choice but to cooperate.

Lord Grim moved and the four immediately followed.

Liu Fei’s Fallen Angel was currently hiding behind a coffin. With regards to Gunners, those types of long-ranged classes, using a cover when fighting with an opponent was a common strategy. But using a shield had its advantages and disadvantages. When they hid, the cover blocked not only the enemy’s field of view, but also their own. So they had no way of knowing the entire situation.

However, in a team, this flaw was covered. Team members could communicate with each other to understand the parts they couldn’t see.

White Night Black Day and Ashen Moon weren’t considered long-ranged classes, but they still found a place to hide. With their overlapping views, they could understand the field clearly. In the end, pro-players were still pro-players. This type of defense for attack strategy was quite simple for them.

“The other side is in a Cross Formation. The Brawler at the front, Striker on the left, Blade Master in the middle, Battle Mage in the back, Lord Grim on the right.” White Night Black Day informed everyone of their opponent’s positioning.

“They’re advancing towards Yifan.” Gao Yingjie said.

“Ah……” Qiao Yifan tensed up.

‘Fei Fei get their attention!” Zhou Yebai said. At this moment, Xiao Yun wasn’t there yet, so he acted as the temporarily leader for now.

“Okay!” Liu Fei answered. She suddenly moved. Fallen Angel rolled out from a coffin, crouched, c*cked her gun, and fired.

“Peng!” A gun sound rang out and blood blossomed out from Fallen Angel’s forehead.

Liu Fei was extremely astonished. She didn’t think that she would be the first one to be hit by a shot. On the opponent’s side, smoke slowly drifted out from the tip of Lord Grim’s umbrella-like thing.

Bullets affected the character’s positioning. Hand cannons had the largest push back and had the highest attack. Next was the rifle and last was the handgun.

The Thousand Chance Umbrella’s bullets belonged to the Rifle type. Its firing rate wasn’t as fast as the revolver or handgun, but it had a higher impact.

Fallen Angel staggered back after being hit by the bullet. Liu Fei’s intended surprise attack flew off.

But as a pro-player, she obviously possessed the ability to adapt. Liu Fei controlled Fallen Angel to run back to position, while continuing to fire back.

“Peng!” A second shot rang out and more blood blossomed from Fallen Angel’s body. Her body was hit askew and her counterfire missed again.

Liu Fei was even more astonished.

Her opponent’s timing was too perfect, just happening to hit the instant she fired.

If she had been hit slightly earlier, then Liu Fei would have had time to adjust her shot, so it wouldn’t go crooked. If she had been hit slightly later, then obviously, Falling Angel’s bullet would have already flew out and both of them would be hit.

In the end, her opponent’s bullet had hit her twice in the instant her Fallen Angel had fired, making Liu Fei unable to adjust in time.

As a Gunner, Liu Fei knew how difficult it was to pull off such precise timing. She had always thought that that type of legend that could only be done in theory, yet she had just been hit twice like that just now.

The opponent’s Cross Formation had already adjusted towards a new target. They were now rushing towards her. No matter what had happened, on a whole, she had grabbed the enemy’s attention.

Liu Fei didn’t dare remain out in the open. She hastily ran towards another hiding place.

“Peng Peng!”

Two shots in a row hit the tombstone she was hiding behind, stone broke off swirling in the air. Afterwards, she heard a muffled sound as if something had smashed into the tombstone. It didn’t seem like a bullet. Liu Fei was very curious, but she didn’t dare expose her head.

“No, no. The angle wasn’t good. It was a bit under.” Ye Xiu was still leisurely instructing Steamed Bun Invasion, telling him that the angle the Brick he had just thrown was off.

“It looks like the distance between us is a bit too far?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked.

“You can jump up to make the Brick fly farther!” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh right!” Steamed Bun Invasion exclaimed.

“Crash!” Another thing directly hit the tombstone. That sound resounded in her ears and she heard it too vividly. Liu Fei jumped up in fright.

“What was that?” Liu Fei asked her teammates.

“Brick……” The people who had saw couldn’t help but answer.

“Brick?”

“He’s practicing what angle he needed to throw the Brick and one just happened to smash into the tombstone you were hiding behind.” Zhou Yebai said.

“Prac……practice?” Liu Fei was speechless. What exactly were they doing?

“Crash!” Another Brick came over, making the tombstone tremble as if it were going to break.

One Brick after the other. They weren’t too frequent. After all, Brick wasn’t a normal attack, but a skill with a cooldown. She obviously knew what the cooldown was for Brick. She had originally calculated the time and braced for the impact. But the fourth one didn’t arrive. Liu Fei made Fallen Angel sneak a peek. In the end, just as half her head extended out, “Crash!” A Brick smashed into her forehead and she began seeing stars. She had actually been Dizzied by it.

Soon after, two “Peng Peng” sounds rang out. She had been hit twice by Lord Grim again. Liu Fei wanted to dodge, but had no way of doing so. Fallen Angel was still Dizzy. Half of her head was still exposed to the outside.

“Did it hit? Was I hit?”

Clearly, the five players had closed in, close enough that Liu Fei could hear her opponents’ voices.

“No. She exposed her head, which was why you were able to hit her. If not, then it would have went over.” Ye Xiu said.

“Why did that idiot expose her head?” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“You acted too slowly, so she probably did it because she was anxious!” Ye Xiu said.

“Ha ha ha, she’s fallen in love with my Brick.” Steamed Bun Invasion said delightedly.

“You just watch!!!” Liu Fei was extremely furious. She was even too angry to type it out and directly roared it out.

“Ha ha, we’re coming.” Steamed Bun Invasion unexpectedly answered back. Liu Fei almost collapsed from anger. Her roar obviously wasn’t directed at these five players. It was only because she was too angry to type it out. Even though, she may have been too far away in game for her teammates to hear. Don’t forget that her teammates were all sitting together. Liu Fei’s roar had directly penetrated her teammates’ headphones. The three suddenly shivered. Yet in the end, Steamed Bun Invasion answered back.

“Don’t panic……” Zhou Yebai said in a low voice. Liu Fei’s role was to attract the enemy’s’ attention. Even though she had suffered a bit, her original aim had been reached. The five players were currently headed towards their trap.

“Little Jie, get ready.” Zhou Yebai reminded Gao Yingjie.

“Okay……” Gao Yingjie said.

Qiao Yifan was extremely lonely. He was also a part of the team, but……he wasn’t a part of the strategy. He didn’t know if it was on purpose or not. But in brief, he had been forgotten. Ashen Moon was hiding behind a tombstone, staring at this ice-cold tombstone that represented the dead. Qiao Yifan didn’t know what to do. But he was already used to this sort of feeling.

“Move out!” Zhou Yebai suddenly ordered. His White Night Black Day and Gao Yingjie’s Weeping Crow flashed out from the left and right. Weeping Crow shook his sleeves, preparing to use a Shadow Cloak to Bind the five players. On the side, Zhou Yebai was waiting for Weeping Crow’s Cloak. Afterwards, he would summon a Phantom Ghost and then follow up with a Ghost Slash.

According to Glory’s explanation, Ghostblades set up fields with special effects and summoned Ghosts to assist them. This ability was named Phantom Ghost. Whether it was for an individual or a team, it was extremely useful as a support. White Night Black Day was a Level 26 Ghostblade and could summon the first Ghost Sword Soul. After a Sword Soul appeared, all teammates inside its boundary would have their Strength and Intelligence attributes raised. Of course, this was only limited to inside the boundary. There wouldn’t be any effects outside of the boundary. If the Ghost’s power could be applied whenever, Ghostblades would be unrivalled.

Once the Witch’s Shadow Cloak bound the enemies, he would use this interval to summon a Phantom Ghost and then kill or heavily injure the enemies within the boundary. This was Zhou Yebai’s plan. At this moment, he was waiting for Weeping Crow’s Shadow Cloak to bind the enemies.

Who knew that just as Weeping Crow threw out his skill, a sword light flashed over. No one knew who had acted first. With Gao Yingjie’s reaction speed and skill, he didn’t think that he would lost to anyone when fighting for time. But this time, his opponent’s skill had unexpectedly arrived first. Sword Draw’s sword light arrived, making Gao Yingjie feel extremely astonished. He could only helplessly choose to dodge it. Even if he directly took on the attack, there was no way his Shadow Cloak would hit. Just like this, he and Zhou Yebai’s plans had been easily crushed.

The player who had sent out the attack wasn’t Lord Grim and was impressively Sleeping Moon. Though it was true that this attack had been made on Ye Xiu’s orders.

When Ye Xiu yelled out for him to attack, he hadn’t even seen the target yet. His attack wasn’t any different than sending it out with his eyes closed. In the end, just after his attack was sent out, he saw Weeping Crow jump out.

Let alone Gao Yingjie, even Sleeping Moon, who had sent out the attack, was extremely astonished. In Sleeping Moon’s eyes, his attack hadn’t hit because of himself, but rather because someone had stupidly jumped out towards the attack.

Cover Strategy’s Flaw: Even if they could mutually communicate their field of view, they could only use it to report to each other and reduce the dangers. In regards to their understanding of the situation at a moment’s notice, it was still somewhat lacking.

Chapter 132 – Team Wiped Out

Since Shadow Cloak failed, it wouldn’t be easy for Zhou Yebai to use Phantom Ghost. Phantom Ghost wasn’t an instant cast. It was a summoning skill that had a cast time. As a result, if he just openly began summoning, it would definitely be interrupted.

Even though there was no way for Phantom Ghost to be openly cast, his White Night Black Day was already standing out in the open. Seeing that his plan had failed, he immediately sent out a Ghost Slash.

Phantom Ghosts obviously weren’t the only skills that Ghostblades could use. They also had a few attack skills. Even though Ghost Slash was a low-leveled skill, its direct damage was quite high. However, it had a very long delay, so there were a lot of openings after using it. However, Zhou Yebai had calculated the distance and determined that there was enough time for the delay to finish, which was why he so bravely decided to use this skill.

A lot of Ghostblade skills were innately dark-attributed. Ghost Slash was one of them and fit Boneyard’s atmosphere well. A dark purple sword light came down like lightning with dense killing intent and extraordinary momentum.

Unfortunately, White Night Black Day had come out directly facing the Cross Formation’s right side, Lord Grim.

Ghost Slash arrived and the Thousand Chance Umbrella in Lord Grim’s hands suddenly opened. There was no other transformation. This time, it really was what it was. The umbrella really was an umbrella.

Zhou Yebai stared blankly.

In his eyes, this form, this usage, obviously didn’t make him feel as if it was an umbrella. In his eyes, it was clearly a shield.

Apart from strengthening defense and absorbing damage, more importantly, Shields provided strong resistances to knock-backs, knock-ups, Stuns, Bleed, Dizzy, etc. all those status effects. Of course, the pre-condition was that you had to use the Shield to block the opponent’s attack first.

As a result, from this perspective, besides the stats a Shield provided, the surface area of a Shield was also important to look at. A large surface area usually meant that it had a large volume. A large volume usually meant that it was heavy. Heavy usually meant that it would be a huge burden. A huge burden affected movement speed, attack speed, jump height, etc. This was why weight was an important factor to consider. Shields were extremely heavy equipment. A slightly larger Shield wouldn’t mean that it would only be a tiny bit heavier. If you only sought after the largest Shield possible, then you would be moving extremely slowly like a turtle.

But Lord Grim’s Thousand Chance Umbrella was so large that Zhou Yebai even saw it as a bit shameless.

His White Night Black Day’s Ghost Slash finally hit onto the Thousand Chance Umbrella. Soon afterwards, he unexpectedly found that his Slash had caused Lord Grim to move back a bit.

Ghost Slash had a small Blow Away effect, but it wasn’t very strong. An ordinary Level 25 Shield could completely block this Blow Away effect. But with Lord Grim’s Shield, after being hit by the Slash, even though the Slash didn’t make Lord Grim completely fly away, there was still a slight knock-back. Zhou Yebai saw immediately that even though its surface area was large, it was very light, so its resistance to status effects were extremely lacking.

For this type of light Shield, first, it had poor defense. Second, its durability was too low for a shield. Shields had their Durability used up relatively quick compared to other equipments. Seeing how the Shield in Lord Grim’s hands wasn’t able to completely resist his Glost Slash’s Blow Away effect, Zhou Yebai reckoned that if this Shield was given to an MT like a Knight, it might not even last for a single dungeon run.

Zhou Yebai’s judgement wasn’t wrong at all. The Thousand Chance Umbrella’s Shield Form, like the other forms, had a Weight of 2.3 kg. Its Durability was only 23. For Shields, this was a simply terrible number. However, the Shield’s base stats weren’t bad. The Level 25 Thousand Chance Umbrella Shield Form had a 24% Defense Increase and a 16% Damage Absorption, equivalent to a Level 35 Purple Shield.

The Thousand Chance Umbrella Shield Form had already been upgraded twice by “Strong Spider Silk” and “White Wolf Bristles” and was one of the first to reach Level 25.

Even though the Thousand Chance Umbrella blocked the Ghost Slash, Lord Grim still took some damage. But after eating the attack, the Thousand Chance Umbrella immediately closed. In that instant, it felt like the Umbrella had sucked in the Ghost Slash. The Thousand Chance Umbrella then transformed into the Battle Lance form, which directly stabbed towards White Night Black Day.

No matter how pro Zhou Yebai was, this was the first time he had seen such a change. In the end, he found that there wasn’t enough time for the delay to finish. His character was still in the middle of its animation, when Lord Grim had sent a lance flying forward.

Tang Rou’s Soft Mist had also moved out at this moment. Her character looked just like the initial Cloudy Heavens with seven Ice Chasers revolving around her. However, Xiao Yun’s Cloudy Heavens had been tragically juggled around by Lord Grim for thirty seconds and his Ice Chasers had disappeared one after the other. Right now, Soft Mist followed Lord Grim’s Dragon Tooth right after the Stun wore off with her own Dragon Tooth. An Ice Chaser flew out and the Stunned White Night Black Day had no way of dodging it. The Ice Chaser smashed into him, ice blossoming across his face. His body immediately began emitting a chilly aura, entering a Slowed state.

Zhou Yebai wasn’t even an opponent for Ye Xiu, let alone both Ye Xiu and Tang Rou. Ye Xiu controlled him, while Tang Rou put out damage, making Zhou Yebai’s White Night Black Day’s life drop down like flowing water. Ghostblades weren’t a class with high defense. They wore Cloth Armor and were as defenseless as Mages.

Seven Ice Chasers fluttered towards White Night Black Days like shining pearls. Chasers auto-chased the target. The only way for it to miss was to use an attack to destroy it. Zhou Yebai’s hands went out of control. Of the Seven Chasers, he was only able to hit down two of them. The other five all hit. Luckily, Chasers were classified as Magic Attacks. Cloth Armor may have low Physical Defense, but they had high Magic Defense.

Seven Fields, Sleeping Moon, and Steamed Bun Invasion now rushed forward under Ye Xiu’s commands. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim stepped aside. He used a Circle Swing picking up White Night Black Day and flipping him over. Sleeping Moon immediately jumped to Lord Grim’s original position. Their coordination seemed a little rough, but when White Night Black Day got up, he discovered he was now in the middle of the Cross Formation and was then attacked on all four sides by the four players.

This was all done in the blink of an eye. Gao Yingjie hastily controlled his Weeping Crow to fly over, but Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim stepped out to block him.

Disperse Powder was thrown down. Lord Grim leisurely opened up his umbrella and strolled over. After blocking Disperse Powder, he once again closed the umbrella and stabbed up at the flying Weeping Crow. No matter how fast Gao Yingjie’s reaction speed was, there was no way for him to dodge it. Following after, he used a Circle Swing and flung Weeping Crow into the center of the Cross. Weeping Crow and White Night Black Day were now back to back fighting against the encirclement.

Liu Fei’s Fallen Angel had been hoping for her teammates to come help her. However, she didn’t yet have time to react after the tombstone incident, when Zhou Yebai and Gao Yingjie one after another were thrown into a trap like fish. Liu Fei was aware that the situation wasn’t looking good. She then suddenly saw Lord Grim’s figure flash by. Right when she began to panic, she was hit by a Falling Flower Palm from behind and Fallen Angel was blasted away. Soft Mist lifted her spear, caught her, and then threw her into their encirclement too.

It wasn’t possible to only rely on Tang Rou and the other three to trap three pro-players. But with Ye Xiu’s commands along with Ye Xiu’s own task of personally sending them over, the three pro-players really did want to cry, but no tears came out.

Pro-players? In this moment, the three didn’t feel that they were anymore.

No matter who it was, Zhou Yebai and Liu Fei who had been in official matches, or the extremely talented and future star Gao Yingjie, they had all fallen into the net like little fishes. Punches, Bricks, Slashes, Stabs, Bullets, whatever there was, they got.

The three players were all looking for a chance to rush out. No one paid attention to who was who and they all shouted and yelled at each other. But no matter what they did, their opponents always seemed to be able to figure out what they wanted to do and took the initiative to stops their plans. The three players were completely desperate.

Zhou Yebai’s White Night Black Day had the lowest defense of the three and was also the first to be thrown in. In the end, he was the first to die. Zhou Yebai furiously smashed his keyboard. His gaze suddenly shifted after thinking of something and then roared in rage: “YIFAN, WHERE THE F*CK ARE YOU!!!”

The forgotten Qiao Yifan’s Ashen Moon had actually been foolishly standing to the side the entire time. His teammates had never called for him to come up, so the opponents also ignored him. Seeing that even Gao Yingjie had been easily thrown into the encirclement, Qiao Yifan truly didn’t know what to do. At this moment, he heard Zhou Yebai’s roar, he no longer cared if he had the ability and stupidly rushed forward. Naturally, it turned out to be a tragedy. His skill level was the worst among the four. In front of Ye Xiu, how could he be a match? After a few rounds of combat face to face, Lord Grim threw him into the encirclement too, which could be considered as having answered Zhou Yebai’s question.

Zhou Yebai helplessly fell from his seat. His roar at Qiao Yifan had drained him. There was no way he actually placed his hopes on him. Even more so, when he had yelled, he himself had already died.

At this moment, even Cloudy Heavens, who was heading over to their location, had stopped. Xiao Yun stupidly stared at the screens of his teammates next to him. He silently watched as the opponents killed them off one after another.

Team wiped out……

Even though, they had been killed at different times. It was a fact that each of the five players had died once. The five players sat in front of their screen. Besides Xiao Yun, they were all staring at their corpses, somewhat at a loss.

Lord Grim and the others were still in the surroundings circling about. What were they saying? It was unfortunate that corpses would automatically have their sound cut off. At this moment, they weren’t able to hear any voices or sounds as if they really were dead, just like how they were all feeling right now.

“This……” When Xiao Yun made a mistake, he felt that he could force out an explanation. But now, the four other players had been wiped out by the opponents. There was nothing they could say about this. Even though they were only subs for the Club, which two of them hadn’t even had official match experience yet, in the end, they were still pro-players. The five of them were players that could come out as team representatives at any time in a team competition. But now, in the game, in a team battle, with just one person as their objective, their team had been wiped out and none of their opponents had died. Even in an actual pro-match, they probably wouldn’t have suffered such a disastrous defeat.

“How annoying! As a Level 27 Sharpshooter, I don’t have a lot of skills I can use. I’m so not used to it!!” Liu Fei was the first to speak. What a wise girl. She was the first to find an excuse.

“Yeah, it is a bit annoying……” Zhou Yebai borrowed the excuse with great difficulty.

“That’s what I said before.” A “You finally understand” was written all over Xiao Yun’s face.

Gao Yingjie and Qiao Yifan didn’t say anything. Gao Yingjie was an honest, introverted child and felt too embarrassed to make an excuse. As for Qiao Yifan, would an excuse give them back face? He laughed bitterly. What was face? It’s not like he’d ever had it before!

Chapter 133 – Measuring Skill

That night, Club Tiny Herb’s reserve team slept extremely uneasy.

They didn’t go group together and look for trouble with Lord Grim again. Even though almost everyone used the excuse “low-leveled characters didn’t have every class skill available, so they weren’t used to it”, they all knew in their hearts that that wasn’t an excuse. They were pro-players. Just because they weren’t used to it didn’t mean that their team should get wiped out by in-game players, right? If that were true, then pro-players weren’t worth anything.

The next day, Tiny Herb’s main team and the reserve team met up with each other in the practice rooms and greeted each other.

As pro-players, they had to participate in the daily drills. Even though there was no lack of players who didn’t want to practice, there were no such members in Tiny Herb. With captain Wang Jiexi’s stare, half of the members were even too afraid to speak out.

“Woah, did you not sleep?” When Qiao Yifan saw his good friend Gao Yingjie, he jumped in fright. Gao Yingjie’s dark bags under his eyes like a panda.

“Ah…….” Gao Yingjie muttered and didn’t really answer him.

Qiao Yifan looked again. Xiao Yun, Zhou Yebai, and Liu Fei – which one of their complexions looked good? However, their minds were still somewhat better than Gao Yingjie and the bags under their eyes weren’t as heavy.

And Qiao Yifan? He hadn’t felt any pressure. It wasn’t like anyone had any hopes for him.

At 9 o’clock sharp, Wang Jiexi arrived at the practice room on time. Tiny Herb’s official training was split into the morning and the afternoon. Coaches, those types of people, still weren’t established in Glory. After all, Glory had only been a game for ten years and the pro-scene had only been around for seven years. Everything was still in the testing stages. In the entire scene, first-class Gods like Wang Jiexi were already at the peak, whether it was in theorycrafting or skill. As a result, there weren’t any people with the skill to coach them.

As a result, for Clubs like Tiny Herb, they didn’t have coaching staff and instead had advising staff. Their work was extremely complex: find information on their opponents, analyze the opponent’s tactics, provide a few tactical options, research possible strategies for a map, etc. These were all tasks that the advising staff had to do. But the person with the highest authority was the team captain.

To be frank, the highest value of the advising staff was saving energy for pro-players. They saved a lot of energy for pro-players. In the initial stages of the pro-scene, those tasks all used to be work for the pro-players themselves to do. Now that Clubs had developed, with their financial resources, the money could now be used for these, giving pro-players more time to concentrate on practicing and competing.

Currently, in the Alliance, the only real coaches were Zhang Yiwei and Li Bo. The two were early-generation pro-players and were each in a small Club working as coaches.

Club Mysterious Fantasy were newcomers that had joined the Alliance just last year. The team was full of new players. Their skill levels varied and they lacked experience. The owner of the team also didn’t have a lot of financial resources and didn’t have any ambition. And in the end, he just randomly invited Zhang Yiwei to help the team. Who would have thought that the results would be so good. They ended up 17th place last season, which for a new team that had just entered the Alliance, was already quite good, considering that they didn’t drop to the bottom two places. Some of the teams that entered for the first time spent money scouting people and tried to quickly build a team around pro-players. Those teams all ended as terrible failures. This wasn’t only a one-time thing either. From this perspective, coaches were quite cost-effective. At the very least, they were a small investment that had few risks.

As a result, the new Club Bright Green followed Club Mysterious Fantasy and invited Li Bo. But currently, these two Clubs were both in extremely bad situations. The previous year’s 17th place Mysterious Fantasy directly fell to 20th place. And even though Bright Green was ranked 18th, the team they were above was Excellent Era. The Excellent Era, which in theory, shouldn’t have fallen to 19th place. In addition, they were only ahead of Excellent Era by 3 points and no one believed that they would be able to beat Excellent Era and relegate them.

Coaches were far from being deciding factors in the Glory competitive scene. This was something that everyone agreed upon. Zhang Yiwei and Li Bo were currently suffering in their bad situation and burned-out from trying to prove their worth.

Once Wang Jiexi arrived, the murmurs and whispering immediately stopped and all of the team members began focusing on their practice materials. Wang Jiexi walked around and, in the end, came to where the subs were located. Everyone there immediately sucked in a cold breath. Usually, everyone hoped that God Jiexi would notice them, but now they all hoped that they were invisible. Qiao Yifan was the only exception. He had always been invisible.

“How was last night?” Wang Jiexi, all in all, began speaking. The five players were all looking at each other. None of them dared to answer. In the end, Xiao Yun lifted his head and saw that Wang Jiexi was staring at him. He helplessly replied: “Uh……. we encountered a few difficulties.”

“How?’ Wang Jiexi asked.

“We…..” Xiao Yun began thinking of how to word it. “Team wiped out” was too negative, he couldn’t say that. He was the first to die and the other four had died later. Everyone had died at different times, so it wasn’t technically a team wipe out. As a result, Xiao Yun avoided this phrase, carefully wording his reply, while paying attention to Wang Jiexi’s expression.

“D*mn, how sly!!” Zhou Yebai and Liu Fei heard him talking and then regretted not speaking out first. Right now, Xiao Yun held the power of speech. That guy lightly skimmed over his initial loss and then vividly described the other four’s wipe out. Moreover, he even had a bit of a “If I was there, that wouldn’t have happened” tone. Zhou Yebai and Liu Fei both wanted to speak and argue, but seeing Wang Jiexi’s dark expression, they didn’t dare utter a word.

Xiao Yun finally finished and concluded: “Oh! We’ve decided to practice on these low-leveled accounts and then go look for him again tonight.”

After all of his explaining, besides the excuse “we aren’t used to low-leveled accounts”, there was nothing else he could come up with, so Xiao Yun could only say this.

Wang Jiexi didn’t comment. After a short while of silence, he suddenly said to Gao Yingjie: “What do you think Little Jie?”

Xiao Yun and the others were envious.

Gao Yingjie stood up, somewhat terrified, and then stammered: “I think…… really strong”

“What’s really strong?” Wang Jiexi asked.

“That Lord Grim.” Gao Yingjie said.

“How strong?” Wang Jiexi asked.

Gao Yingjie looked at Xiao Yun. Because Xiao Yun had only briefly skimmed over what had happened to him, he hadn’t mentioned that Lord Grim had played with him to his death using Vanishing Step. Even though Gao Yingjie wasn’t a very considerate person, he at least understood what Xiao Yun wanted. But Vanishing Step really was a good indicator of Lord Grim’s skill level……

In the end, Gao Yingjie thought like this. If he really did take Xiao Yun’s intent into consideration and didn’t tell the truth, then it would mean that he wouldn’t be a simple and honest person. He quickly began saying the truth: “I saw Lord Grim use Vanishing Step to defeat Brother Xiao. When the four of us fought against him later, all of our movements were within their calculations. I think this was all done by Lord Grim, too.”

“Oh? What did you think of him?’ Wang Jiexi asked.

“He is extremely experienced. All of his attacks and skills were used to gain an advantage. And all of his decisions were very accurate.” Gao Yingjie said.

“Have you ever met someone as skilled as him before?” Wang Jiexi said.

Gao Yingjie stared blankly and then said after quite a long while: “Only captain.”

“What about you all?” Wang Jiexi’s gaze looked over the others: “Besides me, have you ever met this type of expert before?”

Xiao Yun and the others looked at each other. Lord Grim was an expert. They all recognized that. But Gao Yingjie had said that besides Wang Jiexi, he had never met someone as skilled as him. Wasn’t that a bit too exaggerated?

“Do you guys not feel that it isn’t possible for such an expert to appear in the new server?” Wang Jiexi said.

The three players were silent, although Liu Fei nodded her head.

“It was because you had that type of preconceived line of thinking that you felt he was so strong. But……. you only recognized that he was strong, that’s all. None of you could measure his skill, right?” Wang Jiexi said.

The three players continued to look at one another.

“Lord Grim isn’t an ordinary player.” Wang Jiexi said.

“Who is he?” Liu Fei asked in doubt.

“There’s an 80% chance that he’s Ye Qiu.”

“What?” Everyone cried out in surprise.

“Is he online right now?” Wang Jiexi asked.

At this moment, everyone was on their main accounts practicing. Hearing the captain ask the question, Xiao Yun immediately logged out. He then swiped his 10th server account card and logged into the game. He searched for Lord Grim’s name and nodded his head: “He’s online.”

“He was online last night and he’s still online now. He’s an all-nighter…… No matter how he plays, he probably won’t be playing during the afternoon. That should be his resting time. He’ll most likely appear again tonight.” After Wang Jiexi calculated, he suddenly waved his hands and hit the table. Every player that heard it looked. Those that were wearing their headphones and didn’t hear it were quickly reminded by the people beside them.

“After dinner, there’ll be one more practice.” Wang Jiexi announced to the entire team.

“What practice?” One of the main roster players asked his team captain.

“Kill a BOSS.” Wang Jiexi said.

“BOSS? What BOSS?” Some people didn’t understand.

‘The greatest BOSS in the history of Glory.” Wang Jiexi said.

Everyone stared foolishly. They still didn’t understand what he meant.

“Fusheng, go grab a few account cards. They need to be tenth server accounts Level 25 and up with their classes matching our team members. The reserve team members won’t need them.” Wang Jiexi instructed. Deng Fusheng was Club Tiny Herb’s vice-captain. His account was called Angelica, a Knight.

“Okay.” Deng Fusheng answered, got up, and then left.

In the practice room, everyone couldn’t help but begin discussing amongst themselves. In the end, Wang Jiexi hit the table again: “RIght now, continue practicing.”

The practice room immediately quieted down. Shortly after, keyboard and mouse sounds rang out, there was no other noise. Wang Jiexi was still at the reserve team’s area. He asked: “Do you have any recordings of yesterday?”

Everyone stared blankly. Liu Fei blurted out: “Captain, you never told us to record it……”

Zhou Yebai immediately glared at her. This girl really didn’t know how to talk. She actually pushed the blame onto the team captain.

In the far corners of the room, Qiao Yifan weakly raised his hands: “I have recordings.”

“Oh? Let me see them.” Wang Jiexi quickly walked over to Qiao Yifan’s computer. Qiao Yifan hastily gave him his seat.

Chapter 134 – Tour Group

The recording was naturally in the recording character’s perspective. Everything was automatic. The camera could be zoomed in and out, but it wasn’t possible to rotate it. Qiao Yifan’s recording started from when his Ashen Moon rushed forward to Lord Grim blocking him to being surrounded and then attacked. These sections were naturally a mess. Apart from seeing his hardships and difficulties, nothing else could really be seen. On the side, Xiao Yun let out a sigh of relief. His death from Vanishing Step hadn’t been recorded.

Who knew that Wang Jiexi’s eyes and hands were so precise. He repeatedly clicked on the screen to pause the recording. He wasn’t looking at Ashen Moon being attacked on all sides, but rather at Lord Grim, where Cloudy Heavens was being hit in the air.

Once, twice, thrice……

Whole body, half body, a third of the body.

In the end, Xiao Yun still lowered his head in embarrassment. He hadn’t been recorded, but he could still be seen in this way.

Wang Jiexi didn’t say anything. This section of the recording had ended when Ashen Moon escaped from the encirclement along with Gao Yingjie’s Weeping Crow. In the second section, the scene began somewhat choppy. Qiao Yifan was clearly having Ashen Moon hide and then occasionally have him take a peek outside. Once the fighting started, the forgotten Qiao Yifan had a good view of the entire scene up until Zhou Yebai’s White Night Black Day was killed. Only after his roar did Ashen Moon move up and begin fighting randomly.

Everyone nervously stood behind Wang Jiexi, watching the recording. They all had their heads down waiting for the scolding! But Wang Jiexi didn’t say anything. He instead got up, patted Qiao Yifan, and then left.

Xiao Yun and the others all hesitated. They didn’t know what to do and in the end, returned to their computers to continue practicing. This morning went by as if their bodies and souls were separated.

That afternoon, the vice-captain Deng Fusheng came back with account cards. Most of them were received from Herb Garden with the classes matching the main roster’s classes.

Club Tiny Herb, including Wang Jiexi, had a total of six players in the main roster with five players in the reserve team, for a total of eleven players. In the current league, this 6+5 set-up was the most common arrangement.

Unless there was a match that day, the night time was free for the players, though there was no lack of hard working players that would continue to practice on their own. However, today, since the team captain had announced an activity for them, Tiny Herb’s player gathered at the practice room. After swiping their account cards, they all entered the tenth server together. Everyone’s expressions were somewhat odd. For their team to gather in the game, they had done it before in the Heavenly Domain, but never in a normal server.

“Our target, the player Lord Grim. Everyone, don’t be careless. It’s very likely that this player is the retired Ye Qiu.” Wang Jiexi announced the purpose of their added practice.

Once everyone heard this, they all became interested. They began discussing amongst each other. There were some in-game that had searched for his ID and then immediately reported to Wang Jiexi: “Captain, he’s not online!”

“He’ll definitely come. Everyone, first get familiar with your character. They’re all low-leveled characters that haven’t yet reached Level 30, so you guys aren’t used to them, right?” Wang Jiexi said.

Xiao Yun and the others were flushed in embarrassment. Was captain mocking them? Was he? Or was he not? It was impossible to figure out what God Jiexi was thinking.

At around 8 o’clock, Lord Grim finally came online. The team members immediately informed Wang JIexi. They then asked Herb Garden for Lord Grim’s whereabouts.

Plantago Seed was also hesitant. After yesterday, Tiny Herb’s vice-captain had personally come for accounts cards today. After counting all the cards he had given, he found that they added up to Tiny Herb’s entire team. Was Team Tiny Herb going to tour around in the tenth server? Plantago Seed held his breath, alarmed. But there was no one to speak to. Because these account cards were only used for special cases, they were quite secretive, and definitely couldn’t be taken out and talked about casually.

Tonight, he saw all of the characters come online one by one. Plantago Seed didn’t dare greet them and could only pace about, hoping that he would accidentally bump into Tiny Herb’s tour group. Unfortunately, Tiny Herb’s players were currently wandering around on their own and weren’t grouped together.

Only until 8 o’clock, when Lord Grim went online, did some immediately ask him for Lord Grim’s location.

“Lord Grim again?” Plantago Seed stared blankly. Who exactly was this Lord Grim? The entire Tiny Herb team was going to run over just to see him? Is he an alien? Plantago Seed thought while asking the guild to pay attention to Lord Grim.

After replying to them, he ran over to where Lord Grim was located too.

Desolate Land. This was where Herb Garden’s players had seen Lord Grim.

If it was just for leveling, then Ye Xiu would have definitely went to a higher leveled area to level. However, he still had a few Level 28 quests, which had to be completed in Desolate Land.

Mission description? Background story? These had all stayed the same for ten years. Let alone Ye Xiu, even Plantago Seed wouldn’t read these. For experienced players, quests were only done for the rewards. And since some quests were long and stupid. They would only do these quests if they rewarded attribute points or skill books, those types of necessary items. Players would then impatiently do the prerequisite quests for those types of quests. Ye Xiu was currently at Desolate Land to do these prerequisite quests.

Ye Xiu had used an online guide as a reference. He used the simplest route, where several quests could be done at once. Killing monsters, looking for people, looking for items, delivering items to people, etc. would all be turned in at once. In this way, the quests would be completed quickly.

“Lord Grim is at Desolate Land. He’s alone.” After asking for the circumstances, Tiny Herb’s team members reported the info to Wang Jiexi.

“To Desolate Land.” Wang Jiexi said.

The entire team of eleven flooded in towards Desolate Land. Vice-captain Deng Fusheng, who was sitting beside Wang Jiexi, was rushing over, while saying: “Even if he really is Ye Xiu, if we all go at once, won’t that be a little excessive?

Wang Jiexi turned his head and looked him in the eye, calmly saying: “Have the main force go duel him.”

“Take turns?” Deng Fusheng said.

“Group competition. We’re eleven, he’s one.” Wang Jiexi said.

Deng Fusheng started sweating. Was there a difference?

They quickly reached Desolate Land. Lord Grim was doing quests, so he obviously wasn’t hiding and was easily found. Plantago Seed had also arrived, but he didn’t dare go over and say hello to them. He stealthily found a place to hide and watched from there. Seeing these eleven characters together, he knew that this was the real Team Tiny Herb. An urge swelled up in his heart. He wasn’t sure whether he should record it or not.

“Main roster go challenge him. Who’s going up first?” Wang Jiexi asked in the practice room.

After a moment of silence, someone said: “I’ll go!”

“Okay.” Wang Jiexi answered.

This player was called Liang Fang, a Berserker. His playing was simple and rough, a very wild player. At this moment, he was using the Level 27 Berserker Blood Frenzy with a Level 25 Purple weapon Breaking Water Greatsword: Physical Attack 310, Magic Attack 210, Strength +10, Collapsing Mountain Skill Level +1. Besides this, he wore a few normal Blue or Green equipment from random dungeons and quests. It was already quite impressive that Plantago Seed was able to provide a Purple weapon for everyone. Providing good equipment for everyone was too much for him to handle.

Liang Fang’s Blood Frenzy raised his sword and began heading over. The other ten dispersed to let him go through. Ye Xiu was still killing monsters, not paying attention. Xiao Yun and the others were lonely. With such a large group, how could he not have seen them. They had fought with him the other day, yet today, they weren’t able to draw in any attention from him. This only meant that the other side hadn’t put them in his eyes.

“Hey!” After Blood Frenzy walked over, Liao Fang roared.

Lord Grim ignored him and continued to kill monsters.

Everyone felt annoyed. Liao Fang had such a loud voice. They had all heard it. How could the closer Lord Grim not have heard it? If he didn’t respond, then that meant he was ignoring him.

“Hey!!” Liao Fang yelled again. He wanted to fight him fairly and didn’t want to attack him while he was fighting monsters.

Still ignored.

Liao Fang’s Blood Frenzy coiled around over to Lord Grim’s front so that he could be seen. “I’ll wait until you’re done killing monsters.” Liao Fang said and then quietly waited for him.

Lord Grim killed the monsters he had gathered carelessly like he always did. Liao Fang waited until he saw that he was done. Just as he was about to attack, he saw that…… Lord Grim stopped moving.

Correct. Stopped moving. Not a single movement. The scene was completely still.

“Captain?” Liao Fang looked for help somewhat gloomy.

“Hit him once and see what happens.” Wang Jiexi said.

“Okay!” Liao Fang answered and then directly slashed at him. Lord Grim still didn’t move. He didn’t move the entire time. Liao Fang then suddenly heard what seemed like a girl crying out in fear, distracting Liao Fang. Lord Grim finally moved.

Just as his slash was about to hit him, Lord Grim suddenly crouched and the sword missed his head by a bit. He then rolled on the ground just barely dodging the slash..

“What’s going on? Who is this?” In Happy Internet Cafe, Chen Guo cried out in alarm.

Ye Xiu hadn’t reacted to the eleven people moving closer because he really hadn’t seen them; he hadn’t responded to Liao Fang’s “Hello” because he really hadn’t heard it. He wasn’t wearing headphones. How could he have heard it? He was just casually killing off monsters, but more importantly, he was talking with Chen Guo. After killing off a few monsters, he had stopped to concentrate on talking with boss Chen Guo. His boss was explaining to him Internet Cafe work, serious work.

Chen Guo had been looking at his screen. When she saw Liao Fang suddenly attack, she cried out in alarm. Ye Xiu turned his head and looked. He then immediately turned around and moved his character, unexpectedly dodging the blade in that short instant.

“I don’t know…….” Ye Xiu said, while looking around. He saw Cloudy Heavens and the other’s ID and then immediately said “Oh.”

“Who?” Chen Guo asked.

Ye Xiu shook his head. He wasn’t too sure. But after seeing everyone’s ID and seeing the classes of all eleven players, he was suddenly startled.

Team Tiny Herb?!

Even though Ye Xiu wasn’t a Tiny Herb fan like Plantago Seed, he was old rivals with Tiny Herb, so he was actually even more familiar with Team Tiny herb’s classes than Plantago Seed. With just a glance, he had already determined this, making Ye Xiu extremely surprised.

At yesterday’s fight with that group of players, Ye Xiu had already figured that they weren’t ordinary. They were pro-level, but he hadn’t thought that they were from Tiny Herb. He had actually been suspecting that it was Liu Hao’s doing. He thought that because that guy had failed to beat him in dungeon records, he decided to just directly go and kill him. But these eleven players’ classes all clearly matched with Team Tiny Herb’s classes.

Ye Xiu immediately thought of that day’s intense fight with Plantago Seed. So it really was Wang Jiexi controlling him?

Ye Xiu thought. He then looked at the other Witch besides Weeping Crow among the eleven characters: Fiery Blaze.

Behind Fiery Blaze’s screen, Wang Jiexi calmly said: “Liao Fang, go up!”

Chapter 135 – What Unspecialized Means

“Okay!” Liang Fang replied. This time he didn’t test him and seriously attacked. He tapped his keyboard and his character Blood Frenzy stamped his feet and shook his arm. A blood-red aura surrounded his body, the Level 25 Berserker Skill “Berserk”.

The Berserk status lasted 20 seconds. In those 20 seconds, the character’s strength, attack speed, movement speed, and abnormal status resistance increased, while the character’s intelligence, physical defense, and magic defense fell greatly. Every level required 20 skill points and its max level was 10. It was an essential buff for Berserkers.

Liang Fang just began and he was already in a Berserk state. It really did fit with his personality. He liked to finish things as quick as possible. Endurance battles were battles that Liang Fang hated the most.

After recognizing that the opponents were Team Tiny Herb, he instantly guessed what the other side’s purpose was and helplessly shook his head.

“Boss, can we talk later?” Ye Xiu said to Chen Guo.

“Okay, okay. Hurry up!” Chen Guo was even more worried than Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu’s left hand tapped the keyboard, while his right hand adjusted his earphones. This sort of high-level battle required the assistance of sound. Glory was in a first-person perspective. Movements from behind were mainly determined through sound. Experienced pro-players could determine how far away the opponent was behind them through how loud or soft the opponent’s footsteps were. The frequency of the footsteps could also tell them how quick the opponent was moving.

Ye Xiu put on his headphones and immediately heard Blood Frenzy heavy steps. His character turned and he saw Bloody Frenzy with his two bloodshot eyes slashing towards him.

Level 5 Berserker Skill: Heavy Hit, which fully utilized the weapon’s weight. The damage and weight of the weapon were directly correlated. Blood Frenzy’s Breaking Water Greatsword was around 5 kg, more than twice as heavy as Lord Grim’s Thousand Chance Umbrella. This Heavy Hit’s aura was extremely frightening. Ye Xiu didn’t take it head on and leaped back to avoid it.

Heavy Hit smashed into the ground with a loud bang. A small crater astonishingly appeared right where Lord Grim had just been. Ye Xiu’s mouse swept and Lord Grim stabbed forth with a Dragon Tooth. However, Liao Fang didn’t have Blood Frenzy dodge. Instead, Blood Frenzy lifted his sword and used Back Slash, intending to fight with Lord Grim head on.

The battle lance arrived first, hitting Blood Frenzy square in his chest. However, there was no Stun. Under the Berserk status, the user would have increased resistances to status effects. Dragon Tooth’s Stun effect wasn’t very high originally. With the increased resistances, he naturally wasn’t stunned.

Along with the sword itself, the greatsword brought along chunks of earth, which flew towards Lord Grim. However, Lord Grim had recovered and leapt backwards, dodging this attack.

Liao Fang stared blankly. He immediately knew that the attack speed of the battle lance in Lord Grim’s hands didn’t have the slowest attack speed of 1 like he had presumed. Because of this disadvantage in attack speeds, fighting Lord Grim head on wouldn’t work.

Pro-level battles were like this. Any random detail could give them lots of information.

Even though Liang Fang’s Blood Frenzy was in a Berserk state. It was only a Level 2 Berserk. Even when Berserk was maxed, it would only increase attack speed by 1, which would still be far from the Thousand Chance Umbrella’s attack speed of 5.

Even though being slower didn’t guarantee a loss, Liang Fang was currently fighting against a top-tier God. Along with his battle lance, which had an attack speed of 5, that was simply too difficult. Ye Xiu fully utilized his advantage though and easily suppressed Liang Fang’s Blood Frenzy. After 20 seconds, Blood Frenzy’s Berserk status ended and he clearly hadn’t succeeded in his original intent of a quick battle.

While fighting against Blood Frenzy, Ye Xiu watched the others and discovered that the other ten players didn’t have any intent on acting, even when he had Lord Grim deliberately enter their attack range.

Ye Xiu smiled. His hand speed suddenly exploded out. Lord Grim’s Thousand Chance Umbrella immediately changed three times, completing three different class’s skills. Blood Frenzy was blasted out. However, as a pro-player, he naturally didn’t have any trouble Quick Recovering. Blood Frenzy rolled and just as he was about to stand up. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had already used a Shadow Clone Technique to shift to his position. The distance he would fly had clearly been calculated by Lord Grim.

Unable to get up in time, Blood Frenzy was torn up into a bloody mess and died shortly after. Liang Fang was staring blankly at his screen. From beginning to end, he hadn’t found any chance of winning. Suppressed, completely suppressed. Every plan, every movement had been calculated by his opponent. The opponent’s movements in the beginning weren’t too quick, but even so, he had been completely suppressed so easily. Once the opponent’s hand speed burst forth, his end had quickly come.

In game, everything was silent.

Tiny Herb’s practice room was also completely silent.

“Xiaobie, your turn.” Wang Jiexi spoke and chose a player.

“Okay.” He answered.

Liu Xiaobie, a very strange-sounding name, was widely known for his hand speed.

Even for pro-players, there were differences in hand speed. Liu Xiaobie could be ranked as having the fastest absolute hand speed in Tiny Herb. However, in terms of effective hand speed, he lost to captain Wang Jiexi by a level. Pro-players clearly knew that absolute hand speed was just for show, while effective hand speed was the truly valuable in real combat. Liu Xiaobie still had a ways to go there. His hand speed wasn’t being completely utilized yet.

Liu Xiaobie was a Blade Master. Once he heard captain’s orders, he immediately had his character move out.

Slash Slash Draw, Level 27 Blade Master, Lightsaber Mastery, Level 25 Purple Weapon Flickering Light Sword. Physical Attack: 233, Magic Attack: 253. Strength + 11. Attacks had a 2% chance to Dizzy.

“Wait a minute.” Ye Xiu suddenly said. Everyone was startled.

“Are you guys planning on doing a Group Competition?” Ye Xiu said.

“Yeah.” Wang Jiexi unexpectedly answered back. Lord Grim was now standing face to face with his Fiery Blaze. Liang Fang’s Blood Frenzy had been killed by Lord Grim under his watch.

“Too annoying.” Ye Xiu said.

“Then what do you suggest?” Wang Jiexi asked.

“Let’s just do a team competition!” Ye Xiu said.

Everyone immediately went into an uproar. This guy actually wanted to do a team competition with the ten of them. The problem was, he was only a single person. And the ten players over here weren’t any ordinary ten players. They were Team Tiny Herb, last year’s Champions. This year, they were also the favorites for being Champions and they hoped to be the second team to be consecutive Champions like Excellent Era. To be looked down upon like this, everyone was immediately infuriated on the spot. Liu Xiaobie already began shouting: “Captain, let me destroy him!!!”

“What happened?’ Liang Fang, who had just revived, was still on the way there, so he didn’t know what was happening.

“That guy actually said he wanted to fight against our entire team by himself. F*ck!” A teammate next to him said.

Liang Fang was startled. He wanted to say something, but he held back.

He had lost, extremely miserably and tragically and was thoroughly convinced by his loss that his opponent’s experience, knowledge, and mechanical skill were all above his own by a level. Plus with an unspecialized character’s advantage…….. In all honesty, Liang Fang had never seen an unspecialized character before. Unspecialized characters had already become legends when he had first started playing Glory. He had only heard a few old teammates talk about how strong and what unspecialized characters were. Today, he had finally experienced their might personally, which was clearly even more abnormal than what the old teammates had said. Unspecialized character’s attacks were impossible to predict. Although they were only low-leveled skills, it included skills from all 24 classes. How could anyone figure out which one of those skills he was going to use?

This type of advantage would still exist at high levels. Unspecialized characters only lacked the explosive power of high-level skills.

Right now, Liang Fang really wanted to say that no one was his opponent if they dueled. Even if captain had personally come up, Liang Fang still wasn’t confident. He was a pro-player with his own clear judgement. He wasn’t like those loyal fans who exaggerated their idol’s strength.

But to say that no one was his opponent would arouse Lord Grim’s fighting spirits. Even if this player was extremely skilled, to actually want to solo their entire team, even Liang Fang, who knew how terrifying he was, couldn’t help but feel that he was being a bit too ridiculous.

“Captain!! I’m going up!” Liu Xiaobie yelled, sucked in a deep breath, and then moved!

His Blade Master Slash Slash Draw used a Triple Slash to instantly close in on Lord Grim and used an Upward Slash.

“Dong”. Lord Grim had unexpectedly drawn his sword and then used Guard to block it.

Sword Draw!!

This thought immediately flashed across Liu Xiaobie’s mind. At this moment, Blade Masters would definitely use Sword Draw, this fairly long-ranged attack, to chase him down.

He had to be quick!

Liu Xiaobie was a player with high hand speed. He of course loved to go all-in. Fight with hand speed. This thought flashed through his mind. His fingers also quickly moved. Slash Slash Draw sheathed his sword and then pulled it out! Sword Draw’s sword light instantly flashed……

“Ta ta ta ta ta……”

A string of crisp machine gun sounds rang out. Slash Slash Draw’s Sword Draw was instantly dissipated and his entire body poured out blood. If this wasn’t a game, he’d have become a corpse bleeding from bullet holes long ago.

Launcher Skill: Gatling Gun.

At this moment, Liu Xiaobie finally understood what an unspecialized character was and what others meant by it having attacks impossible to predict.

He originally wanted to compete in hand speed and see whose Sword Draw was faster! However, his opponent didn’t use Sword Slash and instead moved backwards to use Gatling Gun.

No matter how far Sword Draw reached, how could it reach farther than a gun?

The chain of bullets hit Liu Xiaobie. Just as Gatling Gun finished, the opponent’s Sword Draw suddenly came out. Liu Xiaobie deserved to be called a player with high hand speed. In this short instant, he completed a Guard. Slash Slash Draw lifted his sword upright. “Dong” The Sword Draw was blocked. Just as he was being hit back by the blow, he heard three consecutive sounds. The opponent’s sword had turned into a gun. Launcher Skill: Anti-Tank Missile.

Liu Xiaobie wanted to hide, but in the end he was still hit. The three Anti-Tank Missiles weren’t in a straight line. The opponent used Tri-Shot and the three Anti-Tank Missiles were pulled into a triangle formation, enshrouding an area. No matter how Slash Slash Draw moved, he would be hit by one.

Following after were a string of low-leveled skills, no signs, impossible to predict. Liu Xiaobie and Liang Fang were the same. They had only heard of the era when unspecialized characters reigned free. And this time, they had personally experienced it for themselves.

Defeated. Liu Xiaobie was also defeated handily. And he was the same as Liang Fang. He had been beaten extremely miserably without any chance of fighting back. This wasn’t supposed to be possible for pro-players. Even if they were against God-level opponents, such as their team captain, it shouldn’t go so far as to not even having a chance of winning!

Chances always existed, it just depended on whether or not the individual could grasp it.

But when fighting against Lord Grim, Liu Xiaobie and Liang Fang both discovered that there was only one way to not lose: don’t go up and duel him.

Chapter 136 – True Unspecialized

In the so-called Arena Contest, two players had already fallen. Their defeats had been thorough and beautiful, making the others lose their confidence.

Vice-captain Deng Fusheng stole a glance at the captain. Wang Jiexi’s expression was as usual, as if he wasn’t affected. But what about the team? Deng Fusheng looked around. The team members all had nervous expressions. Some were also glancing at the captain. Deng Fusheng knew that they were all scared that their captain would choose them to go up next. None of the team members had confidence in defeating Lord Grim.

And Lord Grim? He was just sitting there, eating food and drinking potions, recovering his health and mana. Wang Jiexi didn’t stop him. And none of the team members did either. They weren’t there to murder him, so they didn’t mind if Lord Grim rested. If they won by dragging the fights out until his mana ran out, there wouldn’t be any meaning to winning for Tiny Herb.

But what should they do next? Wang Jiexi was also a bit hesitant.

It wasn’t possible to beat him in a duel, that was already clear. Let alone the other team members, he himself didn’t have confidence in beating Lord Grim in a duel. This unspecialized character……

“Ha ha…….” A laugh was suddenly heard. It didn’t come from the practice room, but rather from the game.

At this moment, who in Team Tiny Herb could laugh?

The person who laughed was, of course, Ye Xiu.

“Like I was saying.. if you’re looking to use me as a training partner, this way isn’t very useful, right?” Ye Xiu said.

“It’s a rare opportunity.” Wang Jiexi replied.

“You’re not afraid these children are going to be mentally traumatized?” Ye Xiu said.

Children!!! Besides Gao Yingjie and Qiao Yifan, everyone was petrified. Who were children?

“You’re a bit too confident, aren’t you?” Wang Jiexi said.

“Ha ha.” Ye Xiu laughed again, “Let me ask you. Among everyone here, including you, has anyone here ever fought with a true unspecialized character?”

Silence reigned, both within game and outside of the game.

In the practice room, Team Tiny Herb’s members all looked at each other, unsure.

It was true. To them, unspecialized characters were only a myth. Unspecialized characters had already disappeared by the time the pro-scene had started. Those who knew about unspecialized characters and could tell stories about them could already be considered seniors. And Wang Jiexi? He had already been in the Alliance for five years. As of today, this season was his sixth year. His experience couldn’t be considered shallow, but when Ye Xiu had led Excellent Era to victory as three-time consecutive Champions, he had only just started playing Glory. And at that time, unspecialized characters had already long disappeared.

Those with ten years of experience in Glory weren’t few among the player population. But there were only a few left in the pro-scene. As long as a player wanted to play the game, he could play. But for pro-players, they couldn’t avoid growing washed-out due to the pro-scene’s competitiveness. Whether they could continue playing as a pro wasn’t something that they could just do if they wanted to.

Unspecialized characters were also a myth to Wang Jiexi. But if you said that he had zero experience with them, then that wasn’t true.

When Wang Jiexi entered Tiny Herb, there was a senior team member that had once played unspecialized. When the third server opened, he didn’t abandon his account or change classes like other unspecialized characters did. Instead, he kept his unspecialized character as a memento. That was how Wang Jiexi knew of the existence of unspecialized characters. He had even tried comparing notes with his senior’s unspecialized character and personally experienced and understood an unspecialized character’s advantages and disadvantages at that time. And in the end, when that senior retired, he gave his unspecialized account card as a gift to Wang Jiexi, which he had kept well to this day.

Wang Jiexi still remembered his senior’s lament towards unspecialized characters: Unspecialized characters are still a bit of a fantasy. Even if the level restriction is freed. The issue of weapons and the issue of the user are still large problems that are enough to restrict players from playing unspecialized.

“Perhaps, if there was a single weapon that could use all of the skills and an extremely experienced user proficient in every class, then it may be possible to truly use an unspecialized character’s strength.”

This had originally been a joke. But now, this joke had become a reality that was now in front of his eyes.

Ye Qiu, an existence known as a textbook in Glory, proficient in all classes, extremely experienced, was now using one.

As for the weapon, the weird weapon in Lord Grim’s hand had been noticed by everyone already and there wasn’t any shortage of discussion on it.

This Lord Grim had clearly never changed his weapon before. It was only his weapon that changed forms, which allowed him to use all sorts of skills. Sword to gun. Gun to sword. Switching forms in that way didn’t have any cooldowns like how changing weapons did. The knowledgeable pro-players could already see that this was a self-made weapon.. a terrifying self-made weapon.

True unspecialized character! This was a true unspecialized character!

After recalling that joke his senior teammate once said, Wang Jiexi finally understood what Ye Xiu was saying. A true unspecialized character, this was a true unspecialized character. Even in that era of unspecialized characters, there was never once a true unspecialized character. There was no one out there who had any experience fighting against a true unspecialized like him.

Keep on dueling Ye Qiu? Wang Jiexi looked around left and right. All he saw were worried faces. Even in last year’s deciding match, these faces hadn’t appeared. At that time, even though they were nervous, it wasn’t like now where they had absolutely no confidence in obtaining victory. Under those worried faces hid confusion, not nervousness.

And they hadn’t even fought with Lord Grim yet. They had only seen Lord Grim fight with Liang Fang and Liu Xiaobie.. and that was all.

And those two?

Wang Jiexi thought. He looked at Liang Fang and Liu Xiaobie. From their two faces, Wang Jiexi saw dismay and disappointment.

Wang Jiexi finally understood that Ye Qiu wasn’t being overconfident. Wang Jiexi thought that he had found a God to practice with, but now from the looks of it, this God had struck a blow to his team’s morale, destroying his teammates’ self-confidence. The creative idea Wang Jiexi had come up with had turned disastrous.

What now?

Wang Jiexi found that the current situation was quite problematic. He had gotten into a situation which he couldn’t get out of.

If they continued dueling, then all that would do is destroy everyone’s self-confidence, possibly including himself too. Wang Jiexi already found that his state of mind had already been affected. He had been overcautious all because their opponent’s strength had also deeply shocked him. Like this, the only way he’d be able to win back his team’s confidence was to personally duel and beat him. However, at this moment, he already had no confidence. He was afraid. He was afraid that if he lost, his teammates’ confidence would be thoroughly destroyed with no way of recovering.

Wang Jiexi clearly knew his position in his teammates’ hearts. Since the beginning, he had been used to carrying his teammates and rushing forward for the win. But this time, he wasn’t able to carry them. He didn’t dare carry them. Ye Qiu was truly too terrifying. Even though he had only defeated two of Tiny Herb’s members, even Wang Jiexi was feeling the pressure.

Should we leave? But Lord Grim’s psychological pressure had already been planted into everyone’s hearts. With this mental trauma, their future improvements, performance, and stability might all be negatively affected. These were not exaggerated words. Their mental state during a competition was a very important element. With how they were right now, would they be able to overcome their current psychological fears through their mental fortitude?

No!

This was the enormous psychological pressure from Lord Grim’s astonishing strength. Unless they defeated Lord Grim, there would be no way of getting rid of it. But for this to happen, it wasn’t really possible for them to duel and beat him. This time, they could only rely on the entire team’s strength. Wang Jiexi decided on a plan and immediately shouted calmly: “Everyone!”

The teammates at this moment were all somewhat out of it. Hearing their captain’s shout, they immediately focused.

“Up together!” Everyone heard their captain’s two words.

Nine players. At this moment, they had a total of nine players. Liang Fang and Liu Xiaobie hadn’t yet come back. However, nine pro-players against one…….

“Don’t be polite! Let’s go!” Wang Jiexi shouted. Right now, he had to break their doubts of nine against one. Using his position in the team, this was still something he could do.

Sure enough, after hearing their captain’s resolute command, everyone’s attention returned to the battlefield.

“Oh?” Lord Grim also got up. Ye Xiu laughed: “Is this okay?”

How could Wang Jiexi not know that nine versus one was somewhat overkill. But there was already no way he could change that. Although this way of obtaining victory would be somewhat embarrassing, at least this feeling would be better than the mental scar of having no way of winning.

“A team competition, just like you wanted.” Wang Jiexi hoped that he could at least dissolve his teammates’ embarrassment, even if he himself looked shameless.

“That wasn’t what I meant.” Ye Xiu still calmly laughed, “What I mean is, if your entire team goes up and your team gets wiped out, wouldn’t that be an even bigger blow? Is this….okay?”

“F*ck!!” Hearing this, Tiny Herb’s team members all suddenly had their fighting spirits ignited. The previous them harbored thoughts of fear. A nine versus one battle didn’t stimulate any of their fighting spirit. However, now that they heard how arrogant Ye Qiu was, their fighting spirits once again roared.

“Thank you. Your words came at the perfect time.” Wang Jiexi smiled. Their embarrassment for a nine versus one battle had been wiped out because of Ye Qiu’s words.

“Let’s go!” Ye Xiu said and then suddenly moved. Lord Grim turned around and unexpectedly ran off.

“There’s nowhere to run!” Wang Jiexi found that everything was developing better than he had imagined. With Lord Grim running away, his image of being invincible had collapsed a little bit, although running away wasn’t really shameful in a 9v1 situation.

Wang Jiexi’s Fiery Blaze rode his broom and with a whoosh, chased Lord Grim hoping to block him using his advantage in speed. However, Lord Grim flashed, leaving behind a shadow clone for him, while his real self disappeared without a trace.

“Captain!!” The other teammates weren’t in the battle yet, but they could see the field clearly. Lord Grim’s real body had flashed up into the air, heading straight for Fiery Blaze, who was riding on his broom underneath him.

“I know.” Wang Jiexi had rich experience. He wouldn’t be hit so easily. His character rolled on his broom and jumped down, just barely dodging this attack. With a sweep of his broom, his Witch sent an accurate attack towards Lord Grim.

Chapter 137 – Encirclement

A gun sound rang out!

Lord Grim suddenly fired and a bullet came out. Using the recoil, he flew back, just barely dodging Fiery Blaze’s Sweep.

However, his bullet had missed. A Witch could complete six combos in midair because Sweep gave the user a small knock-up effect. If not, then no matter how fast your hand speed was, it wasn’t possible to complete more than two normal attacks before you landed.

Wang Jiexi wasn’t an ordinary player. He fully utilized this and used Sweep while controlling his character in order to dodge his opponent’s attack. Even though the bullet was fired closely and quickly, it still wasn’t able to hit him.

“Li Ji!!” Wang Jiexi called out a name. Someone immediately answered back and then fired his gun at Lord Grim.

Li Ji. Part of Team Tiny Herb’s Main Roster. He was currently using the Level 27 Sharpshooter, Untraceable Bullet. As a long-ranged character, he immediately fired towards Lord Grim.

Pro players’ marksmanship didn’t need to be mentioned. Though they didn’t have 100% accuracy, their accuracy was much higher than normal players’. Untraceable Bullet was using the Level 25 Purple Weapon Western Revolver and instantly shot out six bullets.

Guns were different from other weapons. Attack Speed didn’t indicated the bullet’s movement speed, but rather the firing rate. The quickest is the Handgun with an Attack Speed of 10, capable of firing eight bullets in a row. Next is the Revolver, with an Attack Speed of 7 or 8, which could shoot out six bullets in a row. Next is the Crossbow, which could shoot out four bullets in a row. Fourth is the Rifle, with an Attack Speed of 2 or 3, and it could usually shoot out two bullets in a row. The slowest was the Hand Cannon, which could only be shot once before needing to reload.

Thus, like this the five types of guns had differences in Attack Speed. Players used whichever gun type they preferred. Besides Attack speed, different gun types did different amounts of damage and had different ways of calculating damage.

For example, for the revolver, the weapon fired a total of six times before needing to reload. Thus, each bullet’s damage would be ⅙ of the gun’s damage. The other gun times were calculated similarly. Besides this, there were also other special effects. For example, the Hand Cannon had AoE damage and the Rifle had Penetrating damage. All of the these effects could be triggered by normal attacks.

Untraceable Bullet shot out six bullets. It was too difficult for Lord Grim to dodge in midair, thus he immediately opened up his Umbrella. The Umbrella opened and all six bullets hit. However, these bullets just became a pushing force, letting Lord Grim move backwards even faster.

Everyone coughed a bit of blood. This ever-changing weapon was a bit too ridiculous! It could even be used as a Shield.

After Lord Grim landed on the ground, without even turning his head, he ran.

One versus nine. It definitely wasn’t possible for him to fight them head on. These were all pro-players. Even if unspecialized characters had the advantage of a vast pool of skills, it wasn’t so ridiculous that he could do that.

The reason Ye Xiu could easily beat Liang Fang and Liu Xiaobie was because one, he was more skilled; two, unspecialized characters had the advantage in the amount of skills; three, those two players didn’t have any experience against an unspecialized character. It was because of these reasons that he was able to completely destroy these two opponents. The latter two reasons were the most important points. If not, then even if he is a God-level player, he still wouldn’t be able to always win even against normal pro-players. The issue of on-stage performance had to be considered. Otherwise, what was the point of competition? If that was the case, then the winner would be decided just by looking at the player roster. This reasoning is the same as in football or basketball.

“Little Jie!” Wang Jiexi shouted. Gao Yingjie answered. His Weeping Crow quickly rode his Broom to chase after Lord Grim. Just as Wang Jiexi’s Fiery Blaze landed, he quickly jumped onto his broom. These two Witches flew extremely low, almost touching the ground. The lower one flew, the faster one would be. This was because the distance that could be flown was limited. At the distance limit, the faster one jumped down, the faster one would be. This faster movement had to be done quickly.

Weeping Crow and Fiery Blaze flew at the lowest possible altitude. This action relied on mechanical skill to complete. Only extremely quick hands could instantly complete this move.

Lord Grim suddenly stopped. He turned around and sent out a Gatling Gun. With a shake, the bullets split into two towards the two players. Weeping Crow and Fiery Blaze split off going left and right respectively, avoiding the bullets. Because the two pulled away to dodge the bullets, they had no way of recovering their lost distance and time.

This halt gave enough time for the gunner to get into firing range. Li Ji and Liu Fei, the two Sharpshooters, both fired. The bullets flew out and the PK temporarily turned into a gunfight.

As overlapping classes in the team, the coordination between Li Ji and Liu Fei was originally a type of tactical choice. The two coordinated exceptionally well. Liu Fei’s Fallen Angel fired straight at Lord Grim, while Li Ji fired where he predicted where Lord Grim would move.

The bullets repeatedly fell at Lord Grim’s feet, hitting dirt into the air, but were unable to hit Lord Grim. Although Li Ji and Liu Fei’s coordination was exceptional, how could Ye Xiu not understand what they were trying to do? Li Ji had predicted where he would move, while he counter-predicted where Li Ji would shoot.

Li Ji and Liu Fei were helpless. Their below Level 30 characters really did restrict their performance. If they had a few more skills, then they’d at least be able to control a larger area. But right now? Normal attacks were their main methods of attacking. In a PK, how could normal attacks work? In a PK, players mostly relied on their character’s skills. But the low-leveled skills below Level 30 weren’t really helpful right now for Li Ji and Liu Fei’s coordination.

Yet even though they missed, their attacks still delayed Lord Grim. On the side, Wang Jiexi and Gao Yingjie continued to close in on him.

Desolate Land wasn’t a flat land. While Ye Xiu made Lord Grim dodge, he had already figured out which direction to go to long ago. After a few steps, he jumped up and leaped over a short wall. With this leap, the two gunners could only vent their anger at the earth wall.

“Li Yihui, Zhou Yebai, to the left. Xiao Yun, Qiao Yifan, to the right. Gunners continue attacking head on to restrict his movements.” Wang Jiexi ordered.

“Yes!!” The team members all answered and then set out to complete their orders.

Li Ji and Liu Fei continued to fire, so that Lord Grim wouldn’t be able to expose his head and scout around. Li Yihui’s character was a Grappler and he rushed forward from the left along with Zhou Yebai’s Ghostblade. Xiao Yun’s Battle Mage Cloudy Heavens and Qiao Yifan’s Assassin Ashen Moon rushed forward from the right. The two Witches came in from the middle.

Of course, the Witches were the first to arrive. The left and right routes were to prevent Lord Grim from escaping to the side. Wang Jiexi’s plan was careful and thorough. Except when he and Gao Yingjie’s Witch flew over the earth wall, they looked around left and right, but Lord Grim had disappeared.

Wang Jiexi’s gaze turned and turned until it landed on a shabby, clay room close to the earth wall.

The troops from the left and right also went around the earth wall, but after seeing that Lord Grim wasn’t there, they all stared blankly. Wang Jiexi didn’t shout anything this time and individually messaged everyone where to look.

The troops from the left and right each circled around the clay room and then reported: “There’s no other entrance.”

Wang Jiexi nodded his head. At that moment, vice-captain Deng Fusheng’s Knight and the two Sharpshooters had arrived. Wang Jiexi set up the arrangement. The nine players each went into their respective position and then made a surprise attack.

The two Sharpshooters open fired at the room.

Deng Fusheng’s Knight raised his shield. The other close-combat characters followed closely behind. The two Witches rode on their Brooms above the building. They would completely fill the building as fast as possible without giving Lord Grim any chance to escape.

In the blink of an eye, they arrived at the building. Deng Fusheng’s Knight crouched and rolled, giving the two Witches enough space to fly through. Without looking, they began throwing out Disperse Powder left and right. The troops behind them quickly followed. In the end…..

In the end, there was no Lord Grim there. Everyone was at a loss. Only the two Sharpshooters outside didn’t know what was going on. Their task was to cover for them. Their guns were still aimed at the door. Once Lord Grim rushed out, their task would be to stop him.

“Where is he?” Someone finally asked the question in uncertainty.

Wang Jiexi stared blankly for quite a while too. His character came out of the room and he once again looked around left and right carefully.

In Desolate Land, there really were a lot of these broken-down clay rooms. But in that short amount of time, Lord Grim only had enough time to move to this room. If he moved anywhere else, he would have definitely been noticed by the others.

“What happened?” Outside, the Sharpshooters felt that something wasn’t right.

“He’s gone.” Someone replied to the two of them.

“Strange. Did you see him?” In Tiny Herb’s practice room, everyone began discussing amongst each other. They all thought that their character’s camera wasn’t enough, so they were all looking at each other’s computers to look for him.

“To the right, Sharpshooters fire!” Wang Jiexi suddenly ordered.

Everyone stared blankly. The two Sharpshooters turned their camera. On the right, there really was another building. The two didn’t hesitate and immediately fired at it.

“Yifan, go check the back. Everyone else come with me and charge!” Wang Jiexi ordered. Qiao Yifan’s Ashen Moon ran to go see if there was an exit at the back. The others hurried to inside this room.

They almost forgot. That guy had Shadow Clone Technique. If he used it to move, it would be possible for him to reach here.

Wang Jiexi had been thinking of this just a moment ago. After recalculating how far Lord Grim could move, he discovered that it was possible for Lord Grim to have escaped to this room.

The Sharpshooters kept guard on the outside. The Knight raised his shield and rolled in. The Witches both flew in together and threw down Disperse Powder. Qiao Yifan reported that there was no other exit and everyone rushed in.

Everything went smoothly. They had perfectly executed a surprise attack again. However, the results were the same as last time: there was no Lord Grim.

Wang Jiexi jumped out of the room and once again reassessed the situation.

That was it. Besides this room, Lord Grim had no other options. Even if he used Shadow Clone Technique, it wasn’t possible.

“Could there be some other low-leveled skill that I overlooked?” Wang Jiexi began going over all 120 skills that could be learned before Level 20.

Chapter 138 – Logout Escape

Wang Jiexi’s Fiery Blaze walked out from the room and continued to observe the surrounding terrain. He knew that he had definitely overlooked something because there was no way Lord Grim had just disappeared. There were no sneak skills below level 20 that could make a character disappear.

They had already eliminated the possibility of Lord Grim being in these two rooms. The third closest room…..

After looking around, Wang Jiexi shook his head.

Impossible……. There wasn’t enough time to reach this room. The moving while crouching was very slow. Even if Lord Grim had rolled the way through, there still wouldn’t be enough time. If he wanted to escape into the room before everyone got there, unless he could fly at a low altitude like a Witch, it wasn’t possible for unspecialized characters.

Low altitude flight……

Low altitude flight?!

Wang Jiexi suddenly thought of something. It was possible for Lord Grim to fly at a low altitude like a Witch. But the ability to fly wasn’t something only Witches could do. The Gunner’s Aerial Fire could fly too.

However, flying low with Aerial Fire meant that he wouldn’t have flown far. But he’d at least maintain a certain movement speed. Aerial Fire was a technique, so there wasn’t any cooldown and it could be used several times. As long as they were strung together, then it’d work. This couldn’t be considered difficult for pro-players.

“11 o’clock, that building!” Wang Jiexi couldn’t deal with being very careful. After making this sort of judgement, once they tried it, they would know.

“Yifan, to the back. Everyone else, with me.”

It was the same order. Even though the others didn’t understand why yet, they still followed their captain’s orders. The same tactic was employed. The process was done once again. And the results……. were the same.

”

“He’s not either!!!”

Wang Jiexi’s judgement had failed three times. This was a situation that Tiny Herb’s members had never encountered before. At this moment, everyone was extremely astonished. Where exactly was this Lord Grim hiding?

Wang Jiexi’s Witch went outside of the building. After looking around left and right, no matter how hard he wracked his brains, he wasn’t able to figure out where Lord Grim could possibly be…….

“You you you……. what are you doing!!”

In Happy Internet Cafe, Chen Guo had originally been talking serious business with Ye Xiu. After Ye Xiu began fighting, she had stood behind Ye Xiu watching the entire time, dumbstruck.

With her view of the situation, she naturally knew where Lord Grim was going.

After Lord Grim jumped over the wall and crouched down, Ye Xiu immediately used Aerial Fire. Again and again, the distance he flew with each one was very small. But the speed was very fast. Ye Xiu’s tempo was quite outstanding. He would use Aerial Fire again the moment he landed. Like this, if Chen Guo hadn’t been able to see the tongues of flames from the gun barrel every time he fired, she wouldn’t have been able to tell that he was moving because of him chaining Aerial Fire together.

After moving in this way for several seconds, Lord Grim suddenly turned around. The scene changed as he entered a building. While escaping into the room, he used the Shadow Clone Technique. Using it once was to use it and instantly move. Using it twice was to get rid of the clone. The Shadow Clone Technique wasn’t like a bullet fired from a Gunner. The clone could be removed.

And after that, Ye Xiu quickly used the move: force logout.

Only when the game went to the login screen did Chen Guo yell that out.

“What did you say?” Ye Xiu had just taken off his headphones.

“You….. logged out of the game? Are you looking to die?” Chen Guo pointed at the screen and said. Nowadays, technology had improved, so the delay for going online and offline had been reduced by a lot. However, during battle, it wasn’t possible to offline normally. Of course, there wasn’t any way of preventing players from force quitting the game. But if it was done like this, the characters would stay in their original position for a long time. When the user went back online, his character would be dead nine times out of ten. If players could instantly log out at any time during battle, then no player would ever die.

“There’s enough time.” Ye Xiu laughed.

“Impossible.” Chen Guo said.

“By the time they find me, I’ll have already logged out.” Ye Xiu said.

“How could they take that long to find you?” Chen Guo said.

“They didn’t see that I entered this building.” Ye Xiu said.

“Why not?” Chen Guo didn’t understand.

“Were you not paying attention? I flew low with Aerial Fire the entire time. Plus, with the earth wall blocking their view, they couldn’t have seen me. And the Shadow Clone I used after that had been removed by the time they got there. By the time they arrived, they couldn’t have found me.” Ye Xiu said.

“But the place where you were at…… it looked like there were only a few buildings there? If they just casually looked around, wouldn’t they have found you?” Chen Guo was a bit hesitant. Honestly speaking, Lord Grim’s camera had only quickly swept around the terrain, so she didn’t pay too much attention to it and didn’t remember it too clearly.

“I only had enough time to sneak into one of three rooms. There was one facing me that I could have directly entered. On the right, after crouching down, using Shadow Clone Technique was enough to let me enter it. But for me to enter the one I went into, you saw, I had to use Aerial Fire to quickly move there to make it in time. If I went into the closest one, I’m guessing they would have decided to check that one first. After seeing that it was empty, they would go to the second one…… and then the third.”

“Why couldn’t they split up and search?” Chen Guo said.

“If there was a clear decision to make, why would they go separate to look?” Ye Xiu said, while getting up: “You should keep talking about what you were talking about before!”

“You’re….. just going to leave it like that?” Chen Guo pointed at the screen.

“I’ve already logged out. What’s there to do?”

“You’re not going back online?”

“I’ll listen to you talk first!” Ye Xiu said.

“You….. didn’t you say you were going to wipe out their team?” Chen Guo had been behind Ye Xiu the entire time, so Chen Guo had heard him talking.

“That was just something I said. 1v9.. how could I do that?” Ye Xiu said.

“What type of person are you??” Chen Guo coughed blood, “Then why were you bragging?”

“To give them pressure.” Ye Xiu said.

“How could they believe that?” Chen Guo asked.

Ye Xiu said to her: “How come it looked like you believed it?”

“I…….” Chen Guo had no words. In the past few days, she hadn’t bothered with him. Her mind was nice and peaceful. But today, with just a few words, she was once again speechless.

In game, Wang Jiexi was still wracking his brains trying to figure out where Lord Grim was. Unable to bear it any longer, he decided to go add Lord Grim as a friend. But after looking him up, the system said that Lord Grim was no longer online. Wang Jiexi stood there staring foolishly.

Offline…..

As a pro-player who was used to competing in the competitive scene, there was absolutely no way he could have come up with that solution. This was an issue of habit.

However, at this moment, Wang Jiexi had already understood everything.

That guy had planned to go offline from the very start. Their first fights were all done in order to pull the distance between them.

Those three simple buildings past the wall were the crucial points. Those three rooms were a trap. There was a chance that the plan would fail, but it was unlikely. The room closest to them would be the first that they would think about. The two other rooms were more difficult to figure out. In the end, Wang Jiexi led his team to go over every building one at a time, giving him enough time to go offline.

Seeing everyone’s puzzled faces, Wang Jiexi didn’t know whether to laugh or cry. One versus nine. Sure enough, it was all just done to create pressure!

“Captain…….” Vice captain Deng Fusheng lightly said to him. Team Tiny Herb’s morale had reached its lowest point. They still hadn’t figured out that Lord Grim had went offline. They were all turning and turning, searching like mad, yet how could they find him?

Wang Jiexi stood up. Everyone turned to look at him and hastily took off their headphones. They knew their captain was about to speak.

“There’s no need to keep looking. That guy logged off.” Wang Jiexi said.

“What?” Everyone was astonished. Even though they believed their captain, they still couldn’t resist confirming it in the game. Just as expected, the system prompted that Lord Grim wasn’t online.

Who knew how many times today the practice room was deathly silent.

“Logout escape…”

“Didn’t he say he was going to wipe out our team? Why’d he run?” Someone looked down on him.

“If this was a match, then it would be equivalent to him forfeiting.” Someone knew what this logout escape meant in a competitive setting.

“Then that’s it for today! You guys can rest now. Those who are interested can stay here and wait for him to come online.” Wang Jiexi finished. He himself went back to his seat, keeping guard with his Fiery Blaze account.

The captain was going to wait! Everyone obviously saw this.

As a result, no one left. The captain was their model. Even though he said that they could rest, if the captain was going to stay, then who was going to leave?

Liang Fang’s and Liu Xiaobie’s characters had already ran back. Tiny Herb had a total of eleven players on the team and now began to disperse.

“Captain, should we ambush him?” The vice-captain ran to Wang Jiexi’s Fiery Blaze to talk to him.

“is there a need to? Killing him isn’t our goal. Our goal is to use him to raise our team’s skill level.” Wang Jiexi said.

“Oh……”

“Li Ji, Liu Fei, you two.” Wang Jiexi shouted.

“Yes?” The two immediately responded.

“The coordination between the two of you is extremely good. However, today, you two had no way of stopping Lord Grim. Your patterns follow conventional reasoning too well, so it’s easy for others to see through it, especially for experienced veterans like Ye Qiu. You two need to be a bit more imaginative by acting more freely!” Wang Jiexi said.

“Yes……” The two replied.

“Liang Fang, Liu Xiaobie.” Wang Jiexi called for the two who had lost their duels. The two hastily ran over.

“What are your thoughts?” Wang Jiexi asked.

The two were silent.

“In the low-levels, unspecialized characters have a large advantage due to their vast amount of skills. None of you have ever encountered a single character with all of these assortments of skills and lack the experience necessary to beat him. That’s why losing to him is very normal. Even I’m not an opponent for him in a duel.” Wang Jiexi said.

“Everyone listen well.” Wang Jiexi raised his voice. Everyone paid attention.

“Everyone knows who Ye Qiu is. Even if he’s retired, his skill level is still top-tier in the Alliance. Right now, he’s also using an unspecialized character, which has such an early-game advantage in skills. Everyone is also very unfamiliar with this class, so don’t be concerned about winning or losing. Everyone should treasure this opportunity to fight hand in hand with this type of top-tier player. Discover your own flaws and think of a way to improve. This is our purpose for clearing this BOSS.” Wang Jiexi said.

“Hey, hey. What BOSS? Should you be talking like that?” A voice suddenly interrupted.

Chapter 139 – Who’s the Training Partner?

Wang Jiexi’s Fiery Blaze was standing outside the clay building’s entrance. After hearing the voice, he immediately turned around and entered the building.

No one. Still no one. Then who had been speaking just before?

Outside of the building, Team Tiny Herb’s players were also thinking the same, but quickly found the answer.

Soft Mist!!

Last night, one of the players that had wiped out their team was a female Battle Mage, who was currently standing to the side.

This was a very ordinary location in Desolate Land. Monsters respawned here and random players would pass by. Team Tiny Herb had been keeping guard, waiting for the BOSS to respawn, so they weren’t looking around too carefully, especially when the captain had spoken. Even though it was in the game, everyone still had their characters look towards Fiery Blaze.

This was how Soft Mist was able to get beside them without them noticing.

Of the ten players, only the five subs from last night recognized Soft Mist. The five players from the main roster were still looking around left and right trying to figure out who it was.

“You guys really have a lot of patience.” Soft Mist was speaking. However, it was a male’s voice.. Ye Xiu’s voice.

Correct. Ye Xiu had taken Tang Rou’s account and ran over to take a look at the situation. Tang Rou was sitting behind him with a rice bowl in her hands. She had just gotten up and was currently eating dinner!

“Who are these guys? Why doe they keep coming back?” Tang Rou asked. She also recognized those five players from last night. However, today, their troops had grown larger and it looked like they had called more troops over for revenge.

“Yeah, they’re endless.” Ye Xiu said.

However, his words could be heard in-game by Team Tiny Herb’s members. Everyone was extremely gloomy. But they didn’t act blindly without thinking and waited for their captain to give them orders.

“Battle Mage.” Wang Jiexi’s Fiery Blaze walked up and said.

“Yup!” Ye Xiu said. He brandished the battle lance in Soft Mist’s hands. Battle Mage! This was the class that he had truly used for ten years. Even though his ten years of experience had let him be proficient in every class, the Battle Mage was still his most liked and most familiar class.

“Xiao Yun, you go up.” Wang Jiexi called for him.

“Ah?” Xiao Yun stared blankly.

They were the same class. He was Level 26 and his opponent was Level 28. There wouldn’t be much of a difference between their equipment. However, he was still lacking in terms of skill levels and stats, so there was still a small difference.

“Don’t be nervous. Don’t forget, you’re one of the members of a champion team!” Wang Jiexi said.

At this moment, Wang Jiexi didn’t say “It doesn’t matter whether you win or lose.” It doesn’t matter whether you win or lose could only be said when team morale was at its lowest. It was a type of comfort.

During a real battle, even if it was only for learning, this type of mentality couldn’t be had, especially for a member of a team that wanted to be Champions. Winning was always number one. Don’t worry about winning or losing, that type of talk, could only be said by Wang Jiexi at a suitable time to get rid of any unnecessary baggage in everyone’s minds.

“Xiao Yun, you can do it!” A few teammates cheered him on.

Xiao Yun’s fighting spirit suddenly ignited. Even though he was against a trump card God among Battle Mages, this was already of the past. Ye Qiu had already left the pro-scene. And himself? He was currently ascending up the ladder slowly. Why should he be afraid of a washed-up player?

Thinking like this, Xiao Yun’s Battle Mage Cloudy Heavens raised his battle lance and went out to do battle.

“Ha ha, so it’s you!” Ye Xiu laughed.

Xiao Yun suddenly weakened. It was only five simple words. However, his tone made Xiao Yun suddenly think of his tragic experience last night of getting killed by Vanishing Step.

“Do you need a few Chasers first?” Ye Xiu asked.

Xiao Yun felt even more embarrassed. Yesterday, he had carried seven Chasers to kill him, but he never had the chance to use them. For a Battle Mage, to not be able to use the class’s most characteristic feature, Chasers, was too much of a joke.

Xiao Yun was about to say something, when he heard his team captain shout out from behind: “Xiao Yun, don’t waste time trash talking.”

Trash talking? Xiao Yun stared blankly.

In Glory’s competitive scene, any taunting or provoking done between two sides in chat was called trash talking. But in game, the other side didn’t have to type out messages and could directly talk. As pro-players, they had to learn how to deal with these types of situations. Trash talking was always done deliberately by experts to find a weak point and to irritate you. There were very few people who truly enjoyed saying such words. This was also one tactic for psychological warfare.

Xiao Yun took a deep breath. There were two ways of dealing with trash talk. One way was to counter with your own trash talk and see who was better at it. The second way was to ignore it and maintain a calm mental state. The current expert at using both ways was Huang Shaotian. For that guy, first of all, he talked to himself, so he didn’t care about what the other side was saying. Second was his typing attacks, which were classified as group attacks. Directly attacking the entire team was something that he had done before.

For new players, trash talk was an extremely serious challenge for them. For example, for Gao Yingjie, who was viewed as the player who would succeed Wang Jiexi, although his skill level was already very good, he still hadn’t had any experience in an official match. This was all because his shy and introverted nature still had to be tempered. If he was sent into a match against Huang Shaotian’s typing attacks, it wasn’t wrong to say that there was a chance he would be attacked until he was crying.

After hearing the captain speak, Xiao Yun collected himself and stopped thinking about what Ye Xiu had said. Afraid that Ye Xiu would say something that would make hurt him even more, he immediately raised his battle lance and attacked. Soft Mist also raised her battle lance and welcomed him. The two battle mages began fighting in an instant.

Everyone subconsciously walked closer a few steps in order to see the battle unfold more clearly.

“Everyone, record it.” Wang Jiexi ordered and then opened the record function too.

In a battle of the same class, there was less fancy maneuvers and more caution. Because they both knew their class from top to bottom, their usual ways of fighting were usually useless.

Xiao Yun went up and used Dragon Tooth, Sky Strike, Falling Flower Palm, Circle Swing, chaining together the Battle Mage’s most basic set of four skills. However, none of them hit. Following up, Soft Mist did the same and chained together these four skills, which also all missed Cloudy Heavens. Against a class he himself was extremely familiar with, Xiao Yun clearly performed a lot better than last time.

Dodging and attacking, the two Battle Mages took turns attacking. But their Magic Chasers were never able to form. Until now, the two hadn’t yet successfully hit each other yet.

The more Xiao Yun fought, the more energetic he became. He discovered that once Ye Qiu took off that weird unspecialized class, he was only just so-so. Sure enough, he really was a retired pro-player. His fighting was extremely ordinary! Unfortunately, this was only a battle between low-leveled accounts in the new server. If this was in a pro-match, the finals, at a key moment, his teammates were all dead and only him and One Autumn Leaf were fighting in the decisive battle, where victory would signify their spot as Champions, and he……..

Found an opening!!

At this moment, a clear opening had been exposed on Soft Mist. Xiao Yun didn’t let the opportunity pass. The battle lance in Cloudy Heaven’s hands stabbed forward like a viper. His attack hit and this battle’s first Magic Chaser was formed. Immediately following, a Sky Strike headed towards Soft Mist along with the Neutral Chaser he had just formed.

The Chaser exploded. Magic damage! Cloudy Heavens also gained a movement speed buff and his movements quickened. He swiftly closed in. Seeing Soft Mist, he wanted to also play around with her using Vanishing Step. But, all in all, he didn’t have enough skill to do so. By the time he’d have figured out where he should move towards, Soft Mist would have already almost fallen to the ground by then.

His opponent wasn’t like a doll and responded with a mid-air stab to try and stop Cloudy Heavens from coming closer. However, this attack was clearly a bit frantic while in midair. Cloudy Heavens leaped backwards and easily dodged it. He quickly stepped forward and then used a Falling Flower Palm, hitting her directly. Not waiting for his opponent to fly, he immediately followed up with a Circle Swing and Soft Mist crashed to the ground.

Xiao Yun was extraordinarily proud. He felt that he was an MVP-level God. He rushed forward to attack. While doing so, he thought he heard a “My turn”……

Xiao Yun didn’t have time to think carefully. He attacked twice at that Soft Mist, who was laying the ground laying there like a dead person. Xiao Yun also hesitated, when he suddenly heard the captain yell, “Look out!”

Just as it was said, Soft Mist suddenly rolled. Xiao Yun had Cloudy Heavens chase him with a stab, full of confidence. The opponent got up and then jumped, just barely dodging Cloudy Heaven’s lance. High up in the sky, the battle lance pricked up and a Sky Strike flew over. Xiao Yun hastily did a roll and Cloudy Heavens avoided it.

After Soft Mist landed, she immediately used a Dragon Tooth. Cloudy Heavens sidestepped, dodging it. The opponent’s skills along with normal attacks arrived one after another, while saying: “See, it’s best to use a few normal attacks between skills in order to change up your tempo. When trying to maintain the situation, the more available skills you have the better. For example, when you chained four skills at once, even though it has a lot of power, once the combos finished and those three skills go on cooldown, there are a lot fewer choices you can make during that time, so it’ll be much easier for your opponent to see through you. This isn’t only for in the early game. You’ll have to pay attention to do this when you reach the late-game too. Even though you have more skills in the late-game, the cooldowns for high-levels skills are longer. Throwing down all your skills at once isn’t a very smart way of fighting.”

“Oh……” Tang Rou, who was standing behind Ye Xiu, replied. She had been fighting against the player who had been beaten up in the air by Ye Xiu yesterday. Only after fighting against him did she realize that his person had been played around with wasn’t as easy to deal with as she had previously thought.

“When all of a your skills are ready to be used, that’s when you’re at your strongest. In reverse, you also have to pay attention to how many skills your opponent has used too. What is the cooldown for that skill? See, he just used a Falling Flower Palm, so in the next four seconds, Falling Flower Palm can’t be used by him. Use this time to close in. Besides Falling Flower Palm, the current Battle Mage skills that can be used are all line or point attacks, so if we choose to close in quickly at a slight angle. Look, he doesn’t have any skills he can use to stop us right now.”

“Oops, Falling Flower Palm……. I said too much and four seconds have passed, so Falling Flower Palm is off cooldown….” Just as Ye Xiu was about to close in, Cloudy Heavens used a Falling Flower Palm. He hastily leaped back, letting Soft Mist dodge it.

“What are you doing? Who are you talking with?!” Xiao Yun shouted.

Chapter 140 – Find Me Next Door

“Watch this!” Soft Mist said this and then once again took advantage of the fact that Cloudy Heaven’s skills were on cooldown and closed in to attack. This time, Ye Xiu didn’t say anything further. He would first demonstrate it before saying anything more.

After only two moves, Cloudy Heaven was knocked into the air. Xiao Yun was extremely gloomy. At this moment, he had already figured out what had happened. The two Soft Mists before and after were completely different. As a pro-player, of course he had this level of judgement. Plus, with Ye Xiu’s sudden non-stop chatter, Xiao Yun finally understood that in the beginning, he had been the one brought as a training partner. And now? He was once again being used a teaching prop.

Xiao Yun impatiently tried to hurry up and get out of the mid-air situation. But whenever his camera angle changed, he couldn’t find his opponent.

Vanishing Step. Vanishing Step again!

Xiao Yun really hated this! Since he couldn’t break out of the situation, it would clearly mean that his skill level was lower by a level. Thinking of how the entire team was watching him right now, he even had thoughts of dying. Fortunately, the opponent wasn’t as vicious as last time. Even though he still used Vanishing Step, after a few hits, he used a Circle Swing to throw him into the ground.

Xiao Yun immediately did a roll and then got up, afraid that his opponent would chase him down. However, Soft Mist didn’t move. She stood there, chatting incessantly. Clearly, the player using her was explaining what he had just been doing.

Teaching dummy! He really did become a teaching dummy. Xiao Yun was fuming in anger. He rushed forward to engage in combat again. Soft Mist casually dissolved his efforts while commenting. What went wrong there, what should be done, etc. Xiao Yun went from a teaching dummy to teaching material.

Even more unfortunate was that his anger didn’t bring out any hidden power for Xiao Yun. His movements were still that same as before. And, on the contrary, his impatience made him expose even more openings.

“Xiao Yun, withdraw!” Wang Jiexi finally said. As spectators with clear views of the scene, they figured out long ago that the Soft Mists before and after were played by two different people. At this moment, Xiao Yun’s desire to win was quite fierce. However, his mental state had already gone out of control and he was now only pushing attacks with his anger.

But Xiao Yun was still extremely focused with his playing. He unexpectedly hadn’t heard Wang Jiexi’s words. Zhou Yebai, who was sitting next to him, hastily patted him: “Xiao Yun, captain wanted you to withdraw!”

This time, Xiao Yun got the message. After staring blankly for a bit, he gloomily withdrew to his captain’s side. This was one of their customs. At moments like these, their captain would say a few words to them.

“Were you listening to what Ye Qiu had been saying just before?” Wang Jiexi asked.

Xiao Yun stared blankly. He had heard. He really had heard, so much so that he saw through him and discovered that he was being used by Ye Qiu as a teaching dummy. But he knew that his captain definitely wasn’t talking about this.

“I already knew everything he said……” Xiao Yun justified himself. None of those theories were any big secret. Not just pro-players, but even normal players knew about them. However, even if one knew about them, actually putting them to use was an entirely different matter.

“Since you didn’t need to listen, why did you take his words as trash talk?” Wang Jiexi said.

Xiao Yun stared blankly again. Wang Jiexi didn’t say anything more and let him reflect on his own.

“Captain, let me try.” At this moment, a player actively requested to go up and fight. The player was the player who had been previously defeated, Liu Xiaobie. But seeing that the opponent wasn’t using an unspecialized character, that truly difficult to deal with class, everyone was already eager to give it a try. Liu Xiaobie had lost once, so he had a bit of revenge on his mind.

“Let me try!” The player who had also died once just before, Liang Fang, asked to go up too.

“Hey, hey!” Before their captain was able to reply, Soft Mist walked over. Soft Mist was a female character, although the voice clearly belonged to a male. Everyone felt that it was a bit weird.

“Aren’t we here to compare notes? Let’s go to the Arena.” Ye Xiu said.

“It looks like you have someone next to you who also needs guidance?” Wang Jiexi said.

“Yup! But I don’t have as many people as you do.” Ye Xiu said.

“What type of person?”

“A little sister from the Internet Cafe.” Ye Xiu said.

“…….”

“I’m going to go on my account.” Ye Xiu said and then left. Soft Mist was returned to Tang Rou. Ye Xiu logged into Lord Grim and then walked out of the clay building. Team Tiny Herb’s eleven players were all waiting outside. And for some time, they weren’t sure what had just happened.

“Don’t you think that this phrase would be amazing?” Lord Grim walked up, while Ye Xiu asked.

“What phrase?” Wang Jiexi asked.

“Champion team becomes training partners with internet cafe girl. That would probably make the headlines, right?” Ye Xiu said.

“The girl you’re talking about is this Soft Mist, right?” Wang Jiexi said.

“Right.”

“She’s clearly a new player. Don’t you think that directly using pro-players as training partners is a bit too excessive?” Wang Jiexi said.

“Ha ha. For her, doing it this way fits her quite nicely!” Ye Xiu said.

“But I don’t see how training with her will provide any benefits to us.” Wang Jiexi said.

“If you can’t beat her, then you don’t have the qualifications to fight with me.” Ye Xiu said.

Wang Jiexi was speechless for a while: “That’ll be quite easy for us to do.”

“That’s why you guys won’t lose out. Unless you guys want to keeping doing things like this and play hide and seek with me everyday. You guys should be pretty busy, right? Do you guys really have that much time?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Arena.” Wang Jiexi’s character Fiery Blaze turned around and then announced the news to everyone.

“Are these players all experts?” Tang Rou’s Soft Mist walked over to Lord Grim to ask.

“Yeah.” Ye Xiu replied.

“How good?” Tang Rou asked.

“They’re a bit worse than me.” Ye Xiu said.

Coughs immediately sprang up.

Ye Xiu ignored them. He asked Tang Rou: “If you keep on losing, will you cry?”

“What do you think?” Tang Rou asked back.

“I just want you to be prepared.” Ye Xiu said.

“I don’t believe it. Aren’t you exaggerating too much?” Tang Rou said.

“Yeah. That’s the spirit.” Ye Xiu lit his cigarette.

The group returned to town and entered the Arena.

“Can I use my unspecialized?” Ye Xiu asked.

Everyone in Tiny Herb was speechless. This wasn’t an easy question to answer! If you said no, then it’d mean that they were scared. If you said yes, then they really would be scared! Going against an unspecialized was extremely hard.

In the end, they heard the captain say: “What are you guys worrying about? If you can’t get over it, then go to bed.”

Winning or losing doesn’t matter couldn’t always be said. Wang Jiexi hoped that his teammates would show that they didn’t fear losing and learn from their failure. Beating an unspecialized at this level, especially Ye Qiu’s Lord Grim, truly was nearly impossible for everyone. Under this situation, this would tell him who had the courage to face against a loss and improve because of it.

The team was silent. It didn’t matter whether or not their mental states could bear it. No one was going to choose to leave.

“Who wants to go first?” Wang Jiexi asked.

“Me!” Liu Xiaobie walked directly to Lord Grim.

“We’ve already agreed that you have to pass her first.” Ye Xiu hinted at Tang Rou.

“It’ll be quick.” Liu Xiaobie said full of confidence. He created a 1v1 room. The others joined as spectators. After Ye Xiu entered, he left a message and then left: If you win, come find me next door, password 15951.

“How long can she last?” Ye Xiu silently thought in his newly created room. He wasn’t sitting together with Tang Rou, so he couldn’t see how the battle was going and could only guess.

As a first opponent, Liu Xiaobie was quite unfavorable for Tang Rou.

Tang Rou’s main advantage was her hand speed. However, Liu Xiaobie was famous in the pro-scene for his hand speed. What had originally been Tang Rou’s advantage was a disadvantage to her in front of Liu Xiaobie. As for experience, understanding, knowledge, and decision-making, they weren’t comparable.

“Probably around 40 seconds…….” Ye Xiu guessed a time. For him, this was a type of habit. Using his experience, he could directly simulate a match and, from that, he could make a final guess.

43 seconds!

The time wasn’t far from Ye Xiu’s guess. Liu Xiaobie started out extremely fiercely and didn’t show any mercy towards her. He was even more impatient about wasting his time on a noob like her. This was the first time that she felt powerless because someone’s hand speed was higher than hers. Against that Battle Mage Cloudy Heavens, she could still put up a fight. But up against this Blade Master, she was completely suppressed from the very start and never had a chance to counterattack. It was a complete victory……

Everyone in the room suddenly disappeared. Tang Rou stared blankly and then left, too. She joined the room next door as a spectator, but didn’t find Lord Grim.

“Where are you?” Tang Rou asked Ye Xiu.

“Find me next door.” Ye Xiu replied.

“I am next door. I don’t see you.” Tang Rou replied.

“Find me next door is the room’s name…..”

Tang Rou was speechless. She left the room and then searched. Sure enough, there was a room called “Find me next door”. She typed in the password and entered. Lord Grim was the only one inside. The others had probably been thrown off by the play on words, too.

“How was it?” Ye Xiu asked Tang Rou.

“They really were strong.” Tang Rou said.

“That opponent just happened to counter you.” Ye Xiu said.

“It doesn’t matter who the person is, I’ll beat him.” Tang Rou said.

“It’d be great if you could do that.” Ye Xiu said.

“Definitely.” Tang Rou said.

The two continued to chat. Someone from Tiny Herb finally entered. Soon afterwards, the others rushed in.

‘Was there a point…..” Wang Jiexi clearly didn’t appreciate Ye Xiu’s little play on words.

Everyone was in spectator mode, ready to watch Liu Xiaobie enter the field. However, they didn’t see him. After a while, they saw him enter as a spectator and say: “What’s going on? I can’t join the battle.”

“Pay attention to the conditions for joining the battle!” Ye Xiu said.

“I already beat her.” Liu Xiaobie said.

“I was talking about the system setup.” Ye Xiu said.

“System setup?” Everyone was puzzled. In the end, Wang Jiexi found it the fastest: “Gambling match?”

“Of course, it’s a gambling match.” Ye Xiu said.

“40 Strong Spider Silk?” Wang Jiexi saw Ye Xiu’s bet.

“I don’t think you guys have high-level materials either.” In reality, Ye Xiu didn’t have anything on him. He had used up all of the materials he recently got. These Strong Spider Silk were from the extra he earned from the first time he substituted in. Gambling matches couldn’t be made in the Arena without a starting bet. The stakes were all mortgaged by the system.

“We don’t have these either.” Wang Jiexi said impolitely.

“Come on, find a way. If you don’t have these, then an equivalent exchange is fine. Would you like me to give you a list of items?” Ye Xiu asked.

Chapter 141 – Wreck and Then Get Wrecked

“Oh? You want materials for your Silver weapon and you also want to train a new player. Quite ambitious, huh.” Wang Jiexi said.

“That’s why if you want take another Championship, then you’re going to need to seize the chance now.” Ye Xiu said.

Tiny Herb’s team members were listening to the conversation between these two gods. In their hearts, they were extremely hesitant. Was Ye Qiu planning on coming back to the pro-scene? The problem was.. didn’t he just retire a few days ago? Wasn’t it a little strange that he wanted to come back already?

“Say it. What materials do you want?” Wang Jiexi asked.

A wall of text quickly flashed over. It was clearly impossible for it to have been typed out in that short amount of time.

“So you really had prepared long ago?” Wang Jiexi looked at these materials. They were practically all materials from the Level 25-30 stage of the game. Some were from hidden BOSSes, some were from wild BOSSes, and some were even worthless items. But for Wang Jiexi, that level of a player, he had a bit of knowledge on the equipment editor, especially since their club’s technology department was considered the top in the Alliance. After Excellent Era’s reign, for Team Tiny Herb to be able to become two-time Champions, this was one of their reasons.

These self-made weapon materials were unexpectedly all laid out right in front of him. Was he not scared of exposing how his weapon was made? It has to be known that self-made weapons were all very secretive items.

Does he think that we won’t be able to see through it or did he put in some sort of trick? Wang Jiexi thought to himself, but didn’t say anything. He immediately contacted Herb Garden’s guild leader Plantago Seed on this server and told him his needs.

Plantago Seed was actually outside the Arena!

This guy had been following them the entire time from start to finish. But because he was too afraid to go near them, he just watched them from afar, which was why no one noticed him. However, when he reached the Arena, he didn’t know which room everyone went into and had no choice but to get ready to leave. Who would have thought that he would suddenly receive a message from Fiery Blaze?

God Jiexi!! Plantago Seed obviously knew that this character was a Witch. Either this one or Weeping Crow, one of them had to be Wang Jiexi.

Plantago Seed looked at the list that was sent over and then immediately ran to the guild’s storehouse, carrying everything they had so far with him. He then contacted Fiery Blaze to find out which Arena room they were in and then hastily sent the items over.

All sorts of materials were brought over. Wang Jiexi clearly knew that the stakes weren’t any different from gifts to him because their chances of winning were so low. If Plantago Seed had to make the decision, he definitely wouldn’t have agreed to the requests. He would have at least tried to lessen the damages. But in Wang Jiexi’s eyes, these low-leveled materials were nothing to him. If they were the tuition for training his team, then so be it.

With the materials, Liu Xiaobie accepted the stakes and his character then entered the 1v1 match.

“Wow, so quick! You really deserve to be called the Champion team!” Ye Xiu said.

“Cut the crap!” Liu Xiaobie was in high spirits. He knew his opponent was the God Ye Qiu, so he of course wouldn’t hold back Using his famed hand speed in the pro-scene to go all-out, the match instantly began with a horizontal sweep of his sword.

The record function in the Arena was very different from the record function in the wild. It didn’t require the recording to be in a player’s perspective. The perspective could be looked at from a God’s perspective. When the recording was rewinding or playing, the perspective could be changed to a player’s perspective, zoomed-out, a close-up, a birds-eye view, any perspective, which was clearly advantageous for studying it. For Wang Jiexi and the other team members, they were using this sort of God’s perspective even now, allowing them to freely choose which perspective they wanted to watch the battle in.

Liu Xiaobie made the first attack. His movements looked like he was in a panic, but it was actually all under his control. This was because against an unspecialized player’s unpredictable actions, where even pro-players had no way of guarding against, Liu Xiaobie’s only choice was to go frantic with his hand speed, hoping to use chain attacks to stop his opponent from doing any weird tricks or stop him from having any time to think about what to do next.

Wang Jiexi saw this and secretly nodded his head. All in all, Liu Xiaobie was a player from the main roster, so his mind was quite mature and his decision-making was very on-point. In comparison, even though Xiao Yun had participated in almost half of their matches, he still appeared hot-tempered.

However, if he wanted to win, it would be somewhat difficult.

Just as this thought went through Wang Jiexi’s head, Lord Grim had begun counter-attacking.

Just like that, the violent sword swings that flew out like a tempest from Liu Xiaobie’s Blade Master were dissolved in an instant. Lance, Gun, Sword, and Fist attacks were thrown out following after. Liu Xiaobie’s Blade Master Slash Slash Draw was forced to retreat. However, he was still focused, looking for an opportunity.

“Good!” Wang Jiexi typed out this word, boosting Liu Xiaobie’s morale. This was what he wanted to see: not being discouraged by a defeat.

After a short moment, Liu Xiaobie still fell. The bets they had made were automatically sent as a package to Lord Grim.

“Thanks.” Ye Xiu typed.

“My turn!!” Liang Fang jumped out to try.

“Pass the test first.” Ye Xiu kicked him out of the room.

Tang Rou also received the news. She left and created a room. This time, the others didn’t go and watch. There really wasn’t much to see from a new Battle Mage like her.

Shortly after, Liang Fang and Tang Rou both returned. Tang Rou was naturally defeated without any suspense. Liang Fang brought the materials up to the field and the two sides began fighting. Liang Fang quickly felt some type of familiarity with the situation. This familiarity was the similar to how when he and Soft Mist had fought. Except this time, their roles had swapped and he became the one struggling…..

Liang Fang was a wild and hot-blooded person. His blood became even more excited in this type of situation and often used ways that caused both sides to suffer damage. However, this didn’t mean that he had lost his cool. Liang Fang’s Berserker class preferred this way of fighting. This was because after changing classes, Berserkers could learn the skill “Blood Awakening”. For Berserkers that learned this passive skill, when their health hit below 50%, they would gain additional strength. More so, the lower the health, the higher the increase. In other words, the lower a Berserker’s health, the stronger the attacks would be. Later, if the two sides continued to fight with both sides suffering, then the one who would lose out in the end would be the opponent.

Liang Fang fiercely attacked in this way. Ye Xiu didn’t seem to be having an easy time either. He often went into desperate situations where he had no other choice but to trade hits. The two side’s health continued to deplete. Although health of Liang Fang’s Berserker was dropping faster, thinking of how his damage was increasing because of it, Liang Fang became more and more confident.

Liang Fang paid attention to Lord Grim’s health. From one half, to one third, to one fourth, to one fifth. And although his health was dropping faster, his attacks were becoming much stronger.

“Almost! Almost there!!” Liang Fang watched both of their health bars. Finally, when his health reached a certain point, Liang Fang’s expression greatly changed.

He furiously discovered that he could no longer trade hits!

He saw that if he hit Lord Grim another two times, he would be able to beat him. But the problem was, if he was hit one more time, then he would be the first one to fall.

“What bad luck!!” Liang Fang angrily threw his mouse.

“You must be tired. You’re still missing one more hit.” Immediately following, Liang Fang heard his opponent speak.

This guy!!!

So it wasn’t that his luck was bad, but rather because his opponent had calculated the end result, which was why he just stood there trading hits with Liang Fang. This type of judgement wasn’t something that Liang Fang didn’t want to make, but rather because he couldn’t make it. He didn’t know the stats of his opponent’s Silver Weapon. If it was just a normal weapon, he might have been able to make an approximate guess from the damage he took, but the problem was, this guy’s weapon kept on changing forms. Different forms did different amounts of damage. Moreover, unspecialized characters had a vast variety of skills. Of those 120 skills, who knew what level each of those skills were? There was simply no way of evaluating it. In the end, Liang Fang, who had gambled on his luck, lost to the opponent’s accurate calculations.

“Okay, next one.” Liang Fang lost this match and then exited the field. Ye Xiu typed it out to call for the next person.

This time, the next contestant knew what to do and directly went to fight against Tang Rou first. After a short moment, he handily beat Tang Rou and then went to look for Ye Xiu to do battle.

As a result, Tiny Herb’s team members all began to go through the same cycle. They first crushed the novice Soft Mist and then got crushed like novices by Ye Xiu.

The materials were depleted one after another. Plantago Seed could only watch heart-broken. Right now, his heart wasn’t aching because of those materials. Those materials were taken away by the team in any case, so he wasn’t accountable for them. What was making him so frightened was that of the team’s 11 players, 6 of them had already lost to Lord Grim. How could this guy be so terrifying?

What made Wang Jiexi gratified was that even though they kept on losing, the atmosphere of the team was extremely good. Apart from the team member, who was fighting with Lord Grim, the others had all taken off their headphones, watching the match while discussing it with their fellow teammates. Everyone was trying hard looking for a way to beat Lord Grim. They were listening to each other’s suggestions and looking for their own flaws. Every contestant that went up was given lots of encouragement by their teammates.

Unfortunately, even though it was like this, from Tiny Herb’s main roster to the reserve team, they were all beaten cleanly. No matter how many suggestions had been made, they still hadn’t seen any way of winning.

Eleven players. At this moment, ten players had already lost. Only Wang Jiexi hadn’t come out. Of course no one was happy that everyone had been defeated. But they weren’t mentally traumatized like what Wang Jiexi had been worrying about. Everyone was confronting their losses in a very rational manner.

“Big-eyed Wang, you’re not going to try?!” At this moment, Lord Grim suddenly sent out a message.

The entire Team Tiny Herb began sweating like mad.

Big-eyed Wang…… This really was a nickname their team captain once had. Wang Jiexi’s two eyes were of different sizes. But what was different from others was that instead of having one small eye and one normal eye, one eye was extremely normal while the other eye was extremely large.

As a result, when he first entered the Alliance, he was given the bad-sounding nickname “Big-eyed Wang” because of the abnormality he was born with. At that time, he was still a new novice, so the veterans and seniors all called him that. But now, Wang Jiexi was already Tiny Herb’s team captain. All of the team’s seniors had already retired. He was counted as the oldest on the team, so it had been a long time since that nickname came up.

This Ye Qiu, this Ye Qiu……

Tiny herb’s teammates were all very angry. But the more they thought about it, the more they calmed down. They couldn’t call the team captain by that nickname. But for seniors, they really did all call their captain by that nickname. And in the Alliance, what other player could be more of a senior than Ye Qiu?!

Chapter 142 – Magician

When Ye Xiu yelled “Big-eyed Wang”, even though Tiny Herb’s team members weren’t happy about it, there was nothing they could say. Everyone quietly looked at their captain’s face and saw that their captain wasn’t angry about it.

“Trash talk, trash talk!” Tiny Herb’s team members said to each other.

“Come!” Wang Jiexi typed out, but then hinted towards Tang Rou’s Soft Mist and they both left the room.

Tang Rou’s Soft Mist followed him out. Ye Xiu waited until there was nothing going on before sending Tang Rou a message: “Did you cry?”

“My face is covered with tears!” Tang Rou said.

“Wipe them away and continue fighting!” Ye Xiu said.

“Yes!” Tang Rou replied.

Ye Xiu knew that Tang Rou was fine. Just as expected, he had picked correctly. To this sister, this type of method couldn’t have fit her any better. Being defeated wouldn’t affect her at all. For this girl, the more she failed, the braver she would get. She was also smart. Ye Xiu was confident that having this Champion team train with her would definitely help her improve a lot.

As for the other player with great potential, Steamed Bun Invasion, Ye Xiu didn’t call out to him for now. Steamed Bun Invasion had a video game background. He wasn’t weak either, so once he started playing Glory, he had his own way of making decisions. To put it simply, he had his own unique style.

Nowadays, in the pro-scene, in order to achieve steadiness, a lot of the new players all received coaching, so their skill in strategy and tactics became more and more set in stone. There were few new players with their own unique styles. This was especially so for those players that had been trained by the Club from the start, such as Gao Yingjie, who was simply being molded into another Wang Jiexi.

This was why on this point, Steamed Bun Invasion was even better. Although his unique style might be a bit noobish and stupid right now, Ye Xiu was looking forward to how this unique style would develop.

Coming back on topic, Steamed Bun Invasion was still only an online friend and wasn’t like Tang Rou, who he could talk to in real life. As for his character, Ye Xiu couldn’t really figure him out. If there was a chance, it would be okay for him to try fighting with an expert. But to directly have him get mercilessly crushed one round after another like Tang Rou.. that was something he couldn’t place his luck on. Even Wang Jiexi was afraid that his team of pro-players would be negatively impacted by being mercilessly crushed. How could Ye Xiu dare to let Steamed Bun Invasion, who he didn’t really understand well enough, undergo a cleansing.

“They should be finished by now.” He once again made a prediction for Wang Jiexi and Tang Rou’s fight and felt that it was about time now. Sure enough, after a few seconds, the two players came back. Wang Jiexi didn’t say anything more and brought his Fiery Blaze directly up onto the field.

“Tsk tsk, you’ve become more merciful. If it was the you from before, then shouldn’t 30 seconds have probably been enough? Of course, now that you’re the captain, things have changed.” Ye Xiu said. Once Wang Jiexi’s character entered the field, the two could talk.

“Let’s start!” Wang Jiexi said.

“Do you want me to let you win this one? You guys have lost ten matches. If you happen to win this one, then it’d be a big boost to your team’s morale.” Ye Xiu said.

“But I don’t think I’ll lose for certain.” Wang Jiexi said.

“But you know it.” Ye Xiu dully said.

“Is there any point in trash talking…..” Wang Jiexi said.

“Yeah, there is. Just look at Huang Shaotian.” Ye Xiu said.

“……” Wang Jiexi didn’t have any words for a moment. With regards to trash talk, especially Huang Shaotian’s trash talk, it really was a pain for their Tiny Herb.

Tiny Herb was last season’s, Glory Professional Alliance’s, Season 7 Champions. Apart from that, they were also the Season 5 Champions. In between, they had their title as Champions taken away by Huang Shaotian in Season 6. If it wasn’t for this, Tiny Herb would have already become three-time Champions, creating a new era.

Unfortunately, on their road to becoming Champions, the team’s mentality wasn’t good enough. Under the pressure from their fans’ expectations, when they were faced with Huang Shaotian’s full-screen trash talk, everyone became somewhat unsteady. In that final deciding match, they lost, making them feel extremely depressed and unwilling to accept the result.

This was an experience that Tiny Herb hated to bring up. But now, Ye Xiu had brought it up…..

This was trash talk!

Wang Jiexi decided. He collected his thoughts and didn’t say anything more, completely entering a competitive state of mind.

Everyone in Team Tiny Herb was extremely nervous. Even though they had maintained a steady competitive state of mind the entire way through, losing from the beginning to the end really was very shameful, which was why everyone was hopeful that their captain would pull out a win. Also, wasn’t one of their little brothers from Herb Garden watching them? This person knew of their identities. If he saw them lose from the beginning to the end, then wouldn’t that turn their fan into a hater?

This “little brother” was Plantago Seed, Herb Garden’s tenth server guild leader. In front of the team’s pro-players, of course he would be treated as a little brother. Ten losses in a row! Plantago Seed really was speechless. Lord Grim: this player’s strength had been looked down on! This was a player that shouldn’t even have existed in the game!

Right now, it was God Jiexi’s turn. He was Team Tiny Herb’s last hope. Plantago Seed was even more nervous than anyone else. For the team he supported to lose so badly.. He was worried too!

Magic Missile!!

Wang Jiexi’s Witch was the first to move, suddenly sending out a Magic Missile.

Lord Grim sidestepped and dodged it. He raised the weapon in his hands. Ta ta ta, three consecutive sounds, three Anti-Tank Missiles.

He was once again using Tri-Shot and the three Anti-Tank Missiles formed a triangle. But this wouldn’t stop Wang Jiexi. With a move, his Fiery Blaze leaped onto his Broom and flew away, avoiding it.

However, that sort of unavoidable situation was something every Tiny Herb member had experienced.

If you said you were melee, then we would use our long-range advantage to deal with you. If you were long-ranged, then we would find a way to close in on you.

But unspecialized characters! If you had a long-range advantage, then he would just fire back at you. If you were melee, then he would fight you in close combat. It didn’t matter if you were melee or ranged, he simply didn’t care. It really was too shameless.

Fiery Blaze avoided the bullets. He waved his hands and blue dust was sprinkled onto his broom.

Frost Powder!!

It added some Ice Element Magic Damage to a Witch’s normal attacks for a duration of up to 20 seconds.

Ice Damage could directly cause a person to Freeze and could also cause a Slow effect like a Battle Mage’s Ice Chasers.

The additional damage from the Frost Powder wasn’t considered scary. And even if it could Slow, the chances were low. This skill was mostly used for extra damage.

After being sprinkled with Frost Powder, the Broom immediately turned gleaming blue. When Fiery Blaze rode on his broom, icy mist sprinkled out from the broom, making the scene look extremely beautiful.

In the blink of an eye, Fiery Blaze closed in. Unspecialized characters really were too shameless. They weren’t afraid of close combat or long-ranged fights. Lord Grim and Fiery Blaze began battling.

The flying broom still had ice crystals sprinkle out. If these hit you, then there wouldn’t be any damage. They were simply there for visual effects. Except under Wang Jiexi’s movements, his broom danced quicker and more rhythmically, so the ice crystals came out with a more steady rhythm, making him look relaxed and refreshed.

Looking at Lord Grim, his weapon continued to change and change. It would be like that for one second and then something else the next. In any case, his weapon would change forms and use an unexpected skill at an unexpected time. In the eyes of Team Tiny Herb, they didn’t have any good feelings towards it. There was only one word to describe what they were feeling: shameless.

Disperse Powder, Umbrella opened.

Magic Missile, Return Fire.

Shadow Cloak, Shadow Clone Technique.

The two fought against each other using their different skills. But no matter how it was looked at, the current Witch’s total of 7 skills couldn’t be compared to an unspecialized character’s 120 skills. Wang Jiexi paid close attention to what Ye Xiu had taught Tang Rou: keep as many skills in reserve as possible. He had to be even more careful, especially since his opponent had more skills than him. As a result, in this battle, Wang Jiexi mostly used his Broom’s movements and Broom Dance’s normal attacks to fight.

Broom Dance was a nickname for a move. It was a way of using normal attacks, connecting them together, making it look like a dance. It wasn’t an actual skill name. Wang Jiexi faced his opponent like this. But against his opponent’s hundreds of tricks, it didn’t need to be said that he lost out.

“Shameless, too shameless!”

Tiny Herb’s team members saw that their captain was playing outstandingly well, but he still wasn’t winning. They all felt that it wasn’t his fault he was losing, but completely because of the opponent’s OP class.

But the more Wang Jiexi fought, the faster he moved. Fiery Blaze’s flying became more and more crafty and his Broom Dance became more and more artful.

“Oh!” Ye Xiu felt this change and exclaimed.

And on Tiny Herb’s side, the expressions of the senior members, such as vice-captain Deng Fusheng, also changed.

Magician!!

This was Wang Jiexi’s Magician style.

Unimaginable flying along with completely unpredictable angles of attack. From this perspective, the Magician style was the same as an unspecialized character’s. It was to make it so that the opponent had no way of predicting the next move. But unspecialized characters did this through the way their class was set-up, while Wang Jiexi’s title of Magician was completely done through his knowledge, decision-making, and mechanics.

Even though there weren’t any skills, with just normal attacks and flying, Wang Jiexi’s Witch truly deserved to be called Magician. As the future inheritor, Gao Yingjie’s eyes grew wider and wider. Even he couldn’t predict what his captain’s Witch was going to do next and he could already be considered a senior among Witches.

Everyone in the team saw their captain’s transformation. Everyone was extremely excited, but stayed silent so that they wouldn’t disturb their captain’s playing. Everyone held their breath and clenched their fists, silently cheering their captain on.

As for Plantago Seed, all he felt was a blur. Dizziness was his only feeling.

And as for Tang Rou, who had fought with Wang Jiexi before, she hadn’t seen her opponent use this style of fighting. All she knew was that if he had fought in this way, she would have lost even faster.

The two fought at high speed, their health quickly dropping. Fiery Blaze moved up, down, left, right, and then spun around Lord Grim. Attack after attack after attack…..

Everyone watched, their hearts hanging in suspense, when suddenly, a bang exploded. The two looked as if they collided and then suddenly crashed down.

“You…..”

“Sigh, seeing how hard you’re fighting, I should give you some face!” Ye Xiu dully said.

Fiery Blaze. Lord Grim. The two characters crashed to the ground. But neither of them stood back up.

Chapter 143 – Unexpected Discovery

The two character’s health bars dropped to zero at the same time.

Of course this type of situation could occur. In an official match, the two characters that died at the same time would recover a fifth of their hp and fight again. As for in the Arena, that depended on what the players decided. The normal setting was that it would be considered a draw, where there would be no winner or loser.

When Ye Xiu created the room, besides setting up the Gambling, he didn’t touch anything else, so it was in the normal setting.

The practice room in Team Tiny Herb was in awesome silence. After a while, someone suddenly sighed: “That’s our captain!!”

The other team members immediately added as if they had woken up from a dream: “Yeah, yeah!”

But on Wang Jiexi’s face, there wasn’t any sort of happiness or anger on his face. He only let out a sigh and then took off his headphones.

The practice room immediately went silent.

A draw. Even though it was already an achievement that none of the other teammates were able to get, being happy about a draw shouldn’t be a Champion team’s attitude. As a result, everyone was gasping at their captain’s amazingness, but they weren’t showing any happiness, especially after they saw their captain’s somber expression.

“That’ll be all for today!” Wang Jiexi announced.

“Yes.” Everyone answered.

“In the future, every day, two players form a team. You’re all free to choose who you want to team up with. Then go contact Lord Grim and spar with him. This extra practice isn’t required by the Club, but I hope that everyone will do it and learn from it. I think everyone knows what type of person Ye Qiu is. His experience, his knowledge, and even his trash talk are all things that we can learn from him.” Wang Jiexi said.

“Yes.”

“Okay, everyone go to sleep! Don’t be late for tomorrow morning’s practice.” Wang Jiexi said.

The team members all logged out of the game and got up. They found their friends and left together. Some discovered that their captain was still in his seat and hadn’t moved. However, they weren’t meddlesome and didn’t question. After a short moment, the only person left in the practice room was Wang Jiexi.

Back in the game, since all of his challengers had gone offline, Ye Xiu saw that it looked like they weren’t going to keep fighting, so he closed the room. His screen jumped to the Arena selection screen. After Wang Jiexi exited out, he returned to outside the Arena’s entrance and saw that Lord Grim was currently talking with their Herb Garden’s Plantago Seed!

“It must have been hard. How many materials do you have left in your storeroom?” Ye Xiu asked this just as Wang Jiexi’s Fiery Blaze walked up.

Plantago Seed was obviously very gloomy and didn’t know how to respond. He suddenly saw God Jiexi’s character walk over and immediately stepped to the side subconsciously.

“Oh? You still haven’t left?” Ye Xiu saw him.

“Yeah.” Wang Jiexi answered.

“How was it? Did it boost your team’s morale?” Ye Xiu laughed.

“If you just directly let me win, wouldn’t that be even better?” Wang Jiexi said.

“I don’t want to lose either!” Ye Xiu said.

“Yeah, no one wants to lose.” Wang Jiexi said.

“Yeah, if I lose, then I lose materials.” Ye Xiu pointed out.

“…….” Wang Jiexi had never connected winning or losing and those materials together. He didn’t care whether they won or lost materials. But the person in front of him, who was supposed to be a God level player like himself and whose history was even grander than his, was haggling because of these tiny materials?

If it was earlier, when Wang Jiexi hadn’t yet seen Ye Xiu’s intentions, he would have thought that Ye Xiu had fallen and was at the end of his road. However, after seeing Ye Xiu training new players and pursuing materials, Wang Jiexi knew that such a feeling was too superficial.

“My teammates will come look for you every night.” Wang Jiexi said.

“Welcome, welcome. The rules will be the same as before.” Ye Xiu said.

“Plantago Seed. You should try to provide the materials as best as you can. I’ll contact you.” Wang Jiexi said.

“Oh……” Plantago Seed replied. The materials they had gotten were mainly for the Club and in the end, they were to help their Team. Right now, seeing that God Jiexi had spoken, Plantago Seed didn’t feel any heart aches. It’s not like the materials were his anyways. Except who exactly was this Lord Grim? Plantago Seed was even more curious now. Seeing how this person talked with God Jiexi, it seemed like they recognized each other, neither familiar nor new with each other, who was this person? Could he be……

“Okay. I’ll be leaving first then.” Wang Jiexi said.

“Really? Just like that? The dungeons will be refreshed in a bit. You’re not going to dungeon?” Ye Xiu said.

“I’ll be cheering you on.” Wang Jiexi said. How he could have the time for such a low-leveled dungeon?

“Go back and tell your teammates to level up well! I train for ten hours every day. If the gap between us grows too big, I won’t be responsible.” Ye Xiu said.

That really was a problem. Wang Jiexi didn’t reply. He thought about it and then went offline. They were a pro team. Leveling low-leveled accounts really was too much of a waste of time. It looked like they were going to need to find people to train the accounts for them.

Materials, leveling……. Busy with this and that. And in the end, all they wanted to do was lose to Lord Grim?

After Wang Jiexi collected his thoughts, he himself didn’t know whether to laugh or cry. And that wasn’t all. They were also being used as training partners! This Ye Qiu, business with him was simply a scam!

However, this time, besides finding a rare training partner, the unexpected discovery was that…… Wang Jiexi sat at the practice room. After a short moment of silence, he left.

The next day, the time to kill the BOSS came again. Wang Jiexi said the day before that only two players needed to come. But that night, Tiny Herb’s entire team gathered. Everyone was extremely positive. Wang Jiexi obviously wouldn’t scold them for having too many team members come, though it was quite unfortunate for Plantago Seed.

Plantago Seed had calculated the amount of materials they had given out yesterday from fighting with Lord Grim one round. If they continued to fight like that and Team Tiny Herb continued to lose and never win, their Herb Garden’s storeroom would only last four days. Even if he put in the revenue they’d get each day, it would only be five days at max.

This was only the new server and everything Lord Grim wanted were uncommon materials. This was Herb Garden too, yet they could only last for four or five days. If this was a guild set up by a normal player, they wouldn’t be able to last one round. Those types of guilds didn’t have any defined management department. The items from dungeons would be rolled for and then directly put into the player’s pocket. How could the guild earn any profit like that? Only those guilds with Clubs behind them, with their own set of management methods, had a fair-trade system where the players and guilds got what they needed from each other. In any case, players were there to play the game. They weren’t there to be laborers. How could they just give everything they found to the guild?

Plantago Seed once again saw that Team Tiny Herb’s entire roster had come. He really had no one to complain to. He could only gather the materials for them and pray that today they’d do a little better and not all lose.

On Ye Xiu’s side, Ye Xiu had come with Tang Rou. The rules were still the same as before. Tang Rou first and then Ye Xiu.

Yesterday, everyone had been focused on fighting, so they hadn’t yet added each other as friends. Today, they were more polite and added each other as friends. The members of Tiny Herb showed their proper respects to their senior as well. The atmosphere was very friendly.

While watching the fighting, Tang Rou, who had just lost, suddenly received a message. After opening it, she saw that it was from that Gunner called Fallen Angel: “Sister, watching these matches all the time can get boring. What do you say we go play for a few rounds?”

“Okay!” Tang Rou happily accepted. She followed Liu Fei out of the room. The two created a room and they fought. Tang Rou looked and she unexpectedly saw another person had followed them in to watch. She looked and recognized him, Fiery Blaze. Tang Rou understood that this person was probably their leader.

After the countdown, the two began fighting.

Tang Rou was even sadder than Tiny Herb yesterday. She had lost all eleven rounds. There wasn’t a shred of mercy from them either. Even though there were differences in skill between the members of Tiny Herb, it was still extremely easy for them to deal with Tang Rou. Of those eleven players, besides Qiao Yifan’s Ashen Moon, who she had fought with for a relatively long time, the other ten had all beaten her in around a minute. These guys had all been impatiently waiting to go fight with Lord Grim, so they weren’t polite at all with her.

Tang Rou knew that her current opponent was also a female. The day before yesterday, Ye Xiu had brought her and they had taught them a miserable lesson. But now that she was dueling, she was being completely controlled. This type of feeling was like when she had first fought with Ye Xiu.

1 minute 47 seconds!

This was how long it took for her to fall. Compared to yesterday, she had lasted for 20 more seconds. She remembered this very clearly because she had recordings for every match yesterday. In the second half of the night, after clearing all the dungeons, Ye Xiu had analyzed every match for her. Tang Rou had been waiting to try again today.

Just a moment ago, from a time perspective, she had improved. However, after fighting her, everyone immediately took off to fight with Ye Xiu. And Ye Xiu didn’t beat them as fast as they were beating her, so she always had to wait a long time, which was why Tang Rou was extremely grateful that this gunner actively sought to fight her.

Unfortunately, she still lost. However, with Ye Xiu’s analysis from yesterday, Tang Rou had noticed a lot of her problems now. Regretfully, hindsight was 20/20. After another round, she suddenly reacted in time: Oh, I shouldn’t have done that that time. It was clear that putting theory into practice wasn’t easy to do.

“Again?” Liu Fei smiled while asking.

“Of course.” Tang Rou didn’t hesitate and faced the challenge.

Another round. 1 minutes 50 seconds passed. There wasn’t much of a difference between last time.

“Again!” This time, Tang Rou asked to fight.

1 minute 44 seconds.

“You play pretty well.” Liu Fei said.

Pity? Tang Rou was helpless. She didn’t like to be pitied. That was the type of praise she wanted to hear when she won.

“It’s my turn now. I’ll be going first.” Liu Fei said.

“Oh…….” Tang Rou replied. But Liu Fei had already hastily left the room, making it so that her words simply faded away in an empty field. Tang Rou suddenly felt extremely lost. This type of feeling of being completely ignored felt absolutely terrible.

“You really do play pretty well.” A voice suddenly echoed out. Tang Rou turned her camera and saw that that Fiery Blaze had unexpectedly entered the field.

“Could I ask you what your name is? I’m talking about your real name.” Wang Jiexi said.

“Tang Rou.”

“Oh, how about we go for a round?” Wang Jiexi said.

“Sure!” This opponent was the strongest among them. For him to actually want to fight her, that was something Tang Rou found somewhat unexpected.

Chapter 144 – Back and Forth

The two began fighting. What made Tang Rou even more astonished was that her opponent was actually going all out. He was actually using the style he had used yesterday in the fight with Ye Xiu. Unpredictable and extremely fast, his swift movements alone already made it hard for Tang Rou.

And these swift movements naturally meant that the camera had to be adjusted quickly. For new players like Tang Rou, who didn’t yet have enough experience, this was a dead end. Wang Jiexi’s ever-changing combat style made it so that Tang Rou had no way of resisting. This was the difference between a top-tier God and a new player. No suspense. No openings. Defeat in 27 seconds!

This was the time that Ye Xiu had estimated.

Tang Rou finally realized how amazing the fight between Fiery Blaze and Lord Grim was.

Extremely strong. So strong that it made others speechless.

At this moment, Tang Rou recalled the scene where Ye Xiu and her had first fought. Repeatedly fighting against such a strong opponent was completely meaningless. The gap between the two sides was way too wide, so much so that she had no way of knowing what went wrong.

Tang Rou silently sat in the field, quietly looking at her Soft Mist.

The world really is large. She once thought that Glory was so simple. But from Ye Xiu and now these players, who could easily deal with her, she now understood that these were the true experts. She pitied her past self, who, after helping Chen Guo beat those unbeatable opponents, believed herself to be extremely amazing. Now that she looked at it, it really felt like was looking at the sky from the bottom of a well.

“Do you want to go again?” Her opponent’s voice suddenly interrupted her train of thought.

“Again?” Tang Rou stared blankly.

“Yeah.”

“There’s no point, right? The gap’s too wide.” Tang Rou said.

“The gap is only temporary. You have a lot of potential!” Wang Jiexi said.

“Thank you.” Tang Rou chuckled. It didn’t matter if her opponent was only doing it to comfort her, it was still a polite compliment, so she wouldn’t be impolite back.

“Do you have any interest in playing in the Pro Alliance?” Wang Jiexi suddenly said.

“Pro Alliance?”Tang Rou stared blankly.

“Right, the Pro Alliance.”

“Oh, so you guys were pro players!” Tang Rou said.

“Correct. We’re Team Tiny Herb. If you really are interested, then right now I want to give you a serious invite. An invite for you to come to our Club for a trial.” Even though Wang Jiexi was the team captain, he still didn’t have the authority to manage the Club’s players. No matter how good of a talent he saw, he could only do his best and give a recommendation to the Club. The Club might listen attentively to his recommendation, but the power to recruit and kick players wasn’t his. No Club’s team captain had that authority.

Team Tiny Herb? What was that? Tang Rou was puzzled for a bit. Her knowledge of the Pro Alliance was extremely shallow. The last match she saw was the first match she had completely watched from start to finish. She felt that she might have heard of Tiny Herb’s name, but she truly couldn’t think of where she had heard it from. She obviously knew that asking such a question was extremely impolite, so she calmly replied: “Thank you, but I don’t think there’s a need to.”

“What?” Wang Jiexi stared blankly. He hadn’t thought that this girl would actually reply so calmly like that. She had even refused too. Pro Alliance! These two words were already enough to make any Glory fan go mad. Entering the Pro Alliance was something many Glory players could only dream of. And to be personally invited by the Champion Team Tiny Herb’s captain, that was something that had never happened before. But in the first time that it had happened, it had been rejected neither softly nor strongly.

For a while, Wang Jiexi had no idea how to respond to Tang Rou’s reply.

“I’m very happy with the way things are right now, so I don’t want that to change.” Tang Rou at least explained her reasoning.

“What ….. type of life are you living?”

“A little sister at the Internet Cafe.” Tang Rou laughed. Although she didn’t mean to listen in on other people’s conversations, she had the title that Ye Xiu gave her yesterday.

“Internet Cafe waitress…..” Wang Jiexi was even more speechless. How could this type of life compare to a pro-player?

‘Okay. You’ve already beaten me, so you can go and duel him. I’ll be in this room, so have your other teammates come!” Tang Rou said.

“You…….. fighting like this with us. For what purpose?” Wang Jiexi avoided saying the reality that she was being repeatedly crushed by them.

“In order to improve, so I can be a better player!” Tang Rou said.

“And after you become a better player?” Wang Jiexi asked.

“After? Even better then. What else is after?” Tang Rou said.

This girl’s thinking wasn’t in the same line as his……. Wang Jiexi felt hard-pressed. The girl in front of him had excellent mental toughness. Her hand speed and mechanical skill weren’t bad either. He could even say that her hardware was all there, but her software was still lacking. Ye Qiu’s perception really was incredible. She was a truly hard to come by talent. For their team’s young talent Gao Yingjie, his mechanical skill was there and his skill level was constantly rising, but his mental toughness was entirely lacking.

Mental toughness. This was a large problem not only for Glory, but other eSports too.

This was all because the average age of eSports pro-players was relatively low. For example, youths such as Gao Yingjie could already enter the pro-scene, but they hadn’t completely matured yet and their mentality was still far from mature adults. Even for those top eSports players, most of them were around 20 years old. Impatience among eSports players was extremely prominent.

Wang Jiexi had already noticed this girl called Tang Rou the other day. She had lost ten times in a row. In addition, she had been beaten every time without a shred of mercy. But in her eleventh match against him, she was still the same as before, calm and unhurried. He didn’t see any sign of irritation or discouragement. All he saw from her was effort, effort, and more effort.

Wang Jiexi was amazed. Today, when he privately asked his teammates, no one had a big impression of her and no one had thought of recording their fights against her. Only under Wang Jiexi’s urge did some teammates just barely recall their fights with her, confirming his judgement towards Tang Rou.

She was definitely a promising talent!

Ye Qiu was clearly aware of this and had even begun training her. But right now, Ye Qiu was an already retired pro-player and could only act as a temporary tutor. If he was able to officially invite her over, wouldn’t he be able to snatch her?

Who knew that when he tried to invite her, she would actually reply calmly in such a way. Wasn’t such stubbornness a bit too excessive?

“Can….. you reconsider it? If you change your mind, come find me at any time.” At this moment, Wang Jiexi didn’t want to force her. He found that he was a bit too hot-headed this time. He should have at least understood the other side’s background first.

But honestly speaking, Wang Jiexi couldn’t be blamed. Who would think that a Glory player wouldn’t respond to being invited by a pro team? Even if this player was new to the game.

“I will. Thank you.” Tang Rou was still as polite as ever.

Wang Jiexi was just about to leave, when someone suddenly entered the room. After Liu Fei lost, Tiny Herb’s next team member arrived.

Wang Jiexi looked and went back into the spectator’s seats to see this match.

“Go ahead, Yifan.” Wang Jiexi sent a message.

The player who had just arrived was Qiao Yifan. Seeing his captain in the room, he felt baffled. After hearing his command, he immediately entered the field. He greeted Tang Rou and then the two began fighting.

For this match, Wang Jiexi looked a bit absent-minded. Although Qiao Yifan was an official team member of Tiny Herb, Wang Jiexi was more focused on Tang Rou.

For a new player to be able to compete with a pro-player and even make it difficult for the pro-player, that made Wang Jiexi sigh with praise. At the same time, he couldn’t help but feel unsatisfied with Qiao Yifan.

This team member was without a doubt the weakest player of the team. It could even be said that his skill level wasn’t enough to be a member of a Champion team. Even if he went to the Alliance’s weakest team, it would still be difficult to say if he could be a part of the main roster.

He had been in the team for so long. The others had all grown, but he hadn’t shown the slightest signs of improvement. He always looked like one of those people who always had their hands and feet bound together, constantly looking backwards. If he never looked ahead, what prospects did he have?

Even though he didn’t have the power over the players’ positions as a team captain, his suggestions still held quite a lot of weight in the Club. Wang Jiexi already couldn’t see any value in keeping Qiao Yifan in the team. He also knew that the kid was having a hard time meshing with the team. Perhaps if he wasn’t in a Champion team and in some other no-pressure mid-tier team, he might be able to make some progress?

The match had been fought for nearly three minutes and still hadn’t ended yet. Tiny Herb’s next team member impatiently ran over to see what was going on. In the end, Qiao Yifan still won. Although he was a small character that was ignored, for a new player like Tang Rou, he was still a strong existence.

Seeing how his captain had watched the entire match, Qiao Yifan felt terrified. He knew that the way he had played definitely wasn’t good. Just from the amount of time it took him, who in the team needed even close to three minutes to finish the opponent?

“Yifan, hurry up!” The team member, who had just arrived, urged him. Qiao Yifan was slow here, but it would be a quick fight against Lord Grim. After urging Qiao Yifan out, the team member immediately began fighting with Tang Rou, in order to hurry up and fight Lord Grim.

In Ye Xiu’s room, Qiao Yifan silently entered. Besides Gao Yingjie, who cheered him on, no one else gave any sort of encouragement to him. It looked like everyone had already determined that he didn’t belong in the team and had already stopped considering him as a member.

Qiao Yifan had gotten used to this long ago. He simply sucked in a deep breath and then entered the field.

“Oh, it’s you!” On the field, Ye Xiu greeted Qiao Yifan.

“Ah…… me…….” Qiao Yifan didn’t know what to say.

It’s you…… This implied that his opponent acknowledged him. When had he ever felt like he existed? And it was in God Ye Qiu’s eyes too. He was the same as captain, an almost godly person!

“You’re the one in your team that uses an Assassin, right?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Yeah.”

“Has anyone ever suggested that you switch classes?” Ye Xiu said.

“Never.”

“What class did you originally play?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Originally…..” That was so long ago. What class did he play before being on Tiny Herb? Qiao Yifan wasn’t able to recall. He only knew that after he joined, the Club tossed a retired player’s Assassin account card to him. And from then on, he used an Assassin. He had never went out on stage in any match before. Besides Gao Yingjie, no other team member ever asked to train with him. The tech department never made any self-made equipment for an Assassin to use. He truly became an Assassin, lonely and invisible.

“The Assassin isn’t a class that lets you use your full potential.” Ye Xiu said.

“Ah? Potential?” Qiao Yifan felt that this was a new word to him.

“Try out a Ghostblade! A Phantom Demon that mainly uses Phantom Ghosts to support the team.” Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 145 – A Bit of Courage is Needed

Ghostblades, one of the four Swordsman sub-classes. They were Swordsmen that controlled Ghosts to fight. Depending on how a player chose his skills, Ghostblades could be divided into two types.

The first type used skills that buffed their attacks. They gave up some of their Phantom Ghosts, in order to achieve the highest attack. They were commonly referred to as Sword Demons.

The other type released their Phantom Ghosts in order to set up a powerful boundary that buffed allies who were in it. They were referred to as Phantom Demons.

The reason there were two types of Ghostblades was because their skill points were limited. No matter how it was said, it wasn’t possible to level every skill to the max level, so players had to choose which skills to prioritize. Ghostblades were considered relatively extreme. After choosing which skills to prioritize, the Ghostblade would take shape as one of two completely different types. Of course, there would certainly be players who chose to take the middle ground and leveled skills from both types. Choosing the middle ground was something which was commonly seen among normal players. However, in the pro-scene, players sought after the most effective route. For pro Ghostblades, if they weren’t Sword Demons, then they were Phantom Demons. There were very few who took the middle ground.

Of these two types, Sword Demons were simpler. They could both attack and defend and act independently. They could be considered a relatively balanced type. As for Phantom Demons, their strengths and weaknesses were very distinct. It was true that a large amount of high-leveled Phantom Ghost boundaries could greatly buff the Ghostblade’s combat strength. However, the boundary set up covered a limited area, which meant that once the Phantom Demon left the boundary, he would be useless.

This weakness wasn’t too obvious against NPCs, but was much more glaring in the Arena. The opponent didn’t need to fight in your boundaries. The opponent could simply wait until your boundaries disappeared. Long-ranged classes could even attack from outside the boundaries. In a 1v1 PK, Phantom Ghosts required more skill and knowledge to use. There were many normal players who even believed that Phantom Demons had no way of dueling against other classes.

From its development to its current state, Sword Demons were the most mainstream Ghostblades. The majority of players would choose to be a Sword Demon. Because the actions that could be done by Phantom Demons were numerous and complex and because the boundaries only covered a limited area, the amount of players who chose to be Phantom Demons grew fewer and fewer. But in these elite teams, Phantom Demons had their niche. But since the Phantom Ghost boundaries of two Phantom Demons didn’t overlap, there were only one or two per team.

For example, the Champion Tiny Herb team had a Phantom Demon. Zhou Yebai’s Ghostblade Rangoon Creeper was a Phantom Demon. He had appeared in an official match before providing the team with more choices and possible tactics.

“Phantom Demon…..” Qiao Yifan muttered to himself. Perhaps it was because no one had specially instructed him for a long time, but once he heard this suggestion, Qiao Yifan immediately accepted it. Even more so, he had been instructed by Ye Qiu, the Glory textbook, who even Wang Jiexi wasn’t as knowledgeable as.

“Correct, your view over the overall situation is very good and your ability to coordinate is very high, so a Phantom Demon suits you very well!” Ye Xiu said.

“But…… but……” Qiao Yifan said two “buts”, but wasn’t able to say anything past that. He had too much he wanted to say and didn’t know where to start.

Switch classes? How could he have the qualifications to do that? Even if he switched to a Phantom Demon, their team already had Zhou Yebai. How could they give Zhou Yebai’s Phantom Demon to him?

Start from scratch? That was even an more unlikely option. The pro-level Assassin he was currently using was already neglected by the Club. A completely new Phantom Demon would be neglected even more.

More importantly, his position in the club was falling lower and lower. After this season was over, his contract would expire. With how he was currently doing in the club, he doubted that the Club would renew his contract. And ever since he began in the pro-scene, he had always been invisible. The only thing he had going for him was the title “Champion team member”. With just this, he might be able to interest a few small Clubs. But if he started learning a new class now, with less than half a year left, would he be able to pass the entry tests?

If he lost his job as a pro-player, what was the point of changing to a more suitable class?

“Sigh……” In the end, Qiao Yifan could only sigh. At this moment, neither side moved. The spectators couldn’t hear what the two were saying. They didn’t know what they were doing. And how could they be polite with Qiao Yifan? They immediately began spamming messages telling him to hurry up.

Qiao Yifan didn’t dare delay any longer. But seeing that Lord Grim didn’t seem to have any intent on starting. He could only helplessly say: “Senior, I’m going to start now.” After finishing this, he began attacking.

Naturally, Ye Xiu handled Qiao Yifan easily. Qiao Yifan was quickly defeated. And sure enough, looking at the time, Qiao Yifan lost the fastest, just like how he took the longest to beat Tang Rou.

“Muster up some courage!”

Qiao Yifan heard Ye Xiu call this out when he left the field.

Courage?

Qiao Yifan silently sat in front of his computer, watching, as the next team member rushed up to face Lord Grim. The two sides began fighting without any polite greetings. The team members around him watched the battle while discussing it amongst each other. Qiao Yifan looked to his side, but Gao Yingjie wasn’t there. Looking to the other side, he saw that Gao Yingjie had been called over by the captain, who seemed to be talking to him.

“How lucky…… to be instructed by a god-level player like captain so often……” Qiao Yifan silently thought. He suddenly wanted to cry. He and Gao Yingjie had entered the team at the same time. They were the same age. One of them received the seniors’ love and affection. One of them became the seniors’ servant.

“Phantom Demon…….” Qiao Yifan couldn’t help but think of the suggestion that that God had made and that small bit of encouragement from him.

Maybe he really did need a bit more courage!

But……. courage wasn’t something that would come just from him saying it. After thinking about it for awhile, Qiao Yifan still felt scared.

Might as well just try it! He finally made this decision. He wouldn’t completely give up the Assassin he was using, but from now on, he would try a Phantom Demon out. Maybe there’ll be a difference?

Just this thought made Qiao Yifan feel extremely happy.

“Yifan, what are you smiling at?” At this moment, Gao Yingjie had returned to his seat. When he came, he saw his good friend with a foolish smile on his face. He looked distracted as if he wasn’t watching the match.

“Oh, it’s nothing.” Qiao Yifan immediately got rid of his smile.

That night, Team Tiny Herb’s record hadn’t changed. They all lost. Except this time, their captain Wang Jiexi hadn’t come out. However, after the day before’s match between the two, no one thought that their captain was afraid of losing. In short, their captain often did something unexpected just like when he suddenly pulled everyone into the game for training. Team Tiny Herb’s members were already used to this, so they simply listened to his commands without guessing what he was up to.

“How was today?” In Happy Internet Cafe, after finishing up with the great battle, Ye Xiu went to ask Tang Rou. The circumstances between the two were completely different. One of them had won every round. One of them had lost every round. Complete opposites.

“It was a bit better than yesterday.” Tang Rou said.

“Amazing!” Ye Xiu praised.

“But……. today, their Fiery Blaze invited me over to do some training or something!” Tang Rou said.

“Really?” Ye Xiu didn’t seem very surprised: “He’s got good eyes. You really do have a lot of potential. Did you accept?”

“I didn’t. I’ve never thought of being a pro-player.” Tang Rou said.

“No matter what, don’t let our boss hear you say that or she’ll choke you to death.” Ye Xiu said.

After thinking about it for awhile, Tang Rou nodded her head: “You’re right.”

“Ha ha, are you going to dungeon tonight?”

“Of course.”

“I’ll see you at 12.”

“Okay.”

After the two finished talking, they went back to their own business. Ye Xiu got ready to switch shifts, while Tang Rou went back to her seat and continued to play.

After 11, the Internet Cafe immediately changed scenes. The noisiness during the peak hours had passed and the place had quieted down a lot.

“Is the Pro Alliance really that fun?”

After Ye Xiu sat down at the receptionist desk, he logged into the game as Lord Grim and then received a message from Soft Mist.

“Is Glory fun?” Ye Xiu replied.

“I guess I could count it as fun.” Tang Rou said.

“Then the Pro Alliance is the same.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh……”

“But with your personality, being a pro-player really suits you well. Don’t you like challenges?” Ye Xiu said.

“Then what about you? Why aren’t you playing in the Pro Alliance?” Tang Rou asked.

“I’ve already played in it. I’m tired right now, so I’m taking a break.” Ye Xiu said.

“Liar.” Tang Rou wasn’t stupid. How could “taking a break” mean running to an Internet Cafe and becoming a manager?

“I’ll be going back later.” Ye Xiu said.

“When?” Tang Rou asked.

“That’s a bit difficult to say……” Ye Xiu replied.

Tang Rou didn’t say anything more. The two quietly played. At 12, the dungeons refreshed. They partied up and did the same as they usually did.

The next day was the same. Except this time, Team Tiny Herb lost even more miserably than last time. There was no way they could improve so much after two or three days. But Ye Xiu on the other hand had gathered quite a lot of materials from the past two days. His Thousand Chance Umbrella had been upgraded all around once again. Every form was now Level 25. This was clearly more efficient than clearing dungeon records. Even better was that this could be done again and again, while dungeon records could only be set once.

Plantago Seed was still busily gathering the materials on the list, when he suddenly received another list of materials. Plantago Seed saw it and directly coughed up blood. This time, the materials were mainly from Level 30-35 areas. Currently, the Three Great Guild’s elite teams had only just hit Level 30 and were only just starting to challenge those areas. How would they be able to gather these materials?

Seeing how fast their resources were being depleted, let alone Herb Garden, even if all of the tenth server guilds gathered everything together, it still wouldn’t be enough. The vast majority of the players were Level 25. The Level 28 players such as Lord Grim were only a bit lower than the big guild’s elite teams. Compared to new players, besides eating and sleeping, Ye Xiu and Tang Rou played non-stop, so there was no way they would fall behind other players. They were already among the craziest of players, who only had one person playing on one account.

No materials. But Wang Jiexi didn’t panic. They were pro-players. Losing and winning were their jobs. They couldn’t just keep on fighting non-stop. They had to analyze too.

As a result, during the days where they had no more materials, Team Tiny Herb spent the night analyzing all of the recordings they had gathered together.

Ye Xiu naturally wasn’t concerned. If no one came to look for him, then he’d continue leveling. After a few days, they hit Level 30. During this period of time, Glory’s 22nd match of the season took place. Team Excellent Era finally realized their fan’s hopes and made a beautiful turnaround match with 9 points to 1.

In comparison, Team Tiny Herb came out with the opposite. Against a mid-tier team, they only took three points.

Chapter 146 – Too Smart

The entire Team Tiny Herb was low on morale. In the news conference after the match, Captain Wang Jiexi revealed to the media that Team Tiny Herb was currently undergoing a special secret training, which affected their team’s condition. But with Tiny Herb’s current dominant position, Wang Jiexi believed that this loss was completely worth it. Tiny Herb only had one goal: Champions. Their record in the regular matches didn’t mean much to them.

This statement wasn’t enough for the public, especially the part about the special secret training. No one knew whether that was the truth or a lie. And their record in the regular matches wasn’t as insignificant as Wang Jiexi had said. Their spot in the playoffs was already set, so they didn’t need worry about it. But their position on the standings affected their prices for the Alliance’s broadcasts and bonuses from their sponsors. The higher a team was on the standings, the higher the bonuses they earned.

As for the playoffs, a playoff team naturally received extra revenue from broadcast rights in the playoffs. Every time the team advanced, they would gain another bonus. The connection between a team’s standings and their benefits was obvious. In addition, a more outstanding record carried with it the obvious benefits to a team’s reputation, publicity, and fans, these types of intangible benefits.

However, all in all, Wang Jiexi’s statement was well-spoken. The match was just a single page in the book and nothing more. Earlier, after Excellent Era made an unfathomable mistake that cost them the match, the newly-appointed team captain Sun Xiang would only say things like he didn’t know or he wasn’t sure to the news conference, brushing away questions as if they were like annoying flies. The difference between his handling of the situation was far from the experienced Wang Jiexi.

Two days after the matches ended, Team Tiny Herb once again gathered together in Glory’s tenth server and called for Lord Grim to come to the Arena.

Following the principle that customers were above all else, Ye Xiu called for Tang Rou to come over. In the past few days, Tang Rou had gone to the Arena to try a few battles. But how could these normal players be her opponents? They were defeated dully and tastelessly. She would occasionally train with Ye Xiu for a few rounds, making Tang Rou feel as if her efforts in the past few days had been pointless. Her fights with Ye Xiu made her feel like she hadn’t made any progress. It was the same as when she first fought him. She lost in every way she could imagine.

In addition, she fought with Steamed Bun Invasion several times. Tang Rou’s chances of winning were a bit better. Steamed Bun Invasion really was a player that fluctuated. He would sometimes completely crush Tang Rou, but would also sometimes get completely crushed. Using Ye Xiu’s words, Steamed Bun Invasion was a player that didn’t care about theory or strategy and completely relied on his intuition. He would sometimes be like a blind cat trying to catch a dead mouse and somehow win. But he would also sometimes be unable to catch the dead mouse. And in that scenario, he became a low-leveled failure and lost extremely miserably.

Ye Xiu had originally wanted Tiny Herb to also train with Steamed Bun Invasion, but who would have thought that Steamed Bun Invasion wouldn’t come today. He had no choice but to have just him and Tang Rou come.

After several busy days, Plantago Seed finally gathered a few of the materials Tiny Herb wanted.

The rules were still the same as before. They had to fight with Tang Rou first, which ended quickly. They then looked for Ye Xiu, who clearly felt that the difficulty had increased. In these past few days, these guys clearly hadn’t been idling around. They had already figured out a few new strategies created specially against him. In addition, their accounts had been leveled and were now Level 30. With more skills and more tactical options, the advantages of an unspecialized character slowly declined as their levels increased.

In other words, unspecialized characters were already completed at Level 20. Besides higher stats and stronger skills, the way they fought wouldn’t change too much with more levels. On the other hand, other classes would have new skills they could learn, so the way they fought became more and more rich. Even though the amount of skills they could learn in the end still couldn’t be compared to unspecialized characters, the gap became less obvious. This situation had already been confirmed by unspecialized character during their era. At that time, they confirmed that as the level cap continued to increased, unspecialized characters would eventually become trash.

They didn’t have to wait long for the end of that era. Once the Level 50 Awakening came out, unspecialized characters directly became trash. The subject of unspecialized characters completely faded away after that. Some of the research that was being conducted on them were also thrown out. Ye Xiu, who picked up this forgotten class, had to do some proper tests too. He had confidence in the class at the Level 50 stage of the game. But afterwards, at Level 60 and 70, he could only rely on his own experiences later to test the class. All in all, he needed to test it. Many of the theories Ye Xiu had come up with needed to be tried when the time came.

The characters of the pro-players in front of him had reached a new stage. Everyone had also studied and learned from their past defeats, so Ye Xiu needed to be more focused while facing them.

This time, there would be a few small twists and turns in every match. Team Tiny Herb finally stopped getting completely crushed. Everyone’s fighting spirit was extremely high and all showed their desire to take down their opponent. However, even with all of their research, Team Tiny Herb still lost every match. The later rounds seemed to be more hopeful for them, but it wasn’t something they could feel happy about. Don’t forget that they were taking turns fighting. Ten players fought ten consecutive rounds and Ye Xiu could no longer be as relaxed as before. Consecutive rounds would obviously take a toll on his spirit and strength.

Actually, when Wang Jiexi had told everyone to form two player groups to train, he was taking this point into account. He was worried that Ye Xiu’s condition would decline and affect their training. In the first two days, they weren’t familiar with unspecialized characters, so they lost tragically and couldn’t see that Ye Xiu’s condition declined with each round. But now that they had a specific plan going in, this sort of situation really did appear, making the training for the later team members not as optimal.

Wang Jiexi only watched Ye Xiu’s matches and never went up. But he did run over to fight with Tang Rou for a few rounds. If someone entered the room without knowing the situation, they would definitely think that he was trying to seduce her.

“Miss Tang, you’ve improved quite a lot over the week!” Wang Jiexi wasn’t flattering her. Tang Rou had talent and with someone guiding her, it’d be strange if she didn’t improve. But….. to have God Ye Qiu coaching her one on one, that really was way, way, way too lucky.

“Thank you.” Tang Rou had improved and was developing similarly to how Team Tiny Herb was doing against Ye Xiu. She was losing, but making things more difficult for the opponent. But against Wang Jiexi, Tang Rou still felt powerless. She understood that this person was more skilled than even those experts by a thread, just like Ye Xiu. He was an existence that she couldn’t touch for now.

“Miss Tang have you considered the topic I raised last time?” Wang Jiexi asked after a few rounds.

“Oh…… I don’t think I’ll be changing my mind right now!” Tang Rou said.

“Really? Well then I’ll still be hoping that you will!” Wang Jiexi said.

“If you’re looking for pro-players, why don’t you guys ask Lord Grim?” Tang Rou suddenly asked curiously. Ye Xiu’s skill level was too obvious. If the other side wanted to invite someone, why wouldn’t they want a talent that was already there?

“Him? He’s a retired pro-player. According to the rules, he’ll need at least a year in order to join again.” Wang Jiexi said.

“Oh, so it’s like that…… I really don’t know anything about the pro-scene!” Tang Rou said.

“And……. he’s already fairly old. If he came back, then he’d only be able to play for a year or two more at most. But for you, Little Tang, you’re still young right? Your future is limitless!” Wang Jiexi said.

“Oh? How do you know my age?” Tang Rou said.

“I could roughly tell from the way you play. Your energy, drive, and attitude. With just one look, I can tell that you’re at the golden age for a pro-player. You should probably be around 20 years old. I hope I didn’t guess wrong.” Wang Jiexi said.

“Woah, you guessed very accurately.” Tang Rou said.

“If you were a normal person, then this age would be a bit late for you to enter the pro-scene. But Miss Tang, you have a strong foundation. If you had formal training with experience from official matches, I’m convinced that you’d quickly grow into a genuine pro-player.”

“Then what about me right now?” Tang Rou asked.

“Right now? Forgive me for my bluntness, but Miss Tang, you’re still only relying on your reaction time and mechanics to fight. Even though you’ve gained a bit of knowledge, you still need a lot of real battles to turn that knowledge into habit. This needs formal pro-level training!” Wang Jiexi said.

“So it’s like this.” Tang Rou replied.

“That’s why I suggest that if Miss Tang is interested, then the earlier you enter the pro-scene the better. Playing the game is too much of a waste of your talent.” Wang Jiexi said.

“Okay, I’ll consider it. Thank you.” Tang Rou replied as calmly as ever.

Wang Jiexi didn’t say anything more. The other side had once again ended the talks calmly. He went back and then watched all of the matches against Lord Grim. he found that Ye Xiu’s condition had clearly deteriorated over time. Wang Jiexi stopped the members that wanted to keep trying, ending that day’s special practice.

“You must be tired.” Wang Jiexi expressed his sympathies to Ye Xiu outside of the Arena entrance.

“It wasn’t tiring at all. Another ten rounds?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Ha ha, I’ll pass!” Wang Jiexi laughed, “I’ll properly arrange everything next time, so it won’t be as tiring.”

“You’re too polite.” Ye Xiu said.

“I should be. Well then, see you next time.” Wang Jiexi said.

“See you later.”

“What a difficult guy!” After seeing them log out, Ye Xiu expressed his regrets to Tang Rou.

“What do you mean?”

“I wanted to win a few more materials, but once this guy saw that I was growing tired, he immediately stopped the training. He doesn’t care about the materials, but he doesn’t want to waste time on me when I’m growing tired!” Ye Xiu said.

“Really, this guy. He’s a bit too smart!” Tang Rou said.

“I really have grown old. I’m not like you. I get tired after ten consecutive rounds.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh? Really? It looked to me like you didn’t have any fighting spirit. You tidied those three-legged cats quite handily. If I were you, I’d also feel bored. It’s not that you’re tired, but rather that you’re bored, right?” Tang Rou said.

“You have a good point. But you should be the one feeling bored going against people that aren’t your opponents.” Ye Xiu said.

“I just don’t believe that someone who can stay focused playing for twelve hours straight will tire after only ten rounds. That doesn’t make sense.” Tang Rou said.

“Yeah…… Fine, you have a point. But there’s still one thing that I need to stress. Those guys aren’t three-legged cats, they’re last year’s Champions.” Ye Xiu said.

“Three-legged cat champions?” Tang Rou said.

“That sounds a lot better.” Ye Xiu laughed.

The two casually chatted, when a system message suddenly popped up. Ye Xiu opened it and looked: The player One Inch Ash wants to add you as a friend. Accept or decline?

Chapter 147 – Difficult Decision

Ever since he made a name for himself with the dungeon records, especially once the final Boneyard record hadn’t been broken again, more and more players began adding Lord Grim as their friend. He had friends from big guilds, small guilds, and privately too.

The big guilds were naturally like Blue Brook Guild and Tyrannical Ambition, who wanted Ye Xiu to be a long-term member of their guild. Small guilds talked about personal development and how he would have more chances at obtaining a promotion than in those big guilds. Noobs might believe them, but Ye Xiu wouldn’t. The private players wanted to build a personal relationship with him, in hopes that he would help them. He moved around among all of these different players. Some were declined, some were pushed away, some were ignored.

Ye Xiu conveniently looked at One Inch Ash’s info. He was a Level 23 Ghostblade. Ye Xiu’s heart swayed and recalled that Assassin Ashen Moon from Team Tiny Herb.

He accepted the friend request and then immediately received a message from the other side: “Senior, I’m Qiao Yifan, that Assassin Ashen Moon from Team Tiny Herb.”

So it really was him. Ye Xiu thought, while replying: “Oh, so it’s you!”

“Yeah, I want to try out a Phantom Demon.”

“Why are you leveling a new account?” Ye Xiu didn’t understand. Each of the guilds had numerous other max-leveled accounts besides the main ones used for the matches. They usually had all of the classes and their different types. If the player wanted one, then he could easily get one. These accounts weren’t armed with luxury equipment, so they didn’t cost much.

Qiao Yifan was in an embarrassingly low position in Team Tiny Herb. As a stranger, how could Ye Xiu have known that?

However, among those in the Alliance, each team knew which teams had which accounts. Ye Xiu had even played in half of the season. Assassin…… Ye Xiu didn’t recall of such a class ever coming out in the season for Tiny Herb. Due to this, he made a rough guess that this Assassin wasn’t in a high position among the players in the Club.

Of course, he could also be a new player in training and wasn’t yet mature enough to come out on stage. But having fought with him before, Ye Xiu could see that Qiao Yifan’s Assassin really was quite ordinary. He couldn’t really see much potential from him. It was only because he saw that this player’s features was clearly suitable to a Phantom Demon that he suggested it. Apart from that, he didn’t have any other motives.

“Um……. I was hoping that I could get some guidance from senior.” Qiao Yifan said.

Ye Xiu stared blankly. He had been a part of the pro-scene for so many years. What type of situation hadn’t he experienced before? At this moment, even though he hadn’t asked and even though Qiao Yifan hadn’t said anything, from how Qiao Yifan said things, he could already guess the other side’s situation.

“How long have you played Glory?” Ye Xiu asked.

“One year.” Qiao Yifan replied.

“Oh.” It wasn’t easy being a novice, Ye Xiu sighed. Ye Xiu had heard that there was a player called Gao Yingjie, who was reputed to be Vaccaria’s successor. He knew that every time such a talent appeared, the talent would inadvertently kill off many of his comrades’ light. For example, Qiao Yifan wasn’t someone who didn’t have any talent. It was just that compared to the talent standing beside him, he appeared rather gray and dark. It was quite sad.

Thinking of all this, Ye Xiu understood that for a player on the edge like Qiao Yifan, choosing a major decision such as changing classes was extremely difficult. To put it seriously, it could practically be considered a final gamble for the player’s career. However, the person who had to make such a decision was just a young teenager.

The choice that the kid chose was in between. He would continued practicing his Assassin with the Club, while secretly training his Phantom Demon to see if he really did have potential. If he continued to stay on the edge for a long time, then the kid would take a serious hit to his confidence. This could already be seen from his extremely careful and cautious style. It was only until yesterday did Ye Xiu remind him to have more courage. To have already gotten to this step in a day could already be considered quite good.

Seeing how his senior God simply answered with a “Oh”, Qiao Yifan felt very nervous. Just as he was trying to figure out what God meant, he received a message.

“You should have some understanding of Phantom Demons, right? This class takes a while to complete. You have to get to at least Level 40 before the Phantom Demon’s strengths begin to appear. A Phantom Demon’s true practice starts then.” Ye Xiu replied with a message.

“Yeah, I know.” Qiao Yifan answered. He was a pro-player after all. There was no way he wouldn’t know at least a little about every class. Any class’s strengths, skills, their uses, etc. These were all basic knowledge for any pro-player.

“Because of this, there isn’t any way of practicing how to use a Phantom Demon in battle right now. I recommend that you find someone to level this account for you, while you do some research on the theories. For example, you could go look at the recordings for Team Void’s matches and study them.” Ye Xiu sent a message.

Team Void. Qiao Yifan obviously knew of this team. Although they weren’t top-tier, they often made it into the playoffs. Team Void’s captain Li Xuan used the account Sobbing Ghost, which was reputed as the number one Phantom Demon in Glory. Team Void was the only team to use the Phantom Demon as their core. It could be considered as one of their unique features.

“Even though Li Xuan’s Sobbing Ghost is the core of Team Void, it’s never his other teammates coordinating with his Sobbing Ghost’s Phantom Ghosts. Watch how Li Xuan deciphers the battles and then uses Phantom Ghosts to create the win for his team.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh, understood.”

“Give the account card to someone else to level for you. Once you reach my level, you can come with me and my party to get a feel for it.” Ye Xiu said.

“Thank you!! Thank you senior!!” Qiao Yifan was extremely happy. When Ye Xiu told him to study recordings, he had felt somewhat at a loss. But now that he knew that there was still a chance for God to coach him, he immediately turned indescribably happy.

Qiao Yifan began doing what Ye Xiu had suggested at once and gathered all sorts of recordings to study and learn from. He also went out to go look for someone to level his account. He signed up for the option that would level his character the fastest and then waited for it to catch up to Lord Grim’s level.

On Ye Xiu’s side, while Qiao Yifan went offline, he on the other hand was still chatting with some other players.

These players were Seven Fields and his group. At this moment, they had just made a difficult decision.

Ever since they had witnessed brother expert’s strength, they had always known that there was no way their poor guild and their puny resources had a place for a God like brother expert. But unfortunately, the rest of the members of the guild didn’t think like that. After seeing Seven Fields and his group go up on TV and break a record with Lord Grim, they were convinced that the relationship between Lord Grim and them wasn’t shallow. They were always nagging for Seven Fields and his group to pull him in.

Seven Fields and the others used an excuse to evade the subject again and again, yet their guild’s members kept on nagging, especially their guild leader, who was very unsatisfied with how they kept evading them.

Those guild members could be ignored, but a portion of the guild’s members such as their guild leader were their old friends who came together from the old server. Seven Fields and the others won glory from being together with brother expert, but the other old friends were still the same as before, struggling under the big guilds’ feet. That was why Seven Fields and the others all felt a bit embarrassed.

But to invite brother expert to join their guild? No matter how one thought about it, that could only be a joke. Seven Fields and the other truly weren’t able to say that, however they truly couldn’t stand their friends in their guild constantly nagging at them. Finally, they made the difficult decision to recommend their guild leader friend to brother expert and let him talk with brother expert directly.

At this moment, Seven Fields and Ye Xiu were discussing about this, asking to bring a guild friend over to play together.

How could Ye Xiu have any opinion about this? In the leveling area, Ye Xiu met with Seven Field’s guild leader friend.

“Hi, I’m Maple Tree, Full Moon Guild’s guild leader!” Seven Field’s friend, the tenth server guild leader Maple Tree, proudly introduced himself. Seven Fields and the others escaped far away with their cheeks streaming with tears. Full Moon Guild’s guild leader? What status was that?

Seven Fields and the others might have once thought differently, but after witnessing brother expert fight, their view of the world grew boundless. The Three Great Guilds became like floating clouds in their eyes and those medium and small guilds became clouds that couldn’t even float. And now, their own guild leader had just presented his status proudly, putting his status, which others thought of as very shameful, as extremely honorable, making him look even more shameful.

“Oh, hello hello. So you’re all friends huh.” Ye Xiu casually greeted him.

It wasn’t midnight yet, so Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon were there, as well as Drifting Water and Sunset Clouds. These two were normal players. They would only play everyday after dinner and as a result, the gaps between their levels gradually widened. They hadn’t had the chance to create a dungeon record with brother expert either, so they were quite lonely.

“Yeah, we’ve known each other since way back. When I think about our time in the Heavenly Domain……” Maple Tree chattered about their guild’s magnificent history.

After setting up his Full Moon Guild’s great image with Ye Xiu, Maple Tree changed the topic of the discussion: “Now that I think about it, with your strength, why haven’t you joined a guild yet?”

“Oh, guilds…… I don’t want to join one!” Ye Xiu said.

“Is it because you haven’t found a suitable one yet? Actually, you might as well just join our Full Moon Guild. Our Full Moon Guild has quite a long history in Glory and one of the oldest guilds out there. Although we can’t compare with a few guilds, but I’m sure you understand that those big guilds all have pro Clubs supporting him, so our guild made up of normal players have no way of comparing with them. But apart from these guilds with pros behind them, our Full Moon Guild is very famous.” Maple Tree said.

“He’s trying to pull him in! He really is trying to pull in brother expert!” Seven Fields said to the others with his face covered in tears, “I was wrong. I should pulled him along at midnight so we could dungeon together and have him witness brother expert’s strength. If that had been done, I’m sure he’d be able to recognize the difference between heaven and earth.”

“That….. are you sure?” Sunset Clouds said.

“In my opinion, Maple Tree’s biggest feature is that he doesn’t know the difference between heaven and earth.” Drifting Water said.

“That’s why having him see brother expert’s strength would only make him want to pull him in even more.”

“Correct. He grew up reading fairy tales. A poor boy chasing a beautiful princess and what not aren’t things that’ll stop him.

“I know. That’s why I kept evading him. But those other guild members are just too annoying. I had no choice but to hope that brother expert wouldn’t mind……” Seven Fields said.

Chapter 148 – Four Scarlet Moon Parts

Seven Fields and the others didn’t have it easy either. This situation was like if you knew a beautiful girl, but had a vulgar, wolf-like friend that wouldn’t stop bothering you to introduce him. No matter what you did, you couldn’t block him or dissuade him and in the end, your only option was to ask the beautiful girl if you could bring your friend along.

It obviously wouldn’t be good to just let him go and do whatever he wanted, but Seven Fields and the others weren’t worried about this. The “beautiful girl” in front of them definitely wouldn’t be bullied around by the wolf. They were only worried that after the beautiful girl beat the wolf to death, they would also get beaten down……. After all, the person they were talking about wasn’t a beautiful little girl, but rather brother expert, a person who had already shocked the world by the time he reached Level 30.

They silently listened as Maple Tree tried to persuade him with all his might. Seven Fields and others were half angry and half laughing. In their view, Maple Tree’s strategy was at the level of a kidnapper waving a goldfish at a small child in order to abduct the child. Except this child was brother expert. It was like trying to kill a strong bull with a cheap knife. How could you not laugh at that?

Even worse, this guy was grinning from ear to ear, not aware of how stupid he looked!

Seven Fields and the others really wished they could see what brother expert’s expression was. Hopefully he hadn’t already smashed his computer to bits yet!

Maple Tree talked and talked about in-game life, economy, and even how wealthy the big guilds were. The way Maple Tree explained all of the little details was as if he was a matchless professional. At this moment, after listening to him for a long time, Ye Xiu finally replied very calmly: “If you’re looking for me to set a dungeon record, then there’s a fee!”

Long live brother expert!

Seven Fields and the others nearly threw their headphones when they heard this. They discovered that there was no need to worry for brother expert. That goldfish scheme wasn’t anything in front of brother expert.

“Oh? A fee! That’s easy, how much money?” Maple Tree said.

“I don’t want money. I want materials, uncommon materials or other things I need.” Ye Xiu laughed.

“Oh, so it’s like that. What do you want?” Maple Tree asked.

“That depends on what dungeon record you want set.” Ye Xiu said.

“Desolate Land.” Maple Tree said. He himself was Level 30 and could be considered at the top among the player population. He obviously couldn’t compare to those big guilds whose elite teams were being leveled 24/7. Normal players didn’t have that sort of advantage.

“Desolate Land…….” Ye Xiu was still a bit hesitant. This was because he had already gotten all of the materials he needed from this dungeon from Team Tiny Herb. His Thousand Chance Umbrella had already reached Level 25. For the next stage, he needed all sorts of materials and equipment from Level 30-40. No matter how fast Full Moon Guild’s players leveled, they would only be a bit ahead of Ye Xiu. They had just reached Level 30 today, so they definitely wouldn’t be able to pay up many Level 30-40 items.

“Hm, how about four parts of the Scarlet Moon set?” Ye Xiu thought about it before giving out the reply.

“This……. shouldn’t be a problem……” Maple Tree was a bit hesitant too. Clearly, for guilds like theirs that were created only for fun, the guild leader didn’t have as much power over the guild like those Three Great Guilds. Most guild leaders didn’t have any sort of leadership aura. On the contrary, they were more like public servants who made great efforts with little benefits.

However, since they were in the new server with lots of new players, veterans like him still had some power in front of those little noobs. Unfortunately, it seemed like this small amount of power wasn’t enough to let him casually take away someone’s equipment and give it out for public use.

The Scarlet Moon set was a Level 30 Battle Mage set.

In Glory, armor was split into head, shoulder, chest, waist, legs, shoes, these six parts. The Scarlet Moon set was one of the most common sets, which consisted of six parts of armour . Every two parts would give additional attributes.

Along with equipment such as Lord Grim’s Vampire Cloak, there were also rings, necklaces, and badges, which were classified as accessories. In Glory, armor usually gave Physical Defense, while accessories gave Magic Defense. Unlike armor, accessories weren’t categorized into types such as cloth, leather, heavy, plate. They could be worn by any class. Accessories were chosen depending on the player’s needs.

For Level 30 players, they didn’t need to be picky with accessories yet, but a full class set of equipment could improve their strengths significantly. With the current state of Glory, players often said that at Level 30, they would begin seeking class sets. Privileged players should switch every 5 Levels, while those weren’t should switch every 10 levels. Those who didn’t pursue these goals were players who didn’t know how to play or had been carried the entire way through.

Ye Xiu was unspecialized, so the value of sets was limited. This was because the additional stats from a set often increased levels of class skills. Since those skills were often Level 20 and up skills, they weren’t useful to Lord Grim, so wearing sets wasn’t worth it. The Scarlet Moon Battle Mage set he requested was obviously for Tang Rou. This girl was one of the main forces in the dungeon-setting team, but her current set of equipment was quite sad to look at.

Ye Xiu and them were a friendly team when they dungeoned. No one fought over equipment. However, there was no way they could match the resources of an organized guild. It was actually quite difficult for them to gather a set of ideal equipment since they could only run a dungeon a limited amount of times each day.

Now that they were Level 30. If they didn’t pursue class sets, then they would fall relatively far behind compared to the big guild’s elite teams, which was quite unfavorable for dungeon-setting. This type of difference couldn’t be completely made up for with skill. These types of low-leveled dungeons also had a limited skill cap. And worse, if Liu Hao wouldn’t let things go, who knew when he might suddenly annoy him again?

“Four Scarlet Moon parts. Is there a problem?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Ah, don’t rush…….” It was clear that Maple Tree didn’t have the sort of authority like the Three Great Guild’s guild leaders. The amount of resources he could allocate was limited, especially for equipment. They had probably all been rolled for in the dungeons and taken away. Give the equipment to the guild? In their sort of guild, such an option didn’t exist..

Seven Fields and the others were quite astonished on the other hand. They didn’t care about how their guild leader was busy trying to get the equipment. They asked in complete disbelief: “Brother expert, you’re going to help our guild set a record?”

“There’s a fee. It’s always been like that.” Ye Xiu said.

“Four Scarlet Moon parts…….” Seven Fields and the others were all veterans, so they knew of their value. When Ye Xiu had helped the Three Great Guilds set a record, his demands were impossible for them. He had even asked for Orange weapons. In comparison to those demands, four parts of the Scarlet Moon set were nothing. The Scarlet Moon set was actually only a set of Blue Equipment.

“Ha ha, I wanted an Orange weapon, but there’s no way your guild could have that, no?” Ye Xiu said.

“We don’t…….” Seven Fields said.

“That’s why a bit less is fine.” Ye Xiu said.

“Why do you need four parts? Why not the entire set?” Seven Fields asked.

“It looks to me like that’s the guild you guys are in!” Ye Xiu said.

“Brother expert, you don’t need to give us face! Really!” Seven Fields was very sincere.

“No way!” Ye Xiu laughed, “The record set in exchange for only four parts won’t be too high.”

“Shameless!!” Sleeping Moon blurted out.

“It’s only fair.” Ye Xiu said, “Even if you guys gave me all six parts, the record still won’t be much higher.”

“Why?” Seven Fields asked.

“See, Soft Mist’s weapon is still only Level 25. Not just her, but Steamed Bun too…… without level 30 Purple weapons and a class set, there’s no way we can set the record at its limit!” Ye Xiu said.

“Then what you’re saying is that……. the record you’re going to set will be broken eventually?” Seven Fields asked.

“For normal players, the current record is already their limit. When we break this record, there shouldn’t be anyone who can beat it.” Ye Xiu said.

“Shouldn’t?”

“Unless some bored players come.” Ye Xiu said.

“What type of players?” Seven Fields and the others were becoming more and more confused.

“Experts!” Ye Xiu continued to make them confused: Experts? How could an expert setting a record be “bored”?

Maple Tree was speaking well and speaking badly to players in the guild. He was asking this and then urging that and explaining the importance of their guild’s development, future, and goals, until finally, he gathered together four parts of the Scarlet Moon set. Of course, these four parts were from four different players. And those four players actually didn’t have the entire set, so losing one wasn’t too heartbreaking.

“I’m going to get the equipment. Let’s meet again at 12!” Maple Tree said as he ran off.

“From the looks of it, he’s planning on going with them?” Seven Fields said.

“Clearly.” Sunset Clouds nodded his head.

“Well, he is the guild leader. Let him go!” Drifting Water said.

“How many spots will there be?” Sleeping Moon asked.

“Usually one?” Seven Fields said while asking Ye Xiu: “Brother expert, how many open spots do you have on your team?”

“Probably one…… who’s going to be coming from your guild?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Our guild leader most likely.” Seven Fields said.

“Oh, that should be fine.” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

“What wouldn’t be fine?” Drifting Water asked.

Ye Xiu looked at his class: “Non-DPS classes wouldn’t be too convenient.”

Tears began pouring out from Drifting Water. He was a Knight, an MT (Main Tank), so he obviously wasn’t considered a DPS class, which probably meant that he would never be able to go up on TV with brother expert’s record-setting team.

“Our condolences.” The others all gave their sympathies.

Maple Tree went and finally came back with the Scarlet Moon parts. Sunset Clouds and Drifting Water took their leave first. They were clearly quite busy people. They didn’t play the game for very long every day and probably weren’t able to completely use up all of their dungeon entries each day.

“Steamed Bun! Steamed Bun!” Ye Xiu began calling for his troops.

“Steamed Bun is here.”

“Tonight we’ll be setting a dungeon record.” Ye Xiu said.

“TV! I like it. I’ll be coming!” Steamed Bun Invasion typed happily.

Near midnight, without needing Ye Xiu to call over, Su Mucheng came online on time. At the same time, the guilds leaders from all the big guilds came. The first ones to contact him were Blue River and Cold Night, his two former customers. Their messages came at practically the same time: “Brother! Can you set the record for Desolate Land tonight?”

“Long-term substitution will begin tonight?”

“Brother, you’re Level 30 huh. Have you thought over long-term substitution?”

The messages didn’t only come from those two. These days, Ye Xiu was entangled with many of the big guilds. What level Lord Grim was and how many dungeon entries he had left; they were sometimes even more clear on those than Ye Xiu himself.

Right now, Lord Grim was Level 30 and his dungeon entries had been refreshed. Everyone guessed that it was the day that the Desolate Lands record would be broken. Which guild would the record fall under? That was what everyone was fighting for. But winning one time wasn’t what they wanted. Every big guild wanted a stable substitution team. If today, the record fell under their guild’s name and then the next day, the record would be set by the same exact players under a different guild’s name, then that wouldn’t look good at all for them.

Ye Xiu wasn’t in a rush with all of these messages. He slowly typed out a reply for every one of them: “Tonight, I’ll be helping Full Moon Guild set the dungeon record.”

Chapter 149 – Bidding War

Full Moon Guild?

At least half of the guild leaders had no knowledge of this guild’s name. To them, the only guilds that they were familiar with were the guilds with Clubs behind them. Those were the only guilds that they recognized as adversaries. Of course, there were some that had heard of this name before. But they definitely knew that this wasn’t a guild with a Club behind it. It was only a guild created by normal players and could be considered an ordinary guild. How could this type of guild be able to snatch Lord Grim away from the encirclement of all of their big-named guilds.

All of the guild leaders were in disbelief. They each asked around to find what type of trick Full Moon Guild had pulled off.

But this turned out to be quite difficult. Guilds like Full Moon Guild clearly didn’t have any spies planted in them from big guilds. They had simply never been an opponent for them. As a result, they didn’t have any inside information and could only see if there was someone who knew a member of that guild.

There actually were a few results that came out of asking around like this. After all, Full Moon Guild wasn’t like them. When Maple Tree went to gather the parts for the Scarlet Moon set, he had shouted for it in the guild channel and used the strength of the masses to pressure four Battle Mages into giving away one of their Scarlet Moon parts. Everyone in the guild knew of this. There wasn’t any need to hide it, so when a friend came to ask, they immediately gave a reply.

Quickly, all of the guild leaders from the big guilds found about the price tag of four Scarlet Moon parts and they all violently coughed up blood.

Four Scarlet Moon parts!

What type of fee was that! For these guilds, such a price was basically giving it to them for free. Most of the equipment dropped from Level 30 dungeons were Blue equipment sets. For something so trivial like four parts of the Scarlet Moon set, all they had to was open their mouth and they’d be able to obtain them. For the elite players from their big guilds, they could easily gather a full set of class-specific equipment for several teams.

And with their guild’s complete set-up, if they needed a Scarlet Moon set, then the guild would by all means compensate for the provider’s losses. As a result, they could easily get the four parts with just a few words. Not like Maple Tree, who was like a child asking for his grandpa, desperately trying to get the four parts.

In short, this sort of condition was too easy for these guilds. How could they let Full Moon Guild get away with such a steal? The guild leaders were no longer calm. Many of them began sending Lord Grim more enticing offers.

“Brother, how about a full Scarlet Moon set?”

“A Scarlet Moon set AND a Level 30 Purple Bright Lance!”

“Two Scarlet Moon sets! One for you and another one for free!”

The offers were endless. In any case, they were all better than four parts of a Scarlet Moon set. Ye Xiu didn’t rush and patiently replied back to each of them. Among all of these, Blue River and Cold Night surprisingly hadn’t come barking.

These two had faced against Ye Xiu more than once, so they had a certain level of understanding. Four parts of a Scarlet Moon set weren’t his bargaining chips for setting a dungeon record.

Lord Grim’s starting prices had one feature. Even though they made you feel somewhat heartbroken, they wouldn’t make you feel that it wasn’t worth it. He clearly had an exceptional understanding of the game and could accurately measure his value. According to his style, four sets should be right! Four parts? What did that mean? What was his goal?

Blue River and Cold Night were both puzzling over this.

And even though the big guilds operated quite similarly, who among them knew about one another well? Although they all had spies among them, the new server had just opened, so the core of the guild was still made up of the veterans from the old servers. The newly recruited low-leveled accounts couldn’t be trusted too much. All of the guild leaders knew this.

However, even with all of their precautions, there were still a few spies among their upper-ranks. These sort of spies weren’t new recruits from the new server. They were already spies in the old server and had signed up to pioneer in the new server. These types of people were already among the guild’s elites in the new servers and were quite powerful.

At this moment, only these deep spies would be able to tell their guild information on other guild’s movements. But there weren’t many of these types of spies. On Blue River’s side, he only had one spy with such authority. That spy was in Guild Samsara.

Guild Samsara was the guild backed by Club Samsara. Team Samsara was a mighty team in the recent years. Their team’s ace Zhou Zekai was currently Glory’s most popular player. Quite a few experts and fans expected a great future for Team Samsara. Thus, they were a strong opponent for them. They would not only be enemies in the Alliance, but in the game too.

“Samsara has offered four class-specific sets!!” The spy messaged Blue River.

“With the way he does things, this should be the limit.” Blue River said.

“It should be. But this time, he rejected it…….” The spy said.

“His reason?” Blue River asked.

“He already agreed that he’d help Full Moon Guild.” The spy said.

“Tch! He obviously knew that we would ask for him to set a dungeon record at level 30. How could he agree to Full Moon Guild’s four Scarlet Moon parts?” Blue River said.

“Do you think he has an ulterior motive?”

“Definitely.” Blue River said.

“I heard that Misty Castle and Blossom Valley have also offered the same price.”

‘How do you know?” This information wasn’t something that could be easily found. The only reason Blue River could find it was because of the spy he had in Samsara Guild.

“Our guild leader went to ask……”

Blue River felt relieved. Even though all of the big guilds competed against each other, they all knew each other. In this type of situation, where they were all unsure, they would sometimes turn their enemies into friends and exchange information. For example, that guy Plantago Seed frequently did this. But Team Tiny Herb and Team Blue Rain were absolutely mortal enemies, which naturally translated in-game too.

“Our guild leader is getting ready to offer a step higher.” The spy suddenly said.

“Oh? How much?”

“Five class-specific sets!”

Blue River stared blankly, when he suddenly had an idea.

Was this what he was trying to do? By deliberately reducing the price and having others offer higher, he would eventually win out. By provoking the guilds to fight over him, he immediately raised his status. For this type of situation, once the price got up, it’d be difficult to bring it down, unless he wasn’t able to complete the employer’s task.

Samsara had taken the first step. Their information partners Blossom Valley and Misty Castle had probably followed closely too. However, these guild leaders weren’t hostile spies. Their exchanges of information were probably only half-truths. Blue River guessed that there was no way of accurately knowing. He only knew that five class-specific sets had already exceeded Lord Grim’s previously set price.

This move was brilliant! Blue River sighed and understood Lord Grim’s intentions. Blue River felt he could go over and negotiate with Lord Grim. Just as he was about to send a message, his spy suddenly typed: “D*mn, rejected again!”

“Rejected, still? What is he trying to do? For what purpose? What else does he want?” Blue River was also startled. Five class-specific sets, this was already enough to make them grind their teeth and cough up blood, but he still wasn’t satisfied? Is really trying to make all of the big guilds go mad?

“He didn’t ask for anything. He said the same thing….. he already agreed to help Full Moon Guild.”

“How could it be like that……. What are you guys going to do next?” Blue River asked.

“I don’t know…… The guild leader is furiously cursing right now!

Of course, Samsara’s tenth server guild leader Lonely Drink would be angry. Four class-specific sets was very fair and the offer should have been accepted. But the way Lord Grim had rejected it? Now that was fast. The reply came just a second after he sent his offer. Lonely Drink was convinced that guy had set-up an automatic reply! How else could he reply so quickly?

He randomly tested his theory. It looked like it wasn’t an automatic reply. This guy really wasn’t considering their offer.

Lonely Drink wasn’t stupid. After having his offer rejected, he was even faster than Blue River in thinking that this time, Lord Grim really was trying to eat them up like a giant lion. This guy saw that all of the guilds were fighting over him right now.

Lonely Drink didn’t say a word for now and ran over to contact the other guild leaders.

Those guys were also angry and cursing at Lord Grim. They all looked like they wanted to kill someone. Lonely Drink obviously wasn’t puzzled by this. These guys all acted as if they hated Lord Grim. If it was someone else, then he might have actually believed that they wouldn’t try to raise the bid again. But Lonely Drink knew that these guild leaders were the same as him, and had already decided to raise the bid once again. Because of this, he had hoped that the competitors would give up this theatrical act.

“Hmph, I’m not playing anymore!!” Lonely Drink finally threw it out, also in order to trick them, and then made a bid with five class-specific sets.

This price increase was quite large. Seeing that the other guild leaders didn’t have any intention of backing down, Lonely Drink also decided to raise it. He felt that his offer wasn’t enough to be accepted by Lord Grim, but he’d at least be able to make the other side feel his sincerity and then they could maybe seriously discuss it?

Who would have thought that he’d be rejected instantly? This time Lonely Drink wasn’t acting anymore and really was furious. If he wasn’t even considering his offer, then did this guy want him to just directly gift him his guild?

Lonely Drink wasn’t happy. He was extremely unhappy. His first few rejections had made him feel somewhat puzzled, but the current him was no longer trying to obtain Lord Grim’s services, he was now trying to fight with Lord Grim to see how deep he really was.

As a result, Lonely Drink sent another message: “Eight class-specific sets. What do you think? You should be happy now, right?!”

Lonely Drink hadn’t negotiated with anyone and was sent out as a gamble. You little punk, are you still trying to cheat me? Fine, I’ll make an unimaginable offer that’ll turn you stupid and make you speechless.

This was the type of goal that the current Lonely Drink was going for!

In the end, not even a second had passed, and his chat box had already flickered. It was the same result as before, as if his offer hadn’t been considered at all. Lonely Drink almost didn’t want to open it. He already felt a bad premonition. But, in the end, he looked at it.

“I’ve already agreed to help Full Moon Guild!”

“F*CK!!!!” These words again! It was these exact words every single time. Lonely Drink now knew that this person hadn’t set up an automatic reply. He was f*cking copying and pasting!

“You you you!! What the heck do you want!!!” Lonely Drink almost felt his heart roar.

“I’m going to dungeon. Let’s talk later.” Not even a second. A reply.

Chapter 150 – So Nervous He Became a Noob

Lonely Drink wasn’t the only victim. Although the other guilds may not have been as impulsive as him and directly offer eight class-specific sets like he had, but for such a ridiculous offer to be rejected in less than a second? How could the other guild leaders even try to compete? The rejected guild leaders were no longer faking it now and were furiously cursing non-stop. Unlike Lonely Drink, they were cursing and complaining particularly about how black Lord Grim’s heart was. Even Lonely Drink’s ridiculous offer had been rejected. After calming down, Lonely Drink began thinking like how Blue River had thought initially: What ulterior motives did this Lord Grim have?

“Hey, do you think this guy has some ulterior motive this time?” At this moment, a different two guild leaders began discussing, Cold Night and Blue River.

These two players hadn’t joined the great bidding war and had been quietly observing from the sides for any changes. Blue River had another perspective he could look at through the lens of the spy at Guild Samsara. Cold Night suddenly asked him this question. Blue River immediately guessed that Tyrannical Ambition wasn’t as simple as he had thought. He was afraid that their guild also had some sort of trump card planted in another guild.

Compared to the other guild leaders, these two were undoubtedly the most calm and rational among those in the bidding war. Their line of thoughts were the closest together, which was why Cold Night had ran over to discuss the situation with Blue River.

“I originally thought that he was going to use this as a way to raise his status, but with the way things have turned out, I don’t think that’s the case……” Blue River said.

“I found information on Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon, who are often with him. They are both from this Full Moon Guild and they seem to be old acquaintances of his.” Cold Night said.

“That might not be it. When everyone was still in beginner village, it was reported that this player called Sleeping Moon had been KSed by Lord Grim. He then started spamming curses at Lord Grim outside of the dungeon. Only after that did they get together.” Blue River recalled.

“So there was something like this!” Cold Night had begun paying attention to Lord Grim slightly later than Blue River had, so he didn’t know that such an event had happened.

“Yeah.”

“But it doesn’t matter what happened because they’re now friends. Or perhaps it’s just a one time trick.” Cold Night said.

“If it’s like that……” If it was because of their friendship, then Blue River would be extremely sad. He had once thought of using such a trick, but never went through with it. If such a trick had been successfully carried out by Full Moon Guild, a guild that they hadn’t even put in their eyes, then he would feel extremely defeated.

“Either way, it looks like Desolate Land’s record has fallen into Full Moon Guild’s hands.” Cold Night said.

“Yeah…..” Blue River didn’t doubt Lord Grim’s strength one bit.

Desolate Land.

The Level 28-30 dungeon was located in a deserted castle in the Desolate Land leveling area. A group of tyrannical bandits had made the castle their temporary home and as a result, became a dungeon.

Starting from Level 28, Ye Xiu and the other had ran the dungeon several times. However, now that they had a new member Maple Tree joining their team, in order to assimilate this Sharpshooter into their team, their strategy naturally had to be adjusted.

With a normal player in their party, they might suddenly have a few more problems come up. But with a pro God like Ye Xiu, given a random class combination, he could easily come up with the most suitable strategy for it. How could such a simple issue like having a normal player be difficult for him?

“This run will only be for experimental purposes. We’ll be adjusting our strategy based on Maple Tree.” Ye Xiu said to everyone after entering Desolate Land.

“Ha ha ha! Relax! I’ve done this dungeon who knows how many times. I’m extremely familiar with it.” Maple Tree boldly said.

“Oh really! Then we’ll be starting now. I’ll be leading!” Ye Xiu said.

“No problem! Lead away!” Maple Tree said.

“Steamed Bun, 8 o’clock. Soft Mist, 10 o’clock. Cleansing Mist, pull the enemies ahead at the bend. Maple Tree go to the stone window on the right. Attack whatever I attack.”

“Wait, wait, wait. What type of strategy is this?” Maple Tree was dumbstruck. Steamed Bun Invasion had two bandits at 8 o’clock. Soft Mist had two thieves at 10 o’clock. And Cleansing Mist had four “enemies ahead at the bend”, who were gathered around playing cards. They were going to be pulled already? And for him, the stone window on the right…… there were two bandits drinking over there! How could he get past them without alarming those two NPCs?

“If we don’t use this strategy, then I don’t think we’ll be able to break the dungeon record.” Ye Xiu said.

Just from equipment, their team couldn’t compare to the current record holders Blue Brook Guild. That five man team had class-specific sets plus Level 30 Purple weapons for each member. Their damage output would be much higher than their team’s, which was how they were able to achieve the current 30:45:66 record. The team with the second fastest record also had equipment on another level than theirs. The difference between the second fastest and the fastest record was miniscule. This indeed was the record’s limit in Desolate Land for normal players.

If Ye Xiu’s team used the normal strategy, then they definitely wouldn’t be able to break the record. If they were going to break it, then they had to fully utilize their team’s advantage in skill. Just like for the record at Frost Forest, where Ye Xiu had relied on his own superiority in skill, in order to carry out a One Wave Rush strategy that wasn’t possible for normal players and set a new record. If they followed how normal players cleared the dungeon, then there wouldn’t be any difference between a God and a normal player and the record obviously wouldn’t be broken.

“You’re going to break it like this? Are you looking to die?” Maple Tree was very noisy.

“Ha ha, just do as I say. I’ll explain things as we go. Everyone, forward.” Ye Xiu said. The other three had already rushed up to do their task, while Maple Tree was still staring at those two bandits drinking: “How do I get to that stone window?”

“Aerial Fire.” Ye Xiu said.

“Those two bandits…..”

“They’ll be gone soon.” Ye Xiu said, while his Lord Grim rushed up. His battle lance sweeped across, hitting two thieves at 1 o’clock. He then turned around and “bang bang” two shots rang out, alarming those two drinking bandits. The bandits threw the alcohol bottles in their hands at Lord Grim and rushed at him.

“You’re pulling four monsters at once?” Maple Tree was astonished. When he brought his team in, there would be a total of eight NPCs around them and they would only pull them out two by two. But this team was different. Two players each pulled two monsters. Lord Grim pulled four monsters and not only that, but he wanted that Launcher to pull four monsters too. Like this, they pulled twelve NPCs total. Maple Tree almost had the urge to leave the dungeon.

“Are you still not going up? If we were setting the record, then you’ve already wasted time.” Ye Xiu said, while his hands moved nonstop. Lord Grim handled the four elite monsters with ease.

Maple Tree stupidly ran towards the window, but his camera was on Lord Grim the entire time, and nearly crashed into the window before stopping in time.

“Use Aerial Fire to go up. You’ve already wasted quite some time doing it that way. We started pulling ten seconds ago, but you still haven’t done anything yet!” Ye Xiu said.

“When you use Aerial Fire, try to hit the monsters too to save time.” Ye Xiu added.

“Okay okay…..” Maple Tree had entered the dungeon with matchless confidence, but in these few seconds, his confidence had already burned to ashes and flown away. Lord Grim, one player against four monsters. Steamed Bun Invasion and Soft Mist were also each fighting two monsters. Maple Tree looked and discovered that they weren’t pulling monsters any more, they were already beginning to kill them. It was just that while they were killing them, they were also bringing the monsters to their desired spots.

Maple Tree didn’t want to delay any longer. But just as he was about to jump onto that stone window, he suddenly felt a tinge of fear and his hands trembled. He hadn’t calculated the distance well and he hadn’t used enough strength, so when he jumped onto the wall, he directly latched onto the wall like a gecko and then slid down.

Ye Xiu saw this and he immediately coughed up blood. This Maple Tree was a guild leader. Even though his task didn’t need high mechanics like Steamed Bun Invasion or Tang Rou, he should at least be an experienced player like Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon! Yet he couldn’t even jump onto a window! He wasn’t a noob right?

Ye Xiu was even more shocked than Maple Tree. If he really was a noob, then that’d be really disastrous. It has to be known that their strategy mainly relied on skill. Even if Maple Tree was an experienced player, all he could be arranged to do was assist them. They couldn’t afford to have him be a noob right now!

“你不是跳不上去吧？”叶修问着。

“Are you not able to jump up there?” Ye Xiu asked.

“No, I’m just a bit nervous……” Maple Tree said.

“Why are you nervous?”

“Your strategy’s too crazy.” Maple Tree said.

“Calm down. It gets crazier later.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay.”

“Hurry up and jump up there.” Ye Xiu said, while fixing his attention on this side. He had to properly see what Maple Tree’s skill level was at. If he really was a noob, then he had to switch him out. Noobs weren’t scary. But noobs that acted like they understood were the scariest.

This time, Maple Tree judged the correct distance. He jumped and steadily landed. Ye Xiu saw that the distance and power had been grasped well. So he really wasn’t a noob.

“I said use Aerial Fire! Why are you still directly jumping up?” But Ye Xiu still had to correct his problem.

“Oh, I forgot. Do it again?” Maple Tree said.

“Do it again and practice at the same time. Going up there with Aerial Fire isn’t that easy. If you can’t get up there, then keep trying!” Ye Xiu said.

“I can do it, I can do it.” Maple Tree hastily said.

Aerial Fire made the user fly backwards. The user had to control the gun in order to grasp the distance and height he flew. When to stop was completely reliant on experience. There wasn’t enough time to turn around and look when flying.

Maple Tree jumped down from the stone window and walked a certain distance away. Ye Xiu saw his position and immediately asked: “How many shots are you planning on firing?”

“Six shots……” Maple Tree said.

“Six shots and you’ll hit your head.”

“Hit my head?”

“Too high…… you won’t be able to get into the window.” Ye Xiu said.

“Really? Then a bit farther away?”

“Go a bit closer and five shots will be enough.” Ye Xiu said.

“Here?” Maple Tree moved a bit.

“That’s good.”

“Okay!” Maple Tree answered. He stood at the position, jumped up, and then turned around and fired at the ground. He shot five times in a row and sure enough, he was sent up to the window.

At this moment, Su Mucheng had already brought those four monsters over. And soon, all twelve monsters were gathered together and the four quickly began attacking them. Maple Tree was still sitting at the window all lonely. He wasn’t there to be some background decoration.

“Maple Tree, have you noticed that those two in the dead center are in your attack range?” The orders for him to act had finally arrived.

Chapter 151 – Burning with Anxiety

Maple Tree carefully looked towards the mob of monsters. After looking for a while, he finally cried: “Where’s the dead center!?”

These twelve monsters weren’t standing in a line waiting for him to inspect them. Amidst the intense battle, they were all mixed into a mess. Even Lord Grim and the others would sometimes enter the mob of monsters. Maple Tree watched the battle attentively for a minute, but still hadn’t found any signs of a “dead center” amidst the chaos.

“Watch me attack.” A girl suddenly spoke out. Maple Tree couldn’t tell if the voice came from Soft Mist or Cleansing Mist. But he quickly saw Cleansing Mist run off, jump, turn around, and then fire. With the recoil from the flying artillery shell, she also leaped up onto a window.

“Did you see it?” That voice came again.

“Huh?” Maple Tree stared blankly.

“The place where I fired at just moments ago!’ The other side said.

“That artillery shell?” Maple Tree asked.

“Yes!”

“Oops, I was only watching you and wasn’t looking at the shell……” Maple Tree said gloomily. This explanation made him feel very childish!

A bullet from a Sharpshooter would cause blood to spurt out from the target that had been hit. It was obvious at a glance. But an artillery shell from a Launcher was different. It would explode with a bang once it hit a mob of monsters and instantly turn into smoke, which was why he wasn’t able to tell who exactly the shell had hit.

“Watch closely this time.” Su Mucheng said. Her Cleansing Mist rapidly fired using the skill “Gatling Gun”. This time, she didn’t shake the gun, so the bullets flew in a straight line from the gun nozzle directly to a monster in the middle of the mob.

“I saw it! I saw it!” Maple Tree hastily cried. If he still hadn’t seen it, then he’d have to die from shame.

“That’s good then.”

Maple Tree immediately pulled out his gun and then began firing at the monster. Just as he was pondering over why this monster was considered the dead center, he suddenly saw the monster turn around and move towards Cleansing Mist, shouting: “Little girl, you’re looking to die!!”

The monsters of Desolate Land such as the bandits and thieves were all human, so of course they could speak. They weren’t like those shrieking Goblins or wailing undead monsters.

“OT!!!” Maple Tree, who had claimed he was extremely familiar with Desolate Land, immediately knew that this monster’s aggro had shifted onto Cleansing Mist. This girl had accidentally caused it to OT (Off Tank) when she had instructed him. Maple Tree truly felt extremely ashamed.

In the end, it looked as if Cleansing Mist didn’t know what had happened, as she continued to fire ferociously. He then saw a ball of light condense and a laser shoot out directly at that hooting OTed monster.

This was the Launcher Level 30 skill: Laser Rifle. It was the skill with the longest range in all of Glory. Its power could be stored up and did tremendous damage. After storing up power, its damage would increase by 40%, but would also cause it to have a strong recoil. The player had to manually step back in order to take the recoil. If it wasn’t done right, then the player might flip over and the accuracy of the shot might also be affected.

This sort of fundamental maneuver naturally wasn’t a problem for Su Mucheng. At the same time the laser fired, Cleansing Mist stepped back, completely nullifying the recoil.

But she had clearly OTed already, so why did she use such a powerful skill? Was she looking to die even faster? This was something that Maple Tree couldn’t understand at all. Even though the two of them were both on the high grounds, the high grounds were only convenient for their long-ranged attacks. It wasn’t like the monster would just stand there staring above him, waiting to die. These were human NPCs. If they could talk, why wouldn’t they be able to jump? Of course they could.

“OT, OT!!!” Maple Tree repeatedly warned everyone. OT often lead to a party wipe-out. Maple Tree attached a lot of importance to this.

“Ha ha ha ha, calm down, noob. It’s just an OT.” Steamed Bun Invasion laughed out loud.

Noob???

It’s just an OT!

Maple Tree couldn’t accept these two statements. He felt that anyone who called OT as “just” was the true noob. Just as he was about to retort, he heard that Launcher: “It’s not a big deal, look!”

Another look! What was there to look at? Maple Tree was gloomy. His gaze hadn’t strayed away from the mob of monsters!

“Look at what?” So he asked.

“Look at the monster that had been OTed.” Su Mucheng said.

“Where……” Maple Tree mumbled and then looked again carefully. He discovered that that monster was nowhere to be seen. The monster’s aggro had clearly went onto Cleansing Mist. The monster should have separated from the mob and chased after Cleansing Mist. That should have been what happened. But in a short moment of distraction, he unexpectedly couldn’t find any signs of such a monster.

Maple Tree was still in shock, when he saw three artillery shells explode in the middle of the mob. That Launcher had shot another Anti-Tank Missile.

“Slow down!!” Maple Tree cried out in fear. This Launcher was clearly a girl, yet her fighting style was so violently reckless without any control over her damage output. These attacks and skills were thrown out non-stop. Was she going to OT again?

In the end, Su Mucheng gave him a response that made him almost panic in desperation. Cleansing Mist closely followed with another Cannonball and this time she had even stored up power.

For classes like Launchers, which attacked relatively slowly, they usually had relatively high burst damage. Thus, Launcher skills did quite a lot of damage. At this moment, Cleansing Mist had chained the three strongest skills a Level 30 Launcher could use. Let alone a party without a specialized MT, even with one, the party still wouldn’t be able to handle such a rude burst of damage!

OT again, Maple Tree sighed. Sure enough, another monster in the mob shouted “Little girl, you’re looking to die!”

A tragedy. What a tragedy!

Maple Tree looked up at the sky and let out a lengthy sigh. But when he finished sighing and looked again, the OTed monster was once again nowhere to be seen.

Its aggro was pulled back?

Maple Tree truly didn’t understand what had happened. He wasn’t doubting these players’ skill, but with a Launcher’s burst damage, if the OT by the previous Laser Rifle was pulled back, then that was understandable, but an Anti-Tank Missile and a Cannonball chained together along with it? Without a specialized Taunt skill, just relying on damage output, it was impossible to pull the aggro back in an instant. It was impossible. It was absolutely impossible.

Maple Tree had been standing at the window in a daze the entire time. At this moment, Su Mucheng suddenly yelled: “Why aren’t you attacking?”

“Attack? Attack what?” Maple Tree was still pondering over this OT mystery.

“The targets I attack. Just hit whatever I hit and you’ll be fine.” Su Mucheng said.

“The targets you attack?” Maple Tree was still in a daze, when Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist use Gatling Gun again. This time she used Gun Shake and her gun shook left and right. The bullets that came out split into two lines, hitting two different monsters in the mob.

“Ah!! Dual lines!” Maple Tree was astonished again. He also played a Gunner. Even though he wasn’t a Launcher, he still understood the theory behind this move.

It wasn’t easy to use Gun Shake to scatter the bullets from Gatling Gun, but having the bullets accurately hit two different targets with it was even harder. This required exceptionally precise mouse movements, otherwise the path of the bullets wouldn’t be able to split into two lines and perhaps split into three or four lines.

When he saw those two lines of bullets hit their targets, Maple Tree suddenly discovered something even more astonishing.

The two monsters had been hit by the bullets, but they hadn’t given up struggling. The two monsters were still headed towards Cleansing Mist with no signs of stopping. Their aggro was clearly on Cleansing Mist.

“Quickly, quickly!! Those two!!” Maple Tree hastily yelled. Gatling Gun’s attack had already finished. When the two monsters closed in on Cleansing Mist, a battle lance with a monster stuck on it smashed down from the sky and the two monsters immediately crashed to the ground. And after this Circle Swing, Soft Mist promptly went to fight other monsters.

“Oh……” Maple Tree was just about to warn Soft Mist of those two monster’s aggro, when he saw Steamed Bun Invasion dash towards these two monsters. But he didn’t make a move against them and went right by.

When the two monsters climbed back up and stubbornly rushed at Cleansing Mist, their comrades happened to be passing by, blocking them. Those comrades had their aggro on Steamed Bun Invasion and were currently chasing him.

The two NPCs had no choice but to go around this blockade, but they hadn’t yet taken two steps, when a bang rang out! Lord Grim had used Falling Flower Palm to send a monster flying over, hitting those two monsters.

“This is……” Maple Tree wasn’t stupid. These two monsters, which had clearly been OTed, weren’t able to get close to their target. They were on the ground half the time and trying to get up the other half. After a long time, they still hadn’t moved far from their original positions. And this type of situation was because of the way these three players moved and attacked.

“Could it be…..”

Maple Tree was currently thinking, when a Laser beam shot out from up above. That Cleansing Mist’s Laser Rifle had just come off cooldown and had been impolitely shot out. Those two monsters, which had just gotten back up, were immediately knocked to the ground again. Just as they got up again, Soft Mist’s Falling Flower Palm sent two more monsters crashing into them.

“So it’s because of their coordination?” Maple Tree finally understood.

OTed monsters didn’t need to be worried about because of the way those four players used their skills or moved. Those OTed monsters were firmly under their control. Cleansing Mist’s tempo matched the other players’ tempos perfectly. Under this type of coordination, OT clearly wasn’t an issue.

OT, really had happened. Maple Tree’s judgement wasn’t wrong.

But it still made him burn with anxiety…..

It turns out it was only because I was an idiot? Maple Tree’s cheeks streamed with tears.

Chapter 152 – The Bystander Becomes the Deciding Role

“Ha ha ha, don’t be so nervous noob!! We’ve only been playing for a short while and you keep on calling out OT OT!! Are you OTMAN?” Steamed Bun Invasion laughed out loud.

“F*CK!” Maple Tree raised his gun and wildly shot at the two monsters that Cleansing Mist was attacking. In his heart, he felt extremely depressed.

What was wrong with worrying over OT? How could I have known that such a freak team existed? So it was actually possible to prevent OT like this. This type of control is ridiculous. Maple Tree comforted himself as he gloomily fired at the monsters.

In this guild, he was the senior, the boss. When they dungeoned, he was the leader; he gave the orders; whatever he said was the law.

But now? He was the noob. He was the OTMAN. He was burning with anxiety. His face was covered in tears.

Maple Tree felt wronged!

Before he came, he had already mentally prepared himself. After all, it was the team that could step all over the big guild’s records, how could their skill be questioned? Maple Tree didn’t doubt that they were experts. But after seeing them personally, he discovered that he hadn’t prepared himself well enough.

These players’ skill levels were way beyond his wildest imaginations. At this moment, Maple Tree had a hard time staying level-headed. He felt that his existence in the team was replaceable. Those four players coordinated exceptionally well, while he was an outsider, playing a small role, a bystander. This was a feeling he had never experienced before!

“Steamed Bun, don’t get distracted. You made a mistake just a moment ago.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh? Really?”

“Really. That Back Attack you did with your Knee wasn’t placed well. If you went right 30 degrees, then the monster would have been knocked back and would have smashed into the monster Soft Mist sent flying.”

“Oh…….”

“This is just a test run. In a bit, you’re going to have to focus more. This mistake won’t affect the overall situation, but it’ll affect our efficiency. A few mistakes here and there will add up to a significant amount of wasted time.” Ye Xiu said.

“OKay! But if I focus more, who’s going to take care of that noob?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked.

“He’ll take care of himself.” Ye Xiu said.

“You can do it, noob!!” Steamed Bun Invasion encouraged him.

Maple Tree: “…….”

As they advanced through the dungeon, Maple Tree experienced the four player’s coordination and skill another step. Maple Tree’s luck wasn’t too good. If he had went with Ye Xiu and the others to Desolate Land at Level 28, then he might not have fallen to such a depressed state.

At that time, Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion were still completely new to the dungeon and were genuine noobs. Unfortunately, everyone was now Level 30 already. They had never failed to run Desolate Land the limit of three times per day. With their mechanics and Ye Xiu’s tactical guidance, their many days of practice had drilled into them this level of tacit understanding, making Maple Tree feel extremely inferior.

Regarding the tactical plan for Maple Tree, it was basically under the lead of Cleansing Mist. The two were both long-ranged characters and provided assistance to the other three in the middle of the mob.

But Cleansing Mist was actually helping. Every effect, every crowd control, from every attack she made were all being put to use. As for Maple Tree, his only task was to shoot the bullets from his gun and use his skills whenever they went off cooldown. Then…….make sure that he hit his target. And that was all.

\

He originally thought he was just there to cheer them on, but as they advanced through the dungeon, Maple Tree discovered that Lord Grim began paying more and more attention to him and slowly found that he was starting to become a part of their team. He figured this out through one incident, where he thoughtlessly fired at a monster. The target he hit unexpectedly caused the entire team to go into a mess. From this, he quickly realized that the task Lord Grim had assigned to him wasn’t to be a bystander. His sloppy playing nearly caused a major disaster.

“No good!” Steamed Bun Invasion opened his mouth, “It looks like I should still take care of the noob!”

“No need!” Maple Tree clenched his teeth, “I’m fine. I got distracted because my cell phone suddenly rang.” Maple Tree lied to fight for his position. He didn’t want to be regarded as a noob. He didn’t want to be a bystander. He wanted to become an integral part of the team.

“Just take care of yourself Steamed Bun. Don’t worry about it.” Ye Xiu said to Steamed Bun Invasion.

“Fine then!” Steamed Bun Invasion had no choice but to reluctantly accept it, “Then I leave this noob to you.” With the tone he used, it seemed like Maple Tree was a noob he had brought in and was entrusting him to someone else.

“Maple Tree, focus……” Ye Xiu finally said. In the first half of the run, he had been examining Maple Tree’ strength. He at least needed to know his skill level before he could clearly use him in the team. For a team that had their sights on the record, the team definitely couldn’t afford to bring along a useless bystander. Everyone had to be perform at their very best. This was how record-setting teams operated, regardless of whether only four players were needed to set the record. This wasn’t an issue of ability. This was an issue of attitude.

After observing for half the dungeon, Ye Xiu could already see what Maple Tree’s skill level was. He wasn’t any expert of any kind. He was around the same as Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon, an experienced player. Letting him handle situations that required high mechanics obviously wasn’t going to happen. However, there was still a lot he could do. At this moment, Ye Xiu was explaining things to Maple Tree bit by bit.

He explained, while experimenting.

The moment Maple Tree went up, he caused a small disaster. But with two pro-level players and two mechanically-skilled players, they wouldn’t have any problem dealing with the situation no matter how chaotic it was. Maple Tree felt even more ashamed. His previous “I’m extremely familiar” arrogant attitude had disappeared long ago. He really was like a student. He listened to Ye Xiu’s instructions and did as he was told bit by bit.

Because of this, the latter half of the dungeon slowed down a little. However, no one complained. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion had also been taught like this. Su Mucheng didn’t need to be said. She constantly helped Ye Xiu teach Maple Tree and often demonstrated what he needed to do personally.

After pushing through the dungeon, Maple Tree wiped the sweat off his forehead. This small dungeon, which he had ran who knew how many times, made him feel extremely stressed this time. The detailed strategy Ye Xiu had planned needed to be done with meticulous precision. Everyone’s play affected one another, so they all had to perform well and work together. They couldn’t afford to make mistakes and wasted time.

This type of strategy brought out everyone’s full potential. It was the type of strategy that was the most suitable for trying to set new records.

This dungeon run took a total of one hour to run. They obviously didn’t care about the time. They had gotten rid of many problems over the course of the run, which was why it had taken so long.

“Okay, the second time. Let’s try to challenge the record this time. Maple Tree, is there anything you don’t understand?” Ye Xiu said.

“Yeah. Those noobs who act like they understand everything are the team killers. You’d better not be one of those.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“I’m not a noob! I’m the guild leader of Full Moon Guild.” Maple Tree identified himself.

“Full Moon Guild? Why aren’t you called Full Star Guild?” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“Why Full Star?” Maple Tree stared blankly.

“Because Full Moon doesn’t sound good.” Steamed Bun Invasion’s line of thinking was so simple! So simple that Maple Tree couldn’t follow it. Meanwhile, the other players had already entered the dungeon.

On their second run, Maple Tree had begun assimilating with the team. But breaking the record this run? Ye Xiu had no hopes whatsoever. If Maple Tree had been one of Blue Brook Guild’s or any of those type of big guild’s elite experts, then it might have been possible. But for someone who was just an experienced player, it would be very difficult to completely grasp the strategy on the second try. Even if no mistakes were made, there would still be some flaws in his playing. They wouldn’t be able to reach the most optimal state and thus their efficiency would take a hit.

If everyone’s equipment was at the level of the big guilds’ elite teams, then there’d be more leeway for Maple Tree. But in their situation, they needed Maple Tree’s 100% in order to take down the record.

In the end, it was just as Ye Xiu had predicted. Maple Tree was still in the difficult stage of fitting in with the team. Even though there weren’t many major errors, there were still a lot of places that required him to think and a lot of places where he acted too slowly, which would all delay them.

In the end, their time for their second run was 35:14:41. There weren’t any other major issues, it all depended on Maple Tree’s performance now. This was already the main reason that their final time couldn’t beat the record.

However, it didn’t look like the task could be finished today. They could only run the dungeon once more. Ye Xiu reckoned that Maple Tree wouldn’t be able to adapt so quickly.

Sure enough, in the third run, Maple Tree improved again. But it wasn’t enough. Their final time was 34:47:68 and their three runs for the day were now all used up.

How could Maple Tree not know that the problem lay with him? The other players didn’t make any mistakes and were all lowering their tempo to adapt to him. Being someone on the team that held everyone back didn’t feel good at all! Maple Tree couldn’t help but think of his guild’s dungeon team. If there was such a terrible noob on it, everyone would hate him. And the current him? Although he wasn’t destroying the team, they still weren’t able to set the record all because of him, leaving a bad taste in Maple Tree’s mouth.

“You have a main account, right?” Lord Grim suddenly asked.

“Ah…. I do!”

“You should use the accounts you have to practice! The team’s current problems are almost all on you. As long as you practice a bit more, we’ll be able to take down this record…… But if we keep on practicing like this and we accidentally reach Level 31, then that’d be really bad.” Ye Xiu said.

“Yeah…. I’ll think of a way.” Maple Tree said.

“Desolate Land’s elite monsters in the dungeon, in terms of their attack patterns and habits, they’re about the same as the monsters in the leveling area. There are a few things you can practice in the leveling area. For example…..” Ye Xiu suggested a few things Maple Tree could do.

Maple Tree listened attentively. He was repeatedly nodding his head in front of the computer. Nodding and nodding, he suddenly realized that there was no way the other side could see him doing so and as a result, felt embarrassed again.

“Okay, that’ll be it for today. You can do it! We’ll see you tomorrow night.”

“See you tomorrow night!” Maple Tree took off and then began thinking of ways to practice more.

Chapter 153 – Exchange Market

“It’s 2 o’clock. I’ll be going off too then?” Su Mucheng said.

“How are you leveling your account?” Ye Xiu asked her. Su Mucheng shouldn’t have the time to level her low-leveled account. But right now, her Cleansing Mist was very close to Lord Grim’s level, not a step slower.

“You don’t need to worry about that!” Su Mucheng hummed a tune and then logged out.

“Dungeon again?” Tang Rou asked. Now that they were Level 30, running Frost Forest was no longer a viable option, but Boneyard could still give some experience. Apart from this, they could enter a new dungeon, the Level 30-33 dungeon Line Canyon.

This dungeon was still a five-member dungeon and could only be run three times every day, the same as Desolate Land. Yesterday, after leveling to 30, Ye Xiu and the others had already began running it. The unfamiliarity of the dungeon for the first three runs naturally made Tang Rou feel challenged by it, so she was now quite interested in going to Line Canyon.

“No rush. We’re going shopping.” Ye Xiu said.

“Shopping?” Tang Rou stared blankly.

“We’re Level 30 now. You two should start paying attention to your equipment now.” Ye Xiu said, “For equipment, higher-leveled doesn’t necessarily mean that it’s better. True experts have to know how to choose equipment that fit their play style. Movement speed, attack speed, these types of speed-related stats, higher doesn’t necessarily mean better either. When the speed is too high, it’s pretty common for players to go out of control and expose an opening. Experts don’t chase after equipment with the highest stats. They chase after equipment that suits them the best. Why are self-made equipment so strong? It’s not just because their stats are higher than an Orange equipment by a level. More importantly, it’s because they’re custom-made specially to suit the player’s style. Take my Thousand Chance Umbrella as an example. If you don’t have enough experience in the game, it wouldn’t be possible to fully utilize this weapon’s might.”

“For weapons, normal players usually choose the weapon with the highest attack. But for experts, attack isn’t the only thing to be considered because it doesn’t how they use the weapon. What truly affects their weapon choice is the weapon’s attack speed, length, weight, etc. These sort of properties are all necessary to consider in real battle. Let’s say I give you a Lance with an attack twice as high as your current one, but with a length that’s a third of yours. If you used the one I give you, do you think your strength will increase or decrease?” Ye Xiu explained and then suddenly quizzed Tang Rou.

Tang Rou heard the question and was stumped. Whether she’d be stronger or weaker, she had no way of judging that. But she at least understood what Ye Xiu was trying to get at.

“The greater the expert, the higher the expert’s awareness towards how different weapons feel. Because I’m not you, as a bystander, I can only give you some suggestions, but what exactly you choose depends on you. This means that you’re going to have to try out lots of different weapons. What you’re looking for is the most suitable equipment. Either that or you’re going to need to adjust your playing style to the equipment you choose. In the end, it all depends on you to decide.”

They walked while they talked, until the three characters finally arrived at Congee City.

Congee City was much larger than Bulls Town. This was one of the major cities in Glory. It was also the first major city that players would come across and a gathering place for low to mid level players.

From Level 30 onwards, players paid closer attention to equipment and so the Exchange Market would become much more popular. Lots of messages for buying and selling would begin to appear on the world channel too. Once a player entered Congee City, the player would see players buying and selling items everywhere around them.

However, the prices for many of the items were extremely high. The new servers had lots of new players. But even though new players didn’t understand, they weren’t stupid. There were very few fools who sold items as if they were trash. Most players who didn’t know of an item’s price would look around first. They would go to the market and ask around. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion were both left speechless after looking at the marked prices.

Along their journey to Level 30, they hadn’t gotten any super-lucky gains. Besides the rewards from quests, their only source of income was from monster drops. However, these were all just chump change. The money they had accumulated up until now didn’t exceed 10 Gold coins. Buying potions and so on usually used Silver coins as the unit of measure. In the beginner village, the lowest leveled health and mana potions were 1 Silver coin a bottle. 1 Gold coin was equal to 100 Silver coins. 10 Gold coins were enough to buy a lot of these potions. However, these were all the lowest-leveled potions. For Level 30 players, it wasn’t worth buying them.

For Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion to have been able to accumulate that much money was already considered quite good. Their skill levels were high, so they were able to dodge most attacks in real battle. If not, then if they were normal new players, they would have used up all of their money from quests and drops on potions. If they didn’t do any reselling for profit trading, then they wouldn’t be able to afford anything. 10 Gold coins was already considered quite rich among these normal players.

Ye Xiu looked through several booths. He discovered that even though the market had already taken form, Level 30 and up items were still rare. The reason was because Level 30 players were currently a very small part of the player population. The majority of players were still trying to reach Level 30. At this moment, there were quite a lot of booths, but most of them were players under Level 30 setting up booths after seeing others do it. As a result, the majority of equipment sold weren’t Level 30. Besides a few unique equipment, the rest weren’t anything remarkable.

Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion at least knew to look for equipment based on their levels. They ignored everything under Level 30 and only looked at equipment Level 30 and above.

“So expensive!!” Seeing the prices on the equipment, the two expressed their regrets.

A normal Level 30 Blue piece of equipment cost 10 gold coins, their entire fortune. Class-set equipment were even more expensive. They varied from 20 Gold coins to 40 Gold coins for one. Why was there a difference? This was because even though Glory’s 24 classes were balanced well, there were still classes more popular than others. For example, Blade Masters and Sharpshooters were the two most popular classes in Glory. It was the same in the new server. With a greater demand, the equipment for those classes were naturally a bit more expensive.

Armor was like this. Weapons were even more so. A Level 30 Blue weapon cost between 30 gold coins to 50 gold coins. The variance was also because of the difference in classes. As for Purple weapons, normal ones cost 100 gold coins. For ones with more outstanding stats, those could cost nearly 200 gold coins.

These prices were a bit more fair. After all, the vast majority of players that had hit Level 30 were veterans from the big guilds. Under the standards they set, those crazier players that had hit Level 30 too set their prices in the same way. There weren’t too many with ridiculous prices.

“If I wanted to buy a weapon, how long would I need to save up money?” Tang Rou said.

“It looks like it’d be better to just save up points in the Arena!” Steamed Bun Invasion was still using that Level 25 Purple Claw he got from the Arena.

“Ha ha, as long as the equipment isn’t binded, then you can always resell your equipment later!” Ye Xiu said.

In Glory, equipment from the normal servers could be binded. After being binded, the equipment wouldn’t drop if you died. But it also meant that it couldn’t be traded. Once the equipment was bound, it wasn’t possible to unbind it, which was why at this stage of the game, practically no one bound their equipment. Everyone wanted to sell their equipment later after it grew outdated. But because of this reason, the price for low-leveled equipment would eventually take a dive as the equipment grew outdated. For example, in the oldest first server, the equipment that Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion were gasping at were ten times cheaper. Moreover, most players didn’t want to waste their time peddling them and directly sold them in the NPC stores.

“Then what do we need to buy?” Tang Rou asked.

“Weapons.” Ye Xiu said. After witnessing Maple Tree’s performance three times, Ye Xiu didn’t want to put his entire trust onto whether that guy would improve. In the end, he decided that they should upgrade their equipment and be more ready.

“Where are we going to get that money?” Tang Rou said. She had seen a Purple Lance being sold for 120 gold coins. Blue Lances were a lot cheaper; they were all under 40 gold coins. But a Level 30 Blue weapon was about the same as her Level 25 Purple weapon, so there was no point in buying one. If she were going to switch weapons, she’d had to buy a Purple Lance.

“Money isn’t a problem. Just look for a weapon that you like! If you think the one you’re using right now is good, then you should choose the Level 30 Scarlet Moon Lance. It’s the around the same length and weight as your current one.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh? Them I’m going to go look around. I’ll pay you back later.” Tang Rou said.

“Buy me a cigarette pack and that’ll be enough.” Ye Xiu said.

“I’m waiting for my pay to come…..” Tang Rou said gloomily. She currently had no money. She had lost it all to Ye Xiu.

“Steamed Bun! Look for a weapon you like, it’ll be my gift!” Ye Xiu said to Steamed Bun Invasion.

“Ha ha, I get one too!!” Steamed Bun Invasion cheered.

“Of course.”

“Then I’m going to go look.” Steamed Bun Invasion wasn’t as polite. He had gaming experience. Even though it wasn’t in Glory, he could still infer one thing from three in many places. In his eyes, Ye Xiu and him were at a completely different level. Ye Xiu was an expert. A god. Experts gifting new players equipment was a very common occurrence, so there was no need to be polite.

Steamed Bun Invasion returned after a short while and said he found a weapon that he liked. Ye Xiu followed him to go look and immediately regretted what he had said: “Steamed Bun, you really aren’t polite at all!”

“Ha ha!” Steamed Bun Invasion laughed. He had found an Orange weapon. Ye Xiu had looked around all day and this was the first Orange equipment he had seen. How did Steamed Bun Invasion smell that out? In just a minute after he heard that he’d be gifted an equipment, he fished this out.

Level 30 Orange weapon Vampiric Claw, 800 gold coins. How could the price of Orange weapons be similar to Blue or Purple weapons?

“Can I?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked.

“Of course not! I only have 15 gold coins on me. I have to go sell things to buy you guys weapons. 800 gold coins. Do you want me to sell myself!!” Ye Xiu said. The only reason he had 5 more gold coins than Steamed Bun Invasion and Tang Rou was all because he had consumed even fewer potions and food than them.

“Really? Then I’ll go look around again.” Steamed Bun Invasion ran off.

“Orange weapons are no good!!” Ye Xiu stressed.

“Got it!” Steamed Bun Invasion’s voice came from far away.

Ye Xiu shook his head and then immediately let Lord Grim head to one corner of the market. He had noticed a booth with a sign: Buying Uncommon Materials.

“How are you buying Strong Spider Silk?” Lord Grim walked forward and then asked.

The other side turned his character to look at him. After a short moment of silence, he said: “Lord Grim….. Didn’t you earn these Strong Spider Silk from us? And now you want to sell it back to us?”

Chapter 154 – Where’d These Materials Come From?

“Oh, you are?” Ye Xiu had seen the booth’s sign board and came over. He hadn’t noticed the vendor’s name. He glanced: Blue Brook Guild, Bound Boat.

“I’m called Bound Boat. I’m from Blue Brook Guild.” Bound Boat introduced himself. Actually, he had met Lord Grim a while ago. It was just that because he was a Cleric, he had been kicked out of the dungeon team. The two hadn’t talked to each other before, so he wouldn’t be surprised if Lord Grim had forgotten him.

“Oh, so it’s you.” Ye Xiu grinned while saying, “It’d be great if I could sell them back to you guys. What’s the point of money? Uncommon materials are forever. They’ll always be useful!”

(TLCN: Adapted from “A diamond is forever” – 钻石恒久远,一颗永留传”)

Bound Boat heard this and laughed. This phrase had been around for a long time, but there were very few that still said it. Most new players had never heard of it. Players that say this phrase with ease meant that they had at least five years of experience in Glory.

Having many years of experience in the game didn’t necessarily mean that they were pro-players. There were numerous players in the normal player community that had played for a long time. Especially among the experts, most of them were ones that had played Glory for many years. They weren’t like pro-players, however. No matter how good or bad a pro-player was, they still had some level of talent. Most normal players had mediocre talent. If they wanted to reach a certain level of skill, they could only use time and effort to slowly train themselves. It wasn’t easy for them.

Bound Boat was this type of player. He had played Glory for seven years. Even in the eyes of the pro-community, he’d be considered as having played the game for a long time. As for this Lord Grim, Bound Boat believed that he was a veteran that didn’t lose to him in experience.

Two players, who were extremely knowledgable on Glory, would be able to save a lot on buying and selling. In any case, they wouldn’t be ripped off.

“40 Silver coins for each Strong Spider Silk.” Bound Boat didn’t say anything more.

“Don’t joke with me. It should be 1 Gold coin for each.” Ye Xiu said.

“In front of us two seniors, the new server is just like floating clouds, which is why we have to do things according to our knowledge as seniors. If I consider that you’re the one buying, then 80 Silver coin for each.”

“If I can buy them at 40 Silver coins each, why should I buy them at 80?” Bound Boat said.

“That’s only right now. Sooner or later, you’re going to have to start buying them at 80 Silver coins each. Just think of it like that.” Ye Xiu said.

“You should go back to reality. This is the new server.” Bound Boat laughed. It was clear that this was a very calm and careful person. Lord Grim’s powerful strength hadn’t affected his judgement on business transactions. He wouldn’t let up an inch.

Ye Xiu was also helpless and had no choice but to ask again: “If it’s 40 Silver pieces for each Strong Spider Silk, then what about Frosted Stones?” Those were much more valuable than Strong Spider Silk. They were items that only dropped from hidden BOSSes at Line Canyon. Players could only run the dungeon three times every day in addition to their low chances of meeting a hidden BOSS. Yesterday, Ye Xiu and the others had run the dungeon three times and they hadn’t met a single one.

“20 Gold coins.” Bound Boat said.

“35 is more like it.”

“New server, new server.” Bound Boat emphasized.

“30! 20 is looking down on the fact that I’m a senior too much.” Ye Xiu said.

“Ha ha, how many do you have?” Bound Boat asked.

“If it’s for 30, then I can give you ten of them!” Ye Xiu said.

“Ten….. ten?” Bound Boat stammered. Because of his cool-headedness and carefulness, he had immediately felt that picking up ten Frost Stones was unimaginable for someone who had just hit Level 30. These were materials that only dropped from a specific hidden BOSS. Even though their chances of dropping were high, that wasn’t the reason why they were uncommon, rather it was because of the probability of meeting that specific hidden BOSS. Only once this was considered, could uncommon materials have the word “uncommon” in them.

Lord Grim had just reached Level 30 yesterday. This was something that Blue Brook Guild had been watching closely. Adding in two day’s worth of runs, Line Canyon could have only been run six times at most. Even if he had met a hidden BOSS every run and each hidden BOSS all happened to be the exact same one, then it still might not mean that he’d be able to get ten of them. The chances of this happening weren’t zero, but it was close.

“What do you think?” Ye Xiu asked.

“How do you have so many Frosted Stones?” Bound Boat couldn’t figure it out. It wasn’t possible for him to get that amount by himself. If he had purchased them, it didn’t make sense for him to go sell them to someone who purchased materials like himself. For a senior with so much experience, that would be too stupid. Apart from that, Bound Boat could only think of him getting those through some shady business like killing others for their items.

“10 is a lot?” Ye Xiu, on the other hand, was grinning.

“You have more?” Bound Boat was astonished.

“I have plenty. To be honest, I probably have as many as the amount in your Blue Brook Guild’s storehouse.” Ye Xiu said.

“Impossible……” Bound Boat still doubtful, “How did you get them?”

“You don’t have to worry about that! Just tell me whether you want them or not!” Ye Xiu said.

Bound Boat was unexpectedly unable to answer at this moment. Even though he had put a price on Frosted Stones, he hadn’t had any plans on how much he would purchase. At this moment, only high-leveled players would have these items and the majority of these were from big guilds like his. Big guilds would only buy materials and use them. They would practically never sell them. It still wasn’t the time for Frosted Stones yet.

When Lord Grim had suddenly asked him, Bound Boat had thought that even if Lord Grim had gotten lucky, he would only have one or two at most, which was why he didn’t care too much about it. But who would have thought that Lord Grim would be so mysterious and start out with ten. Besides the big guilds with Clubs behind them, this amount shouldn’t be possible for anyone to have. And in addition, Lord Grim’s tone implied that ten wasn’t all he had.

“How many do you have total?” Bound Boat asked. He hadn’t made any plans for them because he hadn’t thought that he’d be able to get any. But some would come sooner or later. Seeing that the goods had already arrived, he didn’t want to miss the opportunity.

“Thirty to forty!” Ye Xiu said.

Bound Boat almost fell off his chair. If this guy really had as many as that, then it really would be about how many Blue Brook Guild had. Before Bound Boat went out to buy materials, he had checked up on their guild’s storehouse and recalled that they only had around forty, less than fifty Frost Stones.

“25 Gold coins! I want them all.” Bound Boat said. This type of large purchase wasn’t something that he would ever see again. There was no way a private player could gather this many uncommon materials.

“When did I say I was selling them all? I’m only selling 10. 300 Gold coins and they’re yours!” Ye Xiu said.

“25!” Bound Boat didn’t care if it was all of them or ten of them. He’d buy whatever he could.

“And then me 29, you 26, me 28, you 27, in the end we’d agree on 27.5, so 275 Gold coins? Your guild’s so big, what’s 25 Gold coins to you guys? How shameful! 300!” Ye Xiu said.

“How’d you come up with that.” Bound Boat said.

“You really are calm.” Ye Xiu said.

“Ha ha, 25 Gold coins is a very fair price!” Bound Boat said.

“It’s you who doesn’t want them!” Ye Xiu said. Lord Grim suddenly stood next to Bound Boat.

“干什么？”系舟不由地慌了一下，他一直很怀疑君莫笑这么多材料的来路，这肯定不可能是刷副本来的。系舟最终想到的就是堵在副本门外杀人越货。可是能爆到这么多，这应该早掀起轩然大波了。系舟也天天都去一线峡谷的副本，可是从来没听说过……

“What are you doing?” Bound Boat couldn’t help but panic. He had been puzzling over how Lord Grim had obtained so many materials. He definitely couldn’t have gotten them from only clearing dungeons. Bound Boat could only come up with Lord Grim killing others and stealing their items. But to get this many would mean that there would be a huge fuss over it. Bound Boat had also ran Line Canyon everyday, but he had never heard of anything like that…..

Don’t tell me he somehow hacked the game? Old players had experienced a lot, so they had a lot of ideas. Glory hadn’t been hacked in many years, but Bound Boat still recalled how players robbed from each other in the early days.

But after Lord Grim had walked over to his side, Lord Grim immediately moved. He had created his own booth and then said: “At 30 Gold coins as the retail price, they’ll be sold off in an instant. It’s your own fault you didn’t want them.”

After saying this, Lord Grim’s booth was finished setting-up. Ten Frosted Stones were placed on the table. Each of them 30 Gold coins.

Bound Boat stared blankly. In the game, items had a purchase price and a retail price. The purchase price was relatively low, but was a stable path for the seller. It was very easy to find someone who would buy it. As for the retail price, the price was a bit higher. Only players who really needed it would buy it. It was difficult to say how long it would take to sell the item off. It required patience. For players that were in urgent need of money, they clearly wouldn’t set their items at a retail price.

Right now, Lord Grim set his items at a retail price. In the Heavenly Domain, the retail price for Frosted Stones were usually around 35-40 Gold coins, while the purchase price was around 30 Gold coins. Ye Xiu was set on 30 Gold coins and wouldn’t budge. In the end, Bound Boat didn’t reply, which was he just straight-up set up a booth.

30 Gold coins. For the new servers, this was considered a retail price. A retail price that required patience. But what had to be noted was that this was in the tenth server. Practically no one was selling Frosted Stones. Currently, the big guilds wouldn’t use these to make money off of them. As a result, this was extremely convenient for Ye Xiu. Right now, it looked as if he was at the very front of players in terms of levels. He had gotten a few high-leveled materials on his own and as a result was selling them however he wanted to. And moreover, he wasn’t setting up any monopoly price. It was only 30 Gold coins, the normal market price.

“Let me think, at Level 30, what equipment blueprints can Frosted Stones be used for?” Ye Xiu muttered as if talking to himself.

“Right, isn’t Soul Staff one of them? This weapon does extra damage to undead monsters, very useful. The dungeon only drops the blueprint, so you’d need Frosted Stones if you wanted it.”

“Oh, and the Polished Cross, a light-element weapon. If a Cleric uses it, then their Light Elemental skills will have increased effects. And dungeons only drop the blueprints, so you’d have to make it yourself. You should know this right? Ah? Cleric.” Ye Xiu said.

“Hm? Seeing that Berserker, I suddenly remembered that their Rock Cutter needs Frosted Stones too! Oh! He’s coming over! He’s coming over to buy! Ah, too bad. He’s not. He’s a Tachi Berserker. How unfortunate. Rock Cutter ah Rock Cutter. If you buy my Frosted Stones, you can make a Rock Cutter.” Ye Xiu reminisced.

The calm Bound Boat was finally shaken up. It was true that only the blueprints for these Purple weapons dropped. They required the secondary professions and the materials to create them. Frosted Stones were all one of the necessary materials for them. It was just 30 Gold coins. A player that wanted to make one of those Purple weapons wouldn’t hesitate to buy them, right?

Just as he was thinking, he saw a player walk forward forward: “Oh? This place is selling Frosted Stones!”

“They’re all gone. I’ve already bought them all.” Bound Boat hastily said.

Chapter 155 – Overlapping Tracking

“30 Gold coins each.” Lord Grim turned around and said to Bound Boat.

“Fine, 30 is 30!” Bound Boat said. The people who had come up to ask for the price were a couple. This type of combination was too terrifying, especially since the person who was asking was the lady. Let alone 30, even if it was 300, then that brother would still clench his teeth and pay up!

Bound Boat had immediately made a decision and rushed to buy it. Lord Grim was the seller who set up the booth. The goods were sitting there with their price tags. If anyone walked by and felt like they were a good price, then they could just buy it and walk away. Bound Boat was afraid that that brother would be too gallant and buy eight or ten without a moment of hesitation. If that were the case, how terrible would that be for him?

At this moment, Bound Boat showcased his exceptional mechanics as a veteran. He instantly closed his booth and his character stepped in front of Lord Grim’s booth. His mouse repeatedly clicked and without even looking, he instantly cleaned up Lord Grim’s entire booth. That male and female duo just stood there watching without a word. In the end, they threw out a “that guy must be mad” and then swiftly parted.

“Wow, how fast!” Ye Xiu also gasped.

“Thank you.” Bound Boat said politely.

“But did you confirm everything? Each one of them was 30 Gold coins?” Ye Xiu asked.

Bound Boat turned pale. He hastily opened up his money back and checked. In the end, he found that he wasn’t missing anything. He had lost a total of 300 Gold coins. There wasn’t any problem with the trade.

“Don’t joke……” Bound Boat felt a lingering fear in his heart! In that instant just moments ago, he really hadn’t looked at the prices. Since he was buying materials for his guild, he had a large chunk of the guild’s money. If the price had been set in the thousands of Gold coins, then it’d be impossible for him not to cry.

“If you had been able to check the prices in that short instant, then you’d really be amazing.” Ye Xiu said, while letting Lord Grim stand up: “I’m leaving.”

“Bye.” Bound Boat said in a daze as he watched Lord Grim’s figure calmly fade away into the crowds of people in the streets. After a long while, he returned back to reality and immediately reported back to Blue River.

“Lord Grim? How could that be? You bumped into him in the city? Shouldn’t he be setting the dungeon record? Did he finish?” Blue River hastily asked a bunch of questions. How could he care so much about those Frosted Stones that Bound Boat was so hesitant about? If he set the dungeon record, then why didn’t he show up on TV? Blue River carried this doubt, while he checked the records. Their Blue Brook Guild’s record still stood at the lead. The second and third place records hadn’t moved either. There was no sign of Lord Grim.

“That’s weird. Maybe they haven’t started setting it yet?” Blue River asked Bound Boat.

“How would I know…… But right now, if he’s going to set it, it should be done soon. Maybe he wasn’t able to break the record? Lord Grim was selling Frosted Stones. For someone like him, how could he come out and sell uncommon materials like this? My guess is that they might have bumped into some sort of small wall in the dungeon, which is why he needs the money so badly. He’s probably going to use it to buy some equipment?” Bound Boat really did have exceptional analytical ability. Even if he couldn’t figure out where those Frosted Stones came from, he was still able to guess the reason why Ye Xiu was selling them.

“So it’s like this….. You said ten Frosted Stones?” Only now did Blue River come to this question. Dungeons and so on weren’t under his control. If Lord Grim wanted to set it today, then he’d set it today. If he wanted to set it tomorrow, then he’d set it tomorrow. All he could do was sit and watch.

“Yeah, and from the looks of it, that’s not all he has.” Bound Boat said.

“That’s impossible. Right now the only people with more than ten Frosted Stones are all certainly from the guilds with Clubs behind them. There’s no way normal guilds can get that number and there’s no way that amount could be gathered by a single person.” Blue River said.

“That’s why I said it was strange…..” Bound Boat said.

“Maybe he’s already been bought off by some guild?” Blue River suddenly thought.

“Ha ha, we’ll see!” Bound Boat said.

“How do we see?”

“I told Thousand Creations to follow him. Let’s see who he’s going to meet up with.” Bound Boat replied.

At this moment, Blue River wasn’t the only player watching the record rankings closely. When these guild leaders thought of how such a small existence like Full Moon Guild would destroy this record, they all felt sick in their hearts. Although they didn’t feel good about it, they were helpless to do anything. Even so, they still paid close attention to the system announcements.

From 0 o’clock to 1 o’clock to 2 o’clock, the guild leaders were all feeling restless, but how could they know that Ye Xiu was just taking a stroll around the streets?

“How have things been? Have you found an equipment you want?” Ye Xiu sent Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion messages. 300 Gold coins. Since their team didn’t have any Blade Masters or any of those extremely popular classes, they had enough for three Purple weapons.

“That Scarlet Moon Lance you were talking about. I saw one.” Tang Rou replied.

“Okay. Where?” Ye Xiu asked.

After asking where each of them were, he sent them the Gold coins. They spent 190 Gold coins for two Purple weapons. They then went to a booth he saw earlier and spent 100 Gold coins on a Purple Handcannon.

“Senior, you really have a lot of money!” Steamed Bun Invasion praised and switched his weapon with the new Level 30 Purple Sandstorm Claw. His original title of God for Ye Xiu was changed to Senior, making them seem closer. Steamed Bun Invasion was very simple and made the change because of this.

“Ha ha, let’s go!” Ye Xiu said. The three then left Congee City’s busy streets.

Thousand Creations was currently following these three players. As a veteran at KSing, he was quite skilled at this. After leaving the city, the outskirts were spacious and empty, so instead of closely following behind the three, he switched routes and maintained a route parallel to them.

Seeing where those three were heading towards, it seemed like they were heading towards Line Canyon. Thousand Creations reckoned that they were just going to dungeon and nothing more. But Bound Boat had told him to pay attention to who Lord Grim was going to meet. If they were going to party up for the dungeon, then that’d be perfect, so Thousand Creations could only continue to follow them silently.

Walking and walking, Thousand Creations suddenly discovered that he wasn’t the only one following Lord Grim and the others.

With those three as the center, countless players were scattered on the map going in the same direction.

For players like this, if it was just one player, then it wouldn’t be considered weird. But at this moment, there were suddenly numerous of these types of players. If they really were headed to Line Canyon, then they’d be walking along the main road like Lord Grim and the others were. But right now, all of these trackers seemed to be experienced players like Thousand Creations. They weren’t tailing them from behind, they were taking a route parallel to theirs. With so many players doing the same thing, how could that be normal?

Thousand Creations discovered that everyone had also realized this. Some began hesitating. Some immediately changed their routes and directly followed Lord Grim from behind. Their originally secretive way suddenly seemed very normal in this weird situation.

Thousand Creations was different from the others. He ran over to the closest player and after seeing the player’s name clearly, he immediately sent Bound Boat a message: “He shouldn’t have made any agreements with Howling Heights.”

The name of the player he had looked at was from Guild Wind Howl Manor. Even though the other side had hidden his guild’s name, unlucky for him, Thousand Creations recognized his ID.

“Oh? How do you know?” Bound Boat was puzzled. He had no way of knowing how Thousand Creations had come to that conclusion.

“Because one of Wind Howl’s players is doing the same thing as me.” Thousand Creations said.

Bound Boat was speechless. It looks like this Lord Grim had captured the entire tenth server’s attention now. Before, everyone was trying to rope him in without the knowledge of the other competing guilds. But now, it looks like under this weird situation, everyone’s been exposed.

“Fussy Dawn, do you know which guild this player’s in?” Thousand Creations looked at another player’s name, except this time he didn’t recognize it. The other side had also hidden his guild’s name, so he could only let Bound Boat look it up.

“Let me check…..” After asking how his name was spelled, he contacted someone to investigate. (TL: In Chinese, many words are pronounced the same and are all written differently. Ex: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lion-Eating_Poet_in_the_Stone_Den)

Like this, Thousand Creation continued his overlapping tracking and reported 9 players to be checked. Actually, there were originally 11 players, but 2 of them had retreated after seeing the situation.

Among these 9 players, there were already five guilds that had been found: Tyrannical Ambition, Royal Heritage, Wind Howl Manor, Samsara, and Blossom Valley. These five guilds had all participated in the great tracking and saw that Lord Grim hadn’t made any agreements with anyone.

“Are you guys still continuing?” Bound Boat asked.

“Yeah, we’re almost at Line Canyon. I’ll wait until after Lord Grim enters the dungeon, then us ten can go form a team to run the dungeon. I haven’t used my entries for today yet!” Thousand Creations said.

“Alright, have fun.” Bound Boat didn’t say anything more.

They arrived at Line Canyon in the blink of an eye. Even though the game said it was a canyon, there weren’t any tall mountains. Line Canyon was a giant crack in Glory’s land. In the yellow-soiled plains, there was a large crack as if it had been cut open by a hatchet. It was long, wide, and deep. There wasn’t any kind of vegetation there, only a few animal skeletons. What lived here were poisonous insects. Of course, for players, these were all providers of experience.

As a Level 30-33 Leveling Area, Line Canyon was currently considered a high-leveled area. Unless the game was being played as a job, then only players who played the game 12 hours and up would be able to reach Level 30. There obviously weren’t many of these types of players, so at this moment, Line Canyon was quite empty.

Lord Grim and the others went down to Line Canyon. They ignored the small monsters along the way and headed directly to the dungeon. A group of players followed behind them, but after seeing who Lord Grim was calling to form parties with, they lost all hope.

Seven Fields. Sleeping Moon.

For the ones who did their homework, they all recognized that these two players were from Full Moon Guild. And not only this, each of the big guilds had already sent out spies to go join Full Moon Guild. That night, Full Moon Guild grew a lot larger. These players who had joined weren’t low-leveled.

The spies had all gathered there to figure out what exactly Lord Grim’s intent was.

And outside of this Line Canyon, there were trackers sent by their guilds to take a peek.

The big guilds were all having an extremely difficult time for this one expert. After seeing that Lord Grim and the other two party up with Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon and enter the dungeon, they all reported back, exhausted.

Once this was done, the group of players all looked at each other.

“Are we actually going to party up and run the dungeon?” Thousand Creations muttered inwardly, when the others scattered like birds.

“Tch…..” Thousand Creations disdained. He was about to leave when he saw a player killing monsters to level not far from the dungeon. His hands suddenly began to itch. His flaw flared up and he rushed over to KS that player’s monster.

Thousand Creations flaunted his talent as he fought to steal that monster, when he suddenly discovered that the players around them that were killing monsters had shaken off their monsters and were now rushing at him all at once. Thousand Creations saw that the situation wasn’t looking good and thought in astonishment: Where did all of these brave heroes come from? And they’re all gathered together in the same place too!

Chapter 156 – Power of an Encirclement

Thousand Creations was a player that sought to kill steal monsters. How many battles had he gone through because of KSing? So when it came to PK, Thousand Creation had plenty of experience.

An army of heroes? Thousand Creations didn’t believe it. The player who he had stolen from wasn’t some girl. How could there so many heroes just hanging around? Now that the crowd of players arrived, the answer was too clear: they were originally together.

“How interesting!” Thousand Creations swept over the surroundings. Some of the players rushing over were far away, while some were close. In this instant, he didn’t have enough time to count how them, though there were at least 20 players. Thousand Creation’s Neutral Chaser buffed his movement speed, so he moved quickly. He saw an opening in the crowd of players and slipped into it.

“Bang!” The other side’s long-ranged Gunners hadn’t arrived yet, but their bullets had. Thousand Creations hastily dodged. The artillery shell exploded. The shock wave from the explosion was larger than Thousand Creations had anticipated and had unexpectedly hit his side.

Thousand Creations reacted quickly. He pulled his body back in mid-air and steadied himself. In Glory, “Knockback” was a type of CC effect. But with these types of shockwave attacks, their knockbacks effects were more chaotic and caused the target to lose balance. However, the target could steady himself. If it wasn’t done right, then the target might get Knocked Down to the ground. And for the CC “Knock Down”, players had no way of countering it with normal movements. Only skills like Quick Recover could counter it.

With this shot, Thousand Creations had already failed to take advantage of the key moment. The crowd of players closed in and the original opening had been repaired. All sorts of classes stood in position. The several close-combat classes had already advanced and surrounded Thousand Creations.

“Not good……” Thousand Creations had already fallen into despair. He knew that the situation was already hopeless, but he didn’t want to give up. He shouted, brandished his battle lance, and rushed forward trying to take one down with him. But his hopes were all a dream and in the end, Thousand Creations was killed off with practically zero casualties on the other side.

“Who are these guys!” Thousand Creations, who had revived in Congee City, thought, while sending a few names to Bound Boat, hoping that he would help him look them up. These were names which he had worked hard to get while fighting that crowd. But he had died way too quickly and wasn’t able to remember too many names in that short amount of time.

“Huh? Why are there so many?” Bound Boat asked.

“Don’t worry about that. Just look them up for me!” Thousand Creations said.

“Did you stir up trouble again?” Bound Boat asked.

Thousand Creations was silent. His existence in the guild was quite special. Usually, players like him with such a nasty habit wouldn’t be kept by the big guilds. But Blue Brook Guild appreciated his skill, so they still let him into the guild. Because Thousand Creations was in a big guild, getting good equipment was much easier. For example, right now, he already had a completed Scarlet Moon Set and his Level 30 Coiling Snake Lance was a rare Purple weapon. If he wasn’t a part of Blue Brook Guild, how could he have gotten these equipment so easily?

Even though the guild took care of Thousand Creations, there was no way they could support his misdeeds. Thousand Creations had no objections towards this. This was also why whether he lived or died in these large or small battles depended on himself. He could not involve the guild.

As a result, this time, Thousand Creations was still planning on going in solo to resolve the problem. There was nothing wrong with using the guild’s resources though!

After reviving in Congee City, Thousand Creations had to recover from his Weakened state, so he slowly walked towards Line Canyon, while waiting for Bound Boat’s reply. In his heart, he felt that there was something weird about those players’ actions. If they were there just for leveling in the wild, twenty players in a group was a bit ridiculous. Moreover, these players were all fighting separately. What was the point in being in a group?

Even Thousand Creations, with his experienced eyes of a KSer, couldn’t see that these players were in a group. And since they were, why were they so scattered? What exactly was their plan?

As Thousand Creations slowly walked over, his Weakened state gradually disappeared. He had lost 10% of his EXP with this death. Apart from this, his equipment had also lost some durability and he lost some of his Gold coins. These were all fixed. None of his equipment dropped though. In the normal servers, the chances of equipment dropping at death wasn’t high.

“Thousand Creations, I wasn’t able to figure out where these guys are from. At least, they’re not from the big guilds.” Bound Boat’s message finally arrived.

“Oh.” Thousand Creations wasn’t too surprised. The world was wide. With so many players, how could Blue Brook Guild have information on everyone. The ones they paid closer attention to were those guilds with Clubs that they were competing against. If they weren’t from those guilds, then those that they knew were extremely limited.

“Hold back a bit. Don’t stir up too much trouble in the new server.” Bound Boat didn’t completely block him. If Thousand Creations was the type of person that could be stopped, then he wouldn’t be in that position. Bound Boat also reminded him to not bring the guild into his affairs at the very least. Although it was somewhat heartless, Thousand Creations liked this sort of special position.

He slowly walked until his Weakened state was completely eliminated. Only then did Thousand Creations start jogging. Jogging was faster than walking, but slower than Swift Running. However, Swift Running consumed the player’s stamina, so most players Jogged to hurry forward.

He quickly returned to Line Canyon, but he didn’t charge in. The other side had twenty or so people. If he directly challenged them, then wasn’t that certain death? Thousand Creations planned on waiting for the right opportunity and then striking. He didn’t care despicable or low he was. As someone who liked to KS, such a principle practically didn’t exist.

If his name could be hidden like his guild’s name, how great would that be! Thousand Creations lamented. He chose an entrance to Line Canyon and then sneakily headed towards that direction.

Line Canyon was extremely quiet. The only sounds were the rustling of the poisonous insects there. Thousand Creations ignored these monsters and hurried over to the place where those players were. When he got close, he slowed down and after carefully analyzing the terrain, he crouched over to behind a dirt mound and snuck his head out.

One, two, three……

From here, he could see three players. They were all minding their own business and fighting by themselves. Thousand Creations hadn’t been too vigilant before, but now that he was more aware, he saw that although these three were fighting their own monsters, their positions were all in a range where they could help each other if needed. He looked again from a different angle and found two others. They were also fighting separately, but they maintained a distance not too far from each other.

This is going to be difficult….. Thousand Creations furrowed his brow.

These people were ready to work together at a moment’s notice, which made it difficult for him to find an opening. But why were these guys doing things like this? What were they trying to do?

Thousand Creations was hiding far away from them. He switched positions many times, seeing each of the twenty or so people at least once. He pulled out a piece of paper and drew the positions for each of them.

Their current positions seemed a bit different from before. These people had gathered together closer to one side. Thousand Creations looked at the paper while thinking of this. He looked at the entire drawing from afar and from an overall perspective, Thousand Creations immediately saw something. Their positions were all directed towards the dungeon entrance! Were these guys waiting to ambush someone? Were they waiting for someone to go in or someone to come out?

Hm? Thousand Creations suddenly thought of someone, an extreme anomaly in the tenth server.

Lord Grim, were they waiting for him?

Thousand Creations couldn’t help but think of this. But these twenty or so people didn’t look like they had good intentions. Even though the wind was blowing in Lord Grim’s direction, could he have angered someone? Even if he refused all of the big guild’s invite this time and ran to help Full Moon Guild, they shouldn’t have gone so far as to send people out to kill him right?

Thousand Creations thought of this and sent Bound Boat another message: “Are you sure these players aren’t from a big guild?”

“I’m certain that they’re not from a big guild. Why?”

“Looking at their positions, it looks like they’re waiting to attack Lord Grim.” Thousand Creations said.

“What type of players are they?” Bound Boat asked.

“They’re outside Line Canyon dungeon. They’re acting like they’re leveling on their own, but it’s clear that they’re in an encirclement around players coming out of the dungeon.” Thousand Creations said.

“Who did Lord Grim offend?” Bound Boat was puzzled.

“I don’t know either…..” Thousand Creations was also puzzled, when he suddenly heard a movement from nearby. Hiding behind the dirt mound, Thousand Creations immediately extended his head to look and saw that five players had come out of the dungeon. If that wasn’t Lord Grim and his group, then he didn’t know who was.

Thousand Creations wasn’t yet sure whether he should give Lord Grim a heads up, when that ambush group had already begun moving.

So those guys really were looking for him?

This time, Thousand Creations counted carefully. If he hadn’t messed up, then there were a total of 24 people.

The 24 moved out like the wind. In one second, Thousand Creations saw them running. And in the next, the gunners fired their bullets, the mages cast their magic, and the close combat classes rushed forward from all different directions. In particular, at the entrance, six characters immediately stood on guard.

Thousand Creations then saw Lord Grim suddenly lift up his battle lance and use a Sky Strike. This move unexpectedly launched his four companions into the air. Thousand Creations was taken by surprise. First, he had no idea why Lord Grim had attacked his own allies. Second, he didn’t understand how his Sky Strike had launched all four targets into the air. According to Thousand Creation’s knowledge and what he knew from guides, Sky Strike could only launch three targets at once! To hit up an extra one, how fast was his hand speed?

“Bang!” Lord Grim had sent out a palm, unexpectedly hitting his four allies. The four flew out at the same time. Only then did Thousand Creations suddenly realize what Lord Grim intended to do.

He had impressively executed this even faster and sent his four allies outside of the encirclement in an instant. The formation those 24 players were in could dissolve escapes from any direction, but this method was certainly outside of their expectations. Thousand Creations had studied the paper he had drawn with their positions for awhile and believed that he hadn’t judged incorrectly. This move by Lord Grim had definitely messed up the other side’s plan.

“Peng!”

Another gun sound. This time, Thousand Creations saw Lord Grim jump and use Aerial Fire, chasing after his four allies.

Sky Strike, Falling Flower Palm, Aerial Fire!

These three moves were completed in an instant, almost quicker than how fast Thousand Creations could think. By the time he understood what had happened, Lord Grim’s party of five had already completely escaped from the encirclement, heading towards his dirt mound. As for those 24 players, their carefully planned encirclement had been foiled in less than a second and were now chasing after them in chaos.

Chapter 157 – Running Test

“Go to that dirt mound!!” Thousand Creations heard Lord Grim yell this. Just as he was trying to see which dirt mound Lord Grim was talking about, he saw three of the four players quickly rush up to in front of him.

Why three? Because when Ye Xiu used Falling Flower Palm to blow them away, they had to use Quick Recover in order to prevent themselves from getting knocked down. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion acted skillfully. On the other hand, Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon didn’t do as well. Seven Fields failed in the end and crashed to the ground. Since he had to climb back up, of course he was bit slower than the others.

“Woah! There’s someone here and it looks like he’s pooping!” Steamed Bun Invasion yelled. The three ran over and saw Thousand Creations crouching down vulgarly behind the dirt mound.

“Sh*t!” Thousand Creations disagreed with this description. He was waiting there to ambush, how could he be pooping! But worse was what came after. He heard Lord Grim shout without any hesitation: “Kill him!”

“F*ck f*ck f*ck!” Thousand Creations cursed as he did a backwards roll. A scarlet blade flashed by his eyes. The fastest and fiercest on that side was that female battle mage. Thousand Creations recognized that the scarlet battle lance was the Level 30 Purple weapon Scarlet Moon, which just barely missed him.

Having missed, Soft Mist took a step forward to try again. All in all, Thousand Creations had some skill and after rolling, he returned back with a Sky Strike. Soft Mist sidestepped it and then with a practiced coordination, Steamed Bun Invasion slyly snuck behind Thousand Creations and smashed down with a Brick.

At this moment, the tardy Lord Grim finally arrived. With a glance, he recognized Thousand Creation’s ID and then hastily said to Steamed Bun Invasion: “Wait, he’s not with them.”

“You know who they are?” Thousand Creations heard this and felt like Lord Grim knew where those enemies came from, so he promptly asked.

“I have a rough idea.” Ye Xiu said.

“Who are they?” Thousand Creations asked.

“How about we start running first before we start chatting?” Lord Grim led the way out. Those four closely followed behind and Thousand Creations had no choice and also followed along. Of those twenty four pursuers, the long-ranged classes continuously fired at them. Thousand Creations madly dashed in an S path, so that the other side had no way of accurately firing at him. He then Swift Ran to catch up to those five and found that Lord Grim was unexpectedly teaching those four other players.

“There are three types of movements: Walk, Jog, and Swift Run. Swift Run is the fastest, but also uses your stamina. Walking is the slowest, but it’ll slowly recover stamina. Jogging is neither fast nor slow, but won’t use up your stamina. Directly using Swift Run will obviously let you move the fastest in a short amount of time, but once you run out of stamina and start Jogging, an experienced opponent will definitely catch you. See, look at that Thousand Creations. Right now he’s using Swift Run to get past us, but this is only temporary. Everyone follow my tempo and pay attention to how I switch between these three types of movement. After half a minute, he’ll be left behind.”

“F*ck!” Having been used as a teaching material, Thousand Creations gloomily stopped. Just as he was about to speak, those five ran past him. That Steamed Bun Invasion even asked: “He suddenly stopped. What type of move is this?”

“The I-want-to-be-blown-to-bits move.” Lord Grim said.

“Bang!”

An artillery shell exploded near Thousand Creations. His mind blurred and he flopped through the air. Fortunately, he was able to use Quick Recover in time and after rolling, he swiftly dashed and caught up to those five players.

“He caught up again.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“This method is even worse. He was even hit by an attack.” Ye Xiu said.

Thousand Creations was so angry, he spat blood. When he carefully looked at those five players, under Lord Grim’s constant reminders, those five players repeatedly switched between the three types of movements. There was no set tempo. They would sometimes move one way for a minute and sometimes even move another way for only two or three steps. Thousand Creations involuntarily copying what they were doing. In the end, that loud-mouthed Steamed Bun Invasion said: “It looks like he’s copying us?”

“Too late. His initial stamina was different from ours, so he’ll definitely use up his stamina first and will be blown to bits in the end.” Ye Xiu said.

“It’s no good if your stamina is too low.” Steamed Bun Invasion sympathized.

Thousand Creations grinded his teeth. He didn’t have a habit of asking others for help. At this moment, even though he copied how Lord Grim and the others were moving, it looked like he’d have to rely on himself in the end because that Lord Grim said that he’d be the first to run out of stamina……..

Thousand Creations glanced at his stamina. It really was running low. And even though the twenty four players behind him hadn’t caught up, the distance between them had clearly shrunken.

“Hey, can we actually escape from them?” Thousand Creations asked.

“The distance between us has shrunken? It’s only temporary.” Ye Xiu replied.

Sure enough, after their opponents madly Swift Ran at them, only a few were able to catch up. And after their stamina ran out and they began Jogging, the distance between the two sides gradually widened.

“We really have pulled away!!” Steamed Bun Invasion cheered.

“We have? Then there’s no need to run anymore.” Ye Xiu laughed.

“Why?”

“Because through this test, I can already tell that our enemies’ skill levels aren’t too high. We could even try fighting with them.” Ye Xiu said.

“We only have five.” Seven Fields reminded.

“Six, no? Thousand Creations is a person too!” Ye Xiu said.

“This is the Internet. In the Internet, there’s no way you can tell if the person is real or fake.” Steamed Bun Invasion said solemnly.

“He’s spoken before.” Ye Xiu helplessly said.

Thousand Creations was extremely gloomy, but at this moment, Lord Grim stopped and turned around.

“Look, among those 24 players, there’s only one of them that has some skill. It’s that Battle Mage over there.” Ye Xiu said. He then had his Lord Grim move up to face them and shout: “Chen Yehui, is that you?”

Those 24 players stopped moving. The valley fell deathly silent.

Having been called out, Chen Yehui felt extremely depressed. His plans had been ruined from the very start.

Liu Hao had to take care of the team’s performance, so he could no longer afford to get distracted and tangle with Ye Qiu in the game. As a result, Liu Hao had handed the task of obstructing Ye Qiu’s progress to him.

But to go against Ye Qiu, what methods did he have? Without any pro-players to help, there was no way he could compete in the dungeon records. After thinking for awhile, in the end, he realized his greatest advantage: manpower.

This time, he personally brought the guild to pioneer in the new server. His ambitions weren’t small. Compared to other guilds, their manpower in the tenth server was the greatest.

Originally, Excellent Dynasty had intended to compete strongly against the other big guilds and restore their former glory. But who could have known that Lord Grim would appear and cause a storm? Right now, there was only one thing in the competition between the big guilds. It was to see who could win over Lord Grim’s help.

Chen Yehui was extremely bitter! He already knew who Lord Grim was, so he didn’t have any hopes that Lord Grim would help their Excellent Dynasty. He could be considered as one of the Club’s official staff, so he had quite a lot of knowledge on the reasons for Ye Qiu’s retirement. For the current Ye Qiu to not deliberately look for trouble with Excellent Dynasty was already very nice of him.

It was impossible for Chen Yehui to win over Lord Grim, so he could only carefully prepare to fight against Lord Grim. They originally didn’t have many empty accounts left, so he specially leveled many new ones just for this occasion. After all of their trouble of catching up to Lord Grim and reaching Level 30, Chen Yehui immediately moved out without any hesitation. He wanted to take advantage of this opportunity to strike at Ye Qiu. If not, then if that guy ran to some guild for shelter, then their advantage would be gone.

Unfortunately, after carefully creating a formation that he thought would be impossible to break, none of the plans he had prepared were used. Lord Grim’s immediate attack to send the four players out of the encirclement was completely out of his expectations. Chen Yehui’s numerous plans had been destroyed in an instant.

Chen Yehui obviously wasn’t satisfied. Even though the encirclement had been broken, he still had the advantage in numbers, so he had everyone chase them.

In the end, right when it looked like they were about to escape, they suddenly stopped and then faced towards them.

“Your movements are too poor, Chen Yehui.” Ye Xiu continued to say, “I’ve already completely seen through your group’s strength.”

Chen Yehui stared blankly. He finally realized that their chase had been a test. That type of control over movements could be considered high-end pro-level content. There were very few normal players who could do it well. Ye Xiu had tested them to immediately know whether Liu Hao or other pro-level players were among the group. If it was just more people, then there was nothing to be afraid of.

“What are you trying to do?” Thousand Creations went over and asked him.

“Wipe them out.” Ye Xiu calmly replied.

“Are you crazy?”

“Do you want to join in?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Are you….. for real?”

“If not, then why wouldn’t we be running right now?” Ye Xiu said.

“There’s only six of us!”

“The number of people doesn’t matter. In a team battle, teamwork is the most important.” Ye Xiu said.

“Fine! Then let’s see just how capable you are.” Thousand Creations brandished his lance and walked up.

“Get ready to move out!” Ye Xiu yelled.

“Yes!”

“Ready!”

“Forward!” Thousand Creations also shouted, but Steamed Bun Invasion and Soft Mist had already rushed forward. They, along with Lord Grim, had begun fighting. No one had come up to ask for his help.

“Huh?” Thousand Creations stared blankly. Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon had already walked up to him.

“Just relax and be our support!” Seven Fields said.

With just this, they moved ahead and joined in the slaughter. Lord Grim, Soft Mist, Steamed Bun Invasion stood back to back in a triangle formation. They directly stormed through the crowd of enemies. It looked as if a flood had swept over and drowned them, when blood suddenly began flying out. However, it wasn’t from any of those three, but rather from their enemies.

“More people really is an advantage but there has to at least certain amount!” Ye Xiu said. Lord Grim suddenly left their triangle formation and rushed out. He flew forward with a Collapsing Mountain towards Chen Yehui’s dispatched troops.

Chen Yehui’s thinking was very simple too. He didn’t care if others lived or died. As long as they could kill Lord Grim, then it would be their victory!

Chapter 158 – He Really is an Expert at KSing

Chen Yehui’s intentions were clear, but the nature of Ye Xiu’s attacks were even more so. Ye Xiu had completely seen through Chen Yehui’s plans. This Collapsing Mountain attacked the core of the enemy’s group. The shockwave spread out. Those who reacted slower weren’t able to dodge it in time. They hadn’t even gotten into formation yet and many had already been hit askew.

Sky Strike, Falling Flower!

Lord Grim’s weapon closed and his battle lance executed two Battle Mage skills, launching four players into the sky.

After lifting his legs and kicking another, his Thousand Chance Umbrella transformed into the gun form. The bullets shot out and this player was hit back in a burst of blood; Ye Xiu had fired BBQ in a straight line. This usage of the move had to be done extremely quickly. Right when the target was hit into the air, the skill had to be used. The theory behind it was the same as how Witches tried to fly as low as possible.

The enemy player that had been knocked back smashed into numerous others. The player hadn’t flown far, but had hit three others.

The formation Chen Yehui had tried to set up was destroyed in three attacks. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion were now sending out attacks separately, one on the left, one on the right. They attacked incomparably fast. In just a few moments, although only a few enemies had been killed, there weren’t many that were still standing.

Of Chen Yehui’s 24 thugs, 1 died, 13 were on the ground, and the other 10 were spinning around in confusion. Lord Grim, Soft Mist, and Steamed Bun Invasion were once again back-to-back in a triangle formation. They stood there in the middle of the circle with their weapons raised. The pressure they emitted crushed down on the enemies.

Thousand Creations was stunned, completely stunned.

So six players was unnecessary? With just these three players, the 24 enemy offensive was thoroughly suppressed.

Thousand Creations had fought with the enemies before. Even though he had been killed extremely quickly, this only meant that the other side’s strength and coordination weren’t weak. But against these three players, why did they look like scraps of paper? It hadn’t even been a minute yet and their encirclement no longer existed. Some were lying on the ground. Some were spinning around trying to find the correct direction. Some were standing still not daring to act.

Strong…… too strong!

Thousand Creations admired them.

As a person who always went solo, he always wanted to stand majestically in the midst of disarrayed enemies. And now, this dream became a reality. Even though there were only three people, this really was the dream he always imagined.

At this moment, the other side’s characters were clearly still moving, but Thousand Creations felt as if time had stopped. Because in his eyes, those guys were only background characters. They were completely ignored. In his eyes, only those three figures existed.

“Gunners, open fire!!!”

“Witches, mess up their sight!!”

“Blade Masters, what are you doing! Stay in position!!!”

“Summoners, you idiots! Get into position before summoning! F*CK!! Interrupted again! Go f*cking die!!”

Chen Yehui’s commands continued to be shouted out, but it was useless, completely useless.

Bullets and artillery shells flew through the air. But in the end, they simply became background noise and added to the scene’s atmosphere. They had virtually no impact. The other side’s pathing and tempo were far better than their rate of fire.

Witches wanted to use their quick flying to mess up their opponent’s line of sight? Whenever they flew by their opponent’s line of sight, they’d be swatted down and form a crater on the ground.

Blade Masters stay in position? The Blade Masters were lost! What were their positions? How come it seemed like they were getting farther and farther away from the battle?

As for the Summoners…… how terrible! Summoners had to summon their pets to help fight. However, summoning had a casting time. The battle had gone on for so long and their previously summoned pets had been killed long ago without ever recovering. No matter what direction they ran towards, every time they tried casting, a bullet would interrupt them.

The unfortunate Summoners all felt the same: these bullets were their most faithful summons. Whenever they started summoning, a bullet would immediately be called to them.

Thousand Creations had already turned hot-blooded. He ran towards Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon and yelled: “Let’s go up too!”

“Go up to do what?” Seven Fields asked.

“Fight!” Thousand Creations said.

“How about we just stay out of their way?” Seven Fields said.

“What!? Get in their way!!” Sleeping Moon suddenly erupted. Even though he’d mixed in with Lord Grim recently, he still hadn’t forgotten their initial enmity! Lord Grim still hadn’t added him as a friend yet.

“Forward!” Sleeping Moon unsheathed his sword and rushed forward. Thousand Creations also raised his lance and went forward too.

The other side were currently being crushed into tears, when newcomers suddenly joined the battle. The situation became even more alarming initially, but after trading a few blows, some immediately yelled out excitedly: “Ha ha, these two are easy to deal with!!”

“Really, really!!” Everyone grew excited. Quite a few immediately ran off to fight those two. The Lord Grim trio unexpectedly became ignored.

At this moment, Chen Yehui, Thousand Creations, Sleeping Moon all became one family. They almost died from anger.

The family felt the same pressure. Chen Yehui instantly became marked by Ye Xiu and the others, while Thousand Creations and Sleeping Moon became everyone’s prey.

Both side’s reactions were unanimous: if you can’t beat them, then run. Chen Yehui went left. Thousand Creations and Sleeping Moon went right. They started running in retreat.

Seven Fields hastily went to the side. He just hoped that everyone would put him as a background character.

“Hey, hey! There’s another one!!” Unfortunately, his hopes were crushed. The other side had also included him in the chase.

Seven Field’s cheeks streamed with tears. He had no other choice and escaped with Sleeping Moon. The originally solemn battlefield instantly turned into a clown fiesta. Ye Xiu was also speechless and sighed towards the frantically running Thousand Creations: “He really is an expert at KSing…….”

Fortunately, not everyone was unfaithful. There was still a portion of them that continued to fight with Ye Xiu and the others. Unfortunately, their forces had thinned and they had no way of contesting with Ye Xiu and the others. Chen Yehui ran off and saw that the three hadn’t chased him, so he immediately began shouting orders again. But there weren’t as many people as before. And half of them were out of position, so his leading was completely pointless.

Down. Down.

People continued to fall down.

In Line Canyon, the sound of fighting gradually lessened. As every person fell down, the noise quieted down.

“Not good!” Tang Rou said.

Not good? The other side heard this and immediately brightened. Was it no more health or no more mana?

“What?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Too weak.” Tang Rou said.

Everyone’s cheeks streamed with tears. So it was because they weren’t good…..

“Even if they’re weak, we still have to focus! That’s the respect our opponents deserve!” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“Well said, Steamed Bun.” Ye Xiu said.

“Yup!” Steamed Bun Invasion was immensely satisfied and then continued to bully others.

On the other side, Thousand Creations and the others were currently being bullied around. They were covering their heads and running away with their tails behind them. In the end, they didn’t die because the other side felt a bit embarrassed. Their boss, Chen Yehui, had been roaring at them the entire time. If they kept on acting like they didn’t hear him, that wasn’t good. But just as they were about to circle back, they found that there was no need to go through that trouble. Their more loyal allies had been cleaned up well by Lord Grim’s group, who was now heading towards them.

Thousand Creations and his group saw this and went hid behind Lord Grim’s trio.

The remnants of the enemies couldn’t hold on any longer. Their allies had either died or ran away. At this point, even Thousand Creations could recognize that Chen Yehui was the leader. Thousand Creation had once died at their hands and still had some personal enmity. He chased after him, not letting up in the slightest. Chen Yehui also kept on running. The two were of the same class, so their movement speed were about the same. But Chen Yehui was clearly slightly more skilled and their distance gradually increased.

Thousand Creations immediately recalled what Lord Grim had said about switching between the different types of movements and asked: “How should I run?”

No answer. Thousand Creations looked around left and right. There was no one there! At this moment, he unexpectedly became the only one chasing.

Thousand Creations promptly halted.

“Well, I can’t chase him down anyways…..” Thousand Creations said. He then turned around and ran back. But when he got to Line Canyon, Lord Grim and the others were no longer there. It looked as if a battle had never taken place. Line Canyon was already completely silent.

“Where’d everyone go?” Thousand Creations muttered. He didn’t have any of them as friends, so he had no way of asking them. He ran around Line Canyon for half an hour but couldn’t find anyone. In the end, he went back to his initial position, when a light suddenly flashed outside of the dungeon and five players came out.

Thousand Creations glanced at the five IDs and coughed blood. It was Lord Grim and the others. After the battle, these five actually went back to dungeon. They didn’t even give him a heads up. He had been looking around for the battle everywhere, but during that time, they were actually dungeoning.

“Hey!” Thousand Creations called out to them, when the five entered the dungeon again.

“F*ck f*ck f*ck!!” Thousand Creation’s cheeks streamed with tears.

I’m out of here!

Thousand Creations turned his head and left Line Canyon.

Compared to Thousand Creations, Chen Yehui was even more gloomy. He had been secretly paying attention to Lord Grim for a long time and had prepared a meticulous plan, but when the time came, there wasn’t a single chance of victory for them. Starting from the very first second, they had been completely suppressed by the other side and had to run away.

On the fields of Line Canyon, Chen Yehui didn’t see any of his comrades. Of those 24 players, including him, only six survived. The others all died.

Experience, money, durability, even equipment……. Chen Yehui could ignore these losses, but he still felt his heart hurt.

It was like he was a student who had meticulously studied for an exam. He had grasped all of the rules for arithmetic extremely well. And after walking into the test full of confidence, he saw the test. Sh*t! The test was on calculus. The difference was just too big!

The current Chen Yehui stifled this type of deep feeling of powerlessness. Against pro-players, using this type of battle to cause trouble was worthless.

Chapter 159 – Furry Guest

After running Line Canyon three times, it was around four in the morning. Ye Xiu stretched and got up to move around. Seeing this, Tang Rou also got up to get some water. She took her tea cup and slipped away to the front desk.

“Are those people gone?” Tang Rou drank her tea, while asking.

“Who knows!” Ye Xiu said.

“What type of hate is there between you and them?” Tang Rou asked. In the game, of course everyone had asked who those people were. Ye Xiu just said a few words and left it at that. Steamed Bun Invasion didn’t care. Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon always had that respectful look towards Ye Xiu and knew in their hearts that the two parties involved weren’t on the same level, so even though they were curious, they didn’t question too closely.

Only Tang Rou, who was the closest to Ye Xiu, heard Ye Xiu say those words and then connected them with those guys who were making trouble for him in the Internet Cafe last time.

‘Hmm……. how do I say it? It’s probably because they don’t want to see me in front of them ever again!” Ye Xiu said.

“How did you offend them?” Tang Rou asked.

“There was a time when I didn’t want to see them in front of me ever again too.” Ye Xiu said.

Tang Rou stared blankly. Even though she hadn’t known Ye Xiu for very long, she knew that he was a very carefree person. She had difficulty imagining that such a person could seriously hate someone.

“Can I ask why?” Tang Rou asked.

“Because they weren’t professional enough.” Ye Xiu said.

“Not professional enough?”

“You know that guy we ran into tonight? To a certain extent, I ended that guy’s pro career.” Ye Xiu said.

“Why?”

“Didn’t I already say it? It’s because he wasn’t professional enough.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh……” Tang Rou understood, “You’re not wrong.”

“Of course.” Ye Xiu grinned.

“But you already left, so why are they still bothering you? It looks like they’re afraid of you coming back. So then it looks like…… you were forced to leave?” Tang Rou said.

“Oh? How smart!” Ye Xiu was amazed.

“It looks like you didn’t completely cut them off, so you left them a chance to bite you back. If not, then how could you be chased and pressured by them?” Tang Rou said.

“Yup! I was too lazy. I should have worked a bit harder.” Ye Xiu said.

“Or maybe you hadn’t thought of completely cutting them off?” Tang Rou said, but didn’t wait for Ye Xiu to reply. She raised her right arm and waved it twice. “Boneyard, we can still do it four times!!” She said, while returning back to her seat.

The night went by like this. After morning came, they ate breakfast and discussed things. Chen Guo woke up and saw these two looking like they were treating the game as work. While eating the breakfast those two bought back, she shook her head and scolded them. This was already a daily task in Happy Internet Cafe.

After eating breakfast, the two went to rest. Tang Rou used to switch between the morning and afternoon shifts, but because she was now playing the game all-night every day, if she took the morning shift, then she’d have to endure through the morning shift before she could sleep. Chen Guo had seen her tired face sprawled on the reception desk and couldn’t bear it anymore, so she simply made it so that she only had afternoon shifts. All night was all night! She would at least have a set schedule.

The day continued on like this. 11 o’clock, the Internet Cafe’s busy day ended, while these two’s day were just beginning. Speaking of this, Ye Xiu’s time in-game was actually a bit longer than Tang Rou. After all, he was playing the game when he was on shift too, while Tang Rou didn’t have as easy as a time when she was on shift. During that time, her leveling speed wasn’t high, so most of her time was spent on looking at the guides Ye Xiu had sent to her. She would also frequently be interrupted even while doing that.

When midnight approached, the team gathered, ready to challenge Desolate Land’s record again. Full Moon Guilds’ guild leader Maple Tree confidently came and narrated the practice he did that day, which earned Senior Steamed Bun’s praise.

But when midnight hit, Su Mucheng hadn’t come online.

“Where’s Mu Mu?” Tang Rou asked. After so many days of playing the game together, everyone had become quite familiar with each other. The names the girls called each other clearly showed that they were close. This one called that one Mumu. That one called this one Rou Rou. Neither of them cared if others felt sick hearing them.

“I have no idea!” Ye Xiu was also very puzzled. If Su Mucheng wasn’t going to come, then she’d definitely leave him a message. But in-game or QQ, there was no sign of one. Cell phone……. Ye Xiu didn’t have that yet. He didn’t use cell phones.

‘Could something have happened?” Ye Xiu muttered in his heart. He grabbed the phone next to the computer and was just about to go ask, when suddenly a customer knocked on the reception desk.

“Computer.” The customer’s voice sounded unclear. Ye Xiu lifted his head to look. What a guy! Was it really that cold today? This person was wearing a thick furry overcoat and a furry hat. The large furry scarf covered the person’s entire face. Only two eyes could be seen. Every other part of this person’s body was covered in fur.

Ye Xiu sighed and put down the phone: “You win. You’ve finally dressed in a way that even I can’t recognize you.”

“Really?” The person that came pulled down her scarf. It looked like she was quite satisfied with her disguise: “I also felt like no one would be able to recognize me.”

“But don’t you think that you’d stand out in the Internet Cafe like this?’ Ye Xiu said.

“It’s not like there are a lot of people here.” Su Mucheng turned her head and scanned the Internet Cafe. The customers were thinly scattered. Business during the night was naturally very different from business during the day.

“You could have just stayed in your room. What was the point in running over here so late at night.”

“I was bored, so I came looking to play with you.” Su Mucheng said.

“Let me figure out where you should go sit…….” Ye Xiu got up and looked around the Internet Cafe. Last time, Huang Shaotian had hid up in that empty corner, where there was no lights or air conditioning, where it was dark and cold. Ye Xiu looked around and then he patted the seat beside him, said: “How about over there?”

“Not bad!” Su Mucheng liked it and took a seat there.

Ye Xiu helped her turn on her computer and then warned her: “This is the server computer, so don’t mess around with anything. If not, then all of the Internet Cafe computers will die.”

“It’s that fun?”

“It’s not fun at all!” Ye Xiu stressed.

“Hurry up and log in. We’re all waiting for you!” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay okay.” Su Mucheng didn’t take off her hat and logged into the game like this.

“She’s here. She’s finally here.” Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was still with everyone. When Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist came on, she heard everyone’s pleasant surprised voices.

“Yeah. She’s here.” Ye Xiu said, but didn’t say if the person was coming directly over.

“Where are you?” Su Mucheng turned her head to see where Ye Xiu and the others were and then rushed over.

“Sorry, I’m late.” Su Mucheng greeted everyone.

“It’s not a problem. Being late is a girl’s privilege.” Steamed Bun Invasion said. Coming from this guy’s mouth, no one could tell if he was joking or trying to win her favor……. or maybe he was actually serious.

“Cough. I won’t say too much. Let’s start?” Ye Xiu put on his headphones and said.

“Let’s go, let’s go.” Steamed Bun Invasion seemed to regard Ye Xiu as the commander while he was the vanguard. He loved to be at the front and was always the first to go in.

Soft Mist and Maple Tree also rushed in. Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist was just about to go in too, when Ye Xiu told her to stop.

“Take this.” Ye Xiu sent her a trade request.

“What is it?” Su Mucheng accepted the trade request and looked, it was a Level 30 Purple Handcannon.

“You bought it for me?”

“Of course.”

“How much?”

“100.”

“How cheap.”

“That’s not cheap in the new server!” Ye Xiu said.

“But you’re rich!” Su Mucheng said. She obviously knew of Ye Xiu’s bets with Tiny Herb. He had won over almost the entire guild’s storehouse.

The two chatted as they entered the dungeon. The five players officially started.

Ye Xiu and the other three didn’t have any problems with their coordination. As for Maple Tree, everything that needed to be made clear had already been made clear. It was fortunate that he wasn’t a noob and was familiar with the dungeon. After Ye Xiu explained the theory behind the strategy, he grasped the concepts very quickly, but was a bit lacking in practice. However, now that Su Mucheng, Tang Rou, and Steamed Bun obtained new Purple weapons, their damage output was much higher and as long as Maple Tree wasn’t too off, then they’d be able to make up for his weaknesses.

As soon as these four entered the dungeon, they had already found their targets. Maple Tree immediately did as he was ordered the day before and Aerial Fired up to the window.

The five bullets from his Aerial Fire wasn’t wasted either and headed towards the monsters Lord Grim had pulled. However, when his character reached the window, the monsters that were fired at were already angrily chasing after him.

“O……” Maple Tree stopped his “OT” halfway because those aggroed monsters were instantly taken back by Lord Grim with a Circle Swing.

“Beautiful.” Ye Xiu praised him.

Maple Tree shook his head. He reminded himself that he wasn’t in a normal dungeon team and he had to get rid of those wrong notions. In this team, OT and so on didn’t exist. All he had to do was put out damage. The fiercer he was the faster they would advance. That was his task.

As he thought, Maple Tree ferociously fired at the monsters Lord Grim was attacking.

“So good!” Maple Trees said. This was DPS! When he attacked before, he had to always pay attention to the MT. That truly didn’t feel as good!

Maple Tree fired his pistol happily. The other monsters had already been pulled over. Cleansing Mist flew up to the high grounds and attacked like she did the day before. However, today, Maple Tree didn’t need Su Mucheng to tell him where those two monsters in the center were at. After understanding the theory behind the strategy, he could already figure out where he should be attacking.

Although he could openly let out his damage, he still had to coordinate with everyone! The damage he put out couldn’t just be fired out at random.

This first wave of 12 monsters was cleared much faster than the day before. When the last monster died, Ye Xiu glanced at the time. Sure enough, there was a big improvement.

“Keep it up everyone! Let’s break the record on our first try.” Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 160 – Suppressed

The Desolate Land dungeon was located at an abandoned castle. The inside had a lot of side routes, so first-time runners would often take the wrong path. And for those who were there for experience, they often took the wrong paths on purpose in order to clear the entire dungeon. As for those who were there to set a record, they naturally wanted to take the most direct path to the final BOSS.

Even though Maple Tree’s performance still wasn’t perfect, there weren’t any major mistakes that affected the overall situation, so their journey to the bosses could be considered as having gone smoothly.

After slaughtering their way past all of the normal monsters, as well as the first and second BOSS, the team finally broke into the castle’s rear garden.

The garden’s condition was similar to the broken-down castle. And waiting here was the final BOSS called Desolate Land Ruler Toya.

Even if their way here had gone by without any mistakes, the final BOSS Toya was still a deciding variable.

This was all because Toya was a BOSS with many skills. He was an abnormal entity with skills from many classes.

Because there were so many skills, it meant that he had a lot of options to choose from. Toya was one of rarely seen NPCs with no fixed attack pattern. When fighting against Toya, each time would be a different experience, so the time needed to kill Toya also depended quite a bit on luck. They had to see what this guy would do this time.

Fortunately, they didn’t need to spend time discussing the strategy on how to deal with him. This BOSS tested the players’ ability to adapt on the spot.

After rushing into the garden, the five players didn’t hesitate and rushed in as soon as they saw Toya.

Their individual set-up was similar to when they entered the dungeon.

Cleansing Mist and Maple Tree, the two long-ranged classes, leapt to the high grounds after entering the garden. Cleansing Mist lifted her cannon and fired an Anti-Tank Missile over. Her pulling was incomparably quick.

Amidst the smoke from the explosion, Toya cursed loudly and then rushed out. He wore a dark red leather jacket and an iron chain around his waist. Hair of all different colors streamed down his head. Toya didn’t have an appearance befitting a Desolate Land Ruler and looked more like a rebellious teen.

Toya shot out of the smoke. His figure shook —— Shadow Clone Technique. The fake body stayed in the original position to lure in players, while the real one flashed behind Cleansing Mist.

From a player’s analysis, the usage of this instant movement technique to appear next to his target was very fierce.

Standing there, Cleansing Mist looked like she didn’t know what had happened, making Maple Tree want to remind her in alarm. But before he could say anything, he heard the repeated firing of a machine gun. Beneath them, Lord Grim had already switched his Thousand Chance Umbrella into the Gun form and a Gatling Gun shot at Toya.

Toya, who was just about to attack Cleansing Mist, was immediately hit by the line of bullets and unable to move. At this moment, Cleansing Mist turned around and used the Gunner skill “Swing” to swat Toya down from the high grounds. She then followed up with her own Gatling Gun, firing at the falling Toya.

Lord Grim’s Gatling Gun also followed the falling Toya. The firing from the two players’ guns shot out in two lines. It looked as if they were sending Toya down to the ground.

The two’s skilled coordination wasn’t anything new to Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion. But Maple Tree hadn’t seen it in the three runs done the day before and was now staring, dumbstruck. If he wasn’t so stunned, as a long-ranged class, he would have also begun firing.

Of course, with the target moving so fast, whether he could hit the target accurately was a big question.

Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion didn’t need any reminders. The two were already waiting in position. Lord Grim’s and Cleansing Mist’s attack from both sides sent Toya to them. Tang Rou didn’t wait for Toya to hit the ground and used a Circle Swing. The Scarlet Moon Lance in Soft Mist’s hands turned into an arc of red light, accurately stabbing the falling Toya. A large swing followed afterwards, smashing Toya into the ground.

“Attack, don’t daydream!” Ye Xiu called out Maple Tree.

Maple Tree woke up and immediately began sending out skills at Toya.

Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion, who had been beating up the knocked-down Toya, jumped away in order to avoid the shockwave attack the BOSS would make when getting up.

Toya directly leapt up and kicked towards Soft Mist. But before the kick could reach her, a large energy ball smashed into his body and after an explosion, he crashed back to the ground.

Cannonball!

Of course, only Su Mucheng’s Launcher could have fired this. Cleansing Mist’s gun was now gathering energy for a Laser. This time, Toya moved swiftly and Quick Recovered to avoid getting knocked down. After rolling, he used a Roundhouse Kick, a Sharpshooter skill. This time, the chasing Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion weren’t able to defend in time and the two were kicked stumbling.

However, this skill didn’t cause the targets it hit to be knocked to the ground. And with their mechanics, they were able to steady their balance in an instant. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim rushed forward and chopped with a Collapsing Mountain. Toya, who had just finished executing the Roundhouse Kick, was once again flung down. Cleansing Mist’s Laser shot out at this moment and Toya was hit to the ground.

Shockwave!

Lord Grim didn’t retreat though. He pulled out his sword and Guarded against the shockwave. As he slid backwards, his sword flashed, Sword Draw.

Whether or not Sword Draw could knock down the target depended on the situation. It looked like this time, the move would only cause Toya to stumble a bit. Immediately following, he lifted his leg and used the Striker skill Whirlwind Kick.

Unfortunately, his leg was shorter than Lord Grim’s lance and once the Thousand Chance Umbrella changed into the lance form, Circle Swing was used and Toya was sent smashing into the ground again.

Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion still didn’t have much experience. Toya had many skills, which was quite similar to unspecialized characters. Even Team Tiny Herb, those extremely experienced pro-players, were a bit delayed in their decision-making because there were so many skills. Although Toya wasn’t as ridiculous as unspecialized characters, it was still enough to make Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion unable to react in time.

For example, the two were hit by the previous Roundhouse Kick.

But Ye Xiu was different. No matter how many skills Toya had, he couldn’t leave the boundaries of Glory. And how could Ye Xiu not be familiar with every skill? His experience and decision-making could clearly be seen now.

In addition, Lord Grim was an unspecialized character. Even though Toya had many skills, Ye Xiu could always find a way to counter it. This was an advantage that no normal class possessed. Normal classes all had their own style. They had their own strengths and weaknesses. For example, Launchers had high attack and long range, but their close-combat ability was almost non-existent. They barely had any skills for it and if they didn’t think of a way to widen the distance between the enemies, then they would certainly die.

Unspecialized characters could use skills from all 24 classes. Although they were all low-leveled, there were both close-combat and long-ranged ones of different styles. There would always be a suitable skill to use in any situation. They didn’t lose to Toya’s many skills in any way.

Toya was suppressed!

This was something no record-setting team could ever imagine. Toya’s unpredictable skills always made everyone go mad. How good the dungeon record always depended on that guy’s mood.

But this time, Toya looked like a trapped beast. His usual sharp claws and teeth were useless at this moment.

However, their coordination wasn’t as good in this battle. It was quite clear that Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion were unable to keep up with Ye Xiu’s tempo.

Although Toya had a lot of variations, Ye Xiu could keep up with all of them and always found a way to restrict them. But for others, this battle was quite complex. They didn’t have that type of experience and decision-making, so they naturally had no way of coordinating with him. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion were left almost as embarrassed as Maple Tree. They could only stupidly put out damage.

The only who could echo Lord Grim’s attacks was Su Mucheng. Even though her experience and decision-making weren’t as good as Ye Xiu, she knew Ye Xiu very well.

“This person…… so he really isn’t going all out sometimes…….” Tang Rou lamented. At this moment, she had a feeling of being unable to keep up. For her, this made her feel defeated. In the past three times they ran the dungeon, Ye Xiu hadn’t shown such a dominating pressure here. Everyone had relied on their own skill. But today, Ye Xiu was going all out, making them feel like they were watching a play.

At this moment, Tang Rou only had one question. When they had PKed at that time, did Ye Xiu go all out?

The battle wasn’t advancing in complete silence. Lord Grim’s and Toya’s skills were executed extremely quickly, so there wasn’t much time to talk for the majority of it. But there were still places that Ye Xiu had time to remind everyone. It was just that there weren’t many of these types of places.

“Careful, almost Red Blood!!” For example, Ye Xiu had time to remind them this.

No one had any response. Red blood was red blood. Is that something you can’t deal with?

And sure enough, after going into Red Blood, Toya’s attacks quickened, but the overall situation didn’t change. Ye Xiu was still suppressing him. Just from this point, they could see that the Ye Xiu suppressing Toya before Red Blood wasn’t his limit. If not, then once Toya went Enraged, how could he have kept up? If that wasn’t his limit, then what the heck was it?

Tang Rou was at a loss, but there was no way Steamed Bun Invasion could figure out all of these details. From the very start, he had been shouting and shouting just like always. When it was time to coordinate, he would coordinate. When it wasn’t, he would just act rashly on his own. To him, the game was always fun no matter what.

Chapter 161 – It Isn’t Easy Being an Expert

Toya finally fell.

Even though he had entered the Enraged state with higher speed and faster cast times, it was….. no use. In front of Ye Xiu, these were of no use. Lord Grim seemed like a machine specially designed against him, mechanically precise without any mistakes. Every one of the skills used by Toya was completely suppressed.

Whether it be by interruption or by being the first to attack….

With countless variations and numerous methods, it was fortunate that Toya wasn’t an actual person, otherwise he’d be so sad that he’d have coughed up blood from being suppressed so hard.

Toya fell and the system announcement popped up.

Another incontestable record appeared once again .

Full Moon Guild, 28:01:27.

Compared to Blue Brook Guild’s record of 30:45:66, their record beat it by 2.5 minutes. Compared to the other records set, it was just as ridiculous. Every time Ye Xiu beat a record, it was always by so much more, so much so that it made others feel hopeless. For Blue Brook Guild’s record to have lasted so long, that meant that no other guild was able to beat it by even one second. Only Ye Xiu could beat it by 2.5 minutes.

A pile of messages immediately stormed onto the world channel.

Full Moon Guild? Why Full Moon Guild?

Lord Grim! Lord Grim again.

Wasn’t Lord Grim from Blue Brook Guild? Why did he run to Full Moon Guild?

Steamed Bun Invasion! When are you going to pay me back for that 5 Gold I lent?

The messages were a complete mess. There was even one that mentioned Steamed Bun Invasion’s name.

Steamed Bun Invasion replied on the world channel: “Don’t worry. Once I gather up 10 Gold, I’ll return it to you all at once.”

Sending a message on the world channel had a cooldown. A message could only be sent every two minutes, so the other side couldn’t reply immediately. Plus, most of the messages on the world channel were just jokes, so it’d be much faster and better to reply in private. But with this reply, quite a lot of players copying him and sending payment reminders on the world channel. In a short moment, a bunch of “Man, when are you going to return to me my girlfriend?” came out, making many speechless.

Maple Tree was naturally unimaginably excited and started chatting friendly with members of his guild. There were very few that wouldn’t acknowledge that a guild like Full Moon Guild could set a record like that. Those people were rather narrow-minded. When the announcement came out, many in the guild began paying attention to what type of equipment would be rewarded.

When a new record was set, there was a 100% chance of acquiring a Purple equipment. It was just that Blue Brook Guild, Tyrannical Ambition, those sorts of guilds didn’t care. They only wanted the record for the fame. They had seen plenty of low-leveled Purple equipment, so they simply didn’t put it in their eyes.

Only Maple Tree, a guild leader of that level, would feel excited about what Purple equipment would come out. He couldn’t be blamed. Even as the guild leader, he didn’t have a single piece of Purple equipment. He couldn’t even compare to Lord Grim and the others. When he saw them today with their newly switched Purple weapons, Maple Tree’s eyes nearly popped out.

Purple weapon! Don’t look at how the big guild’s elite teams all had them. In reality, they were quite rare. For example, in his guild, if a Purple weapon came out, the player who got it wouldn’t care if it fit his class. Whoever got it could sell it for a lot of money! The more thoughtful players would give their teammates some sort of small compensation. The selfish, well, they wouldn’t do anything. The dispute that followed had existed since the very beginning of Glory.

Maple Tree felt quite good because the end reward was Purple Revolver, which perfectly suited his class. Moreover, the labourers he hired hadn’t rolled for it, so it went directly to him. He was naturally extremely excited.

Maple Tree was still chattering in the guild channel! Lord Grim went to his side: “The record’s set.”

“Yes, yes. Thank you! Thank you!!” Maple Tree recovered and immediately thanked him.

“The Scarlet Moon Set?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Oh oh oh!” Maple Tree was so happy he forgot. He had brought the Scarlet Moon Set with him and traded Ye Xiu at once. The four parts were the Head, Chest, Belt, and Legs. It was missing the Shoulders and Shoes.

Ye Xiu received them and went to trade Tang Rou.

“What?” Tang Rou accepted the trade.

“Equipment for you.” Ye Xiu put the four parts of the set into the trade window.

“From where?”

“Maple Tree just gave them! We helped him set a record!” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh.” Tang Rou confirmed the trade and wore the newly obtained equipment. This set naturally had its own style when it was all put together. Tang Rou had the main parts to it, so the general style was already clear. Her body was covered in scarlet leather with a belt strapped around her waist. Soft Mist immediately looked a lot stronger.

“Anything for me?” Steamed Bun Invasion snuck in a question.

“Not yet.” Ye Xiu said.

Steamed Bun Invasion wasn’t happy, but it wasn’t towards Ye Xiu, rather it was towards Maple Tree. He charged at him: “Noob guild leader, you’re too stingy. Give me a set too!”

“Ah? There’s no more…..” Maple Tree said in confusion. The trade had already been completed. Why was there more?

“Stingy.” Steamed Bun Invasion disdained.

Maple Tree coughed blood. If he didn’t add a bonus, that was stingy?

“Steamed Bun, don’t worry. This deal was already agreed upon beforehand. Soft Mist first and then you.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay, okay. No hurry. Ladies first.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“We still have two more runs. Maple Tree, are you still going?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Oh…. me……” Maple Tree was now happily chatting with his friends and guild, so he didn’t really want to go. But they had just helped him set a record, so if he just suddenly turned his head and refused them, that wasn’t too good right?

Maple Tree was suffering over his decision, when Ye Xiu said: “Then we’ll continue!”

As he said that, the four players had already left the party and made their own party on the side. They then left Full Moon Guild too.

“Wha……” Maple Tree wanted to say something, when the four directly entered the dungeon. They didn’t even find someone else to add.

So my contact with these experts ended just like this? Maple Tree was suddenly at a loss.

The dungeon continued. Only having four players wasn’t a problem for these experts. Since they weren’t trying to set the record this time, they went around the entire map and killed every monster in every nook and cranny of the castle. Even excluding the fact that the dungeon BOSS always dropped a Blue or higher equipment, the dungeon was still the most profitable place, whether it be in money or experience, the rewards were much greater than in a leveling area. For most of the players, they could let go of not doing other things, but they had to use up all of their dungeon entries. The current dungeons could still be done three or four times, but the higher leveled the dungeon or the larger the scale of the dungeon, the fewer entries they would have. There would even be some dungeons that could only be run once a week. The progress was saved, but they were dungeons that couldn’t be completed in a single day.

After clearing all of the monsters, they had to clean up the BOSS. This time, Ye Xiu wasn’t dedicated again and didn’t fight Toya with all he had like last time. He was the same as yesterday, just casually directing everyone and played with Toya from time to time.

“Hey, why aren’t you playing seriously!” Tang Rou had objections. She didn’t like it when people were hiding their strength.

“You mean like last time?” Ye Xiu said.

“Obviously.”

“I’m already old. How can I always play like that? You youngsters have more strength.” Ye Xiu said.

“How old are you!” Tang Rou was angry.

“In terms of eSports, I really am pretty old.” Ye Xiu said.

“So what? You can clearly play very well.” Tang Rou said.

“Look at it like this.” Ye Xiu said, “The theory is the same as in other sports. Young people grow stronger and rely on their bodies to win. But after a few years, they have to rely on their experience and knowledge. They have to use their brains to win. Against young players’ bodies, they could occasionally compete with them, but if they frequently clashed, they would only shorten their lifespan as an athlete. It’s the same as in eSports. Using extremely fast hand speed to compete in mechanics, that’s the style of you young players. But for people my age, it’s better if we do that less.” Ye Xiu said.

“It can’t be that exaggerated.” Tang Rou said.

“In a few years, you’ll understand. Do you really think being an expert is that easy?” Ye Xiu laughed.

As a result, Tang Rou didn’t say anything more and continued to fight BOSS Toya. Ye Xiu didn’t fully exert himself either. His overall performance was about the same as Tang Rou. Because of this, they had some trouble finishing Toya off.

They didn’t add anyone else and they once again went in as four. Afterwards, they finished using up all of their Desolate Land entries.

“Everyone, I’ll be going off first!” Su Mucheng said habitually. Once they finished the dungeon runs, she would go offline first.

Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion said their farewells. Ye Xiu obviously wouldn’t say anything. Su Mucheng was practically sitting next to him! He took off his headphones and turned his head to ask: “Are you going back?”

‘Yup! I’m going back!” Su Mucheng also took off her headphones. She logged out of the game and mouse, ready to shut down the computer.

“NO NO NO! That’s the server computer, my young lady. Please don’t shut that down!” Ye Xiu sweated madly. He almost charged at Su Mucheng to stop her.

“Oh, I forgot.” Su Mucheng also jumped in fright. She also knew what would happen if she shut down the server computer. It was just that she was so used to shutting down her computer, so she forgot.

“So dangerous.” Ye Xiu wiped away some sweat. Su Mucheng was a pro-player. Her hand speed was fast. It was lucky that he was even faster.

“I’ll be going then!” Su Mucheng got up and saw Ye Xiu turn off the computer monitor.

“See you!”

“I don’t know when I can come next time. The Internet Cafe still is really dangerous, right?” Su Mucheng said.

“Yup!” Ye Xiu nodded.

“Sigh, I’ll be off then.” Su Mucheng regretfully left the reception desk.

“Are you hungry? Do you want something to eat?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Okay!” Su Mucheng quickly came back.

“We have Braised Beef, Mushroom Chicken, Tomatoes and Eggs, Pickled Pork, Shrimp, Fish, all kinds of different instant noodles. Which one would you like?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Oh….. I’ll take the Mushroom Chicken.” Su Mucheng thought hard before replying.

“Wait just a moment……” Ye Xiu had already gotten the Mushroom Chicken noodles and went to get boiling water.

Chapter 162 – Half the Screen

When Ye Xiu came back with the cooked instant noodles, he saw that Su Mucheng had moved a wooden stool next to his seat. She had changed the settings for the game to a windowed screen. Her hand moved the mouse as if she were searching for something.

“The noodles have arrived.” Ye Xiu announced.

“Put it here!” Su Mucheng tapped the table beside her. The reception desk at Happy Internet Cafe had two layers. The outside layer was the front desk, while the inner layer was a regular table that things could be set upon.

Ye Xiu put the noodles on the table and went back to his seat. He saw that Su Mucheng was looking for something on the Internet.

“What are you looking for? I’ll help you look.” Ye Xiu put his hands on the keyboard.

“That Year We Were Holding Hands.” Su Mucheng said.

“The new drama?” Ye Xiu said as he typed it in. With one search in a video platform, several links popped up.

“It’s not really new. Yunxiu recommended it. I hadn’t seen it before.” Su Mucheng said. Chu Yunxiu, Team Misty Rain’s ace player. She was also the player that Ye Xiu regarded as the number one female player in terms of tactics and skill. The Alliance didn’t have many female players. Compared to the male players, they belonged to a disadvantaged group, causing them to be relatively close to each other. They had their own special circle. They also had their own exclusive QQ (similar to Skype) group, which had all the female Alliance players; from those who were retired to those who still played to those who were new.

Ye Xiu obviously didn’t have the qualifications to join the QQ group, but since he was close to Su Mucheng, he would sometimes see it. If no one knew anything about it, they wouldn’t think that it was a gathering of Glory pro-players. They talked about clothing, makeup, celebrities, astrological signs, and gossip in the Glory community…… At least, during the few times Ye Xiu had snuck a peek at it, he hadn’t seen any discussions about serious things like tactics and techniques. It couldn’t even compare to a normal guild in Glory. At least in those, experts would sometimes exchange pointers!

“What episode are you on?” Ye Xiu asked.

“12.”

Opening up the 12th episode, Ye Xiu handed the earphones over to Su Mucheng.

“I’ve worn them for so long, that my ears are already hurting.”

“Then turn up the volume, so you won’t need to wear them.”

Su Mucheng turned up the volume. The first sound that came out was clearly from Glory’s lifelike sound effects as well as Steamed Bun Invasion’s voice. Ye Xiu opened up the settings and closed the game’s sound and voice. He then typed: “Steamed Bun, let’s practice our hand speed. To do so, if you’re going to say something, type it out instead.”

“Yes! I like this practice. Wanna compete to see who can type out the most words in a minute?” Steamed Bun Invasion immediately went into serious mode.

“Line Canyon!” Ye Xiu declared and then headed towards it.

The game was quiet, though it seemed like Ye Xiu was very suited for this. A song drifted from the headphones hanging on Su Mucheng’s neck.

“This song sounds awful.” Ye Xiu said.

“Yeah, skip ahead.” Su Mucheng said.

“How much?”

“2 minutes 43 seconds.”

His mouse moved and the cursor flashed from the game to the web browser. He skipped ahead exactly 2 minutes 43 seconds.

The screen was then split in half. One half was a TV show while the other half was a game.

With Ye Xiu’s skill level, this dungeon was too easy. He would glance at the TV show from time to time. As for Su Mucheng, she was just watching the TV show, so she didn’t need to completely focus on the game. She would glance to see the battles in-game from time to time.

“Are the noodles ready to eat yet?” Su Mucheng said.

“Go ahead!”

“Are you going to eat?” Su Mucheng took the noodles and asked.

“I’ll drink two sips of soup.”

“I’ll wait till you finish these two monsters.” Su Mucheng saw that Ye Xiu was busy dealing with two wild monsters.

The two monsters were defeated quickly. Ye Xiu made his Lord Grim move forward as he took two sips of the soup.

“Not bad. Whoever cooked these instant noodles is quite good.” Ye Xiu said as he handed the bowl back.

“It’s not bad!” Su Mucheng took it and began eating.

In game, Lord Grim arrived at Line Canyon and partied up with Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion. Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon had also run over to join the party. Those two would almost always mix in with Brother Expert when a chance came. They didn’t really play with their guild anymore. Even today, when their guild came together as one happy family, the two didn’t think much of it.

The dungeon went by smoothly and in the blink of an eye, they reached the first BOSS.

The romance in the TV show still hadn’t made any headway. The female lead knew from episode one that the male lead was her childhood friend, but the male lead still thought of the female lead as a newly-made friend.

“Tsk tsk. This guy’s so stupid.” Ye Xiu commented on the male lead.

“Mine, mine! Light Source set!!” Su Mucheng saw that the fallen BOSS had dropped the Light Source Top. Light Source was a Level 30 Launcher set.

“Got it!” Ye Xiu chose to roll for it and the others immediately renounced it.

“It’s just Level 30 equipment.” Ye Xiu felt that Su Mucheng had been too excited. She was a pro-player, so besides self-made equipment, it didn’t make sense for her to be so excited about any other equipment.

“It looks so pretty.” Su Mucheng said.

Ye Xiu was speechless. For god-level experts like him, their skills are amazing, their knowledge is exceptional, but towards Glory’s clothing, hairstyle, fashion, etc,any random female player would be better than them. In this area, female players were gods and they were noobs.

The speechless Ye Xiu threw the Light Source upper-garment into his backpack. The dungeon continued as did the TV show.

Line Canyon took the five of them around for 30 minute runs. It was a bit shorter than the 45 minute episodes.

After two runs, the episode had finished. Just as the next episode was playing, Ye Xiu felt his left shoulder drop.

“You falling asleep?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Yeah……” The head on his shoulder made a noise.

The third run continued. Ye Xiu’s movements became steadier. His movements were so steady that even the smoke from the cigarette ash in his mouth wouldn’t tremble.

They advanced through the dungeon while the TV show continued playing.

After killing the final BOSS, the three dungeon runs were completed and the TV show had finished as well. The ending song played from the headphones, but Su Mucheng didn’t tell Ye Xiu to turn it off. Ye Xiu turned his head and looked. The furry girl’s eyes had already closed.

“Ha ha ha ha, today’s luck is pretty good! Three parts of my Dark Mark set actually dropped! Are you guys jealous of my luck?” Steamed Bun Invasion swiftly typed out, practicing his hand speed.

“Not bad, not bad. Soft Mist, shout out the Scarlet Moon upper-garment you got in the world channel. You should be able to trade it for the shoulders or shoes that you still need.” Ye Xiu said. A part from the Battle Mage Scarlet Moon set had also dropped, however, Soft Mist already had it. Luckily, equipment could be traded, so everyone could trade for the parts they needed.

“Okay.” Tang Rou answered. In a short moment, Soft Mist sent a message for a trade to the world channel.

“Keep sending them out until someone contacts you.” Ye Xiu instructed. Tang Rou really needed this type of instruction too. She was completely new to games, unlike Steamed Bun Invasion.

“Are we still going to Boneyard?” Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon asked.

“Hmm, not now!” Ye Xiu replied.

“Okay!” Everyone answered. Right now, Boneyard wasn’t worth it for the experience. Ye Xiu also didn’t need any materials from the dungeon. Besides, getting the materials for the Thousand Chance Umbrella by himself wasn’t practical.

“Okay.”

Everyone scattered. Those who wanted to dungeon went to dungeon. Those who wanted to Arena went to the Arena. Those who wanted to trade equipment went to trade equipment. Ye Xiu had Lord Grim randomly clear monsters in the nearby area.

“I’ve traded it!” Tang Rou messaged.

“Good. You’re only missing one now.” Ye Xiu said.

“It really is better than normal equipment.” Tang Rou said.

“Of course!” Ye Xiu replied, “Level 30 sets won’t need to be switched until Level 40.”

“Oh.” Tang Rou answered without saying anything else. After a short while, she got up to move around. She went to fill up her tea cup and as usual, walked to pay a visit to the receptionist desk. But this time, she jumped in fear. What was that furry thing leaning on Ye Xiu? Tang Rou’s face stared in astonishment. Ye Xiu turned and gave her a helpless look.

“Who’s that?” Tang Rou finally figured out that it was a person.

“Uh…… Mu Mu.” Ye Xiu used the nickname Tang Rou liked.

“Ah?” Tang Rou was astonished, “So she was playing here?”

“Yeah!” Ye Xiu said.

“She fell asleep?” Tang Rou asked.

“Yeah.”

“She should go upstairs to sleep. She can sleep in my room.” Tang Rou said.

“Don’t worry about it. Here is good!” Ye Xiu smiled.

“Make sure she doesn’t catch a cold.” If she were Chen Guo, she would have grabbed her sister and carried her to bed, but Tang Rou didn’t make him. After saying this, she went back to her seat.

“Mu Mu sounds disgusting when it comes from you.” Su Mucheng looked like she was sleep talking.

“Yeah. I almost vomited those instant noodles.” Ye Xiu said.

“The instant noodles are in my stomach.” Su Mucheng said.

“I also ate a bowl tonight.”

“Really? What flavor?”

“Simmered Beef.”

“Was the cook good?”

“Very good. The same as your bowl.”

“That’s good.” Su Mucheng finished and then became silent.

“When are you planning on going back?” After a long while, Ye Xiu asked.

“When are you off your shift?’ Su Mucheng asked.

“Seven.”

“Then me too!”

“Okay……”

“It’s kind of cold……” Su Mucheng shivered.

“Obviously. Everything you’re wearing is just a disguise!” Ye Xiu said as he took off his jacket and put it on Su Mucheng.

“Where was I in the show? I kind of forgot.” Su Mucheng said.

“It’s not your fault. The show sucks.” Ye Xiu said.

“You’re looking down on Yunxiu’s tastes again.” Su Mucheng said.

“I remember all of my opponent’s weaknesses very clearly.” Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 163 – Shot At Even When Lying Down

That night, Ye Xiu didn’t conduct any more intense activities. However, many people in the tenth server felt uneasy because of his presence.

Records! It was obviously because of the records.

In the end, Desolate Land’s dungeon record was broken. Lord Grim once again proved his indispensability towards records. And Full Moon Guild, the name which made all the big guilds feel sick, took their spot on the Desolate Land leaderboards.

Even worse, Full Moon Guild’s players weren’t humble at all.

In a guild, the guild leader’s temperament greatly affected the entire guild. Maple Tree’s personality, which knew no difference between the heavens and earth, crumbled a little after seeing the extraordinary coordination between Lord Grim and the team. But after breaking the record, he thought of how he fulfilled his role in the team perfectly and couldn’t help but consider himself a member of the expert team. His personality, which had crumbled a little, flared up again.

Full Moon Guild’s members stopped chatting in the guild channel. They changed to the world channel. Their flaunting there made others feel envious. The other guild leaders grinded their teeth in hatred. They had hired someone to break the record for him. Why were they acting like they were so amazing? Many players in the world channel sneered at them, but Full Moon Guild was able to counter them . They brought up Blue Brook Guild and Tyrannical Ambition as similar examples. If these amazing guilds did what they were doing, why should they be ashamed of doing the same?

Getting shot at while down, Blue River and Cold Night felt gloomy, but there was nothing they could say because this was reality. Even the guilds who hadn’t been able to invite Lord Grim could argue against Full Moon Guild. Asking Lord Grim for help setting a dungeon record had always been a task on their daily agenda. If they scoffed at Full Moon Guild and then went to ask Lord Grim for help, wouldn’t that be the same as slapping their own face?

With this, the entire world was now aware of Lord Grim’s substituting acts, so the records set by Lord Grim only had so much weight to them. This was why many players looked down on Full Moon Guild including Blue Brook Guild and Tyrannical Ambition.

New server! New players, born as cows and not afraid of the tigers, were everywhere. But then again, no matter how strong the tigers were, it was only a game. What was there to be afraid of? Playing games is for fun. Nobody spends money on a game to treat it as bitter work. This was why there were many people who said whatever was on their mind. Blue Brook Guild? Tyrannical Ambition? Hmph.

As the players cursed more and more, the braver they got. Slowly, Blue Brook Guild and Tyrannical Ambition were put on the same level as Full Moon Guild; second-rate guilds. They were trash that couldn’t set a record if they didn’t ask for a substitution. The current number two spot on the Desolate Land leaderboard was still held by Blue Brook Guild. But this reality was completely ignored by the players.

Blue River and Cold Night didn’t have enough time to deal with this development. The two couldn’t help but think of an old proverb: the bird in the lead will be shot!

As the two guilds who looked for Lord Grim first, were they really going be discredited like this? Putting it this way, it was quite alarming to hear about. But at this moment, the entire world was voicing their dissent towards their actions. The three guilds would sometimes be mentioned by their name too, which made them feel frightened.

“I say, this isn’t right.” Cold Night messaged Blue River.

“It’s all because of that idiot, Full Moon!” Blue River typed furiously. If those stupid guild members hadn’t run to the world channel to make a mess all over the place, where would they have gotten all this hate? If all the hate didn’t come out, how could they have been shot at even while lying down? They were big guilds and they paid careful attention to their reputation. Right now, they were being put on the same level as that second-rate guild. Plus, they were thought of as having no strength. The damage done was just too high.

But even if they burned down all of Full Moon Guild, the problem would still be there. There was only one way to counter these remarks; set a new record to shut everyone up.

However, the record king Lord Grim blocked their path like a huge mountain. No matter how hard they tried to get over it, they wouldn’t be able to. There was also no way they could rope him in. They were all saying how asking Lord Grim for help meant that they had no strength!

After this short discussion between Cold Night and Blue River, they fell silent. Currently, their guild was amidst a huge crisis.

Even the other guilds were at a loss. In their current situation, inviting Lord Grim to help set a record was a shameless deed. No one wanted to ruin their reputation. Even if they pulled Lord Grim into their guild, a move like that would bring a lot of criticism from other players.

In short, the name Lord Grim still ensured a dungeon record. But at the same time, his name lost value if it were used. This was because using Lord Grim to set a record for a guild would only receive negative comments from everyone. This was completely opposite from why big guilds were setting records. However, thinking back, Lord Grim was now like a parasite; whichever guild he floated to would be regarded as diseased. Putting it like this, it would be quite nice if the enemies had him!

For example, Herb Garden and Excellent Dynasty were quite happy. Their archenemies Blue Brook Guild and Tyrannical Ambition were being ridiculed in the world channel. This was extremely satisfying!

Excellent Dynasty’s Chen Yehui was in the game as well and watched the scene unfold. No one could have predicted that things would turn out this way.

Chen Yehui was originally very happy with what happened to Tyrannical Ambition but as he continued to think about it, he suddenly recognized another point and immediately became even happier!

Killing two birds with one stone!

Ye Qiu. What a blunder!

Chen Yehui couldn’t hold back his happiness! He looked at the time. It was extremely late, but he believed that disturbing Liu Hao with the news about what happened was worth it.

Chen Yehui went offline and then called Liu Hao.

“Hello?” Liu Hao answered the phone with a tone of drowsiness. He had been sleeping nicely until he was suddenly awoken. No one would be happy, but Liu Hao suppressed his anger. The huge mistake he had done before had made him aware that keeping calm was very important.

“Good news, Liu! Ye Qiu’s about to run out of luck.” Chen Yehui shouted.

“Oh? This really is good news. But no matter how good the news is, you could have just told me tomorrow. Only bad and urgent news should be reported at night, so we can figure out a plan quickly, right? Okay, I’m tired. I’ll talk to you later!” Liu Hao finished and then hung up the phone.

The buzzing noise from the phone left Chen Yehui somewhat at a loss. He recognized that Liu Hao’s words were very reasonable. Good news could come later, nothing bad would happen. But the earlier something bad is handled, the better the chances they could have to fix it.

He just didn’t want to believe that only after two weeks, Liu Hao unexpectedly became so rational. So rational that it almost seemed cold and ruthless.

Just how big was his previous wound?

Chen Yehui silently put down the phone. His happiness from before dimmed down.

Liu Hao’s reasoning meant that he had an even more important goal. Ye Qiu was no longer his main opponent. He had already given the task to someone else. It had been thrown to Chen Yehui to deal with.

Chen Yehui felt disturbed.

He managed the guild. He put a lot of effort into the Club’s development. Nicely put, he could be considered a behind-the-scenes hero. However, there was no longer any chance for him to be in the spotlight like a pro-player ever again.

And the person who made him lose that chance was Ye Qiu!!

Chen Yehui suddenly clenched his fists.

It was Ye Qiu who judged him as having no talent and not putting enough effort.

On what basis? On what basis could he deny me so easily with just that? On what basis could the Club kick him from the pro-player list, then make him go online to manage the guild?

Ye Qiu!

The reason Chen Yehui and Liu Hao mingled together so well was because of their deep hatred for this name. But he never had the chance. His position was far beneath the power of Excellent Dynasty’s team captain. Until he noticed Liu Hao. Speaking of this, he was the one who successfully roped in Liu Hao. He had demonstrated himself as a lesson to Liu Hao, making Liu Hao hate Ye Qiu more and more, day by day.

But now, Liu Hao had already stepped on Ye Qiu and had even risen up in the Club. But himself…… besides venting his resentment, what did he have to gain?

Liu Hao no longer thought messing with Ye Qiu was worth it anymore. He had already found a new goal to pursue. And himself? Was he still going to play this little game with him? Was he destined to be at such a low position?

Chen Yehui thought about it and slowly unclenched his fist.

In the game, Plantago Seed had been disturbed greatly by Lord Grim as well. Team Tiny Herb’s pro-players didn’t know how hard it was to get these materials, so they had recklessly gambled it all away to Lord Grim. These were all uncommon materials! Even with their guild’s size, it wasn’t easy to gather those materials.

In reality, Plantago Seed really wanted to give them a suggestion: the Arena could be accessed in all servers. You guys can go to the old servers. Those Herb Gardens were a lot bountiful than they were.

But…… Plantago Seed hated to give up the chance to be with these pro-players. They were his idols, who he looked up to.

Holding on to just this, Plantago Seed clenched his teeth and swallowed the suggestion.

However, the ridicule towards Blue Brook Guild on the world channel really did make him happy. After a few cheerful moments, Plantago Seed felt like he should share his happiness with others. And the person who he wanted to share it with the most was Blue River!

He opened up his friends list and looked.

Blue River wasn’t online! Plantago Seed really felt sorry for him.

Chapter 164 – Asking For Help Separately

Tyrannical Ambition’s Cold Night wasn’t online either.

The two of them were the same. They had both lost control of the situation in the tenth server. They felt that they needed to ask headquarters for help, so they logged out and ran to the Heavenly Domain.

Both of them knew each other’s IDs in the Heavenly Domain and they were both friends too. When they came online, they saw each other on their friends list and had a tacit understanding of each other’s situation.

Blue River hastily contacted his guild leader Changing Spring.

Changing Spring had originally said that he had wanted to go and see exactly how great Lord Grim was, but he never had the opportunity to do that. They had asked Lord Grim for help with Boneyard, but at that time, Lord Grim had gathered his own team, so there was no spot available for him.

After Boneyard, Lord Grim’s strength was recognized by their guild. The dungeon record completely exceeded what they had imagined. As a result, there was no need to personally appraise his strength. All they could do was try their best to win over Lord Grim!

In the end, after fighting over and over again for him, Lord Grim was won by Full Moon guild. And that guild was the one that had caused such a disaster for Blue Brook Guild. Blue River didn’t know what to say.

Changing Spring was also cautiously bringing his guild’s experts to try and set records. The dungeons in the Heavenly Domain were on a completely different level, however. Sometimes, they weren’t even able to complete the dungeon in a single run. Even for an elite team from the Three Great Guilds, if too many players died, there would be a part of the dungeon where they wouldn’t be unable to continue towards.

The Blue Brook Guild’s team was currently in such a predicament.

A forty player dungeon. One run every week. They had sacrificed over half of their team in order to get past two-thirds of the dungeon. In this state, however, they had no way of advancing so Changing Spring eventually made the decision to give up.

Everyone exited the dungeon; their morale was low. Soon after, they saw Blue River, who was supposed to be in the tenth server, waiting outside with his main account Blue Bridge Spring Snow.

Changing Spring had known that Blue River was coming. Although he wasn’t in a very good mood, no matter how he felt, he couldn’t just ignore Blue River, so he kindly went over and asked him what the situation was. The players who were there were all the elite experts of Blue Brook Guild. Since they weren’t outsiders, they gathered around him so they could listen in.

After he explained what was going on, when Changing Spring hadn’t even said anything yet, someone from the group of players sneered.

Blue River didn’t even need to look to know who it was. He was on good terms with nearly everyone there. However there was one who he didn’t get along with: Poplar Beach.

Speaking of which, how unlucky. After going over to the tenth server, he had only come back to the Heavenly Domain twice and coincidentally, he met that guy twice as well. It looked like his luck had been quite terrible recently!

“Super expert? Hilarious. Who went to pioneer in the tenth server again?” Poplar Beach acted as if he was speaking to himself.

Blue River couldn’t avoid getting a bit angry. He had just told them the record Lord Grim had set. Just from this achievement, who here couldn’t see that this guy wasn’t so simple? Poplar Beach obviously understood, but he still felt the need to mock him.

“This Boneyard record is a bit too abnormal.” Changing Spring directly ignored what Poplar Beach said, “That record can’t be right.”

“Yeah!” Quite a few experts agreed.

“Did he hack the leaderboards?” The players gathered there liked to think this way. This was because they were so familiar with the game. Since they believed that such a record wasn’t possible, their only explanation for it was hacking. However, that couldn’t be taken seriously. Glory had gotten rid of external hacking long ago.

“Desolate Land’s record doesn’t seem as abnormal.” Changing Spring noted.

“Yeah. It was made when they just hit Level 30, but their equipment was pretty inadequate and their fifth player’s skill was mediocre.” Blue River said.

“Tsk tsk, and they broke your record like that? Guild leader, let me try! I can guarantee that we’ll take this record back. In this situation, all we have to do is set a new record and prove ourselves to the tenth server’s new players, right?” Poplar Beach interrupted again. Even though he was putting down Blue River, his judgement of the problem was still accurate.

The reason Blue River returned was because he was looking for help like this. He needed experts! When the guild sent players over to pioneer in the tenth server, the guild couldn’t afford to send too many elites. For example, the only tenth server players who were qualified to be a part of the elite team in the Heavenly Domain were probably just him and Thousand Creations. In addition, there were players on the team that were stronger than the two of them.

Ignoring everyone else, only talking about Poplar Beach, Changing Spring had clearly said that Blue River wasn’t as good as him.

With a team of experts of this caliber, they’d definitely be able to beat any guild’s elite teams in the tenth servers. They might even be able to beat Lord Grim’s record.

“Where are our account cards over there from?” Changing Spring asked.

There was no choice. In order to log-in, you had to use an actual card. If you asked others to substitute, they had to be able to obtain the cards in order to do so.

“I have the data. I’ll send it to you in a bit!” Blue River said.

“Okay, then I’ll get people to contact you.” Changing Spring said.

“I’ll be going.” Blue River said and then logged out.

“Guild leader, let me go too!!” Poplar Beach actively signed up. Even though he didn’t feel too good about Changing Spring constantly ignoring him, he was still very polite towards him. For an arrogant person like him, his ambitions weren’t limited to just Blue River’s spot as one of the Five Great Experts. He also had the ambition to take over as guild leader.

Unfortunately, his current records against the guild leader are 11 losses 2 wins. Changing Spring was more skilled than he was. This was why whenever he talked to Changing Spring, he didn’t dare say anything rude.

“Let’s wait until Blue Bridge sends us the data. Once we know where the cards are, we can talk.” Changing Spring calmly said, expressing his attitude clearly: You’re not anything special. You’re dispensable.

“We did really badly on this run! How many times have we run this? We were wiped out two-thirds of the way through? Think about where we went wrong. Okay, you guys can go!” Changing Spring suddenly said. After explaining some things, his players went offline. The others all left as well. Only Poplar Beach and his companions stayed. They were all in the same mood.

These players were all relatively new experts in Blue Brook Guild with Poplar Beach as their leader. They all liked to show off. Today, Poplar Beach’s flaunting had been ignored, making their little group feel depressed.

“The guild leader clearly favors Blue Bridge!” One person said.

“There’s no choice. He’s a guild leader! Of course he wouldn’t want any internal conflict in the guild. Just take a look at how he intentionally averted the duel between Blue River and Poplar Beach and you’ll see what I mean.” Another person said.

“Yeah! He even sent Blue River over to the tenth server. How low.”

“Do you guys even know where that Lord Grim came from? That record is truly abnormal.” Even though they all liked watching Poplar Beach mock Blue River, they still expressed their astonishment over this record.

“Boneyard….. It really is freaky! I say we should study it for a bit.” Poplar Beach said. He wasn’t blindly arrogant. For example, when facing the stronger Changing Spring, he maintained his cool.

On Blue Brook Guild’s side, Changing Spring and Blue River discussed and chose people to go over to the tenth server. On Tyrannical Ambition’s side, Jiang You heard Cold Night’s description of the current situation and knitted his brows.

“How could things have turned out like this? If it’s like this, no one wins. How was Lord Grim able to come up with all of this?” Jiang You was puzzled.

“Lord Grim? I’m afraid that things didn’t go his way either. To have met with Full Moon, such a stupid guild, he’s probably feeling depressed too!” Cold Night said.

“We can’t bother with him right now. We need to rely on our own strength to take back this record!” Jiang You’s decision was the same as Blue Brook Guild’s. The two were in the same plight. The two tenth server guild leaders also had the same intentions.

“However, right now, Blue Brook Guild is in the same situation as us!” Cold Night said.

“Sigh, substitution……. There was never anything glamorous about any of it. But in this situation, we put ourselves in this situation. Blue Brook Guild will probably also try and find people to run Desolate Land, so we shouldn’t compete against them in that dungeon. If we compete with them, one of us isn’t going to be able to get the record. We’ll give them Desolate Land. We’ll go to Line Canyon and set a stable record. Aren’t we almost Level 33?”

“Yeah.” Cold Night nodded his head. Line Canyon was Level 30-33, so the highest records were made by those who were Level 33.

“But there’s still one thing we need to do before all of this.” Jiang You said.

“What thing?”

“Find Lord Grim.” Jiang You said.

“Him again?” Cold Night was surprised.

“Yes….. However, this time we’re not asking him to set a record. Instead we’re going to ask him to not touch the dungeon record. The price for that will be same as him setting one.” Jiang You said.

After saying this, the two suddenly fell silent.

After a while, Cold Night trembled and then said: “No way right?”

“So you also thought of it…….” Jiang You’s voice was much steadier.

“This guy. Could he have calculated everything up to this step? From now on, he wouldn’t even need to do anything. If we want to set a record, instead of buying him to set the record, we’ll do the opposite and pay him to not set the record???” Cold Night said in disbelief.

Chapter 165 – Record Kidnappping

The two of them stood like broken machines amidst the barren desert in the Heavenly Domain. The sand from the large gale seemed as if it was going to bury them.

Lord Grim!

Without a guild, there was no way they could figure out his origins. There also weren’t any signs of background powers assisting him. The tenth server’s dungeon records were solely controlled by his technique. He had even taken control of all of the guilds.

In the new server, dungeon records were extremely important for a guild’s development.

The new server was practically filled with new players. No matter how famous a guild’s name was, in the new server, they would simply be unknown to the eyes of new players. How could they establish their name towards new players? It was through dungeon records. These were undeniable reflections of a guild’s strength.

However, all of the tenth server’s guilds had now been turned into jokes. In the eyes of everyone else, whoever Lord Grim helped would obtain the record.

Ignoring the new players, the big guilds themselves recognized the importance of having Lord Grim when competing for the records and for him.

Once he started to act, there would be no chance for them. The new players had no information about the records, but those who were experienced could immediately tell how ridiculous Lord Grim’s records were. It was impossible for them to achieve records like this, so if they didn’t look for Lord Grim, they couldn’t do anything.

In the end, the big guilds hadn’t prepared well enough for this situation. How could they have imagined that such an overwhelming expert would appear. If the tenth server continued to be like this, it really would become a new age. None of the big guilds would have enough strength to take over. Experts. Experts were originally the biggest advantage that big guilds had in the new server. But with the presence of Lord Grim, their experts were worthless. Since it’s like this, what advantages did they have? They couldn’t just continue spamming in the world channel that they were one of Glory’s greatest guilds, could they?

“Hmm….. I’m also unsure whether this was all just a coincidence.” Cold Night said.

“If it’s not, then not only does this guy have terrifying skill, but he has smarts too.” Jiang You said.

“Should I go back and try to negotiate with him?” Cold Night said.

“Yeah, you should go……”

……

Glory Tenth Server.

Blue River wasn’t aware of this issue yet. He was still creating a dungeon team with Changing Spring. When Cold Night returned to the tenth server, he checked his friends list, but didn’t see Blue River online.

In his friends list, Lord Grim’s name was still lit. The world chat had calmed down quite a bit though. Right now, almost five o’clock, it was a period where there were only a few players online. With the passing of the wave of discussions over the dungeon records, the world chat had returned to its normal state.

However, Cold Night knew that even though the discussions had ended, it didn’t mean that the matter was over. Their guild’s image had been damaged. If they didn’t hurry and seize a record, they might actually fall in the tenth server.

“Brother, are you there?” Cold Night sent Lord Grim a message. During the evening, it was quite normal for a player to be AFK (away from their keyboards).

“Here.” Ye Xiu had been quietly killing monsters in the wild the entire time.

“I want to discuss about Line Canyon with you.” Cold Night said.

“Line Canyon? My level isn’t high enough yet!” Ye Xiu replied.

“Brother, do you really not know what I mean?” Cold Night carefully prodded. He really couldn’t afford to offend him! Cold Night held his breath.

“Tell me.” Ye Xiu replied.

“This time, for Line Canyon’s record, we hope that brother won’t act.” Cold Night said.

“Oh, the price for that is going to be even higher!” Ye Xiu replied.

The reply came instantly. There weren’t any shocks or doubts. He directly moved to the discussion over to the price. If this guy said he hadn’t planned anything beforehand, who would believe him? Lord Grim clearly knew better than he did. Lord Grim had prepared everything long ago. Cold Night felt depressed. He had no choice but to follow up and ask: “What’s the price?”

“Eight Scarlet Scorpion Tails, eight Scarlet Stingers, a Scarlet Berserker Blade, an Amber Crystal, and 40 threads of Sandworm Silk.”

The reply was once again instant. It looked like he prepared the price long ago too. Cold Night was still depressed. He went over the materials one by one and wanted to cry.

Scarlet Scorpion Tails and Scarlet Stingers were both from Line Canyon’s hidden BOSS, Scarlet Scorpion Assassin. The Scarlet Berserker Blade was the hidden BOSS Illusion Swordmaster Ahong’s Saber, an Orange weapon. The Sandworm Silk dropped from the other hidden BOSS, Sandworm. As for the Amber Crystal, that was a drop from the Line Canyon’s wild BOSS, Ronin Alpine.

Even just gathering these five items was extremely difficult.

This was because these items came from every single uncommon BOSS in Line Canyon. According to the number of materials requested, even if these items dropped from the BOSS 100% of the time, they would still have to face the hidden BOSS dozens of times. Just look at Ye Xiu’s two days of dungeoning. He ran the dungeon for a total of six times, yet he hadn’t met a single hidden BOSS. If he had to gather the materials by himself, even if he cleared Line Canyon until he couldn’t get experience from the dungeon anymore, he still wouldn’t be able to gather all of them.

And in order to get the Scarlet Berserker Blade, a player would have to first be lucky enough to meet the hidden BOSS. He then would have to get lucky enough for the Orange weapon to drop.

The Amber Crystal was even more troublesome. Wild BOSSes couldn’t simply be cleared;They had to be stolen through PK. The first kill on Desolate Land and Line Canyon’s wild BOSS had already been completed. These two kills were both done when Ye Xiu wasn’t online, which was why no one had asked him to participate. One of these kills was stolen by Herb Garden, while the other was done by the Tyrannical Ambition. But just thinking about how much they had put in to get this far made his heart ache.

No matter how fierce the fight for dungeon records were, there was no way it could compare with the type of direct PVP needed for the wild BOSS.

After calculating everything, Cold Night almost coughed up blood. He didn’t even want to think about the price of these items. Even gathering them was strenuous enough for him.

Their guild had already begun clearing Line Canyon for some time. They had already gathered enough Scarlet Scorpion Tails and Scarlet Stingers, but they hadn’t found a Scarlet Berserker Blade yet. They were still rather far from 40 threads of Sandworm Silk and the Amber Crystal was even more of a dream. Let alone, Tyrannical Ambition, no one in the entire tenth server had one yet! Wild BOSSes could only be cleared three times a week!

This list of items was clearly not the marked price for his substitution anymore. It was truly much higher.

“Brother, you’re too savage.”

Haggling over the price was a must. Cold Night restrained himself and calmly negotiated with Ye Xiu. Even though his previous impression of this person wasn’t bad, a feeling of grief and anger rose in his heart now. Cold Night felt as though he had been negotiating with a kidnapper. The hostage was the record. If you didn’t agree to my conditions, then I’m going to clear your record!

But after negotiating for a while, the other side didn’t seem to have any intentions of easing up. Cold Night was still discussing gloomily, when a system message suddenly popped up. Blue River had come online.

Cold Night’s heart shook. He suddenly had an idea.

“Old Blue!” Cold Night called.

“Yeah?”

“Which record are you guys planning to set?” Cold Night asked.

“What?” He had to be wary against opponents.They couldn’t throw away their caution even though Tyrannical Ambition and them weren’t archenemies like Herb Garden. Blue River was on guard.

“Let’s communicate this well! Wouldn’t it mean that we’d have to beat each other if both of us clear Desolate Land? This isn’t the time for us to fight.” Cold Night said.

“You’re right. Then this time, each of us will take one dungeon. We’ll clear Desolate Land. We won’t touch Line Canyon, what do you think?” Blue River said.

“Okay. With this, everything’s good.” Cold Night said, “When are you guys planning to set it?”

“Tomorrow during the day!” Blue River said. He had already distributed the cards. But it wouldn’t be convenient right now for the experts to run and get the cards, so it’d be better to wait until the next day.

“Old Blue, I’m just afraid that the records that we set will still be beaten by Lord Grim!” Cold Night said.

“That……. I don’t think he’d do that. In this situation, do you think someone’s going to look for him to set a record?” Blue River said.

“If no one asks him, then what if he himself goes to set it?” Cold Night said.

“Sets it himself?” Blue River froze. If Lord Grim set it himself…… that was also a possibility. They only needed one more person for their team. And in addition, the other side had a fifth member they could use! They had previously seen the fifth person. Among them was that Blade Master, who was still in their guild. It was just that they never saw him online ever again, making Blue River feel very puzzled.

“If no one goes to ask him, why would he put in an effort to do that?” Blue River said.

“If no one asks, how could he be satisfied?” Cold Night discovered that Blue River was a little thick. Everything was already laid out for him. Was he still not able to think of Lord Grim kidnapping the record?

But with this, Blue River finally got it: “So you’re saying……”

“I had been talking with Lord Grim just before and in the end, that guy….. said that not touching the record required a fee.” Cold Night informed Blue River of this startling news.

“Did he really say that?”

Cold Night directly copied the list of items Lord Grim had given him and sent it over. This list had too much of an impact, making Blue River feel a wave of heat.

“But do you think he’ll be able to beat our record?” Blue River replied. They were also experts. Actually, they also had an estimate of what the limit for the record was. No matter how skilled a player was, as long as they hit the limit, that player wouldn’t be able to beat it.

“You look at Boneyard’s record.” Cold Night said.

Blue River stared blankly. Boneyard’s record really was a legend. That record was simply inconceivable.

“According to you, then even if we wanted to set a dungeon record, we’d have to see what he’s up to? If not, then there’s no point in obtaining a record?” Blue River said.

“That’s what I feel……..”

“That would mean that he’d become an enemy to all of the guilds…… can everyone endure that?” Blue River said.

“I don’t know about that. But I do know that right now, the only way for us to pass this wall is to break our way through.” Cold Night said.

Chapter 166 – I Get a Little Lonely Sometimes Too

Blue River and Cold Night weren’t wrong.

If Lord Grim continued with his kidnapping of the record, then the matter wouldn’t just be between him and both of their guilds. The big guilds would unify and propose a way to resolve the issue; whether that was by bribing him or by killing him.

But at the moment, the crisis was only between their guilds. Even if the other guilds knew about Lord Grim’s snatching nature, they wouldn’t come out and help them immediately. They would watch them struggle first. If the two guilds actually fell, then that’d be great news for them.

“What do you plan on doing?” Blue River asked Cold Night.

“I don’t know. I wanted to see what you were thinking.” Cold Night said.

Blue River hesitated. Should he pay the ransom or fight against the kidnapper and compete for the records from now on?

Blue River had already clicked on Lord Grim’s name several times, but he hesitated each time. Record-related matters weren’t trivial. If they were, then he wouldn’t have went over to consult Changing Spring. But since he had just gone to see him, if he went back again, it’d make him seem less capable. Poplar Beach and his gang would definitely mock him for that.

But…… if they knew that he went to pay the ransom, then Poplar Beach and his gang wouldn’t say anything good about that either. Requesting help from the headquarters had already made him look shameful. In all of the new servers’ history, such a situation had never occurred before. For all the previous times, the experts that had been sent used their own strength to start anew.

This time! He definitely couldn’t pay the ransom.

Blue River made a decision. He had to demonstrate his worth.

“I’ve decided to set the record first and then worry about the rest later.” Blue River didn’t click on Lord Grim’s name and instead sent a message to Cold Night.

“Oh? You’re going to ignore Lord Grim’s actions?” Cold Night said.

“Yes!”

“Okay….. I hope that everything goes smoothly.” Cold Night said, but he still felt a bit of uncertainty within his heart. Was Blue River really going to set the record or was he just saying that to avoid giving me a bargaining chip? After all, if word came out that they had paid the ransom to Lord Grim, it would also hurt their reputation. Which is why when he discussed matters with Blue River, Cold Night didn’t say what he had decided on doing. When talking with other guilds, they had to always be on guard.

After verifying Blue River’s attitude on the matter, Cold Night decided to hold back his troops for now. In any case, they still needed some time to prepare for the Line Canyon record. For today, at least, it was impossible for them to do it.

The day gradually brightened. Being Su Mucheng’s pillow for the entire night, Ye Xiu’s shoulder had become sore long ago. But once he heard the quiet snoring, Ye Xiu knew Su Mucheng had really fallen asleep.

However, it was almost seven o’clock. Some of the customers at the Internet Cafe had already tidied up and were ready to leave. It was almost time for a shift change as well, so there was no way for them to continue staying here like this.

“Hey, hey.” Ye Xiu turned his head and said, “It’s time to wake up.”

“What time is it?” Su Mucheng asked drowsily.

“6:50.” Ye Xiu said.

“It’s not even 7 yet, another ten minutes……” Su Mucheng said and even shifted her head to a more comfortable position.

“Hurry up! I still have to take care of the customers who are getting ready to leave! You were lucky today. No one came to buy food at night.”Ye Xiu said. Usually, if anything happened to the machine or if the customers wanted something to eat or drink, it was his responsibility as the manager to take care of it. But it had been particularly peaceful today. It seemed as if everything magically went well for the all-night customers, allowing Su Mucheng to get a good night’s rest.

“Really? Then I really am lucky!” Su Mucheng finally lifted her head. She rubbed her eyes and constantly yawned.

“Cover up well. The customers are coming over.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh.” Su Mucheng wrapped herself up like when she first arrived. Her appearance right now wasn’t too revealing. Everyone was about to leave now!

Su Mucheng left the receptionist desk and watched as Ye Xiu helped the customers log out. Some of the customers, who weren’t leaving yet, paid to continue using the computers. All-night had its own price, while the morning had a different price.

“Brother Ye!” At this moment, the cashiers and managers with the morning shift arrived. Most of them lived close to each other, so they all ate and walked over together.

“Almost done.” Ye Xiu called out to them. He quickly finished up and left the receptionist desk. The morning shift took over. Ye Xiu’s workday was done.

“What would you like to eat?” Ye Xiu asked Su Mucheng.

“Anything is fine…….” Su Mucheng clearly wasn’t fully awake yet. She still looked a bit drowsy.

“Okay, then it’ll be the usual!” Ye Xiu said. The two of them left the Internet Cafe together.

Chen Guo had gotten up early today. As she went downstairs, she happened to see Ye Xiu leave the Internet Cafe with a girl. Her first thought that the girl was Tang Rou, but after getting a better look, she could tell that the girl wasn’t her. She had lived with Tang Rou for a long time, so she would be able to recognize her just from a rear view.

“Who is she?” Chen Guo ran over to ask others. Everyone shook their heads. Ye Xiu hadn’t introduced her to them.

“Little Tang?” Chen Guo turned around and called out to see if Tang Rou was there.

Tang Rou was there, but she was in the middle of playing a game. So she couldn’t hear her with headphones on. But since she sat in the same place everyday, Chen Guo quickly grabbed her.

“You woke up very early today?” Tang Rou turned around and saw Chen Guo.

“Yeah.” Chen Guo replied and then directly asked: “Who’s that sister together with Ye Xiu?”

“Together?” Tang Rou heard this and took a look at the receptionist desk: “They already left?”

“They left! They left just as I came down. Who is she?” Chen Guo said.

“Uh…… I don’t know her actual name, but she’s a girl that dungeons with us everyday.” Tang Rou said.

“An online friend?” Chen Guo was shocked.

“Those two…… know each other I think……..” Tang Rou had seen Su Mucheng sleep on Ye Xiu’s shoulders. Anyone could tell that the relationship between them wasn’t ordinary. But she wasn’t a gossipy person, so she didn’t ask about it. She didn’t want to assume that there was a relationship between those two. Online friends shouldn’t be so close, which meant that they knew each other very well.

“So this guy can seduce a girl too!” Chen Guo expressed her lament, “What does she look like?”

“I don’t know. I couldn’t see her properly.” Tang Rou said.

“What were you doing the entire night then!” Chen Guo expressed her discontent with Tang Rou.

Tang Rou helplessly laughed.

“What do you want to eat?” Chen Guo asked.

“I’ll eat whatever you’re going to eat. It’s not like I have any money. Sigh…….” Tang Rou also acted shamelessly sometimes.

“Wait here!” Chen Guo rolled her eyes and left. She took care of food and shelter, but because she didn’t have any standards, most of the time she would just decide what everyone ate on the spot. Sometimes she would be in a good mood and would invite everyone over for a big meal. Those that were there during those times always felt very lucky.

The area around Happy Internet Cafe had quite a few restaurants. Chen Guo naturally had places she frequently went to. After ordering wontons, steamed buns, porridge, and a bunch of other random dishes, she even looked around trying to catch their affair but wasn’t able to find anything.

When she returned with the breakfast, she didn’t see Ye Xiu. She called for Tang Rou to come and eat. She saw Ye Xiu come back with a cigarette in his mouth once they were halfway done.

“Woah! Boss, you woke up early today!” Ye Xiu greeted Chen Guo.

“What about that girl that was with you!” Chen Guo didn’t even try to ease into the subject. She just straight up asked him.

“She went back.” Ye Xiu replied calmly.

“Hmph, you can’t mix up work with your social life.” Chen Guo said.

“Wow, wontons! Give me a bowl!” Ye Xiu said as he completely went off topic.

“Didn’t you go and eat already?” Chen Guo said.

“I had to pay for that myself, so I ate less.” Ye Xiu said.

“Shameless!” Chen Guo ground her teeth, “There’s none for you.”

“Really? Then I’m going to bed!” Ye Xiu ran off. Chen Guo was baffled. She still wanted to continue prodding. Why’d he have to run off?

“Ha ha ha……” Tang Rou laughed on the side.

“What are you laughing at?” Chen Guo glared at her.

“Nothing…….” Tang Rou didn’t explain.

“You’re becoming more and more like him.” Chen Guo wasn’t happy.

“No way.”

“All you do is play games everyday. And you also have that weird aura. How long has it been since you’ve went out and been in the sun?” Chen Guo said.

“Okay, okay. I’ll take a walk with you on the weekends. Is that good enough?” Tang Rou said.

“Fine.” Chen Guo was satisfied. She had lived with her for almost two years, so Tang Rou had already become her close friend. She was the one who kept egging her on to play Glory. And now that she had succeeded, she discovered that the time they spent together had actually lessened.

In the beginning, Chen Guo thought about whether or not she should level a low-level account and play with them. If Tang Rou or Ye Xiu had brought it up, she would have definitely done it. But those two only minded their own business. There was no way they would have thought of her this much. In the end, after pondering about it for awhile, she discovered that those two’s levels had already gone up. If she started leveling, then she’d have to start from the beginner village, so she threw away that idea.

After all, she had played with Chasing Haze for so long that she was very attached to it. If someone told her to give it up, she definitely wouldn’t be able to. The only reason she wanted to go to the new server was to play with those two. After they got to the Heavenly Domain, she would definitely switch back to her main account. The way she saw it, it was already too late to start from the new server, so it’d be better to just wait for those two to reach the Heavenly Domain.

Although Chen Guo didn’t say it, she really did feel a little lonely nowadays. Whether that was in the game or outside of it, she felt a bit lonely.

“I’m full. I’m going to sleep!” Tang Rou finished her breakfast and got up to leave.

“Go ahead!” Chen Guo waved her hands and shooed Tang Rou away. She sat there by herself with a bowl of porridge and gazed out towards the empty Internet Cafe.

Chapter 167 – Taking Back the Record

At 3 o’clock in the afternoon during Tang Rou’s afternoon shift, the two had once again sat by themselves in front of their computers. Tang Rou had decided to give up playing the game during her shift and decided to look over guides instead. Ye Xiu, on the other hand, went to the smoking area to try and find a computer. One time, when Chen Guo was bored, she secretly made some calculations: if she charged Ye Xiu according to the Internet Cafe’s usual fees, then Ye Xiu would be paying twice the salary he gets.

Chen Guo had managed the Internet Cafe for so many years, but this was the first time she had seen anyone utilize the Internet Cafe employee benefits to such a level. Tang Rou was a close second and she had an even greater desire to take advantage of them than Ye Xiu did. This sister was busiest during the afternoon shift. She practically had no time to play the game, so she asked Chen Guo to move her to the all-night shift. Chen Guo tried very hard to put it off.

In game, the Blue Brook Guild was preparing for their record-setting run when Blue River suddenly saw a notification that Lord Grim had come online. He immediately felt a great deal of pressure.

It wasn’t a coincidence that they would be on at the same time. Blue River and his group often played the game all-night too. Their resting schedule was practically the same as Ye Xiu’s. In fact, they had only come online moments ago. Blue Brook Guild naturally understood the importance to this battle. After Changing Spring arranged for who would go, he called several players to work together and explore the dungeon. Desolate Land was a dungeon that these Heavenly Domain players hadn’t run in a long time, so they had to take some time to familiarize themselves with it.

After doing that, they all went to borrow their provided account cards. Changing Spring had personally brought over three experts to the tenth server. Blue River wasn’t using his own account right now. His character had already leveled past Desolate Land’s level limit, so it couldn’t be used to set the record. These account cards had just been obtained the previous day. This meant that the characters hadn’t used any of their entries for Desolate Land yet.

None of the experts had shown any signs of unfamiliarity with the dungeon on their first run. They were, after all, experts. Blue River was the one who was most familiar with the dungeon as he had entered it the most recent. As a result, he was appointed as the leader. They were able to achieve a time of 29:21:45 with just a few small mistakes. They had beaten their previous record. The experts that came over to help were extremely effective.

Blue River made a major mistake on their second run. The mistake affected their final time, which was 33:54:89. This run ended quite poorly. Even if they stretched out the leaderboards, it wasn’t even fast enough for them to be placed in the top twenty.

“Sorry…….” Blue River apologized to everyone. Their poor performance was all because of his mistake. The more experienced experts knew that, due to mistake, there was no way for them to set the record this time. As a result, they played more carelessly and listened to Blue River’s constant apologies.

They were all old friends, so no one said anything. They couldn’t guarantee that they wouldn’t make a mistake either.

“This is our last run for today……. we can do it everyone.” Changing Spring said.

“Sigh, this is unexpected! After leaving the normal servers for so many years already, to think I’d have to come back and try so hard for this dungeon again.” Someone said.

“Me too. I suddenly feel a bit nostalgic speaking about this!” Another player followed.

“Blue Bridge, hurry up and get to the Heavenly Domain! It’s been so long since we’ve dungeoned together.”

The current five-man team was Blue Brook Guild’s strongest combo.

The guild leader Changing Spring, Ice of Dawn, Chilling Nightfall, Flying Brushstroke, and Blue River’s main account Blue Bridge Spring Snow were Blue Brook Guild’s Five Greatest Experts! Changing Spring had gathered these experts to dungeon in the tenth server, leaving even Poplar Beach unable to object.

The players’ strengths wouldn’t lose out to Poplar Beach in any way. In the guild, they were also considered seniors. Their dispatch meant that Blue Brook Guild was using their greatest strength to fight. Even if Poplar Beach was confident that he was better than Blue River, because of what their team signified, there was no way he’d be able to switch in for Blue River.

“This is our last run for today. We can do it, brothers!!” Blue River said and then took a deep breath. He was even more pressured than the other four. This record was closely related to his guild’s power in the tenth server. But once he thought of Lord Grim, Blue River couldn’t calm down. He was always worried that their record wouldn’t be good enough and that it would be stepped on by Lord Grim again.

Calm down, be cool, concentrate!!

Blue River kept on repeating these words to himself as he entered Desolate Land for their third run.

Changing Spring was a Berserker, Dawn of Ice was a Summoner, Chilling Nightfall was an Elementalist, Flying Brushstroke was a Spitfire. and with Blue River’s Blade Master, their team was a full DPS team without an MT or a Healer either. Even though their skill level couldn’t be compared to pro-players, they were definitely at the peak of normal players.

For a low-leveled dungeon like Desolate Land, even though they weren’t using their main accounts, they were still confident with rolling through the dungeon using their full DPS team. Only this type of DPS team could take the final record. For example, in their previous record for Desolate Land, even though they didn’t have an MT, they still had Bound Boat’s Cleric. Because of this, their DPS was brought down as opposed to Lord Grim’s team which was full DPS. As a result, it was clear that if they didn’t use a DPS team too , then there would be no way to compete with Lord Grim. This was why Blue River needed the help of experts from the Heavenly Domain.

Third try!

Everyone’s spirit was at their peak. They had made mistakes in their last two runs, but this time, they were going to put an end to that. Everyone put in 100% of their effort and pushed on and on.

The first BOSS fell.

The second BOSS fell.

The rest of the way went by smoothly after they had cleared out the monsters. Their current performance was definitely worthy of being praised. However, they had understood very well about BOSS Toya’s style. Stealing time from Toya needed a bit of luck. This BOSS had too many skills. Who knew what he would do when they faced off against him! There wouldn’t be a set time without a good strategy. Many wanted to restrict Toya but, at Level 30, they didn’t have enough skills. So their only choice was to use coordination.But coordinating against such a complicated BOSS needed both time and practice. Due to this, the difficulty of fighting this BOSS increased.

But this was only a low-level dungeon! Many players would only play here for a bit and then move past this stage. Who would take the time to research it? This was why restricting Toya was still just a theory.

The expert team of five hadn’t trained together for any sort of coordination,which meant that they hadn’t thought of that type of theory. These players were just using the usual strategy. They would attack and then rely on themselves to push down Toya.

The battle flew by and the remnants of the battle was displayed on the castle walls and in the rear garden.

Sword lights, bullets, magic, and summoned pets filled the garden as the five players surrounded Toya. At this moment, none of them could afford looking at the time. They could only do their best!

Toya fell. Blue River didn’t even get the opportunity to check the time, when suddenly, the system announcement popped up!

Their Blue Brook Guild had finally taken down this Desolate Land’s record: 26:31:55.

“We did it!” Those four were extremely happy, but Blue River didn’t even think about relaxing yet. 26:31:55. They were only faster than Lord Grim’s record by a minute and a half. But Blue River clearly knew: Lord Grim’s team hadn’t reached their limit yet. Not only was their equipment lacking, but they also had someone on their team who was holding them back. Even so, their Five Greatest Experts team was only able to improve the record by a minute and a half. This meant that this record wasn’t completely unbeatable yet.

“Do you guys think it’s possible to improve this record?” After they exited the dungeon, Blue River asked them seriously.

“You think that this record isn’t enough to beat Lord Grim?” Changing Spring said.

“Yeah.” Blue River nodded his head.

“If we have to improve, then there’s isn’t much we can do about the small monsters. It would all have to depend on Toya. If we are able to completely suppress Toya and be the first to act, then it’s still possible to improve the record.” Flying Brushstroke said.

“In any case, the record’s already been broken and we don’t have anymore entries left. Right now, the whole world is looking at it. Find people to bring back our influence and clean our name!” Changing Spring said.

“Okay!” Blue River replied. They had prepared for this moment. Blue River called the guild and Blue Brook Guild’s name immediately appeared all over the world chat.

The topic today was a follow-up to last night’s topic, which meant that the taunters from last night might not all be present. But Blue Brook Guild wasn’t trying to attack these guys, they were only telling everyone: Blue Brook Guild doesn’t need Lord Grim’s help to set a record.

“Blue Brook Guild actually did it!” Cold Night saw the record and then quietly watched the advertising done by Blue Brook Guild in the world chat.

A minuted and a half. For Lord Grim, it might still be possible to beat that! Cold Night’s line of thinking was similar to Blue River’s.

“It looks like we’ll soon find out what exactly Blue River’s attitude towards this is and what exactly Lord Grim will do.” Cold Night thought to himself.

Meanwhile, Changing Spring and the others withdrew after setting the record. They obviously wouldn’t stay to level these accounts. As for Blue River, he was in a more difficult position. He looked at their record and suddenly feared that Lord Grim’s name would appear in front of theirs.

After the wave of fear, Blue River suddenly realized that Lord Grim should have already used up all of his entries for the day. It wasn’t midnight yet so with this in mind, he felt at ease knowing that their record wouldn’t be broken right now!

It looked like the most crucial stage would take place from 12-2 o’clock again!

Seeing Lord Grim’s name lit up on his friends list, Blue River was in a conflicted mindset regarding whether or not to talk to him. After pondering over it, he decided to not talk to him after all.

The record had already been stolen back. Lord Grim, I won’t come to an agreement with you this time around! Blue River encouraged himself with such thoughts.

Chapter 168 – Fire Witch Cashew

Blue Brook Guild’s PR went quite smoothly. After all, the announcement of their new record was still there. The leaderboards could also be checked at any time. With the presence of this proof, there was nothing new players could criticize them for. New players also didn’t have any sort of hate directed towards Blue Brook Guild. The reason why they suddenly raised a storm upon them was simply because Full Moon Guild’s bragging made them feel unbelievably disgusted.

The time slowly crept towards midnight. Blue River slowly grew nervous as well. From 12:20 – 12:30, those ten minutes, Blue River stopped doing everything and stared at his screen.

The system suddenly made an announcement.

As soon as he saw the word “system”, Blue River froze.

System announcement: Please play the game in a healthy manner and take a break every once in awhile!

“F*ck! My hair almost turned white from fear.” Blue River couldn’t help but curse out loud. It was the system announcement that frequently came during the night to remind the players to take a break from the game. Of course, from a game company’s perspective, they wouldn’t want their players to stop playing the game. Years ago, players might have felt warmhearted from this fake and insincere reminder. Only noobs would be tricked by this reminder!

At 12:30, their record had yet to be broken. Blue River let out a sigh of relief. But then he immediately thought of something else: what if he didn’t start at exactly 12:00?

As a result, Blue River went back to nervously staring at the screen.

“Old Blue, you’re not going to dungeon today?” The team that Blue River played with frequently went over to ask him.

“I’m going. I’m going!” If Lord Grim was really going to break the record, then there was no point in worrying about it and wasting time. Blue River thought this way as he followed his team into the dungeon. However, he couldn’t concentrate on the dungeon. He made numerous mistakes and, at one point, he almost caused the whole team to be wiped out.

“Old Blue, how about I lead……” Everyone was scared now, but they all understood why Blue River was so distracted.

“Okay, you lead then!” With the switch, Blue River didn’t make as many mistakes as he did before. Prior to that, he was practically leading the team to their deaths.

After Line Canyon was cleared, it was as if half the night had gone by. There wasn’t any new system announcements, letting Blue River finally relax a bit.

Meanwhile, on Ye Xiu’s side, they hadn’t gone to set a record tonight. At 11 o’clock, Tang Rou changed shifts and began playing the game. They invited Steamed Bun Invasion and waited for Su Mucheng to come online. The four-player team then went to Fire Forest together.

Frost Forest, Fire Forest, Gloom Forest, and Sunlight Forest were Glory’s four large forests, which were also leveling areas and dungeons.

Frost Forest was the lowest-level one among the four. Fire Forest, which was the one Ye Xiu and his group were going to, was a Level 34-36 area.

As Level 30 characters, Level 35 monsters would give them the most experience. However, no matter how much experience wild monsters gave, there was no way they could compete with the elite monsters in dungeons. Plus, because of the end of dungeon experience rewards, running to the leveling area instead of to a dungeon was not the wisest choice.

A veteran of the game like Ye Xiu definitely wouldn’t make such an unwise choice. However, they weren’t going there to level. Ye Xiu’s goal was the Fire Forest’s wild BOSS, Fire Witch Cashew.

In Frost Forest, the strongest hidden BOSS White Witch was proficient in Ice Elemental Magic. As for Fire Forest, the Fire Witch, proficient in Fire Elemental Magic, was an existence even greater than hidden BOSSes: wild BOSS.

The wild BOSS was always the highest level in the leveling area which meant Fire Witch Cashew was Level 36.

Level 36 was 6 levels higher than Ye Xiu and his group’s characters. They wouldn’t gain much experience because that exceeded the five level limit,. However killing a BOSS wasn’t something that was done to gain levels.

Still, a 6 Level Suppression! This was a huge disadvantage for them. The current elite teams of the big guilds were Level 32, yet even they didn’t dare to provoke the Fire Witch Cashew.;they were already scared of a 4 Level Suppression. After all, she wasn’t just some regular monster. She was the strongest BOSS type, a wild BOSS.

A 4 Level Suppression was already enough to make the players retreat. But Ye Xiu was about to lead his team to battle against this wild BOSS that had a 6 Level Suppression. As for the other three, they weren’t scared at all.

Excluding Su Mucheng, Ye Xiu felt a need to let them know that a 6 Level Suppression wasn’t a joke.

“Everyone, note that there is a 6 Level Suppression between us and the Fire Witch.” Ye Xiu said as they searched for the Fire Witch. The Fire Witch was definitely there. A wild BOSS would just wander around after spawning if it wasn’t killed immediately. The tenth server had opened for three weeks already! It wasn’t just the Fire Witch; wild BOSSes from all other higher-leveled areas were already waiting for players to clear them! It was different from the first week, where the wild BOSSes hadn’t spawned yet.

“Okay.” Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion replied nonchalantly.

“Don’t underestimate this 6 Level Suppression! Combined with her identity as a wild BOSS, a lot of skill effects will be reduced by 60-100%. Do you know what a 100% reduction means? That means a complete reduction; no effect. That’s why during battle, you’re going to need to adjust. Dragon Tooth’s Stun, Sky Strike’s Knock-up, Sand Toss’s Blind, and Brick’s Dizzy. All of these will have a reduced effect on her.” Ye Xiu lectured.

“Oh, so it’s like that!” The two nodded.

“Haven’t we already encountered this type of situation in Line Canyon? Wasn’t the BOSS there higher leveled than us?” Tang Rou said.

“Yeah, it was higher leveled, but starting from Level 30, normal dungeons wouldn’t have level ranges higher than three usually. This is because a very high Level Suppression is difficult to deal with. 3 Levels is still manageable. If it weren’t for that, then the Level 36 Fire Witch would have been killed already. How else could we have gotten a chance to kill it?” Ye Xiu explained.

“Okay, I’ll pay attention to it.” Tang Rou didn’t dare to include Steamed Bun Invasion with a “we”.

“Steamed Bun, do you understand?’ Ye Xiu asked.

“Understood.” Steamed Bun Invasion replied. Ye Xiu couldn’t tell whether or not he actually understood.

The four wandered around Fire Forest and sometimes killed a few of the monsters along the way. The monsters in all the Four Great Forests were Goblins. Their levels were different, so they would obviously be different from each other. The Fire Forest’s Goblins all had red skin with a blood-thirsty look on their faces. They looked much more fierce than Frost Forest’s goblins.

“Here, she’s over here.” Ye Xiu found the silhouette of the Fire Witch Cashew.

In the middle of an open space in the forest, a large bonfire blazed. Fire Witch Cashew was standing crazily on one side. She carried an extremely long magic staff, with a flame-shaped rune on top, which seemed to pulsate with the raging fire. Beside her, a large mob of small Fire Forest Goblins were circling around the bonfire. They seemed to be holding some sort of a grand ritual. They were shouting and running around, but none of them left.

“What do we do? No one has touched it for so long that so many monsters have gathered……” Su Mucheng said.

“Don’t worry, we have time. Everyone has their potions, right?” Ye Xiu said.

“Got ’em.” The others replied. Ye Xiu had already told everyone to spend their money in Congee City and buy mid-grade potions.

“Okay, then the two of you go run away.” Ye Xiu said.

“What?” Tang Rou didn’t understand.

“You and Steamed Bun run. We’ll destroy that bonfire. The enemies will crazily chase after us and then we’ll counterattack.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay.” Tang Rou’s Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion ran off. Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist immediately began to store up energy for a laser. In that instant, Ye Xiu lifted up his Thousand Chance Umbrella and sent Anti-Tank Missiles over.

Three consecutive Anti-Tank Missiles and a giant laser beam shot towards that bonfire. The explosion splashed in every direction like a firework. The Goblins shrieked and ferociously glared at the two of them. The Fire Witch also turned to glance at them. She raised her magic staff and chanted in an unknown language. The Goblin’s arms suddenly glowed with a red light.

“Tsk tsk, the entire mob has Flame Chasers! The system is so shameless.” Ye Xiu said, while having his Lord Grim Aerial Fire backwards. Cleansing Mist did the same.

Although their movement speed was quick, it required them to repeatedly chain the same action over and over again. However, this wasn’t a problem for pro-players. While under their control, their speed wasn’t much slower than a Witch’s low-altitude flight. The only weakness was that they could only fly backwards. Because of this, there were several things they needed to careful of. For example, Ye Xiu was warning Su Mucheng: “Be careful! Don’t crash into a tree!”

“If I follow you, then I won’t crash into anything!” Su Mucheng said.

“That’s not true.”

“If you made a mistake then you’d be the first one to crash into a tree.” Su Mucheng said.

“No…… I’m afraid you’ll crash into me.” Ye Xiu said.

The two talked as they Aerial Fired. It clearly wasn’t anything difficult for them. One of them was in the front; the other in the back. They were both light and quick. The distance between those fierce Goblins and them grew wider and wider, but the Fire Witch’s movement speed wasn’t inferior to those two. She didn’t need to use her legs to run. She simply flew in the air towards them.

“Give her something to play with!” Seeing that the Fire Witch was closing in, Ye Xiu yelled.

“Okay.” Su Mucheng said. The two flew backwards as they fired towards the Fire Witch.

If this was a normal monster, then being repeatedly fired at like this would cause it to be pushed back. But to this Fire Witch who was 6 levels higher, these bullets had no effect on her movement speed.

“A little bigger!!” Ye Xiu yelled as he fired three Anti-Tank Missiles. Su Mucheng was slightly slower, causing their six Anti-Tank Missiles to form a line.

The six consecutive Anti-Tank Missiles exploded one after another. The Fire Witch finally gave the skills some face and was slowed down a bit. But the effects didn’t even last a second as she quickly began closing in again.

Chapter 169 – Skill Interrupt

The 6 Level Suppression truly couldn’t be looked down upon. The knockback caused by the six Anti-Tank Missiles on the Fire Witch wasn’t even equal to that of a normal attack on an ordinary monster. And that was even with the Fire Witch luckily being a Mage type. She wasn’t born with a sturdy body. If she was switched with a Strength type BOSS, then under the 6 Level Suppression, the six Anti-Tank Missiles would simply seem like fleeting clouds.

Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng obviously recognized this, which was why they hadn’t placed very high hopes on it. They only needed to buy a bit more time.

Even with this though, the Fire Witch was still closing in on the two. As soon as they entered her attack range, she immediately lifted her staff and chanted a few words. The space around them seemed to suddenly split open. Two massive fireballs formed and crashed down from the sky towards them.

The Fire Witch continued give chase as she cast the spell.

Magic that required chanting usually couldn’t be done while moving. But there was one exception —— Elementalists. After learning the Level 30 Passive skill Mobile Cast, Elementalists were able to move while casting spells. Of course, their movement speed would be greatly reduced under this situation. Leveling the passive skill would decrease the extent by which the movement speed was reduced. However, even at max level, Elementalists would still only be able to move at 50% of their usual speed. It still couldn’t be compared with moving under normal conditions.

Although the Fire Witch was a BOSS, she still had to comply with the rules of the system.Her movement speed had greatly reduced while she was casting those two massive fireballs. Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng easily dodged the attack and took advantage of the opportunity to widen the distance between them and the Fire Witch.

The Fire Witch’s AI wasn’t very smart. She would first have to catch up to them before attacking. As soon as there was an opportunity to attack, she would cast a spell and slow down. Through this alternation, between her movement speed Lord Grim and Cleansing Mist were always able to maintain a certain distance from her. The goblins were eventually left behind so they gradually left the battle.

The goblins were all normal monsters in the leveling area. They were completely unrelated to the Fire Witch. The reason so many of them had accumulated around her was because the Fire Witch hadn’t been killed for such a long time.

They all had their own way of deciding on aggro. At this moment, their targets were getting further and further away. Soon, they could no longer see their targets, so the goblins turned around and went away to play.

As for Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng, all they could was run around in circles. The BOSS also had a limited range for where she was able to move around. It wasn’t possible to bring the Fire Forest’s Fire Witch all the way to Frost Forest.

“Coordinates 1658, 1542!” Ye Xiu messaged Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion. With the way he and Su Mucheng retreated while attacking, it appeared as if they were kiting the Fire Witch. However, the two of them weren’t able to chain their attacks too closely. In addition, the the BOSS’s life would still automatically recover. Even though the recovery wouldn’t completely mitigate the damage they had done or even if they had infinite mana, it would still take them more than a day to take down the BOSS.

Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion received the message and quickly rushed over. When they got there, they saw that the goblins that used to be with the Fire Witch, were already gone. Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng no longer needed to play tag with the Fire Witch anymore so they began hunting her down.

“We have arrived!!” Steamed Bun Invasion announced. He himself hadn’t arrived yet, though his Brick had. The flying Brick smashed into the back of the Fire Witch’s head. The Fire Witch seemed to have been stunned for a bit, but she instantly recovered.

“Look carefully before using it! Dizzy won’t have much of an effect on her, so only use it to interrupt her skills!!” Ye Xiu instructed Steamed Bun Invasion.

No matter how short the Dizzy effect lasted, it was still a status effect. If the Fire Witch was hit while casting a spell, then the spell would definitely get interrupted. Of course, the prerequisite was that the Dizzy effect activated. If it didn’t, then the damage dealt from it wouldn’t nearly be enough to interrupt her spells.

“You also have Inject Poison. Pay attention to how you use it!” Ye Xiu reminded Steamed Bun Invasion.

Inject Poison was a Level 30 Brawler skill. Even though the skill’s name contained the word poison, it didn’t actually have any Poison effects. This skill had two effects: It could induce a Bleed effect and it could also Break Super Armor.

The target could not be knocked down, launched, knocked back, or interrupted when it was in Super Armor……. Unless a Grab type skill was used, the target could not be moved forcibly.

Inject Poison was a skill that could get rid of this Super Armor. At its lowest level, the skill could dispel Super Armor for up to 5 seconds. At max level, the skill could dispel Super Armor for up to 10 seconds.

Under the Fire Witch’s Level Suppression, there was no way Inject Poison would be able to dispel Super Armor for a full 5 seconds. However, Steamed Bun Invasion could still hear Ye Xiu’s instruction from before telling him that he should circle around the Fire Witch and be ready to use Inject Poison at any time.

Whenever the Fire Witch attacked or cast magic, a red glow would emanate from her. This was her appearance when she was in a Super Armor state. In this state, the Fire Witch was unstoppable. Neither normal attacks nor skills had any way of stopping her movements. She suddenly opened her arms. Not only was there a red glow around her body, a fiery aura also emanated outwards, making everything around her go up in flames. Quite a few dried up leaves also leapt up in flames.

Meteor Shower!

This was the Fire Witch’s AoE spell. The spell summoned numerous meteors that would fall like rain onto the target.

“Inject Poison!!” Ye Xiu didn’t have time to tell him what the spell was. As soon as he saw the Fire Witch raise her hands, he immediately shouted.

Prepared, Steamed Bun Invasion heard Ye Xiu’s command and immediately used “Inject Poison.” The Fire Witch took the Inject Poison and the fiery aura emanating from her body instantly retreated. Steamed Bun Invasion was extremely shameless. He was afraid that he would provoke some sort of response. So after he used Inject Poison, he immediately ran and hid behind a tree.

“Why are you hiding?” Steamed Bun Invasion’s cowardly display made Ye Xiu not know whether he should laugh or cry. If Steamed Bun Invasion wasn’t going to use this chance, then he’d have to make up for him. Luckily, Lord Grim wasn’t too far from the Fire Witch. He sent a Sky Strike and launched the Fire Witch into the air. Under the Level Suppression and the BOSS’s innate defense, this Knock-Up was only able to make the BOSS stumble. However, Ye Xiu quickly followed up with a Falling Flower Palm, hitting the Fire Witch.

After successfully interrupting the Fire Witch’s Meteor Shower, Ye Xiu scolded Steamed Bun Invasion: “Don’t run! Once Inject Poison is used, you have to hurry up and interrupt her spell.” This was supposed to be a chance for Steamed Bun Invasion to practice, but that guy had actually run away.

“I was afraid that she would have some sort of scary spell.” Steamed Bun Invasion immediately replied.

In the time it took to say these words, the Fire Witch had already recovered and returned to kill them. Tang Rou’s Soft Mist went to meet up with her. Three types of Chasers danced around her. Besides the Neutral Chaser and the Ice Chaser, there was also a Fire Chaser from the use of Falling Flower Palm. The Fire Chaser buffed her Strength. At this moment, a layer of red magic fluctuations glowed around her arm. Her appearance with the Fire Chaser looked similar to the buff which the Fire Witch had given to the goblins earlier.

Soft Mist initiated with a Sky Strike. But the Fire Witch didn’t budge as she had Super Armor. The staff in her hands whirled. The rune at the end of her staff brought forth flames as it moved through the air. All of the Fire Witch’s attacks carried the Fire Attribute.

This Witch’s staff was extremely long. The sweep it created covered a wide area. Steamed Bun Invasion, who was just about to go forward, was forced to retreat. Soft Mist, who was already in range, didn’t have time to retreat. She hastily ducked to avoid the attack and then rolled, avoiding the streak of flames that came from the Fire Witch’s staff.

Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist was long-ranged, so she didn’t need to get up close. At this moment, she fired a stored-up Laser Rifle. The Laser Rifle crashed onto the Fire Witch’s body and seemed as if it would penetrate through her body. The momentum it carried was astonishing, but against the Witch’s Super Armor, it was only able to deal damage. The Fire Witch continued what she was doing and was once again about to cast a large AoE spell. Steamed Bun Invasion saw this and panicked: “Inject Poison is still on cooldown!”

He hadn’t finished talking, when Lord Grim rushed forward. He used a Circle Swing and stabbed the Fire Witch, throwing her and interrupting her spell. Grabs ignored Super Armor.

Interrupting a skill this way seemed simple on paper, but a normal player would still fail nine out of ten times. The successful interrupt would only be because of luck.

The BOSS’s skills weren’t so slow that you had time to see it, rush up, and then use a Grab to interrupt it. When the Fire Witch cast a spell like the Fireballs, the cast was nearly instant. It was practically the same as not casting at all. Even for large spells like Meteor Shower, if Steamed Bun Invasion was even a step slower, there wouldn’t have been enough time to follow up with any skill after his Inject Poison.

There was only a one second window and sometimes even less.

During their battle against Frost Forest’s Frost Thain, Blue River had a Super Armor Break skill “Wave Wheel Slasher” to use against the BOSS’s Super Armor skill. But why didn’t he use it then? It was because he wasn’t good enough.

What Ye Xiu could do didn’t necessarily mean that other players could do as well. Even for Tang Rou, even with her high hand speed, she still lacked in experience. If she had tried to use Circle Swing to interrupt the Witch, she would have most likely failed. Too early and the BOSS would have simply gotten back up and re-cast the spell. The Circle Swing would then be on cooldown. Too late and well, the spell would have already been released and the Circle Swing would be interrupted.

Lord Grim was unspecialized. Besides Circle Swing, he also had access to skills like Back Throw and Wave Wheel Slasher, which could Break Super Armor. He had the ability to continuously interrupt the Fire Witch’s casting. Letting Steamed Bun Invasion use Inject Poison was simply a convenient way to help him learn. Fighting against this big BOSS with a huge level gap was to practice interrupting skills.

Chapter 170 – Fire Witch First Kill

“Interrupt! Interrupt!”

Steamed Bun Invasion’s voice repeatedly resounded.

This guy was always immersed into the games he played, and he would often shout out his moves like characters in early Hong Kong kung-fu movies. His punches and kicks all carried whooshing sound effects. This type of constant shouting frequently disturbed the moods of the opponents he faced in the Arena. But truthfully, Steamed Bun Invasion’s dubbing had absolutely no meaning to them. For example, in this big BOSS battle, it definitely wouldn’t affect the situation. Even so, he would still shout as usual.

Ye Xiu deliberately gave Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion chances to practice, letting them have the opportunity to interrupt the Fire Witch. They were only killing a BOSS, so there was no need to worry about time.

Because these two lacked experience, with the way they were fighting, there was no way a mistake wouldn’t be made during the long BOSS battle.

“Not good!! Run!” Ye Xiu suddenly shouted. Tang Rou had been one step too slow in interrupting the Fire Witch’s Meteor Shower. Ye Xiu felt that there wasn’t enough time to rescue the situation, so he hastily warned them.

Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist was already outside the spell’s range, so she was safe. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim used a Shadow Clone Technique and left his fake body there, while his real body instantly escaped. The remaining players, Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion, were in a more difficult predicament.

The two players were melee classes, so they were the closest to the Fire Witch when the spell was cast. The spell array took form and the air above them began to boil. It seemed as if the entire sky had ignited on fire. Fireballs of different sizes swiftly dropped from the sky. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion hastily had their characters run away, but it was impossible to completely dodge them all. The countless meteors showered down and the earth and skies instantly turned into a sea of flames. When the two of them rushed out of the fire, they only had a sliver of health left. They miserably retreated to one side and began drinking potions to recover.

Fortunately, the range of large AoE spells such as Meteor Fall couldn’t be shifted, when the magician cast them while moving. If not, then the Fire Witch would have chased the two of them and they would have already died and returned back to Congee City.

“My bad.” Tang Rou said. She wasn’t someone who refused to admit her mistakes. She only wanted to improve.

“Pay attention to the timing.” Ye Xiu didn’t say too much. He had already indicated when they should act. Putting it into practice depended on them to grasp the timing. It all relied on the individual’s reaction speed and judgement. Ye Xiu couldn’t help them at this.

The successfully cast Meteor Fall set the Fire Forest ablaze. After the Fire Witch shrieked and cackled several times, she continued to wave her staff at them.

“Don’t worry about it! Forward!” Ye Xiu commanded.

With regards to Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion, Ye Xiu wasn’t letting them go and freely practice. For example, the two weren’t at full health yet. If they failed to interrupt a spell again, then they might die. Ye Xiu would take up the task in this type of situation. He had a 100% chance of success in interrupting her spells with his excellent movements.

Wave Wheel Slasher!

This time, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim used a Spellblade skill. The tip of the blade would lock the Fire Witch in a spell array and cast a Wave Wheel that would slash the Fire Witch multiple times. If there were any other enemies nearby, the Wave Wheel would also damage them. Once the Wave Wheel had finished spinning, it would explode and cause the target to fly out, similar to the Fire Witch, who was now on the ground.

The battle continued.

In this type of continuous battling, even top-tier pro-players like Ye Xiu couldn’t guarantee that a mistake wouldn’t occur. So Lord Grim also took some damage. The only player who hadn’t taken damage was the long-ranged Cleansing Mist.

The battle would last for hours. It wasn’t one that could be finished in a matter of minutes.

Time passed by slowly.

No one in the tenth server knew that such an intense and difficult battle was going on in Fire Forest. Four characters were hunting down the wild BOSS Fire Witch that was six levels above them. This was something no player could ever imagine.

All of the guilds’ players were still running dungeons at a suitable level for them. The only wild BOSSes they were paying attention to were the ones in Frost Forest, Boneyard, Desolate Land, and Line Canyon.

Fire Forest? In truth, it was about time. The highest-leveled characters currently were all halfway through to Level 32. As soon as they had reached Level 33, they would begin hunting down Fire Forest’s Fire Witch. Line Canyon and Desolate Land were also done in a similar way.

1:00.

1:30.

2:00.

2:30.

“If they’re running Desolate Land, then they should be done by now, no?” Blue River and his friends had already finished running the dungeon three times. If Lord Grim was going to set the record, then he shouldn’t be so late. Two and a half hours had already passed, yet there were still no signs of any record being set. Could it be that Lord Grim was also having a bit of trouble?

It was only the first day, so Blue River didn’t dare be too happy. He only let out a sigh of relief. He couldn’t smile yet.

“Let’s go to Desolate Land.” Blue River said. They had just run Line Canyon.

But while they were traveling, a system announcement suddenly popped up.

System Announcement: Players Lord Grim, Cleansing Mist, Soft Mist, and Steamed Bun Invasion have completed the First Kill for Fire Witch Cashew.

Amidst all of the random messages in the world channel, this system announcement looked as if it was some joke made by a naive noob.

Fire Cashew First Kill!

Those who reacted were of course, veterans and experts!

In the instant that announcement was made, Blue River froze. The four friends he was with had also frozen.

At this moment, they all had the same reaction. They moved their mouse over to the world channel and dragged the chat box to check the announcement again. Each player carefully and earnestly looked at it over again. Not a single word of it was misplaced.

“Fire Witch?” Blue River didn’t want to believe it.

Fire Forest’s Fire Witch?

Blue River wasn’t the only one with this doubt.

However, to these experienced Glory players, they were well aware that there existed only one Fire Witch in the game.

“No way!!”

There were even a few in the Internet Cafe who cried out in alarm.

The initial waves of the tenth server opening had already passed. There weren’t many Glory players in Happy Internet Cafe who mainly played in the tenth server. Most of the all-night veterans were in the other servers, so they hadn’t seen the news. As a result, they were obviously indifferent towards it.

The few who did react weren’t familiar with each other. They could only discuss the astonishing news with their friends in-game.

Fortunately, they had completed the First Kill late at night. If not, all of those in Happy Internet Cafe who had known that Lord Grim was being played by Ye Xiu would circle around and watch him.

‘So we finally killed it……” In Happy Internet Cafe, Ye Xiu and Tang Rou both let out a sigh of relief. After the final blow hit the Fire Witch, her body burst into flames. Her mean and ferocious expression could be seen in the wisps of leftover flames. Once the flames died down, a few equipment and materials dropped.

Three and a half hours!!

The four of them had been fighting the Fire Witch for a long three and half hours. It could be seen just how hard it was to beat a six level higher wild BOSS from this. Tang Rou’s Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion had almost died several times. Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist was fine. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim, on the other hand, was just playing around. Tang Rou could tell with a single glance that he wasn’t trying his hardest.

“Not easy, ah, not easy. Let’s see what she dropped.” Ye Xiu said as he went to take a look at the dropped equipment and materials.

“Flame Stone! Yes, I’ll be taking this!” Ye Xiu picked up this material.

“Red Flame Staff, a Level 35 Purple weapon! Sadly, we can’t use this rare item, so let’s leave it for selling or for trading equipment!” Ye Xiu looked over the second item.

‘Red Flame Gown, a Level 35 Blue Cloth Armor. It increases Fire Resistance, this….. none of you are Cloth type classes, so we don’t need it either. It can only be sold for money.” The third item.

“Wow, Scarlet Moon Belt…… it looks like someone’s luck is good today. Take it! With this, your set will be complete.” The Fire Witch dropped Level 30-35 items. The fourth drop was given to Tang Rou. Even though she already had it, she could still trade it for the part she was missing.

“Fire Spirit’s Ring…… it also increases Fire Resistance. How useless……” The fifth was also a Blue equipment, a Level 30 Ring that increased Fire Resistance. These types of equipment were only useful against certain kinds of enemies. Under normal circumstances, there wasn’t much of a difference between it and regular Magic Resistance.

“Four equipment were dropped. A Purple weapon too. Not bad.” Ye Xiu nodded his head in approval.

“Are we rich?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked gleefully.

“We’re not that lucky!” Ye Xiu said. He then discovered that they all chose to give up on these items. Only Tang Rou had rolled for the Scarlet Moon Belt.

Seeing everyone’s trust in him, Ye Xiu didn’t object. He picked them all up and then gave the Red Flame Staff to Steamed Bun Invasion: “Selling it for 200 Gold coins won’t be a problem. You can use that to buy a set for yourself.”

“Really? Awesome!” Steamed Bun Invasion received it with excitement.

The other two equipment, the Red Flame Gown and the Fire Spirit’s Ring, were less important from a long-term perspective. However, players were about to hit Level 33 at present. If they were going to compete in this Fire Forest, then Fire Resistant equipment would greatly increase their chances of survival, so it was uncertain how much they would sell for.

“Okay! Let’s go back to dungeoning!”

Because of this First Kill, the entire community was completely shocked. Ye Xiu didn’t care though. As for Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion? They didn’t really take the Fire Witch seriously. The 6 Level Suppression only reduced the damage they dealt and reduced their skills’ effects. It made the battle very long and even though they almost died several times, from a mechanical perspective, the two didn’t feel that killing the BOSS was too difficult.

“So easy!” This was Tang Rou’s final opinion on the matter.

Chapter 171 – If I Can Kill It, Why Can’t I Kill It?

Real or fake?

Ten minutes had passed since the Fire Witch’s First Kill was announced. Ye Xiu’s party had finished picking up the drops, while the experts from the guilds were still going crazy over what had happened.

6 Level Suppression. They only had four players, yet they were able to beat a wild BOSS six levels higher than them. What type of skill was that?

They lost a First Kill? Right now, none of the guilds cared about this. They were acting as if they were normal players and paying their respects to these four players’ strength.

This worshipping lasted for ten minutes. Only then did everyone return to reality.

“Lord Grim….. While we were setting a dungeon record, he ran off to kill a wild BOSS? What does that mean?” After staring blankly into space for ten minutes, Blue River finally spoke.

Bound Boat carefully analyzed: “If we continued with our previous way of thinking, then could it be that he was showing off his strength to us? Would the First Kills for future wild BOSSes be in his hands as well?”

Blue River stared blankly.

Guilds mainly used dungeon records to show off their strength. However, measuring a guild’s strength like this was actually a more comprehensive measurement. After all, this was something snatched directly from fighting other guilds. The result simply proved who was the strongest. But now? They hadn’t even begun preparing for it yet and the First Kill had already been taken.

Besides this, the equipment and materials that dropped from wild BOSSes were items that every big guild needed. The existence of wild BOSSes were more important than the existence of any hidden BOSSes. The items dropped were much more valuable. Wild BOSSes only respawned three times a week. Even if the item they wanted dropped every time, in one year, only 156 of them would drop. With millions of players playing the game, how could the value of such a limited supply of items not be seen?

“They have the strength to fight monsters over six levels higher than them. They only have four players too.” Bound Boat reminded Blue River after seeing his blank stare.

After Level 30, leveling areas had a range of 3 or 4 levels. Possessing the strength to beat a BOSS six levels higher than them meant that Lord Grim would always be ahead of them. It meant that he could First Kill any wild BOSS that they didn’t dare fight yet simply because he had no opponents.

Blue River immediately recognized how serious this issue was. Had Lord Grim taken the wild BOSS First Kills hostage as well??

Blue River couldn’t stay silent any longer. He finally decided to have a talk with Lord Grim.

“Brother……” Blue River sent a message.

“Here!” Ye Xiu replied.

“Congratulations!” Blue River felt awkward when he said it.

“Thank you.” Ye Xiu obviously knew what Blue River wanted to talk about. Actually, at this moment, Blue River wasn’t the only one who was messaging him. Many others had already begun feeling him out. Most of their introductions had started the same way.

“Brother, you’re so strong. You can kill the Level 36 Fire Witch at Level 30.” Blue River said.

“It wasn’t easy! It took us three hours.” Ye Xiu said.

“Brother, what are you planning on doing in the future?” Blue River felt that this question came out a little weird, but he couldn’t think of anything better. He had a weird feeling in his heart. He knew what he wanted to say, but he wasn’t able to put it into words.

“What do you mean?” Ye Xiu replied.

“Uh……. are you going to continue killing BOSSes like this in the future too?” Blue River asked.

“If I can kill, why not kill?” Ye Xiu asked in response.

Blue River suddenly realized what the crucial part of the problem was and why he wasn’t able to put his thoughts into words.

It was simply because of this reasoning.

If you can do it, why not do it?!

An extremely ordinary reasoning was a reasoning that couldn’t be argued against.

If Lord Grim possessed the strength to kill the BOSS, then on what basis could others stop him from killing the BOSS? Was it because if he killed it, they wouldn’t be able to? What type of stupid reasoning was that?

Couldn’t this same reasoning be used for dungeon records too?

If Lord Grim possessed the ability to set a dungeon record, then why shouldn’t he? Wasn’t this the reason why the system had set up this sort of competition? If the big guilds needed the records to prove their strength, then Lord Grim wasn’t able to go set it? That type of logic was even more ludicrous.

Blue River knew why he wasn’t able to say anything. It was because Lord Grim had always been doing what was normal to him. If it was any other player, they would also do the same. If they didn’t, then they would be abnormal.

Kidnapping?

Or maybe Lord Grim had other intentions. However, he wasn’t being immoral.

The big guilds wanted him to give up his rights to ensure their own benefits.

Setting records and killing wild BOSSes were all rights that every player had.

If Lord Grim wanted to kill, let him kill. If he didn’t want to, then he didn’t have to. No one should control him. Right now, the big guilds didn’t want him to kill, which was why he put up conditions. After, they said he what he was doing was the same as kidnapping. That type of logic was simply unacceptable.

If you can kill, why not kill?

Simply put, Blue River was killed instantly.

It wasn’t just him. Others had also probed him out the same way. Ye Xiu had replied to them in the same exact way. They all had no response.

Many guilds had already begun discussing this issue with each other.

This wasn’t some overt scheme. They were just sorting out a common issue. Lord Grim’s strength had been displayed for everyone to see. The circumstances were right in front of them. Lord Grim wasn’t doing anything wrong. Everyone could either ignore him or stop him. If they wanted to stop him, then they would either have to give him what he wanted or use force to suppress him. But if they used force, then he could argue: “On what basis can you prevent others from setting a record?

At this moment, Blue River felt as if a heavy burden had been lifted. It was better than before. After a short pause, he quickly revived and sent a message to Lord Grim: “Brother, what do you think the limit for Desolate Land’s record is?”

Blue River felt that Lord Grim wasn’t unjust, which was why he asked this reasonable question. He didn’t believe that Lord Grim wouldn’t answer his question.

“Probably two minutes faster than your record!” Ye Xiu said.

“Two minutes……”

“I don’t suggest that you fight for this record. The key to this record is the final BOSS Toya. Against this BOSS, my unspecialized character had an overwhelming advantage over the other classes. Even if you guys practiced hard to suppress him, you guys will still be a bit slower.”

“Why?”

“Because we can coordinate as well. However, you guys don’t have an unspecialized.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay…… It looks like the only option is to pay you to not act then?” Blue River said.

“That works too.” Ye Xiu said calmly.

“Okay, brother, what do you want this time?” Blue River had already accepted reality.

A list of items was sent over. Blue River wasn’t surprised looking at it. He didn’t hastily negotiate with him either. In any case, he calmly replied: “Let me think about it.”

Blue River went offline again and went to the Heavenly Domain.

Heavenly Domain’s Blue Brook Guild knew that Blue River wouldn’t come over if there was nothing important to report and it usually wasn’t any good news. Seeing that he had appeared again, the four players who had set the record yesterday froze.

“The record has already been broken?” The Spitfire Flying Brushstroke was the first to ask.

“For now, no.” Blue River said.

“Then why’d you come back?”

“To tell you Lord Grim’s conditions.” Blue River said.

“His conditions? What does that mean?”

“The conditions for him to not break our record.” Blue River said.

“Blue Bridge, you’re saying that our record would definitely be broken by Lord Grim?” Flying Brushstroke wasn’t too happy.

“He said that he could beat our record by more than two minutes. Do you think we can do that?” Blue River said.

“You’re going to believe what he says?”

“Yeah, I believe him.” Blue River said.

“F*ck……” Flying Brushstroke cursed and sent a speechless emoticon.

Changing Spring was too lazy to send messages, so he simply told Blue River to wait outside of the usual dungeon they went to. While Blue River was waiting, Flying Brushstroke had already reported the info to Changing Spring. When they met, Blue River could clearly tell that Changing Spring wasn’t happy.

“What’s wrong with you Blue Bridge? Do you actually want others to treat you like a joke?” Changing Spring asked.

“If we don’t ask Lord Grim to not act, then everyone will look like jokes. There wouldn’t be any time to regret it because we wouldn’t be able to get the record back.” Blue River said.

“Ha ha ha ha, Blue Bridge old friend, you’re that scared of this so-called Lord Grim?” Sure enough, Poplar Beach had taken the opportunity to taunt him.

“I just have a feeling that he’s not a bad person, so I’m willing to believe him.” Blue River calmly said.

“He’s not a bad person? If he’s not a bad person, then why would he go kidnap the records from the big guilds?” Poplar Beach laughed coldly.

“The records don’t belong to the big guilds. Where’d you get kidnapping from?” Blue River said.

“Blue Bridge…… you?” Changing Spring and the others all felt a little strange. Blue River’s attitude was different from before. Blue River had previously been angry at Lord Grim. But after half a day, it seemed like Blue River understood Lord Grim.

“Isn’t that a solid reason? If you have the ability to set a record, why wouldn’t you go and set it? We can’t beat the opponent, so this is the only way to take the record.” Blue River said.

“Who says we can’t beat him!” Flying Brushstroke wasn’t happy.

“Blue Bridge old friend…… but tell me the truth, are you colluding with this Lord Grim?” Poplar Beach suddenly interrupted.

Blue River completely ignored him. He didn’t think that Changing Spring would doubt him like that.

Changing Spring had paused for awhile, before saying: “Blue Bridge, it seems like you’ve been working too hard lately. Relax for a bit! This time, hand this dungeon record matter over to us.”

“You’re saying…….”

“Let Poplar Beach substitute for you. The five of us are going to set the record.” Changing Spring said.

Chapter 172 – A Well-Thought Out Long Term Consideration

Changing Spring’s decision startled everyone.

“Substitute” was an extremely sensitive word. Everyone knew what Changing Spring meant on the outside, but on the inside, did he mean that, from now on, Blue River’s spot as one of the Five Great Experts was going to be replaced?

From a skill level point of view, Poplar Beach was superior to Blue River. Changing Spring wasn’t the only person who saw this. However, the reason why the Five Great Experts were great wasn’t simply decided on their skill. Blue River was far more popular than Poplar Beach was.

However, when Changing Spring suddenly announced his decision, no one approached him to inquire for more information. After all, they were only guessing. They didn’t have the willpower to confirm that those were Changing Spring’s actual motives.

On the other hand, Poplar Beach and his group were, without a doubt, extremely happy. Although they didn’t try to assert whether Changing Spring was raising their position, this was at least an important first step. If he replaced Blue River and set a stable record in the tenth server, which Blue River believed wasn’t possible, then it would prove who was superior and who was inferior. His name would definitely become more well-known. In addition, Blue River’s cowardice caused many to feel dissatisfied with him. He might even be able to win over the supporters of Blue River.

Poplar Beach was excited. Just as he was about to go up and declare his position, he heard Blue River calmly say: “Lord Grim and his party, four Level 30s without a Knight nor a Cleric, completed the First Kill for the Fire Witch.”

“Is that why you’re wavering?” Changing Spring said.

“This is more proof of his strength, but more importantly, I suddenly realized that his actions are completely rational. Our selfish actions are the ones that aren’t. From a neutral perspective, this is fair competition.”

“Then us setting the record is fair competition too.”

“Of course…… But because we need that record, this isn’t a good choice.” Blue River said.

“Good or not, we have to try it first! Blue Bridge, do you believe in that Lord Grim’s skill more than ours?” Poplar Beach had trouble finding this chance. He was truly afraid that Blue River would successfully convince Changing Spring, so he hastily squeezed into the conversation.

Blue River paused for a long time, before saying: “Skill…… isn’t something that a person can have just by believing.”

“Correct. Seeing how Lord Grim’s group was able to beat a wild BOSS six levels higher than them, Lord Grim is definitely more skilled than we are.” Changing Spring said, “However, for a dungeon like Desolate Land, there’s a limit to how much skill can be drawn out. I’d even reckon that if a pro-team came to this dungeon, we’d be on par with them. If they can do it, we can do it too. Whatever they’re able do that we can’t has no effect on this dungeon.”

“You’re certainly right! Guild leader, we should go!” Poplar Beach said excitedly.

“Blue Bridge has to help you find a card first, no?” Changing Spring said.

“Oh, Blue Bridge old friend, sorry to trouble you.” Poplar Beach laughed. He already had thoughts about showing off in the tenth server yesterday. He had already found an account in the tenth server to use. However, there was no need for him to use it. He might as well let Blue River prepare it!

“One last thing!” Blue River wasn’t done yet, “Lord Grim’s class is unspecialized. This is a class that we don’t have. It’s an unknown variable.”

“Even if it’s a variable, why do you think that it’s a disadvantageous variable?” Poplar Beach replied back to Blue River this time, “Even more so, unspecialized characters aren’t something that Lord Grim invented, right? They were invented way back then. If they really are more advantageous, why hasn’t every dungeon record been set by them? Speaking of records, in the record teams of every server, why aren’t there any unspecialized characters, hm? If unspecialized characters are so amazing and can set records that others can’t break, then why aren’t they still popular?”

Poplar Beach really had done his homework. He had intentionally researched the dungeon records and record teams from every server.

“Well, it’s true that unspecialized characters are from way back then……..” Blue River’s explanation was clearly weakening. Some of the brothers nearby were unable to listen to him any longer. None of them understood why Blue River was being so stubborn.

“Old Blue, just let it be!” Someone sent a message.

“Let the guild leader and them try it out.”

“We can fight it out first. If not, then there’ll be other options.”

“Okay, it’s settled then!” Changing Spring finally said, “Blue Bridge, can you prepare another Blade Master? We’ll go set it again during the day.”

Blue River had nothing else to say and could only agree in silence.

At three o’clock, the five man team from the Heavenly Domain’s Blue Brook Guild appeared once again in the tenth server. Except this time, the Blade Master was Poplar Beach.

Flying Brushstroke and the others didn’t say anything. They weren’t happy about Blue River’s stubbornness from the day before either and weren’t happy about Poplar Beach either. However, Poplar Beach was indeed more skilled than Blue River. With him, the record they would set would definitely be higher.

“Seniors, are we going?” Poplar Beach was trembling with excitement.

“Let’s go!” Changing Spring didn’t say anything more. They began setting the record as soon as they got to Desolate Land.

It was just a low-leveled dungeon. They were also familiar with it, so there wasn’t a need for a lot of leading. The atmosphere was heavy the entire time as they pushed their way through the dungeon. It was only when they got to the final BOSS, where they needed better coordination, did they begin to warn each other more. Even so, the heavy atmosphere didn’t lighten up. It seemed like only Poplar Beach was full of spirit. The other four seemed somewhat spiritless. Their final time was still a bit worse than the original record, making them feel quite dissatisfied.

“Seniors, if we just casually go at it, we’ll break the record. If we just practice a bit more, we’ll definitely break it!” Poplar Beach wasn’t discouraged and encouraged them.

“You three, come here.” Changing Spring went to one side. He called over Flying Brushstroke, Chilling Nightfall, and Dawn of Ice.

Poplar Beach was startled. It was obvious they were excluding him. What was this guy saying in private! Poplar Beach felt gloomy, but he didn’t show it. He mindlessly attacked nearby monsters. He raised his volume to the maximum level and almost went crazy hearing the angry yells of the monsters, but he wasn’t able to hear what they were saying.

“What’s wrong with you three?” Changing Spring’s tone was serious.

In the end, of the three characters, one head turned left, one turned right, one looked up at the sky. This movement could be done by changing the camera angle.

“I say. You’re not actually doubting Blue River, are you?” Chilling Nightfall said with his head turned left.

“Nonsense, how could I do that.” Changing Spring said.

“It wasn’t like Blue Bridge’s reasoning made no sense.” Dawn of Ice said with his head looking up at the sky.

“I know.” Changing Spring sighed.

“Was it just that you weren’t happy with his attitude?” Flying Brushstroke said with his head turned right.

“Stupid b*stard, f*ck off, do you think I’m you?” Changing Spring said.

“Oh?”

“In any case, this is the only step we can take.” Changing Spring said.

“What do you mean?”

“If we did as Blue Bridge said and chose to reach an agreement with Lord Grim, then we’d be acting too hasty. If the news spread, what would the guild members think? With that punk Poplar Beach, things might become even messier. That’s why we definitely can’t suddenly come to an agreement with Lord Grim.” Changing Spring said.

“But why’d you replace Blue Bridge? Even if this was something that he didn’t want to do, I believe that he would still go all out. That Poplar Beach looks so pleased with himself. I admit that he’s a bit more skilled than Blue Bridge, but it’s only by a bit.” Flying Brushstroke was someone who wasn’t afraid to say what his opinions were. Whether he was happy or not, he wouldn’t hide it.

“A bit better is just one of the reasons. More importantly, we have to consider whether Lord Grim really can break our record. With Poplar Beach, we’ve shut his group up. Later, if we ever have to make a negotiation with Lord Grim again, they won’t be as arrogant.” Changing Spring said.

Flying Brushstroke heard this and stared blankly. Chilling Nightfall followed: “Then what if Lord Grim isn’t able to break our record?”

“Then that means Blue Bridge was wrong. What else could that mean?” Changing Spring plainly said.

“You…….” Dawn of Ice gasped.

“A well-thought-out long-term strategy!” Flying Brushstroke said.

“That’s why I’m the guild leader and not you.” Changing Spring wasn’t polite, “Okay then, everyone cheer up. F*ck, if Blue Bridge was here, he’d definitely be more spirited than you three. If we don’t set the record today, then I’ll have you guys squat here in the tenth server and never return.”

“Ha ha ha ha, we just need more practice for that record. If we don’t set it this afternoon, we’ll definitely be able to set it tonight!”

The four laughed and then headed towards the entrance.

“We’re going!” They called out to Poplar Beach. Poplar Beach was a bit puzzled. He could clearly feel that after their private conversation, their tones seemed to have changed. What happened?

On their second run, the previous heavy atmosphere suddenly went away. Their communication cleared up as well. Their way through the dungeon went smoothly, yet there were still problems when they got to Toya. Even though they beat the record, they had only improved it by five seconds, far from what they wanted.

“D*mn, this isn’t good. We were only able to beat it by a bit. We haven’t gotten the results we want and we’re about to level up with the experience reward…….” Flying Brushstroke cursed. Besides getting a Purple equipment as a reward, they would also get a lot of experience.

“What are you afraid of! There are plenty of characters for you to use. Continue setting!”

On their third run, they made a major mistake on a mob of monsters. However, none of them cared. Right now, they wanted to improve the record and the only place they would improve on was their coordination against the final BOSS Toya.

They had finished their three runs, but they hadn’t gotten the time they wanted. These runs could be considered as practice.

“We’ll go again at midnight. Right now, come with me to the other nine servers and practice! You all have your account cards, right?!” Changing Spring said.

Chapter 173 – He’s No Good For Dungeoning

Changing Spring was clearly taking this seriously. Blue Brook Guild had power in every one of Glory’s ten servers. Changing Spring had contacted the guild leaders of each server a while ago and sent the Level 30 accounts to the five players. At this moment, they were going to begin in the ninth server. With three chances in every server, they began their slow practice.

Every run would be within thirty minutes, which meant they could clear the dungeon twice per hour. From three in the afternoon to twelve at night, Blue Brook Guild’s strongest team ran Desolate Land eighteen times, making them feel like vomiting just at the mention of the two words, Desolate Land.

However, the results made them happy. The coordination between the five of them grew better and better and their ability to suppress Toya also increased as well. No one in any of the servers had ever placed so much value into researching Desolate Land. Starting from the seventh server, the five man team began to break records. In the sixth and fifth servers, they put the final record under Blue Brook Guild’s name. Unfortunately, these were old servers, so not many paid attention to these low-leveled dungeon records.

“Rest for half an hour. At 12:30, we’ll go back to the tenth server and set the record!” Changing Spring said to the four other team members. At 12 o’clock midnight, the dungeon entries in every server refreshed. They had been running the dungeon so much that their vision had become somewhat blurry. Resting was a necessity. They had to at least get some food to eat! While they were running Desolate Land, they didn’t have any time to eat.

After resting for half an hour, the five characters showed up at the tenth server’s Desolate Land.

Coincidentally, when these five players went online, they saw a character with the name “Lord Grim” outside of the dungeon entrance with his team.

The record had already been broken?

That was the first thought that flashed by in Changing Spring’s mind. He immediately opened up dungeon leaderboards and checked. The record they had set in the afternoon was still at the top!

He looked up and saw that Poplar Beach was walking towards Lord Grim.

“You’re Lord Grim?” Poplar Beach’s tone was always extremely arrogant, always making others feel unhappy. When Ye Xiu heard this voice, he turned Lord Grim around and saw the sign Blue Brook Guild next to the name Cloud Listening Blade.

“Who are you?” Ye Xiu asked.

“I’m called Poplar Beach.” Poplar Beach said.

A loud laugh suddenly interrupted: “Not only is this guy illiterate, he can’t count either! His name clearly has three words, but doesn’t Poplar Beach only have two? Is he stupid?”

Poplar Beach turned furious. Without any warning, he used Sword Draw. How could Steamed Bun Invasion not be able to dodge this? He jumped backwards with a “Woah” and without any warning, countered with a Brick.

Poplar Beach deliberately showed off his skill by immediately raised his sword up and used Guard. However, Steamed Bun Invasion had quickly rushed forward after using Brick and initiated with Sand Toss.

Poplar Beach hadn’t expected that Steamed Bun Invasion would be so quick. He hastily leaped backwards and rolled, however, dodging this Sand Toss would be difficult. But as a player who dared to contend to be one of Blue Brook Guild’s Five Great Experts, Poplar Beach indeed had some skill. Although it was close, Poplar Beach was able to dodge in time. He immediately raised his hands and used Triple Slash.

Triple Slash was an upward, downward, and horizontal slash performed in quick succession and was executed much faster than the speed at which normal attacks could be chained.

Poplar Beach’s dodge and counter was completed in a single breath, putting Steamed Bun Invasion as the one in the difficult situation this time. Steamed Bun Invasion hastily leaped back twice and avoided the first two slashes, but it didn’t look like there would be enough time to dodge the third slash. Poplar Beach was laughing in his heart, when he realized that his third slash had hit nothing but air. Steamed Bun Invasion had crouched to dodge the attack.

Poplar Beach wasn’t able to pull back in time. Steamed Bun Invasion got up and grabbed Poplar Beach’s throat with a Strangle.

Level 30 characters only had so many skills. Steamed Bun Invasion had become extremely familiar with his class. With one hand holding onto Poplar Beach’s throat, his other hand immediately used Brick again, hitting the back of Poplar Beach’s head with a whirl of his arm. Taking advantage of Poplar Beach’s Dizzy condition, Steamed Bun Invasion swiftly circled around to behind his opponent and Uppercutted, launching his opponent into the air. Steamed Bun Invasion quickly followed up with a Knee Attack.

“F*ck off!!” Steamed Bun Invasion shouted and kneed his opponent’s back. If this was just a normal Knee Attack to the back, then Poplar would have only been pushed back. However, because Poplar Beach was in the air, Poplar Beach would be sent flying away.

However, Steamed Bun Invasion’s prediction was wrong. After all, Poplar Beach was an expert. He took advantage of the opportunity to Quick Recover. His character rolled forward and then immediately turned around to counter with a Sword Draw.

By the time the sword aura had arrived, because it was so sudden, Steamed Bun Invasion wasn’t able to dodge in time. In the end, he heard a crash. Lord Grim’s Thousand Chance Umbrella had opened up in front of him. The sword aura hit the umbrella without a metallic ring and dissipated.

After blocking this attack, the Thousand Chance Umbrella immediately closed. Poplar Beach clearly wasn’t happy with how Steamed Bun Invasion had kicked him. Right as he was about to rush forward again, Changing Spring’s character blocked him off. On the other side, Steamed Bun Invasion wasn’t happy either with how he had nearly been hit by the Sword Draw. He also wanted to go up, until when he heard Ye Xiu shout: “Steamed Bun.”

“Don’t be so hasty!” Changing Spring warned in a heavy tone to Poplar Beach.

“The previous Sand Toss you used wasn’t good. Why were you so hasty in using Sand Toss?” On this side, the atmosphere was much lighter. Ye Xiu was lecturing Steamed Bun Invasion.

“I wanted to take advantage of the fact that his Guard was on cooldown!” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“Guard only works against physical attacks! Sand Toss is magic damage. You even know the cooldown for Guard, how do you not know this?” Ye Xiu didn’t know whether to laugh or cry.

“Oh, so it’s like that?” Steamed Bun Invasion felt unsure. He looked around left and right. They didn’t have any Blade Masters on their side, so he looked towards the other side: “Hey, can you tell me what the description for Guard is?”

Poplar Beach and Changing Spring stared blankly. They were in such a tense situation right now. What type of question was this?”

In the end, they heard Steamed Bun Invasion say: “Oh shoot. I forgot. He’s illiterate. He probably can’t read the words.”

“I’m going to kill him!!” Poplar Beach jumped out ready to fight. However, this time Ye Xiu moved his Lord Grim forward, blocking him as he said: “Don’t be hasty, don’t be hasty. I don’t think you’re illiterate, but who are you guys?”

“Changing Spring, Blue Brook Guild’s guild leader.” Changing Spring’s character went forward to speak.

“Oh……”

“Steamed Bun!” Ye Xiu immediately warned Steamed Bun Invasion. He knew that Steamed Bun was definitely about to say that this person was also illiterate.

“Blue Brook Guild’s guild leader.” Ye Xiu repeated. He had already figured out what was going on and laughed: “Are you here to set the record?”

“Correct.” Changing Spring said.

“It must have been difficult for senior to have come from so far away.” Ye Xiu said.

“It’s all because of you!” Changing Spring said.

“Ha ha, I’m very competitive, so you guys are going to have to try very hard.” Ye Xiu laughed.

“It sounds like you’re very confident.” Changing Spring said.

“How so?”

“It was you who told Blue River that we wouldn’t be able to compete against you, right?” Changing Spring asked.

“I think so.”

“You punk, you’re too arrogant! Do you dare duel me?” Poplar Beach shouted. Changing Spring calmly stood to the side and didn’t stop him.

“Blue River didn’t come?” Ye Xiu suddenly asked this random question.

“No.” Changing Spring said.

“Then you guys should call Blue River over.” Ye Xiu said, “If we’re talking about PK, then this person is probably a bit better than Blue River. But for dungeoning, Blue River is more steady and would be better in terms of teamwork.”

Everyone heard this and stared blankly. They didn’t know how well Lord Grim understood Blue River, but they were certain that this was his first time seeing Poplar Beach. With just that short exchange, he could already see how skilled Poplar Beach was?

“What are you saying!! Fight me!!” Poplar Beach shouted.

“See, he knows this too.” Ye Xiu said to Changing Spring, “Let him go wild in the Arena and let Blue River set the records.”

How could Poplar Beach take this? He drew his sword and rushed forward. Steamed Bun Invasion was about to welcome him but this time, Changing Spring didn’t just stand there. He roared, “Stop right there!”

Poplar Beach heard this and immediately halted. After staring blankly, Steamed Bun Invasion stopped as well, seeing that his opponent wasn’t moving. He then heard Ye Xiu follow up: “Correct, don’t be hasty. If you really want to fight me, then you’d at least have to use your main account.”

Changing Spring, Flying Brushstroke, Chilling Nightfall……. stared foolishly.

To them, Poplar Beach was already a very arrogant guy. But Lord Grim was even more arrogant! He actually dared to fight against Poplar Beach’s main account with his Level 30 character? That was a 40 level difference!

Both being equally arrogant, Poplar Beach was someone Blue River could never get along with. , However, it seemed like this Lord Grim was someone who Blue River revered.

They were still puzzled over this, when they heard Poplar Beach reply back with a laugh: “Smart! If you fight my main account with your level 30 account, then it won’t matter if you lose. Do you really think I’d fall for such a stupid trick? I don’t need my main account. I’ll fight you with this Level 30 account.”

“Don’t worry! I won’t be bullying you with this low-leveled account. I’ll borrow a random Level 70 account to fight with you.” Ye Xiu said.

A low-level account bullying a high-level account? Everyone began to sweat. Lord Grim had made “low-leveled” sound like an advantage though.

“Good, where to?” Poplar Beach asked.

“Up to you. We’re going to go dungeoning first. Let’s meet again later.” Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 174 – Challenge Ignored

Lord Grim’s group turned around and entered the dungeon as if nothing had happened. Poplar Beach was stomping his feet in fury. It was too late to prevent them from going. It only took them a few steps to enter the dungeon.

Changing Spring was still calm. After watching Lord Grim’s team enter, the only thing he could do was calmly call out: “We’ll begin as well.”

“Okay.” Three of them answered back. Poplar Beach, on the other hand, clearly hadn’t recovered yet.

“Poplar, we’re going to set the record now. Focus. Don’t forget why we’re here.” Changing Spring reminded Poplar Beach.

Soon after, the five of them entered the dungeon and pushed through as they had practiced. However, Poplar Beach was still angry. When they began clearing the small mobs, the team’s tempo was a complete mess. This guy clearly wasn’t in the right mindset.

Changing Spring, who had reminded him before they had entered, didn’t say a word. On the contrary, Flying Brushstroke couldn’t watch anymore and opened his mouth to remind Poplar Beach. But he had only shouted the name, when Changing Spring interrupted him.

“Forget about it.” Changing Spring said, “Let him vent his anger or he’ll continue playing like this.”

Flying Brushstroke stared blankly for a bit. After recalling what Poplar Beach’s personality was like, he let the matter go. The other two didn’t say anything either. Poplar Beach was completely out of sync with the team. Their advance through the dungeon was not going they way they wanted it to go.

“That Lord Grim, did he intentionally provoke Poplar to affect our performance?” Flying Brushstroke said.

“I don’t think so.” Chilling Nightfall said, “Poplar being angry is just temporary. The competition for the record is different than the competition in the Arena. If we’re not able to do it today, then we can try it again tomorrow. We just have to find new accounts and do it. Do you really think he’ll provoke us every time like this?”

“Then what was the point of him spouting so much nonsense. Does he really think that Blue Bridge is better than Poplar Beach?” Flying Brushstroke said.

“What do you guys think?” Chilling Nightfall asked the other three.

Poplar Beach was on the field with them, so it wasn’t easy to privately discuss this issue. In order to do so, they whispered to each other whenever they crossed each other’s path when fighting the monsters.

“I think……. Blue Bridge’s dungeoning is extremely consistent. However, if you said that Poplar Beach was worse than Blue Bridge, that wouldn’t necessarily be true. We’ve worked with him for a day and we all saw how he performed! Poplar Beach coordinates well us too. It’s hard to say whether or not Blue Bridge is better, no?” Dawn of Ice, who hadn’t spoken up in a long time, commented.

“But at least in this type of situation, I don’t think Blue Bridge would be affected so emotionally like Poplar Beach is now.” Flying Brushstroke said.

“Could it be……” Chilling Nightfall stared blankly. He had blurted out what he was thinking, but had accidentally messed up and staggered behind everyone on Poplar Beach’s side. He quickly swallowed his words.

“What were you going to say?” The other four once again crossed each other’s path. Flying Brushstroke immediately asked.

“Could it be that Lord Grim had provoked Poplar Beach in order for us to see what Poplar Beach’s weakness was?” Chilling Nightfall said.

“You guys are probably thinking too much!” Changing Spring found the opportunity to interject.

“How’d it get so complicated? From how I see it, Poplar Beach provoked them first and then the other side simply countered back.” Changing Spring said.

“Uh…….” The three stared blankly. That was a very rational explanation.

“Don’t think about it so much and just concentrate on the dungeon.” Changing Spring said.

“Okay…….” The three replied.

Their run this time didn’t turn out well. They had reached 30 minutes. The gap between what they wanted and what they got was very big.

After they exited the dungeon, Changing Spring didn’t say anything. Poplar Beach wasn’t an idiot. Changing Spring believed that Poplar Beach knew why their time wasn’t good.

“Second time.” Changing Spring announced dully. Poplar Beach’s emotional issue had been overlooked this time. No one commented on it. This time, Poplar Beach had returned to his normal condition.

However, they still made mistakes in their run. The record limit implied that their performance was flawless. A single mistake meant that the record would no longer be the limit. In a thirty minute dungeon, requiring that every person performed perfectly wasn’t easy.

“Third time! Everyone, be more careful.” Even though they made a mistake last run, with all of their practice, they were able to suppress Toya with their teamwork. Their time was close to the tenth server’s previous record. They all believed that if they didn’t make any mistakes, then they would definitely reach the limit.

“We can do it!” Everyone encouraged each other as they entered Desolate Land for the third time.

They had advanced flawlessly this time. They didn’t make a single mistake all the way up to the final BOSS Toya. This part was the most difficult part of Desolate Land and it was the reason why the team had run Desolate Land eighteen times. Against Toya, the five coordinated perfectly. In their second run, they hadn’t made any mistakes here as well.

They had practiced this part all too well.

24:41:46!!

When the record came out, the five of them let out a long sigh of relief. This was the record limit they had wanted. It was the highest record they could make with their current ability. If they wanted to improve it, then they would need better equipment.

Even though Blue River hadn’t participated in the dungeon team this time, he had done his work properly. When he saw the record come out, Blue Brook Guild immediately sent members to begin bringing up a discussion in the world channel. They were naturally trying to repair the recent damage to their image. They had already done this yesterday, so this time, they were trying to nail it in and follow up their victory with another.

“Lord Grim! The record will be here. We’ll be waiting for you to break it.”

Amidst the countless messages that popped up, this challenge came out. It was sent by Poplar Beach. Poplar Beach spammed the message over and over again, but there was no reply from Lord Grim. In the end, when they looked over the recent messages in the world chat, they discovered that it wasn’t that Lord Grim hadn’t replied, it was just that it was similar to Changing Spring’s “GFY” (Go f*ck yourself) and was too short, so they had missed it.

Lord Grim’s reply was a short three words long: When I’m free.

Seeing this reply, Poplar Beach spat out blood in anger. He continued to spam the message, challenging him to break the record, challenging him to duel him.

This time, Poplar Beach was on the lookout. He paid careful attention to the messages. Except…… Lord Grim’s reply hadn’t changed. It was still the three words: When I’m free.

Poplar Beach really wanted to smash his head into the screen to enter the game world and strangle Lord Grim. But the reality was that it wasn’t possible, so he could only stare blankly at the screen. Should I go ask “When are you free?” What if Lord Grim doesn’t give me face? Poplar Beach worried.

“This guy is really persistent. He’s been messaging for almost an hour already.” In the Internet Cafe, Tang Rou said this to Ye Xiu when she passed by to refill her teacup with water. They had just finished running Desolate Land three times. They had used an hour more than Blue Brook Guild’s team did. This was because Ye Xiu was teaching them a new strategy.

The new strategy wasn’t as efficient as the record for Boneyard, but was actually more difficult to carry out. Tang Rou felt that she wasn’t good enough! She understood the preciseness of this new strategy, but because they weren’t able to do enough damage, they weren’t able to bring out the expected results.

Tang Rou had a faint feeling that if they had a fifth player with them, then with the fifth player’s firepower, they would be able to bring out the desired results.

As a result, after finishing the dungeon runs, Tang Rou brought up Poplar Beach’s spamming again.

“Yeah, it must be tough for the guy.” Ye Xiu said.

“What are you doing?” Tang Rou looked toward Ye Xiu’s screen and saw that he was checking out shops in the Congee City market streets.

“You’re shopping again? What do you plan on buying?” Tang Rou asked.

“Steamed Bun and your sets are pretty much completed, but Cleansing Mist is still missing a few, so I’m helping her look.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh? Do you have enough money? I still have some.” Tang Rou said.

“You should save that money for potions!” Ye Xiu laughed.

“That…….”

“Hm?”

“Desolate Land record. We should go back and take the record back!” Tang Rou said. At this moment, the first three places in the Desolate Land records didn’t have their name on it. And because of Poplar Beach’s constant yelling, even if Tang Rou didn’t say anything out loud, she was already on the verge of exploding out in her heart.

“Of course.” Ye Xiu said.

“When?” Tang Rou asked.

“When we get our fifth team member.” Ye Xiu said.

“Fifth member? Who is it going to be this time?” Tang Rou asked.

“Someone you’ve talked with before.” Ye Xiu said.

“Who?” Tang Rou was puzzled.

“Ashen Moon, do you remember him?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Oh? That person….. I remember him. He was the worst of the bunch, but he was still better than me.” Tang Rou said. Everyone in Team Tiny Herb had beaten her without any suspense. They were after all pros.

“His name is Qiao Yifan. If we’re talking about his ability to duel, then he isn’t very outstanding. However, his true strength lies in his ability to work in a team.” Ye Xiu said.

“When is he coming?” Tang Rou asked.

“Soon. If things go well, then he might even be here tonight.” Ye Xiu looked at his friends list. The Ghostblade One Inch Ash was online 24/7 these days. His level had shot up like an arrow and he was now Level 29.

Chapter 175 – Three Chances Waiting For You

Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash soared from Level 23 to Level 30 in a mere several days. This sort of leveling speed was even quicker than the big guild’s 24 hour online routine.

The big guild’s characters were always at the front of the tenth server. You had to rely on yourself to resolve your own problems. Even though Ye Xiu and his group’s characters were a bit behind, their situation was about the same. They were slower because they weren’t able to play as much.

The power leveling done by Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash didn’t lose to the amount of play time the big guild’s leading characters players had. For his character to level up so quickly, it was because his One Inch Ash started later. The situation was similar to those in the old servers.

A character in any old server would definitely level faster than one in the new server. The reason was simple: there were people to carry them.

Even though the tenth server didn’t have as many high-leveled characters as the old servers, for late starters like One Inch Ash, there would definitely be high-leveled characters to help him. The reason he was able to fully utilize the quickest substitution leveling was because of this.

Ye Xiu naturally knew about this. When he saw how quick One Inch Ash leveled, he had figured out that the character was being power leveled.

As a result, Ye Xiu conducted a special training in Desolate Land today. That’s why after they finished their practice in Desolate Land, he urged everyone repeatedly to not level today.

If they continued leveling, they would reach Level 31. Once they went past the level limit for the dungeon, the record they would set wouldn’t be accepted by the system.

“I hope he’ll come early!” Tang Rou lamented, while carrying her teacup back to her seat.

In game, Poplar Beach spammed messages in the world channel for another half an hour, while Ye Xiu was just doing his own thing. Ye Xiu would sometimes glance at the messages. The ones he didn’t see, well, he didn’t see. He clearly didn’t care about them.

The night passed. They went to sleep when the sun rose.

Club Tiny Herb.

Pro-players obviously couldn’t have their days turn into nights like that, especially for someone like Qiao Yifan, who was on the verge of being kicked out. He didn’t dare make any mistakes. He would follow the Club’s scheduled break and practice time. During daytime practice, he didn’t dare get distracted, but once his free time came during the night, he immediately began researching Ghostblades. He would look at guides, watch recordings, and even bought two Ghostblades to experiment with personally.

However, the character he was looking forward to playing the most was One Inch Ash, because with this character, he could be instructed personally by God Ye Qiu. When he thought of this, Qiao Yifan felt indescribably happy. He hadn’t been sleeping much recently, but he didn’t feel tired. Everyday he would sleep late and wake up early, yet he was still in glowing spirits. Even during the day, when he practiced his Assassin, he would feel that his performance had improved a bit, though he didn’t know whether or not that was because of his mental state.

And today was the scheduled day when he would get his account back. In other words, this was the day, when his One Inch Ash hit Level 30. He could finally go to the tenth server and look for God Ye Qiu for his coaching. In the afternoon, Qiao Yifan got a little distracted and contacted the substitution leveler early. After confirming that there weren’t any problems, he felt even more ecstatic.

“What happened, Yifan? You seem really happy.” During afternoon practice, his good friend Gao Yingjie saw Qiao Yifan’s happiness and couldn’t help but ask.

“He he, am I really?” Qiao Yifan foolishly grinned.

“Are you okay?” Gao Yingjie extended his hand to touch Qiao Yifan’s forehead.

“Nothing’s wrong! I’m completely fine. Hurry, practice is starting.” Qiao Yifan dodged Gao Yingjie’s extended right hand. He retracted his foolish grin and sat down in front of his computer. But after a short while, the corners of his mouth began to rise up slightly again. This hadn’t escaped from Gao Yingjie’s eyes.

Gao Yingjie obviously knew that his good friend was hanging on a balance and that he was under a lot of pressure. Even though he was the Club’s new star, reputed as the successor to God Jiexi, he didn’t have much authority. There was really no way for him to help Qiao Yifan. Seeing how Qiao Yifan’s mood had been so unusually good, he was worried that something might have happened.

When afternoon practice ended, Qiao Yifan hastily ran back to his room. Gao Yingjie wasn’t able to find an opportunity to talk to him. As an important new member in the Club, he would often have extra practice under God Jiexi’s instructions. Just as he was planning on chasing down Qiao Yifan, team captain Wang Jiexi had called for him.

By the time extra practice had ended, it was already dinner time. Gao Yingjie rushed to the Club’s dining hall, but didn’t see Qiao Yifan. When he asked his other friends in the team, no one had noticed someone as invisible as Qiao Yifan. Surprisingly, no one had an answer to whether or not he had come to the dining hall.

Gao Yingjie ran to Qiao Yifan’s room. Similarly, Qiao Yifan wasn’t there either.

Gao Yingjie felt that something was amiss and didn’t know why his friend was acting like so. He didn’t want to report it to the team captain, so he hurriedly called Qiao Yifan’s cellphone number. Qiao Yifan picked up, and said that he had nothing to do after eating dinner, so he had gone outside to take a stroll…….

“I’m coming back!” Qiao Yifan said to Gao Yingjie. He had gone out to retrieve his account card. Even though he could have received it by mail the next day, Qiao Yifan couldn’t wait any longer.

However, he couldn’t let anyone in the Club know about this, which was why he had to quietly slip away. Though for someone as invisible as him, it wasn’t that hard. Who would have thought that his good friend had felt something was amiss? Qiao Yifan felt somewhat moved, but he wasn’t planning on telling Gao Yingjie the situation. This was his own choice. It had nothing to do with anyone else. Even though Gao Yingjie cared about him, he knew that Gao Yingjie wasn’t able to help him. If he kept on dragging Gao Yingjie along, he might even cause trouble for his friend’s future.

By the time Qiao Yifan had returned from picking up his account card, it was already nine at night. Similar to how no one had noticed him leaving, no one had noticed him coming back. Just as he was about to open the door to his room, a voice suddenly called out to him. He turned around and saw Gao Yingjie walking over.

“Yingjie ah, did you just finish your extra practice?” Qiao Yifan greeted him.

“Yeah.” Gao Yingjie replied. He then asked casually: “Where’d you go?”

“I just walked around randomly.” Qiao Yifan said.

“Did……. something happen?” Gao Yingjie said.

“Me? How could something have happened to me!” Qiao Yifan laughed, “It’s getting late. You should go to sleep. I’ll be going back!” Qiao Yifan said as he opened the door.

“Oh…..” Gao Yingjie answered back in this way. In the end, he was still an introvert who wasn’t too good at conversations. He could see that Qiao Yifan had something on his mind, but he didn’t know how to ask about it, so he had been blocked out like this.

Gao Yinjie stared blankly for a good while. In the end, he could only let out a sigh and return to his room.

Qiao Yifan went into his room and turned on his computer. He immediately opened up Glory and logged into his One Inch Ash account. When he came online, he saw Lord Grim online and felt a wave of excitement wash over him. He cautiously sent a message: “Senior, I’m already Level 30.”

“Oh, pretty fast!” The reply was quick.

“Let’s dungeon together at night! Is going past midnight okay?” Ye Xiu followed up and asked him.

“No problem, no problem!” Qiao Yifan responded excitedly.

“Good, do you still remember how to run Desolate Land?” Ye Xiu asked.

“I remember!” Qiao Yifan said.

“Good, but don’t lie! Our goal is to set this server’s record.” Ye Xiu said.

“Really? Then I should go and review it again!” If he was any other pro-player, then he would have put Desolate Land as completely beneath him. But Qiao Yifan didn’t dare be negligent. This was his habit of being extremely cautious at work.

“Okay, take a look then. We only have three chances.” Ye Xiu said.

“Why?”

“Because besides you, after three more runs, our team will probably hit Level 31.” Ye Xiu said.

Qiao Yifan checked the tenth server dungeon leaderboards. The 24:41:46 Desolate Land record made even him, a pro-player, startled.

“The record is really high!” Qiao Yifan said to Ye Xiu in astonishment.

“It is. You could even said that it’s the current limit.” Ye Xiu said.

“Unless they have better equipment. But for a new server, their current equipment is pretty much at the limit as well.” Ye Xiu replied.

“‘Then what are going to do?” Qiao Yifan asked.

“Three chances. As long as you can assimilate into the team, breaking the record won’t be a problem.” Ye Xiu said.

“Three times…….” Qiao Yifan didn’t have confidence. Confidence in himself was his biggest weakness.

“Relax! It won’t be a problem if it’s you. I believe that you can do it, which is why I specifically left three chances waiting for you.” Ye Xiu said.

“Waiting for me?” Qiao Yifan was startled.

“Right, without your Phantom Demon, breaking this record would be really difficult.” Ye Xiu said.

“But I’m still not very familiar with Phantom Demons yet.” Qiao Yifan panicked.

“Three chances should be enough for you to get familiar enough at least in this dungeon. Don’t forget, you’re a pro-player too!” Ye Xiu said.

You’re a pro-player too.

These simple words should have just been simple words. However, Qiao Yifan had never heard these words before. He was used to being invisible. He was used to always being a sub and never going up on stage. He was used to always watching enviously in the shadows as Gao Yingjie was personally instructed by the team captain.

Being in the champion team only gave him more pressure. While his other teammates were proud of themselves, he was always worried that he wasn’t good enough to be on the team.

You’re a pro-player too.

This type of assurance, this type of acknowledgement, didn’t come easy for Qiao Yifan. And having this coming out of God Ye Qiu’s mouth made these words carry even more weight.

Seeing these words, Qiao Yifan’s pent up grievances gushed out. Tears began streaming out from his eyes. He replied, determined: “I am! Three times is more than enough!”

Chapter 176 – Problems in the Details

There were still two hours until midnight. Qiao Yifan stopped being so sentimental. He told God that he’d be right back and then temporarily logged out of One Inch Ash. He switched accounts in order to run Desolate Land in another server and do a quick review of the dungeon.

As a pro-player, he obviously knew how to run this dungeon. However, setting a record meant that he had to understand both the details and the general picture. Qiao Yifan began to study.

The types and patterns of the monsters.

What route to choose when advancing through the dungeon?

The characteristics and patterns of every BOSS.

Qiao Yifan used his main account to run Desolate Land three times. There wasn’t anything wrong with using this account. No matter how borderline he was in the team, having been able to get on the team was already recognition of his strength. Although he was bit worse than his teammates, he was still much better than new players with only strong mechanics like Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion.

After familiarizing himself in those three runs, it was almost midnight. Qiao Yifan switched accounts and returned to the tenth server. He then sent Ye Xiu a message and both sides agreed on where they would meet up outside Desolate Land.

On his way there, Qiao Yifan saw that there was someone in the world channel repeatedly calling out Lord Grim for a challenge. One of his challenges was the Desolate Land record and the other was a duel with Lord Grim.

“Who is this guy?” Qiao Yifan muttered to himself. The dungeon record was another matter. After all, that could only be done with a team. And moreover, the record limit for low-leveled dungeons could be done by normal players as well.

But a duel…… this was a direct clash between the two sides’ skill levels. To actually challenge God Ye Qiu so arrogantly, such a person made Qiao Yifan completely speechless.

Out of everyone he knew, even their team captain Wang Jiexi didn’t dare have this type of attitude in front of God Ye Qiu. The only person he knew who might issue such an open challenge would probably be Tyranny’s Han Wenqing! This God had begun opposing God Ye Qiu ever since he joined the Alliance. After ending Excellent Era’s consecutive Championship titles, the two became true rivals.

In terms of mechanics, Han Wenqing was on par with other Gods. But this guy was extremely aggressive. In addition, his personality was very direct and stubborn. If he ever saw any mistakes, he would immediately start shouting.

Rumors say that after one of the matches, where Tyranny had performed terribly, Han Wenqing furiously reprimanded the team. He repeatedly watched the recordings of that day’s match. Every time he saw a mistake he would immediately start cursing madly. At that time, Tyranny’s boss had come to visit. Midway through, his cellphone suddenly rang and the angry cursing stopped. Han Wenqing turned his head and glared coldly at the boss. He said two words: “Get out.”

The boss gave him face and immediately ran out to pick up his phone. Tyranny’s entire team was scared speechless. Even their boss had been roared away to one side. How could they dare talk back?

Han Wenqing’s behavior was like this as well. In terms of experience and skill, only he could compare with Ye Qiu. But now, in game, some random guy was shouting at God Ye Qiu for a challenge. Qiao Yifan truly didn’t know whether to laugh or to cry.

Outside of Desolate Land, Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash finally met with God’s Lord Grim. He also saw Tang Rou’s Soft Mist, someone who couldn’t be considered a stranger to him anymore. He had also met Steamed Bun Invasion before, in the very beginning. Besides them, there was the Launcher, Cleansing Mist. Seeing this character, the first thing anyone, who knew about the identity of the person playing Lord Grim , would immediately think of Su Mucheng. She was someone who always stood by Ye Qiu, just like that Launcher who always stood behind One Autumn Leaf. But now that Ye Qiu had retired, was this Launcher still Su Mucheng?

Qiao Yifan didn’t ask. Even though he was a member of a Champion team, he clearly knew his current position in it. In the eyes of other teams, his existence was even weaker. His other teammates had fought against other teams’ pro-players and had become friends. But Qiao Yifan didn’t have any opponents, so he didn’t have that type of friend……

“So you’re here.” Seeing that One Inch Ash had arrived, Ye Xiu greeted him. “We’ll begin at 12 o’clock sharp.”

“Okay.” Qiao Yifan replied. He opened up the dungeon record leaderboards to verify the current record. But when he looked at it this time, he immediately felt that one of the team members on the leaderboards was somewhat familiar. Wasn’t this the guy who had challenged God?

“No wonder he’s so arrogant. That record really is quite good. It looks like he’s an expert too. But it looks like he doesn’t know who his opponent is!” Qiao Yifan thought to himself.

“Any problems with your equipment?” Ye Xiu asked.

“No problem.” Qiao Yifan replied. When he bought the substitution leveling services, he had also ordered a set of equipment. The current One Inch Ash had a full Level 30 Ghostblade set and was also carrying a Level 30 Purple Tachi, Demon Slaying Blade. His accessories were quite good too.

“We won’t be going for speed on our first run. We have a new player, so this run will be used to let him learn our strategy.” Ye Xiu said.

“One time is enough?” Steamed Bun Invasion was probably thinking of Full Moon Guild’s guild leader. In the beginning, Ye Xiu had said the same thing, but that guild leader still wasn’t very outstanding even after three runs.

“It’ll be enough.” Ye Xiu laughed.

On the side, even though Qiao Yifan hadn’t replied, he could feel his heart boiling. Seeing that there was still some time before midnight, he ran to splash cold water on his face. He had to maintain his composure and focus. He couldn’t let down God.

“They’re refreshed, let’s go!”

At midnight, the dungeon entries refreshed soYe Xiu led his team into Desolate Land.

At this moment, Blue River, who was also beginning to run the dungeons, began to look anxiously at the messages in the world channel.

Poplar Beach’s spamming often made him feel somewhat angry. He was only being so arrogant because he had participated in setting a faster record. This endless enthusiasm didn’t seem like it was to prove their name, but just to create an unreasonable scene. This wasn’t the first time Blue River had seen people do this, but the problem this time was that that character was from Blue Brook Guild. Everyone who saw these messages knew that. The Desolate Land records hanging on the leaderboards had their name on it!

Not only did he have guild’s name behind him, he was also one of the experts on the leaderboards. Blue River felt that shouting on the world channel constantly like this was so shameful.

It wasn’t as if Blue River hadn’t warned him. It was just that once Poplar Beach received it, he would laugh at him and mock him.

Blue River was feeling conflicted. He obviously hoped that their guild’s record would be able to remain up there, but when he thought of how happy Poplar Beach was, he couldn’t help but want someone to just step all over the record.

Of course, the only who could step all over the record was Lord Grim.

Blue River was feeling somewhat uneasy. He had been paying attention to Lord Grim’s level. It looked like he had spent much longer at Level 30 than one normally would . At this moment, Blue River and the others in the front were already level 33. The higher the level, the more experience was needed. This was why the distance between them was getting smaller. With how fast Lord Grim had been leveling, he should have only been 1.5 levels behind them. But right now, he had stopped at Level 30. The possible meanings this implicated was why Blue River felt uneasy.

Especially now. Blue River had received a message from guild members at Desolate Land saying that they had seen Lord Grim’s group with a new member called One Inch Ash, a Ghostblade without any guild.

One Inch Ash? Who was this? Blue River looked at their guild’s name of lists. Last time, there was that Blade Master Flowing Tree who had only gone online for a brief moment. He couldn’t help but feel alarmed.

Meanwhile, in Desolate Land’s dungeon, the newly-joined Qiao Yifan was employing the strategy that Ye Xiu was instructing and was beautifully coordinating with the others.

“Yeah, just like that. Pay attention to our attack tempo, the timing of your ghost boundaries, and your cooldowns. Maximize the efficiency.” Ye Xiu continuously instructed. Coaching a kid with a solid foundation really was a lot easier, unlike Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion, who had to learn the dungeon’s strategy by rote memorization. In terms of their understanding of the dungeon, in reality, these two weren’t even as good as Full Moon Guild’s guild leader.

Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion’s mechanics were there, but they had to memorize the strategy and increase their game knowledge.

As for Full Moon Guild’s guild leader, he was familiar with the game. Everything Ye Xiu said, he understood. It was just that he wasn’t used to it, which was why he had so much trouble.

As for Qiao Yifan, he had the strengths of both sides. Ye Xiu immediately saw this. He could easily keep up with them, which was why Ye Xiu was certain that one practice run was enough. After all, he was a pro player.

“You don’t need to start with Shadow Image. Instead, it’d be better to attack and deal more damage.. You won’t have the aggro changed to you and you won’t take any damage.” Ye Xiu said.

Shadow Image is a Ghost that Ghostblades can summon at Level 25. This Ghost can be carried by the user, except it would just be a Ghost surrounding the user. The Ghost could absorb and reduce damage. The higher the level, the greater the reduction and the more hits it could take. This was a skill solely used for defense. Ye Xiu had told Qiao Yifan to not use the skill. This was because the other party members would protect him.

Qiao Yifan was used to being cannon fodder. But now, the team was actively putting in energy to protect him.

“Ooh, this Ice Boundary……”

“Is there’s a problem?” Qiao Yifan was terrified.

“No, no. It was done very well.” Ye Xiu turned around to say to Steamed Bun Invasion; “Steamed Bun, it was your mistake this time!”

“It was mine, it was mine.” Steamed Bun Invasion shouted in response.

Originally, the Ice Boundary shouldn’t have been used there, but because of Steamed Bun Invasion’s mistake, the situation had changed. However, Qiao Yifan had adjusted as well. When he cast his Ice Boundary, he immediately got the crowd control effect he wanted, reducing the team’s pressure.

Ice Soul was a Boundary Ghost that could be summoned by Level 30 Ghostblades. Enemies inside the boundary would take Ice Elemental Magic Damage and there was even a chance for the targets to be Frozen. It was a more attack-oriented Ghost Boundary.

“However, there was actually a better choice you could have made.” After criticizing Steamed Bun Invasion’s mistake, he returned to Qiao Yifan.

Chapter 177 – Dual Linking Ghost Boundaries

“Look. Steamed Bun Invasion’s previous mistake made it so that the monsters weren’t gathered perfectly. However, the three monsters that slipped through just happened to be heading towards you. Here, the best choice wasn’t to immediately use Ice Boundary to control them. Instead, you could have first used a Ghost Slash to send the three monsters back into the desired positions and make up for Steamed Bun’s mistake. Then, using Ice Boundary would have been perfect.” Ye Xiu said.

“But there were more than three that had slipped through!” Qiao Yifan said.

“Aren’t we a team?” Ye Xiu smiled, “We can help fix the mistake and coordinate with you as well!”

“If a mistake like this happens, does this mean that there’s no hope for setting the record?” Qiao Yifan said.

“Ha ha, from that perspective, such a mistake really wouldn’t be good. We could make up for the lost time but it wouldn’t be enough. However, more important than the record is training our game knowledge and decision-making by going through these types of scenarios. In the previous scenario, it was easy to pull off an Ice Boundary. But that was in a dungeon. What if that was in a match? Could you be certain that you wouldn’t be interrupted while using your Ice Boundary in a scenario where you have no cover?” Ye Xiu said.

Qiao Yifan immediately understood: “I understand.”

“Even though this is only a dungeon, you still have to try hard and increase your game knowledge!” Ye Xiu said.

“Right, right.” Qiao Yifan responded. He felt as if a door in his heart was opening; as if the bottleneck he had been stuck at was slowly being broken through. He wasn’t sure if it was because he had switched classes or because he had received coaching under a God or maybe even both. Qiao Yifan thought.

Even though he had already taken the dungeon very seriously, after hearing Ye Xiu’s words, he felt that he still hadn’t placed enough emphasis onto it. Even if it was just a dungeon, there were still lots of places for improvement.

Under Ye Xiu’s constant instructions, the team quickly pushed forward. Ye Xiu’s team was using the “missing a player” strategy they were experimenting with last night.

The monsters that they weren’t originally able to kill fast enough and the places where they had originally struggled with, suddenly turned good with the addition of One Inch Ash.

Tang Rou felt indescribably shocked. To be able to create a strategy before one of their members had ever coordinated with them before, just how much further did she need to go before she could catch up to Ye Xiu?

“You two!” Ye Xiu called out to Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion, “Pay more attention to his Ghost Boundaries. Coordination is mutual! Now that I think about it, do you two know the effects of these Ghost Boundaries?”

“No……” The two new players said.

Ye Xiu was helpless. He had no other choice but to give them a brief introduction about the skill. Support classes who provided support on the sidelines didn’t necessarily count as coordination. Those being supported have to fully utilize the support. If you don’t even know what the effects of the support are, then how are you going to utilize them?

In a Level 30 Ghostblade’s arsenal, besides the defense-oriented Ghost Shadow Image and the attack-oriented Boundary Ghost Ice Soul, there was also Sword Soul that could be learned at Level 10.

The Sword Soul’s strength was that the allies within its boundary would have increased Strength and Intelligence, which determined the amount of Physical Damage and Magic Damage one could deal. It could be said that any class within the Sword Soul would gain huge buffs. This skill was also called Sword Boundary by players.

The skill could be learned at Level 10 and could be skilled up every three levels. A Level 30 Ghostblade could have a Level 7 Sword Soul, which would increase Strength and Intelligence by 105. As soon as this number was said by Ye Xiu, Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion jumped back in astonishment. The two checked their profiles and immediately recognized how terrifying an increase in 105 points of Strength and Intelligence were.

Battle Mages and Brawlers had the same Strength growth. At Level 30, without any equipment or stat rewards, their base Strength was 105 points.

Of course, a character’s base stats weren’t the most accurate indicators. In reality, with their equipment and rewards, the two characters would have much more.

However, 105 extra Strength and Intelligence was enough to make them start sweating.

Ghostblades had to cast Sword Soul at the right time and the other characters would have to fully utilize the Sword Soul as well. They should try and deal as much damage as possible within the Sword Boundary during the duration of the effect.

Seeing this incredible number, Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion already understood. The coordination between the two sides was now smoother. Even though it was their first practice trial, it was already much better than their previous trial with Full Moon Guild’s guild leader.

Their coordination with each other had been improved by the utilization of the support, but the crucial point was still Qiao Yifan’s outstanding view of the general situation. Qiao Yifan himself felt like he was a fish back in the water in this dungeon. No, to be more accurate, it was in this team that he found the feeling of being a fish back in the water. Qiao Yifan had already believed that even if they weren’t running a dungeon, even if they were in any other place, even if they were in a pro match, he felt as if he had a place in the team.

So moved!

In such a short moment of time, feelings of being blessed had risen many times. In return, he tried his hardest in this dungeon.

They pushed through the dungeon without a hitch. In the blink of an eye, they reached the final BOSS Toya. Qiao Yifan looked forward to the God’s commands. He knew that Toya was the most influential part of the record.

In the end, God actually talked less in this area. The entire team was more free to do their own thing. Even though there was some coordination, it didn’t seem like it was be good enough. They seemed more passive in front of Toya.

Qiao Yifan was a pro, after all. He could roughly judge that with the way they were playing, they wouldn’t be able to beat the record.

Qiao Yifan felt a bit puzzled. Even he could come up with some sort of strategy for this part. He could at least do better than their current strategy of randomly playing. God Ye Qiu had to have some sort of plan, right?

Just as he was thinking this, he heard God’s Lord Grim move next to him and ask: “What do you think about this?”

After a brief pause, Qiao Yifan said the truth: “I think that if we play like this then breaking the record might be difficult.”

“You don’t need to worry.” Tang Rou’s Soft Mist had also come over. Hearing their discussion, she added: “All of this is because someone here refuses to go all out. If not, then you’d be seeing a completely different scene.”

“Ha ha.” Ye Xiu laughed. He then said to Qiao Yifan : ”When the time comes, you’ll know what to do. You can do it!”

“Uh……” Qiao Yifan was a bit lost, but he didn’t ask.

After finishing the run, they had completely understood the strategy.

“Two chances!” Ye Xiu wasn’t only saying this to Qiao Yifan, but to the other three as well. Having strong mechanics didn’t mean that you wouldn’t make mistakes.

“Yeah.” Tang Rou simply answered.

“Relax! I only show my true strength at crucial times like this.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“You too!” Su Mucheng reminded Ye Xiu as well. Ye Xiu obviously wasn’t someone who was immune to mistakes. In his ten years of gaming, he had plenty of experience making mistakes.

“Begin!”

Under this command, they began.

In the beginning, where they needed to pull monsters, their current strategy was similar to their original one. Except this time, Qiao Yifan’s Once Inch Ash helped pull the monsters. As soon as they gathered together……

“Sword…… Soul!”

Ye Xiu had only said one of the words, when Qiao Yifan’s Sword Soul had been casted.

The timing had been grasped perfectly, coordinating seamlessly with the rest of the team.

Ye Xiu was extremely happy. Bringing an expert like this was so much easier; he grasped everything so quickly!

The others were also controlling the monsters. If not, then the monsters would escape the Sword Soul’s range. The difference between their DPS inside the boundary and outside the boundary was completely different.

There was only one bad part. Sword Soul only lasted 20 seconds, while the cooldown was 30 seconds. There was no way they could keep it on forever, there would always be 10 seconds of free time.

But this time, the instant the Sword Soul disappeared, Lord Grim suddenly jumped backwards to escape from the mob. He then waved his sword and a shadowy mist leapt out of his sword, congealing into a dark violet Ghost.

One Inch Ash’s Sword Soul had faded away, but a new one had followed up closely.

Sword Soul!

“If it’s Sword Soul, I know it as well!” Ye Xiu said. Lord Grim’s sword danced and followed up with a Berserker skill.

The Ghostblade’s Sword Soul was a Level 10 skill, so of course unspecialized had it. The effects of the two couldn’t overlap, but it could be used to fill up the empty gap.

This type of coordination had a name in Glory: “Dual Linking Ghost Boundaries.”

In the current Professional Alliance, only Team Void used this type of strategy. Besides their team captain Li Xuan’s Sobbing Ghost, they also had another Ghostblade class.

However, Ye Xiu and Qiao Yifan’s “Dual Linking Ghost Boundaries” weren’t perfect. After all, Lord Grim’s unspecialized class could only learn the “Sword Soul” and no other Ghost-summoning skill. Even so, it still let them maximize their DPS.

The first wave was cleared quickly inside of the Ghost Boundary.

Second wave…..

Third wave…….

Fourth wave……

On their smooth journey through, there wasn’t any excessive talk. Not just Qiao Yifan, but Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion no longer needed Ye Xiu’s constant reminders after running it so many times. The two weren’t lacking in the slightest in what they had to do.

Qiao Yifan’s Phantom Demon was doing even better. His Ghost Boundaries came out whenever they were needed, and he wouldn’t mess anything up whenever he wasn’t. He also linked together with Lord Grim’s occasional Sword Soul well, too.

Without any suspense, everyone swiftly smashed their way to the dungeon’s rear garden. Only a mere 19 minutes had passed.

Chapter 178 – Their Wishes Finally Came True

For the final BOSS, Toya, if they played randomly like the previous run, there might not be enough time. This was originally a relatively difficult BOSS. Blue Brook Guild’s Changing Spring and the other experts had to train hard numerous times in order to suppress it through coordination. But what about now? What method was left in store? Qiao Yifan recalled how they had said that God wasn’t going all out and became a bit curious as well as a bit uncertain.

“Sword Soul!” Ye Xiu yelled out, while they were rushing forward.

If Qiao Yifan was making the decision, he definitely wouldn’t cast Sword Soul so early. However, he trusted in the God’s decision and immediately cast Sword Soul when he heard it. One Inch Ash’s Demon Slaying Blade flashed. A ghostly mist congealed into a Sword Soul after the chant and formed a Boundary.

This “Sword Soul” shout also seemed to be instructions to others as well. Cleansing Mist’s handcannon spit out a flame tongue and hit the idle BOSS, Toya, with an artillery shell .

Toya turned his head and rushed at them. He stepped on a stone in the garden and somersaulted forward. In mid-air, he whipped out his leg to kick them. Lord Grim moved up as well. His Thousand Chance Umbrella turned into a Battle Lance. The two brushed past each other, however Toya suddenly disappeared. He had unexpectedly been Circle Swung onto the ground by Lord Grim.

“So quick!!!”

Qiao Yifan’s point of view was very different from Tang Rou’s and Steamed Bun Invasion’s. Whenever Ye Xiu attacked, those two had seen it so often that they were completely indifferent to it. However, Qiao Yifan could see how difficult the move was.

Positioning, speed, precision, prediction.

In this type of situation, if even a single one was slightly lacking, the attack would have failed. Just using Circle Swing didn’t mean that you would hit the monster. Glory isn’t such a simple game!

With the way Circle Swing captured the target, Toya had no way of Quick Recovering in order to avoid this knock down. But he could be considered quick as well. Right when he crashed to the ground, he sent out a shock wave in order to get back up. Lord Grim had already anticipated this. As soon as his Circle Swing flung Toya down to the ground, he immediately leaped back. Not only did Toya’s shock wave not hit anything, Lord Grim drew out his sword and sent out a Sword Draw towards him.

“So quick!!!”

Qiao Yifan had the same impression as before. Toya and Lord Grim’s battle tempo really was fast. But Toya was a system NPC. He didn’t need to think or make decisions, but Lord Grim? He was able to make consecutive moves without practically any time to think. Each move he made suppressed Toya’s offensive.

The strength of an unspecialized!

Qiao Yifan understood this, but more importantly, even with an arsenal of skills available for use, God Ye Qiu was able to pick the most suitable choice with little time to think. His quick and accurate decision-making were almost like a robot’s.

“Too scary!” Qiao Yifan was astonished. Just how much experience did he have? If this was any other pro-player, they might be able to make the same accurate decisions, but to do so with almost no time to think, only a select few could do that. Experience could only be gained with time and time couldn’t be controlled. Old generals could no longer be as full of energy as new players. As for new players, if they wanted the experience of the old generals, the only way was to wait and become old generals themselves.

In this situation, where Lord Grim was suppressing Toya by himself, the final obstacle became incomparably easy. To the other four, this battle was just like any other. They were against a very ordinary BOSS. All they had to do was coordinate with Lord Grim and deal damage.

Sword Soul, Ice Soul.

Qiao Yifan switched between the two Boundaries. He could also use Ghost Slash, Moonlight Slash, Full Moon Slash to deal damage. However, these Slash skills clearly weren’t too high-leveled. Skill points had to be saved for skilling up the Phantom Ghosts. The damage dealt by Phantom Demons couldn’t compare with the damage dealt by Sword Demons.

1 minute.

Toya’s health had already dropped by ⅓. If they maintained this tempo, they would definitely finish the battle in three minutes. With so much time left, they could even afford to make a few mistakes.

Too strong!

Qiao Yifan lamented. Even though an enormous amount of importance had been attached to him, he understood very clearly that he wasn’t the final deciding factor in setting the record.

It was a fact that Phantom Demons could increase the entire team’s strength. In theory, the more members in the team, the more useful a Phantom Demon was. This was why all of the big guilds would specially train a few Phantom Demons.

However, in the Professional Alliance’s official matches, the number of players that could go on stage was restricted to only five players; this limited the amount of support a Phantom Demon could provide. In a five-man team, Phantom Demons weren’t the worse class, but the value of their support might not make them more valuable than other classes either. Their existence wasn’t a necessity, but rather just another option.

In Desolate Land, the usefulness of a Phantom Demon was similar to this as well. He could provide support, but he wouldn’t be the main factor for why the team would break the record.

The true factor was still Lord Grim.

It was because the strengths of an unspecialized could be fully utilized which allowed them to surpass this dungeon’s limit.

It was because of the unspecialized that they could employ Dual Overlapping Ghost Boundaries.

It was because of the unspecialized that they could completely suppress Toya.

In addition, Lord Grim’s weapon was clearly self-made. It was clearly a top-tier Silver weapon. How could Qiao Yifan not know about Silver weapons? There was no way other teams had this type of advantage in damage.

The record was right in front of them!

Two minutes had passed. Toya’s health had dropped down by ⅔.

Attack attack attack.

The five continued to attack. This was only the second time Qiao Yifan had coordinated with the others, yet their coordination wasn’t lacking in the slightest. Actively coordinating with others; this was his biggest strength. Whether this was because of talent or because of he was trained as a person on the edge, no one knew.

“Careful, almost Red Blood.” When Toya’s health had dropped down to 10%, Ye Xiu warned them as usual.

Tang Rou and the others were completely indifferent. Toya becoming Enraged didn’t mean anything. He would still be suppressed by Lord Grim.

On the other hand, Qiao Yifan made preparations for Red Blood. As soon as he saw Toya go into Red Blood, he suddenly used the Grab skill Ghost Claw. After capturing Toya, he followed up with a Moonlight Slash, launching Toya into the air. Icy frost formed at the tip of his blade. The ice shattered and an Ice Soul flashed out. Ice Boundary!

The mid-air Toya continuously took Ice Damage. When he fell, he froze into a giant ice cube. The team rushed forward to attack. However, the BOSS’s resistance was high, so the Freeze didn’t last long. But after breaking out of the ice, what could Toya do next? Under Lord Grim’s lead, Toya’s health continued to plummet.

Sky Strike, Dragon Tooth, Falling Flower Palm, Anti-Tank Missile, and even a wretched Brick.

In the final string of attacks, the explosion from the Anti-Tank Missile sent Toya flying into the stone wall. No one moved up to continue attacking. Toya had been killed.

System announcement!

Congratulations to players Lord Grim, Cleansing Mist, Steamed Bun Invasion, Soft Mist, One Inch Ash for breaking the Desolate Land record, time: 22:35:22.

After this brief message appeared, the world channel exploded.

There wasn’t any excessive amazement. For new players in the new server, they didn’t have any concept of what the time for the records should be. They weren’t like the veterans who jumped in fright at this terrifying record. For the tenth server’s players, they only had one thought; the record had been broken. It had been broken by Lord Grim again.

As a result, mostly congratulation messages appeared on the world channel.

Their congratulations weren’t directed towards Lord Grim, but rather Blue Brook Guild, especially that Cloud Listening Blade from Blue Brook Guild.

Cloud Listening Blade was Poplar Beach, who was constantly shouting at Lord Grim to fight him, to break their record.

At this moment, the players were all congratulating Blue Brook Guild and Cloud Listening Blade for having their wishes finally come true. The players were sarcastic and savage. It didn’t matter how skilled or experienced they were. The new players were all mocking them.

Poplar Beach was pale. He had sent another message a few moments ago. He specially guarded this time to provoke him. And in the end, a system announcement had given him a reply.

“Impossible!!” Poplar Beach didn’t want to believe it.

The record they had set was already the limit. Poplar Beach had been confident that it wasn’t possible to improve it, which was why he had been so arrogant. But now, the other side actually improved the time by about two minutes. Poplar Beach couldn’t imagine how this was possible.

The mocking continued. The person who had stepped had been stepped on. This type of show was something everyone loved to see. Everyone was discussing what Cloud Listening Blade was probably feeling right now. Sharp comments popped up one after another. Poplar Beach didn’t want to look at his screen. He was afraid that he’d die from anger in front of his computer.

How should he respond?

Poplar Beach had his head lowered as he stared at his keyboard. He didn’t know what keys he should press.

He suddenly heard a system prompt telling him that a friend had gone offline, making Poplar Beach lift up his head to look.

The one who had gone offline was Blue River. Poplar Beach obviously knew where Blue River was going. Poplar Beach felt embarrassed and resentful. The guy had finally found his sore spot.

Poplar Beach was aware that things weren’t looking good.

How did Lord Grim and his group set this record? These guys didn’t have all Orange equipment, right?

This thought kept circling around Poplar Beach’s head, but he wasn’t convinced. Would he make such a large investment just for a dungeon record? Moreover, this was the new server. Even if you had the money that didn’t mean it was possible to gather a full set of Level 30 Orange equipment for yourself, let alone an entire team. How could Orange equipment be as common as cabbage?

“Lord Grim! To be able to beat our record, it looks like you really do have some skill! Do you have time to duel me now?”

Poplar Beach hesitated for a long time, but in the end, he pressed enter and sent it.

Chapter 179 – A Chance for a Comeback

The entire world was mocking Poplar Beach’s Cloud Listening Blade, so of course they were waiting for his response. As a result, many saw this message and a bunch of new messages immediately appeared. Comments such as “Cloud Listening Blade is such a man”, “Cloud Listening Blade is a true hero”, “Cloud Listening Blade refuses to die with his head low” and so on. They were still filled with sarcasm. Clearly, no one liked arrogant guys like him.

This didn’t mean that people who liked to be arrogant wouldn’t know this, it was just that arrogant people weren’t arrogant so they could be liked. They were arrogant because they liked the pleasure of standing above others and looking down on them.

When Poplar Beach had bragged about the record he had set, although everyone was angry, they had no way of beating his record. This was the pleasure of being arrogant. But now, when he was above everyone, he had suddenly been stepped on. This was an extremely painful feeling.

The reason Poplar Beach continued to demand a duel against Lord Grim was so that he could keep up his arrogant attitude. He couldn’t do anything about the record, so his only choice was to use a duel to prove that he wasn’t a braggart, but rather an amazing top-tier player. This was what it truly meant to be arrogant.

Amidst the storm of ridicule, Poplar Beach waited for Lord Grim’s reply.

He didn’t have to wait long. This time, Lord Grim finally replied to him: “How about tomorrow afternoon? Use your main account.”

“Good, I hope that you won’t run away.” Poplar Beach coldly typed out. He then waited for a very long time, but no reply came. How could Ye Xiu care to respond to such a pointless provocation? Ye Xiu had already brought his party into the dungeon again. This time, everyone was still playing diligently, especially at the final BOSS, Toya. Everyone coordinated with Lord Grim even better this time. This time, the record had been broken again.

22:29:57. The world went into an uproar again.

The record had improved by 6 seconds. It wasn’t much. However, at this record limit, another six seconds wasn’t easy. It was practically the result of a perfect run.

At the same time, after the three runs ended, Lord Grim and the other four characters leveled up to level 31. Su Mucheng left first to sleep. Qiao Yifan was also a pro-player. He shouldn’t have had so much free time. But after being with Ye Xiu and the others for these three runs, a completely different feeling had already risen up in his heart. When the three runs were finished, he actually wasn’t willing to go to sleep and went to Line Canyon with them.

On Blue Brook Guild’s side, after Changing Spring heard Blue River return with the news, they rushed over to the tenth server and saw the new record on the leaderboards. They were all speechless. Before they could even recover, the record had been broken again.

One time, maybe they were just miraculously lucky.

But two times in a row? That, without a doubt, was a proof of their strength.

Even though Changing Spring had braced himself for this long ago, from the guild’s point of view, this was a disastrous result. However, there was nothing they could do. If they hadn’t fought for it, there was no way they could explain it to their own guild. Right now, even at the guild headquarters in the Heavenly Domain, they were discussing the great battle over the records in the tenth server. Everyone, particularly Poplar Beach and his group, would agree to a compromise only if there was no other choice.

In order to keep the peace in Blue Brook Guild, they had to sacrifice a bit of the tenth server’s Blue Brook Guild’s reputation. At least, right now, they were only adding frost to the snow. They were already a laughingstock in the tenth server. Their image could only be recovered at a later time. It could be said that, from here on out, Blue Brook Guild’s development would fall behind the other guilds.

However, a chance for a comeback was still possible.

Poplar Beach’s duel with Lord Grim. This was their chance.

Even though Blue River wasn’t in favor of this duel and wasn’t optimistic about it, he had no choice but to admit that if Poplar Beach won, then they’d be able to win back their guild’s image in the tenth server. This duel was being followed by many. The entire world was talking about it. Who knew how many would wait for the afternoon show?

Poplar Beach’s actions, from a reasoning standpoint, weren’t stupid. This was actually the best way of winning back their guild’s prestige. However, could he win?

Blue River was very very doubtful, but he couldn’t say anything. After all was said and done, he was always for the guild. At this moment, he was hoping that Poplar Beach would win, even though he could foresee that if Poplar Beach actually won, then his arrogance would rise from the earth to the heavens.

This struggle over the record deeply impacted Tyrannical Ambition as well.

Blue Brook Guild had bravely stepped out. This was something they wished to see. As a result, they didn’t rush to fight for the Line Canyon record and decided to carry their tarnished name for two more days. They wanted to see what Lord Grim’s attitude was and what he would do.

In the end, they saw it all. Lord Grim had sneakily stolen the Level 36 wild BOSS First Kill and then easily stepped on Blue Brook Guild’s record twice.

Tyrannical Ambition’s boss, Jiang You, had personally come to the tenth server as well. Similarly, he also gathered the guild’s strongest troops to come over. But after seeing this result, he quickly gave up on his original plan.

The record’s limit?

It seemed like there were two of them. One for normal players like them and another for Lord Grim’s team. Jiang You was truly doubting whether Lord Grim had set the record for the same dungeon. The record that was the limit in their eyes had been crushed by minutes.

“What do we do? Talk with Lord Grim?” Cold Night was naturally depressed. Why was the tenth server so troublesome? Such a difficult guy had popped up.

“Let’s not rush…… They’re still a few days away from reaching Level 33. Right now, Blue Brook Guild is in the spotlight, so we’re being overlooked. I’ll see if there’s any other way to resolve this situation. Giving in to Lord Grim’s demands isn’t good. We have to at least show that we have the strength to resist his suppression, even if it is just once. After that, we can still negotiate with him and we’ll have a better time.” Jiang You said.

“How do we prove our strength?” Cold Night stared blankly. Their experts clearly wouldn’t cut it. Blue Brook Guild was their proof for that.

“I can try and ask the team.” Jiang You said.

“That’s a bit too much, right…….” Cold Night began sweating. Team Tyranny was a powerful team that was aiming to be Champions. Ask them to help them set a record in the tenth server? With the team captain Han Wenqing’s personality, Cold Night felt like they were looking to be shouted at! Jiang You’s suggestion was too brave.

“Uh……. let me think……” Clearly, Jiang You was also hesitant.

Besides these two guilds, the other guilds were extremely happy seeing Lord Grim turn Blue Brook Guild’s record limit into ashes, and twice too. Their emotions were constantly going up and down. But after taking joy in their enemies’ plight, they also had to ponder over their own situation. This issue really was quite troublesome.

The night went by like this.

After Poplar Beach arranged for the duel, he left the tenth server and went on his main account. He went to the Arena and fought for the entire night. He specifically looked for opponents with high win rates and practiced fiercely.

In the blink of an eye, the afternoon came and Poplar Beach went to the tenth server to look for Lord Grim. He hadn’t slept well at all. He was already feeling tired, but his mind couldn’t calm down. As soon as he closed his eyes, he would think of the Arena. Even compared to that time he decided to challenge Blue Bridge Spring Snow, he had never felt so nervous before.

Even though he wasn’t in his best condition, it was truly too shameful to schedule the duel for a different date. Even if he did, he still might not be able to calm down. By then, his condition would be even worse.

Poplar Beach did a quick search and found that Lord Grim was online. He immediately shouted at him in the world channel. The players in the entire server shook. He had arrived. He had finally arrived.

“You should go create the room.” Lord Grim replied.

“Level Field.” Poplar Beach switched to his main account and entered the Arena. He created a room and invited Lord Grim.

In Happy Internet Cafe, Ye Xiu left the tenth server and went to find Chen Guo. Boss Chen was also playing Glory right now. She was sitting in front of her computer and her hands were moving about like the wind. Ye Xiu blew out two smoke rings. Boss Chen’s avatar staggered. She turned around and yelled angrily: “What are you doing?!”

“Boss, let me borrow your account!” Ye Xiu said.

“To do what?”

“To PK with someone.” Ye Xiu said.

“Who?”

“What was his name again?” Ye Xiu scratched his head.

Chen Guo rolled her eyes and said as her character returned to the main city: “Level or Free.”

“Level.” Ye Xiu said.

“Room number?”

“I don’t know…….”

“Then how am I supposed to look for it?” Chen Guo asked.

“Go to the side and say that Lord Grim has arrived or something.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo typed it in. Soon after, a pile of messages from cheering spectators covered the screen, scaring Chen Guo. After that, she received an invite and accepted it.

She entered the field. The map that had been chosen was the most basic ring. It was a simple and straightforward map. Most players liked it. After Chen Guo’s character went in, she immediately sucked in a cold breath. For there to be so many spectators, this was something she had never imagined.

“What’d you do?” Chen Guo had originally planned on playing for awhile, but after seeing so many spectators, she immediately felt that the situation was important. She didn’t want to mess things up, so she got up and let Ye Xiu take over.

And at this moment, the current receptionist Tang Rou stretched out her neck to ask: “Did it start? Did it start?”

“About to.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Help me out for a moment please.” Tang Rou immediately asked a manager to take over for a bit. She then lightly skipped over.

“Watching it like this won’t be very fun. Let’s get onto another account.” Chen Guo had a lot of experience and immediately went to turn on another computer.

“Don’t start yet!!” She didn’t forget to warn Ye Xiu. Even though she didn’t really understand the situation, her curiosity had already been sparked.

Chapter 180 – The Fastest Launcher

“Lord Grim???” Poplar Beach was a bit doubtful when he saw that a female character had entered the field.

“Yeah.” Ye Xiu said.

Poplar Beach wasn’t too surprised though. Lord Grim had said that he would borrow an account. Male characters were the same as female characters; their stats and equipment weren’t much different from each other.

However, this was something that Ye Xiu had said during their dispute in front of Desolate Land’s entrance. How could the other players know this? All they knew was that, yesterday, Lord Grim told his opponent to use his main account, so many concluded that these two characters were both side’s main accounts.

“Poplar Beach!!” This character was quite famous. Many veterans from the Heavenly Domain, who came to pioneer in the new server, knew this character.

“Poplar Beach??” In Happy Internet Cafe, Chen Guo and Tang Rou had turned on a computer and logged into Glory with Soft Mist. They found the room and entered as a spectator. When Chen Guo saw the opponent’s name, she couldn’t help but cry it out in surprise.

“You’re familiar with him?” Tang Rou asked.

“I’m not familiar with him, but I do know of him. He’s from Blue Brook Guild after all. He’s an elite in there, but he’s always shouting arrogantly in the world channel. He’s really annoying.” Chen Guo was in the Heavenly Domain as well, so she recognized the famous experts from Blue Brook Guild. But clearly, her impression of him wasn’t good.

“Oh.” Tang Rou was the type of new player who had no concept of how great “Blue Brook Guild” was. She just thought that they were the same as Full Moon Guild; they were one of the guilds that had asked them to set a record and nothing more.

“Why are they PKing?” Chen Guo asked Tang Rou in doubt, while yelling at Ye Xiu: “Hey, hey. You can start now!”

“Okay.” Ye Xiu put on his headphones and clicked Ready. Poplar Beach immediately clicked Ready as well and their match began. Chen Guo and Tang Rou’s screen flashed and switched to spectator mode.

“Are you a male or female?” Poplar Beach asked. After entering the field, the two were able to talk to each other.

“Male.” Ye Xiu replied.

“So you’ll be using this character. You’re sure that you won’t switch?” Poplar Beach asked.

“Yeah.”

“How many rounds to determine who wins or loses?” Poplar Beach asked about the details of the duel.

“One round is enough.” Ye Xiu laughed, “One round is enough to let you know the gap between us. I guarantee that you won’t fight a second round.”

“CUT THE CRAP!!” Poplar Beach roared.

Even though Chen Guo and Tang Rou weren’t able to listen to the two talk in spectator mode, they could hear Ye Xiu, who was sitting next to them. They could hear whatever Ye Xiu was saying. After hearing this, Chen Guo curled her lips towards Tang Rou: “He sounds really mad!”

“It’s started.” Tang Rou said. Right now, Chen Guo was controlling the computer, so she needed to adjust the spectating angle.

In the ring, after Poplar Beach said that, he took the initiative to attack. His character rushed towards Chasing Haze, which Ye Xiu was controlling. The instant his character entered Chasing Haze’s firing range, his character suddenly flashed. Moving in an irregular pattern, Poplar Beach’s character immediately blurred into one, two, three, four afterimages.

“Shadow Steps! Four afterimages!” Chen Guo immediately shouted.

This was a high-leveled Blade Master skill. The skill’s effects depended on the player’s mechanics. Poplar Beach’s movements created four perfect afterimages, making Chen Guo yell out in astonishment. In her experience against other Blade Masters, she had never met any players who were able to create four afterimages. This Blue Brook Guild’s expert really did have the ability to back up his arrogance.

“Woah, not bad!” Ye Xiu lightly praised. Poplar Beach had quite a bit of experience. His Shadow Steps were timed perfectly. They were completed the instant he entered Chasing Haze’s firing range. To be able to instantly determine Chasing Haze’s firing range was a testament to his exceptional knowledge of the game. This judgement could only be made by looking at Chasing Haze’s equipment.

As for the four afterimages that Chen Guo was so astonished about……. they weren’t anything to Ye Xiu. In the pro-scene, which pro Blade Master couldn’t do this? For top-tier Blade Masters like Huang Shaotian, he could create six and a half afterimages with his movements. Four? Too few……

Ye Xiu instantly recognized which of the four afterimages was the real one. His mouse moved and Chasing Haze immediately fired out a Quantum Bomb. At the same time, he tapped the keyboard with his left hand to have Chasing Haze step back. “Quantum Bomb” and “Laser Rifle” were similar when they were fired. They had a strong recoil, requiring the user to move their character a step backwards in order to dissolve it. If not, then the character would fall backwards towards the ground.

。

Poplar Beach wasn’t too surprised by this “Quantum Bomb”. He slid to the side with Shadow Steps and moved just outside of the Quantum Bomb’s shockwave radius. This precise control made Ye Xiu want to praise him again. But who would have thought that right after Poplar Beach dodged it, he would immediately follow up with a “Sword Draw” to hack at the Quantum Bomb.

The system allowed for this type of attack as long as your hand-eye coordination and hand speed was good enough. In theory, you could even slice apart a Sharpshooter’s bullet. Of course, anyone who could do that would be an expert with mechanics that were even higher than those at the peak.

As for people who could slice apart a “Quantum Bomb”, quite a few people could do that. However, it also required a good enough hand-eye-coordination as well as fast hand speed. However in this situation, Poplar Beach had already avoided the “Quantum Bomb”. For him to suddenly use such a difficult move was completely unnecessary. Besides looking cool, there was no other reason to do so. Ye Xiu helplessly shook his head. Did this guy not understand the situation?

Since things were already like this, how could Ye Xiu ignore this huge opening? Without a word, he switched to a gun and used a “Floating Bullet”.

Launchers could use other weapons other than heavy artillery. It was just that many of the Launcher’s high damage skills required a cannon to use. The skill “Floating Bullet” wasn’t actually a Launcher skill. It was a Level 20 or below Spitfire skill. It was named “Floating Bullet” to indicate the strong Knock-up effect the skill had. If the skill was used with a smaller gun, the bullet would come out faster.

Switching guns and using dual guns was quite common for Gunners. Ye Xiu had noticed that Chasing Haze had a reserve gun when he took over the account. As a result, he pulled out the handgun and quickly fired a Floating Bullet.

However, the following scene made Ye Xiu somewhat surprised. When his Floating Bullet was fired, he immediately put the handgun away and prepared to switch to the cannon to follow up with an attack. But he then saw that Poplar Beach cancelled his Sword Draw mid-animation and jumped forward, dodging the Floating Bullet. After landing on the ground, he followed up with a Triple Slash. As the sword light arced forward, his character closed in on Chasing haze. Triple Slash was a Blade Master skill that was often used to move quickly.

“So it was a trap! This guy!” Ye Xiu immediately understood. Poplar Beach unexpectedly had a few of his own tricks! His previous actions, which aligned with his show-off personality, were just bait. He used the time that his opponent needed to switch weapons in order to close in!

The actions of switching guns wasn’t quick because switching weapons had a cooldown. This was one of the biggest obstacles that limited the power of unspecialized characters.

Seeing that his ploy had worked, Poplar Beach felt ecstatic in his heart. It was already too late for Chasing Haze to raise her cannon and defend. There wasn’t enough time for Chasing Haze to escape with an Aerial Fire either. He had found an opportunity where he could attack and the opponent had no way of resisting! Poplar Beach had already begun his offensive, however, Ye Xiu returned the surprise. Poplar Beach saw his opponent throw his weapon onto the ground.

“What? Did he make a mistake in panic?” Poplar Beach hadn’t expected something like this to happen. Equipment couldn’t be dropped in an Arena, so could this guy have actually thrown down his weapon by accident?

Poplar Beach knew Chasing Haze’s firing range, so he had figured out what his opponent’s weapon were even before that.

Rose Flower Cannon, a Level 70 Purple weapon. If something like this just dropped on the ground, who wouldn’t want to pick it up? Even if you couldn’t use it, it was still worth a lot of money.

“F*CK!!!” Chen Guo jumped up from her seat. That Rose Flower Cannon was hers! Ye Xiu had thrown it on the ground. What if the opponent picked it up and took it away? Chen Guo immediately felt a pang of regret. Hate! Why didn’t she bind it? It was because she was too ambitious. She was always thinking of switching for an Orange weapon and then sell her Purple weapon. But now?

However, Poplar Beach wouldn’t pick up the weapon right now. Although he was surprised, he still continued his offensive. However, he suddenly saw a Knee Strike come flying forward from Chasing Haze.

Knee Strike? What was the use of that?

Poplar Beach sneered. It was true that Knee Strike was an uninterruptible Super Armor skill, but unfortunately, Poplar Beach had anticipated that Chasing Haze would use some sort of Super Armor skill to force them apart. As a result, he used a “Wave Wheel Slasher”, which could break Super Armor.

This skill actually took some time to execute. However, his opponent was the slowest Gunner class, a Launcher, so he had more than enough time to interrupt this Knee Strike. Knee Strike was a low-leveled Sharpshooter skill. Even though the speed of it was unrelated to the user’s firing speed, the weight would affect its speed. A Launcher using a Cannon and Heavy armor would be very slow when using this skill.

Poplar Beach had thought that his decision was perfect, but unexpectedly, Chasing Haze’s Knee Strike was faster than his “Wave Wheel Slasher” so he was launched into the air.

“Impossible……” Poplar Beach adjusted his camera to look down, when he suddenly realized: Weapon weight affected the move’s skill. As a result, what was supposed to be a very slow Launcher, without a cannon, in his hands were……. his hands had no weapon!

A Launcher with nothing in his hands. How fast would the move be? Poplar Beach suddenly realized an issue he had never thought of before.

Chapter 181 – In a Flash

Poplar Beach noticed it just now, but it was already too late. His opponent had already thrown out a Grenade. The timing was perfect. The shock wave from the explosion launched his Blade Master even higher into the air as Chasing Haze picked up her Rose Flower Cannon. Seeing his opponent move like this, Poplar Beach finally realized: throwing down the Rose Flower Cannon was one of the opponent’s ploys!

Chasing Haze crouched and swung the Rose Flower Cannon back onto her shoulder. Blue light began to accumulate at the mouth of the cannon. Poplar Beach moved his camera to look down. Just before his character hit the ground, the stored blue light shot out and a brilliant blue artillery shell flew directly at him.

“X-1 Extruder……” Poplar Beach realized that his opponent’s crouch and swing wasn’t without meaning. The crouch reduced the time needed to put the cannon onto her shoulder. It also let him shoot from a lower height, making it so that the X-1 Extruder would hit him just as he was about to land on the ground.

“X-1 Extruder’s” feature was that it would vacuum in enemies that were hit by it, restricting their movements. The enemies would then fly forward along with it and then explode when it hit the ground, knocking the enemies to the ground along with it. Poplar Beach didn’t have any way of avoiding this vacuum effect. This time, damage would be certain. Just as he was calculating what he would do next to counterattack, he suddenly saw his opponent raise his hand and snap his fingers.

Poplar Beach was startled. This wasn’t a random movement. This was the casting animation for a Launcher’s Heat-Seeking Missile. The finger snap would bring up a crosshair. The final position of the crosshair would direct where the missile would land.

The attack did tons of damage, but the weakness of it was obvious. For one, the crosshair had to be accurate. However, the main weakness was that it was extremely slow. Poplar Beach decided he would do the same as with the Quantum Bomb and slice it apart. In mid-air, a sword light flashed forward. Sword Draw was executed towards the missile.

This move had been used in that match between Excellent Era and 301. Team 301’s Blade Master player Gao Jie had done this to dissolve the Heat-Seeking Missile. Poplar Beach’s situation was similar to Gao Jie’s situation. Both of them acted in midair. However, Poplar Beach wasn’t as skilled as a pro-player. Poplar Beach could only pray that his Sword Draw would hit the target.

Please hit!!

Seeing the flying slash’s direction and the missile’s arc, Poplar Beach determined that they would collide and a surge of happiness immediately washed over him. But who would have thought that at this moment, an explosion would suddenly ring out. Sword Slash’s sword aura had been exploded into three sparks. Poplar Beach was startled. He looked over at Chasing Haze and saw gentle smoke drift out from the mouth of the cannon…..

Sh*t! Poplar Beach’s Sword Slash had been deflected by his opponent’s Anti-Tank Missile. The flying heat-seeking missile flew towards him.

Poplar Beach felt a chill in his heart. He knew that his difficult maneuver had been done out of luck, but what about his opponent?

The bright crosshair finally found its target. A loud boom sounded out from up above in the sky and a Heat-Seeking Missile descended down. Poplar Beach began to fall. He had no way of immediately using Quick Recover. He hadn’t been launched in a normal way. he had been sucked in by “X-1 Extruder”.

The crosshair, Poplar Beach, and the suction from the X-1 Extruder together let the Heat-Seeking Missile arrive and a large mushroom cloud leapt into the air. But things weren’t done yet. Poplar Beach, who had been forced tumbling in the air from the shock wave, saw a large laser beam shoot down, the Gunner’s ultimate: Satellite Beam…..

Poplar Beach had eaten all of the Launcher’s high damage skills.

Poplar Beam was still tumbling from the explosion and light of the Satellite Beam. Ye Xiu used this time to quickly throw out a few more skills. The spectators watched dumbstruck as explosions continued to chain together, reaching a 77 Combo.

The light from explosions receded. The smoke dispersed. Poplar Beach had already been defeated.

Starting from when he was launched into the air by that Knee Strike to the instant he landed on the ground, he wasn’t able to find any opportunity to counter attack. In that span of five seconds, how many skills had hit him? The spectators had to count on their fingers to work it out.

Everyone saw the result: Poplar Beach had been defeated.

Defeated!

He really had been defeated!

In just an instant, the long health bar had been washed clean. The spectators weren’t even able to type. They were completely dumbstruck.

Chen Guo was also staring blankly at the computer screen.

She was already standing because Ye Xiu had thrown her Rose Flower Cannon. She was just about to go over and kill the guy. However, her Rose Flower Cannon had been picked back up and in the blink of an eye, the opponent had turned into a corpse. All of this happened as she jumped up from her seat……..

Chen Guo finally saw how Ye Xiu was able to beat an opponent in a few seconds using her Chasing Haze.

Chen Guo had never thought that her Chasing Haze had the burst power to explode someone to death in one go. Moreover, the person who had died was a famous expert in the Heavenly Domain. Chen Guo felt a surge of excitement! She had originally wanted to go and strangle Ye Xiu to death, but now she couldn’t move, she didn’t know how to describe what she was feeling.

Poplar Beach’s corpse quickly disappeared. The experienced gamers knew that this person had already left the room.

What could Poplar Beach say now?

The arrogant him had been completely shut up. There was nothing he could say.

He realized that Lord Grim’s words weren’t a provocation, but a reality.

One round, it really was one round.

He completely recognized the gap between their skill.

To lose so quickly and tragically, this wasn’t a question of whether it was luck. The match ended so quickly that the spectators had overlooked another reality. This was a “Perfect” match, Chasing Haze hadn’t suffered any damage..

Once Chasing Haze left the room as well, the room was naturally dissolved and the spectators were kicked back into the lobby. But everyone was still in shock and were still circling about. Only Ye Xiu didn’t care. He took off his headphones and turned his head: “Boss, you can have your account back!”

“Huh?” Chen Guo was also one of those who were dumbstruck.

“Did you record it?” Chen Guo suddenly turned her head to ask Tang Rou.

Tang Rou laughed bitterly: “You were the one controlling it!”

“Ah ah ah ah!!!” Everyone had already left the room. How could she still have the chance to record it? Chen Guo felt regretful. It would have been such a great video! It was something she could watch a hundred times.

Chen Guo felt depressed! She suddenly discovered something amiss. She looked around and discovered that a few people were looking at her.

“What are you looking at?” Chen Guo wasn’t very polite. The people looking at her were frequent customers, so they knew each other. She hadn’t done anything out of the ordinary, so what were they all looking at?

“Boss, you’re so fierce!” Someone suddenly said.

“What?” Chen Guo stared blankly.

“Chasing Haze!!” Someone else shouted.

“What? Chasing Haze? Where? Where?” Another person jumped up. This time it was a customer Chen Guo didn’t recognize.

Chen Guo instantly understood. This duel had been seen by some in the Internet Cafe. Among those were a few who didn’t know that Lord Grim was a manager at this Internet Cafe, but they did know that Chen Guo’s Glory character was Chasing haze. After that, they thought that Lord Grim was actually Chen Guo.

And those unfamiliar customers obviously didn’t know anything. They just heard someone in the Internet Cafe speak up about it, so they immediately looked for her and crowded around her. Chen Guo didn’t know whether to laugh or cry. She looked around, but didn’t know where Ye Xiu had slipped away to. She could helplessly cry out: “That wasn’t me. Someone else borrowed my account” and then hastily ran off.

The customers all stared blankly. They didn’t say anything else. The crowd was just there to satisfy their curiosity.In reality, most of the Glory players that knew Chen Guo knew what her skill level was. It was just that the previous match had been too surprising. Poplar Beach! All the veterans knew who he was.

And thus, saying that someone had borrowed the account was very reasonable.

。

There weren’t many who both recognized Chen Guo’s account and watched the match, so there wasn’t too much commotion. Everyone went back to the game to discuss about it in private. This match was too quick. Not only was the course of events quick, even the room had been dissolved quickly, making it so that there wasn’t any place for everyone to talk about it. After the players left the Arena, they immediately began discussing it in the world channel.

In a short moment, a single topic conquered the tenth server world channel.

Lord Grim, Chasing Haze, Launcher, threw down his weapon, instant kill, etc. these were all keywords.

The match was too frightening, making it so that everyone was concentrated on the one who was victorious. At this moment, Poplar Beach was like a pitiful backdrop. Very few people mentioned him.

There were a few new players who didn’t really understand. They obviously didn’t know how incredible Poplar Beach’s background was. They just saw that he had been instantly defeated, so they wanted to mock him. But their mockery was actually met with other’s mockery.

Who won and who lost the match wasn’t because one side was weak, but rather because the other side was too strong.

In everyone’s eyes, this was the impression they got. Of course, no one felt that Poplar Beach’s loss was dignified. However, his defeat wasn’t the main point everyone was talking about.

Chasing Haze, so strong!

Launchers, so strong!

Lord Grim, so strong!

These were the main points.

Chapter 182 – Consultation

The match was beautiful and the reaction to it was massive. But to the big guilds, its impact wasn’t as great as the record that had been set in Desolate Land. The big guilds recognized the result and talked about it for a bit. However, there was no way it would be put above Blue Brook Guild’s tarnished image.

The only ones who were truly concerned over the match was Blue Brook Guild.

Currently, the tenth server’s Blue Brook Guild was completely silent. Everyone silently watched the discussion go on in the world channel.

Don’t look at how the highest among them were only Level 33. The people behind those characters, the senior players in Blue Brook Guild like Changing Spring were all there.

However, Poplar Beach wasn’t there.

After he had left the Arena, he directly logged out of the Heavenly Domain, but didn’t log into his tenth server account.

Even if he was arrogant, right now, he felt too ashamed to meet other guild members.

Lowering Poplar Beach’s arrogance might have been the only reward that Blue Brook Guild received. However, seeing the situation in front of them, Lord Grim’s strength was too ridiculous. It was quite possible that Poplar Beach might have been hurt too much from this match.

“Which of you went and watched it?” Changing Spring asked. Whenever they talked about guild matters, Changing Spring usually had the characters find a place to meet up at. The reason was because their guild leader Changing Spring really wasn’t fond of typing.

“I watched it.” Blue River let out a sigh as he spoke.

“What did you think of it?”

“Pretty much identical to how the world channel is describing it. They’re not exaggerating……. because there’s really isn’t any way to exaggerate it.” Blue River said.

“This Lord Grim really didn’t leave us with anything!” Flying Brushstroke said.

“I think it’s the exact opposite. I think the way he did things actually left us with room to recover.” Blue River said, “If you take a look at the world channel, most of them are discussing about how strong Lord Grim was. There was not anything else being talked about. To us, these results aren’t too bad.”

“Sigh……..” Changing Spring also sighed: “This Lord Grim really isn’t easy to deal with.”

“After our dungeon record was beaten, all the popularity we had recovered dropped again. Today, the number of players who wanted to join our guild fell by 70%…….” Blue River said.

“Line Canyon…… isn’t that the one we said we wouldn’t fight Tyrannical Ambition over?” Changing Spring asked.

“Yeah……”

“Then it looks like the only thing we can do for now is endure.” Changing Spring said somewhat regretfully.

“That…….” Bound Boat had also come to the meeting. In the tenth server, he was second only to Blue River. However, everyone present at the moment were all the seniors in the Heavenly Domain. As a result, Bound Boat clearly seemed smaller; his words also seemed like they were hesitant.

“Oh? Bound Boat, what do you have in mind?” Changing Spring asked. He knew the important players they had sent over to pioneer.

“Maybe we can ask the teams to help us? Even though these are only low-leveled dungeons, which of the current tenth server records are achievable for us? Not just Lord Grim’s records, but that Frost Forest record set by Excellent Dynasty as well! Fortunately, these were made in the new servers. If these were made in the old servers, then these records would have been suspected of being set by pros a long time ago, no?” Bound Boat said.

In the tenth server, there were only records for Frost Forest, Boneyard, and Desolate Land. However, it was just like how Bound Boat had described it. The three records were all records that surpassed their limits. Changing Spring and the others were all at the top of the normal players, yet even they were crushed by Lord Grim’s team. This was a clear and terrifying reality.

“Where exactly did these guys come from?” The background of Lord Grim and these others couldn’t be small. The word pro-level began to spiral around their minds.

“That’s why I say we should look for the experts in the team to help us appraise them.” Bound Boat said.

“Hm. This suggestion truly is quite good.” Changing Spring nodded his head. They weren’t asking them to substitute. They were only asking to chat with the Club’s experts on these incredible records and request for an appraisal. That wouldn’t be difficult to do.

“Alright then. I’m going to go and ask.” Changing Spring decided on this. The people who were participating in the meeting all had weird expressions on their faces. For the pioneering in the new server to be so shocking that they even needed pro-players to come out, this was something they had never even dreamed of before. If they knew that the entire Champion Team Tiny Herb had come to the tenth server for training, their blood pressure would probably shoot up.

“I’ll be leaving first then.” Changing Spring informed everyone. He was also someone who handled things straightforwardly.

After logging out, Changing Spring looked at the time. Right now……. the team should be doing their afternoon practice. Changing Spring ran the Blue Brook Guild in Glory in place of Club Blue Rain. He was just like Chen Yehui in Excellent Era. He could be considered as one of the Club’s official staff members, so he had some say in the Club’s matters.

Changing Spring often came to the team to look around, so he wouldn’t be considered unfamiliar with the pro-players. He’d sometimes even have the chance to compare notes with the team members. Of course, if the pro-players wanted to play two rounds with him for fun, Changing Spring wouldn’t refuse. However, if he went actively look for pro-players to play with him, he would be suspected of wasting their time. Changing Spring understood this.

Changing Spring calculated the time and chose to go at a suitable time. He didn’t have too many restrictions when walking around in the Club. Besides going to the tech team who researched self-made equipment, there wasn’t anywhere he wasn’t allowed to go to.

“Hi Senior Chun!”

Changing Spring had chosen a good time. He arrived just as Team Blue Rain finished practice, a time when everyone was relaxing. When he appeared in front of the entrance, someone saw him and greeted him.

Changing Spring’s real name was Liang Yichun, so the people who were familiar with him called him Senior Chun.

“Hi.” Changing Spring waved his hands at the pro-player that greeted him. The pro-player was a guy called Li Yuan. He was a new player in Blue Rain. He wasn’t as cautious and careful like the majority of new players were. After the young guy joined the team, he was extremely energetic and was always very friendly with everyone. He quickly became familiar with everyone including Changing Spring.

With his greeting, the other pros who hadn’t known that Changing Spring had come turned their heads and looked at him. The majority of the pros nodded their heads as a greeting and then went back to doing whatever they were doing before. However, Yu Wenzhou got up and walked over to him: “Senior Chun’s come over!”

“Yeah, I’m here to take a look……” Changing Spring said politely.

Yu Wenzhou, Team Blue Rain’s team captain. Most of the team captains were also the team’s ace player, but there would obviously be a few exceptions. Blue Rain’s ace player was Huang Shaotian, but their team captain was Yu Wenzhou. Even though Yu Wenzhou’s mechanics weren’t as good as Huang Shaotian’s, his ability in strategy and tactics were extraordinary. Moreover, that Huang Shaotian’s constant chatter pulled down his demeanor. The words of someone who was always talking would feel somewhat frivolous to others.

“You haven’t been here in awhile!” Yu Wenzhou treated him politely as well, seeing that Changing Spring had come to talk with him about something.

Changing Spring also knew that Team Blue Rain’s captain was relatively easy to speak with, unlike Tyrannical Ambition’s Jiang You, who was so hesitant. If Blue Rain’s captain had been so fierce like Han Wenqing, he definitely wouldn’t have immediately logged offline to go look for him.

“Yeah, I’ve been busy. The pioneering in the tenth server!” Changing Spring began to ease into the topic.

“It’s just pioneering. As if you needed to personally lead, right?” Yu Wenzhou chuckled. He knew how the Club’s guild operated in general.

‘But this time’s tenth server is too different!” Changing Spring said very seriously.

“Oh? What do you mean?”

“A bunch of experts suddenly popped up out of nowhere. All of the low-leveled dungeon records that have been set in the tenth server so far are above the all-time records. It looks as if they were all done by pro-players.” Changing Spring said.

“Crash!” A loud crash resounded in the practice room, along with three or four players crying out in alarm: “Huang Shao, are you okay? What happened?”

“It’s nothing. It’s nothing. I slipped, that’s all.” Huang Shaotian said ashen-faced as he supported himself up with his chair. Seeing that Changing Spring was looking at him in astonishment, he hastily waved his hand: “Senior Chun, you’re here! Ha ha ha, long time no see. You’re free today? Have you eaten yet? You probably haven’t eaten, right? Lucky you! It’ll be time to eat soon. You should eat some food before you go!”

“Sure, sure.” Changing Spring repeatedly nodded his head. He didn’t dare say anything too much or else he wouldn’t hear the end of it.

“Do you have a tenth server account card? Let’s take a look at the records!” Yu Wenzhou said.

“I do!” Changing Spring took out a card and gave it to Yu Wenzhou. Of course he had prepared everything before hand.

Yu Wenzhou found a random computer to sit down at and logged into the game. At the same time, without turning his head, he also said: “Shaotian, you should come and look too!”

There wasn’t any response from behind him. Huang Shaotian was wearing his headphones acting as if he hadn’t heard anything. The players beside him pushed him: “Huang Shao, captain’s calling for you!”

“Ah? What is it?” Huang Shaotian took off his headphones and turned around to ask.

“Come over here to look at the tenth server records.” Yu Wenzhou said.

Huang Shaotian had no choice but to get up. As he walked over, he asked: “Tenth server? The new server? What’s there to look at?”

“Woah! The records really are incredible!” Yu Wenzhou had already entered the game and directly clicked on the record leaderboards.

“Shaotian, how do you think these records were made?” Yu Wenzhou asked.

Chapter 183 – Blue Rain Team Captain

After looking at the leaderboards for each of the three dungeons, Yu Wenzhou turned his head to ask Huang Shaotian.

Huang Shaotian stood behind him. He lifted his hand to scratch his chin and shook head: “I haven’t played these dungeons for so long, so I can’t tell just by looking at the time. Do you recognize any of the players who set the record? Is there anything special about them? Do you know what their classes and equipment are?” Huang Shaotian said to Changing Spring.

“Oh…… the key player is Lord Grim.” Changing Spring pointed at the name that appeared in all three leaderboards. Among these, Frost Forest was ranked second on its leaderboard, while Boneyard and Desolate Land were number one on their respective leaderboards.

“What about this person?” Huang Shaotian asked.

。

“This player’s character hasn’t changed classes. He’s an unspecialized character. In addition, the weapon in his hands is really weird. It can change into other weapon forms and use low-leveled skills from all sorts of classes.” Changing Spring said. There was no way to hide the Thousand Chance Umbrella, which was why Ye Xiu never bothered to conceal it. Experts like Blue River, who had seen him in action, had already seen through what it was.

“Oh? So such a weapon exists?” Yu Wenzhou heard this and his interest rose by quite a bit. Before, he had a general idea of why Changing Spring had come, so he was just being polite. But now these words had grabbed his attention.

“This type of weapon is definitely self-made! It sounds like it was made specially for unspecialized characters.” Huang Shaotian said.

“Unspecialized…….” Yu Wenzhou clearly knew about this type of playing style.

“If this is true, then this weapon really would be able to let an unspecialized fully utilize his strengths. The early unspecialized characters were weighed down because switching weapons had a cooldown, which made it so that there were a lot of flaws whenever they tried to combo. They weren’t able to perfectly link together all of the many low-leveled skills. But with this weapon, this issue is solved. Plus, if it has Silver weapon attributes, then the damage output would be even greater than Orange weapons. With a character like this in a team, then their damage output would naturally be a grade higher than the usual teams. This player really is the key character.” Huang Shaotian said.

Yu Wenzhou nodded his head, clearly showing that he agreed with what Huang Shaotian said. He then looked at the other members in Lord Grim’s teams: “What about the others?”

“These three are fixed members in Lord Grim’s teams. One of them is a Battle Mage, one is a Launcher, and there’s also a Brawler. Their skill levels are quite high. The other spot doesn’t seem to be fixed. In Frost Forest, this player is from Tyrannical Ambition. In Boneyard, this Flowing Tree is a Blade Master. At the time, he joined our Blue Brook Guild. He never said anything and then never went online again after setting that record. Finally, this One Inch Ash appeared recently, so we don’t really know much about him.”

“What about this Excellent Dynasty team in Frost Forest?” Yu Wenzhou asked.

Changing Spring immediately told them the situation for this Excellent Dynasty team. This was something they had investigated on before.

“They were clearly substituted players….. This is a new server with new players. There’s no way those types of players could create such a record.” Yu Wenzhou said.

“That’s what I thought as well.” Changing Spring said.

“And these players definitely weren’t ordinary. If you look at the record done by Excellent Dynasty done in Boneyard, this just happened to be done around the time we had our match with Excellent Era. Excellent Era’s vice-captain Liu Hao made numerous low-leveled mistakes in the match. His condition was strangely bad. It looks like this guy ran to the new server and split his attention onto setting these records!” Yu Wenzhou said.

“No way……. For a low-leveled dungeon like this, shouldn’t it be easy for a pro-player to set a record? It shouldn’t go so far as to affect his performance in the match, right?” Changing Spring said.

“This Boneyard record isn’t normal. What do you think Shaotian?” Yu Wenzhou said.

Huang Shaotian nodded his head: “This Boneyard record is no longer a question of skill. It isn’t possible to set this record purely on skill. In the new server, there’s no way they’d have too many good equipment yet, which means that the only way they’d have been able to improve the record would be to create a strategy more outstanding than previous ones.”

“As expected of Huang Shao…….” Changing Spring couldn’t help but gasp in astonishment. They had looked over this record who knew how many times, yet they weren’t able to be certain about such a conclusion. Perhaps only God-level players with incredible judgement like Huang Shaotian would dare be so confident in their answer.

“If you say it like this, then not only was this Excellent Dynasty record substituted in by Liu Hao, he even spent a lot of energy to research a new strategy just for this dungeon. And this was why his condition during the match wasn’t good?” Changing Spring concluded.

“I’m afraid it’s not just that. This guy might not have researched a new strategy, but rather stole a new strategy……..” Yu Wenzhou said.

“What?”

“The records set by the new strategy appeared three times.” Yu Wenzhou tapped the screen as he said, “For two teams to have coincidentally come up with the same strategy at the same time? Look at the first record set by Lord Grim. In this team, there’s a player called Hateful Sword, but after this record was beat by Excellent Dynasty, Lord Grim’s team no longer has a Hateful Sword in it, but a player called Flowing Tree instead. These two characters are of different classes, but in this dungeon, Blade Master’s aren’t any stronger than Berserkers. If the Blade Master player was more skilled than the Berserker player, then why didn’t they just directly use the Blade Master the first time? So the most likely possibility was that this new strategy was researched by Lord Grim. This Berserker Hateful Sword was someone from Excellent Dynasty who had gotten into the team. He then went with them to learn the new strategy and then went back to lead Excellent Dynasty’s players to set a new record. There was obviously no way Lord Grim could look for this Hateful Sword’s help again, which was why he found this Blade Master, Flowing Tree.”

Changing Spring was startled. Yu Wenzhou was able to figure out things he hadn’t even thought of before.

The time the record came out. Excellent Dynasty’s background. The terrible performance of Liu Hao during the match……. Yu Wenzhou had noticed so many small details. This Blue Rain team captain wasn’t just a person who knew how to keep the team together like those on the outside said. This type of judgement and perception wasn’t below Huang Shaotian’s in the slightest. No, he might even be better than Huang Shaotian in this aspect. At least, at this moment, Huang Shaotian hadn’t made such a deduction.

“Team captain, you’ve got to be exaggerating. This sounds like a plot from some fiction novel.” Not only did he not make the deduction, Huang Shaotian even doubted Yu Wenzhou’s deduction.

“Could Liu Hao have gone crazy? He would actually put in so much effort for a dungeon in a new server?” How could Huang Shaotian only have said that? He had to keep going!

“Ha ha, that’s certainly true! That’s why there might be some other special reason that made him place so much importance onto this record. He had directly competed against Lord Grim for Frost Forest. After that, he even infiltrated Lord Grim’s team to spy on them. It seems like he also places a lot of importance on this Lord Grim! To be able to make a pro-player think of him as an enemy, this Lord Grim definitely isn’t any weaker than him. I have a feeling that Liu Hao is well aware who Lord Grim is. His hostile actions seem to be concealing his fear, acknowledgement, and trust. Because of this fear, he ran to spy on them. Because of his acknowledgement, he stole his strategy and directly used it. Because of his trust, he trusted that the strategy being used was already the most optimal choice. There wouldn’t be any strategy better than it.”

Changing Spring’s jaw dropped in astonishment. To be able to make an analysis to such an extent? He couldn’t help but look at Huang Shaotian, who was also listening. He realized that Huang Shaotian wasn’t amazed in the slightest at this. He seemed as calm as ever.

“He really is Huang Shao…….” Changing Spring once again gasped. Perhaps there were many who felt like Huang Shaotian wasn’t calm enough due to his constant chatter, however, in reality, as the most outstanding player in seizing opportunities, Huang Shaotian was completely calm on the inside.

Only with this inner calmness was he able to possess such keen awareness of the battlefield and find the most optimal opportunity to strike.

“That’s why I think that if we want to know who Lord Grim is, then we should just directly call Liu Hao and ask him. Liu Hao’s phone number, I should have it…….” Yu Wenzhou smiled, but then quickly followed: “Oh, I didn’t bring my cellphone with me.” They weren’t allowed to bring their cellphones into the practice room. This was a rule that a lot of Clubs had.

Changing Spring looked forward to it. He looked forward to knowing the answer. He obviously hoped that Yu Wenzhou would be a bit more active. But seeing that Yu Wenzhou didn’t have his cellphone and didn’t intend on going to get it, Changing Spring felt somewhat disappointed. He didn’t dare urge the team captain, but at this moment, maybe he could ask. Just as he was about to speak, he saw Yu Wenzhou patted his pocket and laughed: “Actually, someone who Liu Hao was enemies with, was scared of, was acknowledged by, and trusted. There’s no need to ask. I already know who he is.”

“Who is he?’ Changing Spring blurted out.

“Ye Qiu.” Yu Wenzhou said.

“God Ye Qiu……” Changing Spring didn’t know what to do to express his astonishment.

“Shaotian, have you talked to Ye Qiu recently?” Yu Wenzhou asked.

“Nope, after that guy retired, he just seemed to have evaporated. Maybe he was kidnapped by aliens!” Huang Shaotian said.

“He doesn’t use cellphones, right?” Yu Wenzhou said.

“Yeah.”

“It looks like he was kidnapped by aliens to the tenth server to continue playing Glory…… Unspecialized Lord Grim hm? We might even see him appear in a match again someday!” Yu Wenzhou said.

“…….” Changing Spring had many things he wanted to say, but didn’t know how to start. Yu Wenzhou and Huang Shaotian didn’t seem to have any reaction to such a conclusion. After a few moments of thinking, Yu Wenzhou lifted his head and looked up at the clock on the wall of the practice room. He suddenly stood up.

“It’s time to eat.” Yu Wenzhou said.

“Yeah, yeah. It’s time to eat, it’s time to eat. Come, come, come with us Changing Spring. Do you know where the cafeteria is? I’ll bring you there!” Huang Shaotian put his arm around Changing Spring and dragged him out.

Chapter 184 – That’s a Strength Too?

The Club’s food was quite delicious and for team members, the food was free. Of course, other Club staff could come and eat as well, but they didn’t get to enjoy the same benefits as the team members.

Changing Spring didn’t have those benefits either, however, he followed Huang Shaotian and used his status to get in for free. It was just that he was practically unable to taste the food that went into his mouth. Changing Spring’s mind was still on what Yu Wenzhou had analyzed earlier.

Lord Grim is God Ye Qiu.

This news took a long time for Changing Spring to digest, at least, when compared to his dinner.

In his heart, whether it was him or Blue River, they had already respected Lord Grim. They had recognized that he had a very high skill level, but they had never expected such an outcome.

Ye Qiu…… that was a power at the very peak of Glory! Even though he was retired now, he was still more than enough to tidy up whatever he wanted in game. This could be seen just by how easily Poplar Beach had been tidied up.

If this had taken place during God Ye Qiu’s prime with his Battle God One Autumn Leaf, who knew how terrible Poplar Beach would have been crushed?

Changing Spring originally had a few methods he planned on using to fight against Lord Grim, but after knowing his identity, his heart suddenly dropped.

What should he do now?

Changing Spring felt that the food in front of him tasted like wax. Sitting at the same table were Yu Wenzhou and Huang Shaotian, but the two were casually chatting with each other. They didn’t seem very surprised about Ye Qiu. After all, after thinking about it, they were pro-players as well, so there wasn’t anything too surprising. Ye Qiu had retired, but what was wrong with returning to the game to play? It only affected normal players, who would feel somewhat pressured by God competing with them.

After eating, he decided to leave. Yu Wenzhou and Huang Shaotian didn’t mention Ye Qiu again. Yu Wenzhou was still as friendly as ever and even accompanied him out, but when they parted, he said a few final words: “That Lord Grim, especially his weapon, try and pay more attention to it please!”

“Ah? Oh……” With this sudden mention of Lord Grim, Changing Spring finally responded.

In theory, the team captain didn’t have any power over Changing Spring for in-game guild matters. However, everyone knew that pro-players were the core of the Club. Who wouldn’t take what they said seriously? Changing Spring placed importance on what Yu Wenzhou requested.

“I’ll be going then.” Changing Spring said and then left.

After turning around, Yu Wenzhou saw Huang Shaotian going back to his room and immediately called for him.

“What do you want?” Huang Shaotian replied.

Yu Wenzhou walked over and went into Huang Shaotian’s room along with him.

“What commands do you have, captain?” Huang Shaotian asked.

Yu Wenzhou stood beside a table. He grabbed a pen on the table and began playing with it: “Last time, when we had the match versus Excellent Era, if I remember correctly, you left at night to do something?”

“Huh? There was something like that? That day? Hm hm, let me think……” Huang Shaotian said.

“Was it to go and meet with Ye Qiu?” Yu Wenzhou asked.

Not a peep came out of Huang Shaotian.

“The time you left matches the time when that record was set. The Blade Master on that team, Flowing Tree, was you, right?” Yu Wenzhou said.

“Flowing Tree? Yeah, that name does sound a bit familiar. How could that be? How strange.” Huang Shaotian said.

“Ha ha……” Yu Wenzhou laughed. He didn’t comment on Huang Shaotian’s acting and followed: “What type of weapon is Ye Qiu’s unspecialized weapon?”

Huang Shaotian’s expression immediately turned serious: “Without a doubt, it’s just like I said before, it’s a weapon specially made for unspecialized characters.”

“The attack?”

“Definitely Silver weapon level.”

“Are there any special attributes?”

“I couldn’t tell. It doesn’t look like it has any.”

“Its attack speed?”

“It has the same attack speed for every form. It should have an Attack Speed of 5.”

“What forms does it have?”

“From what I’ve seen, he can use skills from every class.” Huang Shaotian said.

“The level?”

“He probably knows how to upgrade it.” Huang Shaotian said.

“This type of weapon paired with Ye Qiu. It looks like we’ll get a chance to see a true unspecialized.” Yu Wenzhou said with lament.

“But it’ll have to be at least a year later.” Huang Shaotian said.

“Unspecialized huh……” Yu Wenzhou looked out the window as if in deep thought.

Glory Tenth Server.

Changing Spring immediately returned to log into the game. Chilling Nightfall, Flying Brushstroke, and the others hadn’t returned to the Heavenly Domain yet. They were still using the accounts they had borrowed and were waiting for Changing Spring to return with the news.

Blue Brook Guild’s Five Great Experts gathered together once again, along with Blue River’s right hand man, Bound Boat.

“What’d they say?” After seeing Changing Spring, they immediately asked him.

Changing Spring let out a sigh. He had been shocked already. It was their turn now.

“Captain Yu figured out who Lord Grim is.” Changing Spring said.

“Who is he?” Everyone asked.

“Ye Qiu.” Changing Spring pretended to be calm when he said this.

“What?!” Everyone acted as if they hadn’t heard clearly.

“Ye Qiu! Battle God One Autumn Leaf, that Ye Qiu!!” Changing Spring said.

“No way!!!” Flying Brushstroke yelled out in astonishment.

Who was Lord Grim? This was a question they had discussed numerous times ever since they had learned about him. But even their most outrageous speculations couldn’t compare to the truth.

Lord Grim was actually God Ye Qiu!

Blue River didn’t know why, but he felt somewhat excited. Even though Huang Shaotian was his favorite pro-player, the mysterious God Ye Qiu was someone who was worthy of worshipping as well! Seeing Lord Grim on his friends list, Blue River couldn’t help but feel like saying a few words to him. At this moment, he had already forgotten that he was the main reason that caused them so much trouble in the tenth server.

“So he was actually God Ye Qiu all along. I never would have thought of that. What should we do then?” Luckily, Bound Boat was there. This issue pulled Blue River back in.

God Ye Qiu would be a difficult opponent!

Blue River was finally aware of the cruel reality. However, if it was because they were against God Ye Qiu, then retreating wouldn’t be shameful, right? Blue River suddenly felt a lot more relaxed.

At this moment, Changing Spring began to talk: “Even though we know that our opponent is God Ye Qiu, there’s no change in plans. We just have to understand how grim our circumstances are…… Against God Ye Qiu, there’s nothing we can do about setting the records. On how we’re going to fight against him. This isn’t a matter for our Blue Brook Guild. The ambitious and able guilds in the tenth server will need to rally together……. Even if it’s for giving materials, we should still rally…….”

Changing Spring’s final words made even himself not know whether to laugh or cry.

“I think if everyone knows that he’s God Ye Qiu, then there wouldn’t be anymore pointless fights.” Blue River said.

“The problem is, we all believe this, but if you say this to the other guilds, will they believe us?” Changing Spring asked.

Everyone was silent. They understood how suspicious and cautious other guilds were towards each other.

“Since it turned out to be like this, why don’t we think about this some more. If we know Lord Grim’s identity, is there any way we can use this to our advantage?” Changing Spring said.

“The rest will depend on what Blue Bridge decides to do.” Changing Spring suddenly changed the topic.

“Me?”

“Right. After all, these are all tenth server matters!” Changing Spring said.

“Right! Blue Bridge, you can do it!” Flying Brushstroke said.

“To have God Ye Qiu as an opponent, it was nice knowing you.” Chilling Nightfall said.

“We’ve got nothing else to do, so we’ll be going back first?” Dawn of Ice said.

“Yeah, you guys can go back.” Changing Spring answered, “Moonlight Forest hasn’t been run yet, right?”

“Not yet!”

“Okay, we’ll run it tonight.”

“Should we go now?”

“Let’s go!”

“Blue Bridge, good luck! Remember to pay attention to Lord Grim’s weapon.” Changing Spring urged.

“F*ck! You guys…….” Blue River hadn’t finished, when the four went offline one after another.

“These guys are too irresponsible……” Blue Bridge was speechless. As soon as these guys saw that the tenth server’s difficult problem was because of God Ye Qiu, they all acted as if there was nothing wrong and all ran off.

Bound Boat could only force a smile.

“What do you think we should do?” Blue River asked.

“Actually, the guild leader’s already told us what we can do.” Bound Boat said.

“Oh?”

“Knowing Lord Grim’s identity is the one thing we can use.” Bound Boat said.

“Why do I think that all that gives us is more pressure?” Blue River said.

“Pressure can be used! Other guilds might not have this type of pressure, so they’ll still face him directly. As for us, we’ll have to be more careful. We won’t try this sort of thing anymore. We’ll see if we can take advantage of what others do.” Bound Boat said.

“Woah, if you say it like this….. then you’re saying, we should run away from battles against God Ye Qiu and sit back and watch God Ye Qiu clean up these other arrogant guys?’ Blue River said.

“I think that’s what the guild leader was saying.” Bound Boat said.

“That’s the only thing that can be done.” Blue River thought. Was that an advantage? It sounds like we are killing the other guilds with a borrowed knife. But in reality, the knife did whatever it wanted to and we can only follow it with our tail tucked between our legs and pick up the leftovers.

“Next up is Line Canyon. What do you think Tyrannical Ambition will do?” Bound Boat said, but he didn’t hear Blue River respond.

“Uh, are you there?” Bound Boat asked.

“I say.” Blue River was still here.

“What?”

“If I go ask Lord Grim for a signature, would that be bad?”

“F*ck….. what a loser! Even though he’s God Ye Qiu, he’s also a difficult opponent for us!” Bound Boat said.

“Yeah, that’s what I think too. It’s too shameful.” Blue River said.

Bound Boat was speechless.

Chapter 185 – It’s Unfortunate That His Hands Are Handicapped

Lord Grim was Ye Qiu. The tremors brought by this were minimal. Blue River and Bound Boat were the only two who knew of this in the tenth server’s Blue Brook Guild. After discussing it, the two decided to keep this a secret.

The guilds who didn’t know this would continue fighting against Lord Grim. Standing on the sidelines and watching them strike at a stone with eggs; what was wrong with that?

Blue River stopped playing and instead went to the forums to enjoy the videos of Poplar Beach getting destroyed.

Poplar Beach’s name was very distinct. Even though Poplar Beach always made Blue River resentful, Poplar Beach was, after all, a relatively famous player in the game and was one of their Blue Brook Guild’s experts. Being crushed like this didn’t only embarrass himself, but the who Blue Brook Guild as well. The players from the enemy guilds would surely use this to laugh at Blue Brook Guild.

The reason Blue River was on the forums was because this video had been posted on one of the categories in the forum: Heavenly Domain.

There was a Heavenly Domain in the game.

There was a Heavenly Domain in the forums.

These two Heavenly Domains were both places bustling with noise.

These Heavenly Domain people clearly didn’t harbor any good intentions. In the comments, they praised the exceptional skill of Chasing Haze on the surface, but their main way of doing so was by using Poplar Beach as the center.

“Does everyone know who Poplar Beach is? He’s an expert who’s not any weaker than Blue Brook Guild’s Five Great Experts. But to have been beaten like this by Chasing Haze, how skilled do you think this Chasing Haze is?”

This was more or less the method they used. Blue River looked at the later comments. These people’s plots had succeeded. There were many who were looking down and laughing at Poplar Beach. Speaking of this, it was mostly because Poplar Beach’s reputation wasn’t good. He had made a name for himself in the Heavenly Domain through his arrogance. His fall caused many players to attack him like a dead dog. Many of these attacks brought Blue Brook Guild along with him, which made Blue River extremely unhappy.

This video had already exploded into popularity. Those, in the Heavenly Domain and the other servers, who didn’t understand the dispute in the tenth server had already found Chasing Haze in-game.

That day at dinner, Chen Guo scolded Ye Xiu for quite a lengthy amount of time.

She practically couldn’t play the game anymore. Her in-game friends were all asking her how she suddenly become so good. She was only able to explain it to them one by one, which was already annoying enough. But her friends continued to bother her by asking which expert had borrowed the account.

Besides this, there were also numerous strangers who asked her to mentor them. There were random guilds pestering her to join their guilds too. Even weirder was that in the afternoon, there were two people who claimed they were pro-player scouts. They asked her as if she were under an interrogation how old she was, how long she had played Glory, where she was from, and whether she had any interest in becoming a pro-player. This made Chen Guo so angry that she returned with an “I’m not the account’s owner” and then logged out of the game.

Thinking about how she had actually said “I’m not the account’s owner”, Chen Guo felt sad.

“It’s all because of you!” Chen Guo shouted. The rice in her mouth almost sprayed onto Ye Xiu’s face.

“My bad, my bad. Boss, you should drink some soup. Don’t choke.” Ye Xiu immediately handed a bowl of soup over to Chen Guo.

Chen Guo took it and drank two sips. Her anger receded a bit.

“Actually, you can’t completely blame this on me.” Ye Xiu took the opportunity to explain.

“Hm?”

“The opponent was too weak. I……”

“Get the f*ck out of here!!!” Chen Guo’s soup splashed. Amongst everyone’s cries of fear, Ye Xiu swiftly slipped out of the Internet Cafe.

“And you’re laughing, Little Tang!!” Chen Guo said angrily. Tang Rou ate her dinner behind the reception desk. As of right now she was carrying her lunch box. Even though her back was facing Chen Guo, her shoulders were moving up and down. She was clearly laughing uncontrollably.

“I’m not laughing.” Tang Rou quickly stuffed rice into her mouth to try and stifle her laughter.

Ye Xiu had run out, but hadn’t come back. At nine o’clock, Chen Guo ran out of the Internet Cafe to look around, but didn’t see him coming back, so she returned and muttered to Tang Rou: “Where’d he run off to? Could he have crashed into a tree?”

“If that happened, then I’m sure you’d be happy!” Tang Rou said.

“Yeah! I’d be really happy.” Chen Guo said as she continued to glance outside repeatedly.

“What are you doing?” Seeing that Tang Rou wasn’t busy at the front desk, she stretched her neck to look inside and saw Tang Rou studying a guide again. Chen Guo was helpless. Should I go find a random open computer and play? I tried it before, but it was still so noisy. Maybe I should go look at a guide or watch a video? Chen Guo opened up a web page and saw that the lead story was a video and analysis of Poplar Beach getting crushed by Chasing Haze. Chen Guo couldn’t resist clicking on it and playing it over and over again.

The time was nearing 11, but there was still no sign of Ye Xiu.

“Where’d this guy go? He doesn’t have a phone either.” Chen Guo went in and out of the cafe.

“Relax. He’s an adult.” Tang Rou said.

“A shut-in. He probably ran far away and got lost.” Chen Guo said.

“Even if he’s lost, there’s still the police. Don’t worry about him!” Tang Rou said.

“Who’s worrying about him! It’s almost 11 o’clock already. If he doesn’t come back soon, then what about the night shift?” Chen Guo said.

“Aren’t I still here?” Tang Rou said, “You should go to sleep!”

“Okay….” Chen Guo looked outside once again, but finally went up the stairs.

“If he comes back, should I send you a text?” Tang Rou asked.

“Okay……” Chen Guo answered and went up.

Not long after Chen Guo left, the employees who got off at 11 all left. At this moment, Ye Xiu appeared at the entrance of the Internet Cafe like a ghost. After looking inside, he creeped up to the reception desk. Once he saw that only Tang Rou was there, he relaxed.

“Where’s the boss?” Ye Xiu stood straight and lit up a cigarette.

“She went to sleep.” When Tang Rou saw Ye Xiu, after answering him, she took out her cellphone.

“Where’d you run off to?” Tang Rou asked Ye Xiu as she sent a text to Chen Guo.

“I just took a stroll around the area! Out of 100, how many points is boss’s anger worth now?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Hard to say. When you weren’t here, she was at a 0. But now that you’re here, she’s probably at a 100 again.” Tang Rou said.

“It really wasn’t my fault.” Ye Xiu said.

“But you’re such a taunter.” Tang Rou said.

This sister had already begun using a few gaming terms in real life. After typing out the text, she pressed send.

Her phone quickly rang. Tang Rou opened it and chuckled.

“Boss said that you were late, so there won’t be any pay for today.” Tang Rou showed Ye Xiu the text.

“Fine! It doesn’t matter if I don’t get pay as long as I have food and shelter.” Ye Xiu said.

“Should I reply with what you said?” Tang Rou asked.

“Don’t you dare.” Ye Xiu was speechless.

“Ha ha, you should come in. I’m going over there.” Tang Rou got up and gave her seat at the front desk to Ye Xiu. She went to her usual all-nighter seat.

The two logged into the game. Just as Ye Xiu logged into Lord Grim, he received a message: “You’ve been exposed.”

Ye Xiu was puzzled. He replied: “Who are you?”

“F*CK F*CK F*CK F*CK! It’s me, Shaotian!” Huang Shaotian was sad.

“Oh, it’s you!” Ye Xiu thought of Flowing Tree, that low-leveled account that Huang Shaotian had used.

“What’s been exposed?’ Ye Xiu asked.

“Your records were too astonishing. Blue Brook Guild even came by today to look for the team for help. I’m sure you know how amazing our team captain is. In just a few moments, he deduced that you were Lord Grim.” Huang Shaotian replied.

“Oh? How’d he deduce it?” Ye Xiu asked.

The process would clearly take a long time, but who was Huang Shaotian? He could be afraid of anything else, but he wasn’t afraid of talking too much. His hands moved swiftly as he quickly narrated the entire process to Ye Xiu.

“Oh, so it was like that! But if I’ve been exposed, there’s nowhere for you to hide either!” Ye Xiu said.

“Yeah, he also deduced that I was Flowing Tree.” Huang Shaotian said.

“Tsk tsk, Wenzhou really is quite amazing. It’s just too bad that his hand is handicapped.” Ye Xiu said.

“He’s standing right behind me…….” Huang Shaotian replied.

“Then his hand isn’t handicapped?” Ye Xiu said.

“Captain…..” Huang Shaotian turned his head to look at Yu Wenzhou with an innocent expression.

Yu Wenzhou only laughed: “It’s the truth. My hands really are handicapped.”

“Your trash talk has no effect on our team captain.” Huang Shaotian replied.

“Yeah, that’s why I said he’s amazing. If his hands weren’t handicapped, then he really would be an extremely difficult opponent to deal with!” Ye Xiu said.

Huang Shaotian was helpless and turned his head to Yu Wenzhou.

“The handicapped person would like to compare notes with him. Ask him if he wants to come.” Yu Wenzhou laughed.

Huang Shaotian conveyed the message. Ye Xiu quickly replied: “Come! Which account?”

“I’ll just use this one!” After a short moment, the reply came.

“Oh, you’ve already switched?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Yeah!”

“Free Field, whoever gets there first makes the room.” Ye Xiu said.

“Room 45178, password 159.” Yu Wenzhou replied.

“How long have you been waiting!” Ye Xiu replied. His Lord Grim hastily rushed towards the Arena.

Enter, Ready, Begin.

The map was the most common small ring. Flowing Tree stood at one corner.

“Hi!” After Lord Grim entered, Ye Xiu greeted.

“Hi! I heard you’re a manager at an Internet Cafe now?” Yu Wenzhou replied. The character Flowing Tree drew his sword and rushed forward.

“Yeah. For people like us, besides playing games, what else can we do?” Ye Xiu laughed. Lord Grim also swung his Thousand Chance Umbrella. The umbrella transformed into the Battle Lance form. After dodging the attack, he stabbed forward with his lance.

“A Battle Lance with an Attack Speed of 5; How difficult to deal with. Even your Evil Annihilation didn’t have that high of an Attack Speed right?” Yu Wenzhou said.

“It’s just plain stats.” Ye Xiu’s hands hadn’t stopped. He followed up with a few skills as well as a few normal attacks. Yu Wenzhou’s Flowing Tree dodged left and right. There wasn’t any chance for him to counter attack.

“Are you preparing to return with an unspecialized?” Yu Wenzhou was still talking.

“I hope this time the company won’t mess things up.” Ye Xiu said.

“Ha ha, good luck!”

“I need luck to beat you?” Ye Xiu laughed.

“Sometimes, I really admire you guys with your crazy hand speeds.” Yu Wenzhou regretted. Because his Flowing Tree wasn’t able to keep up, he was finally hit under Lord Grim’s relentless attacks.

“If you also had this type of hand speed, how could there be any contest?” Ye Xiu wasn’t polite though and continued to attack.

Chapter 186 – An Unspecialized Character’s False Combos

When comboing, the numerous skills an unspecialized possessed was a huge advantage. No other class had so many short cooldown skills. Of course, this also meant that using them was more complicated.

In order to do the same amount of damage as a single high-leveled skill did, unspecialized characters would need to chain several skills. Moreover, there couldn’t be any mistakes. Unspecialized characters were actually quite a difficult class.

However, to Ye Xiu, who had played Glory for ten years, his mechanics were as precise as a machine.

His opponent Yu Wenzhou was also an absolute expert in the professional scene though. To be comboed until death, that was something that would only happen to someone like Tang Rou and Poplar Beach.

Even under the relentless attacks, Yu Wenzhou was able to find an opportunity.

With a swing, a cold light flashed and Flowing Tree used Sword Draw. The sword aura flew in an arc towards Lord Grim.

Lord Grim’s Thousand Chance Umbrella shook and a Dragon Tooth thrust forward at Flowing Tree.

Two blood blossoms flew out into the air at the same time. Flowing Tree had been hit by Dragon Tooth. Lord Grim had been cut by Sword Draw.

Characters that were hit by Dragon Tooth would be briefly stunned. Characters that were cut by Sword Draw would fly backwards. However, while flying back, Lord Grim’s Thousand Chance Umbrella transformed into a Gun Form. A burst of flame shot out from the tip of his umbrella and Anti-Tank Missiles shot out. The three Anti-Tank Missiles exploded into a blazing flame, burning Flowing Tree from top to bottom.

Lord Grim used Quick Recover as he landed on the ground. He flipped over and stood up. His hands continued to fire, attacking from afar. Even though Flowing Tree’s Sword Draw had done damage to Lord Grim, it hadn’t interrupted Ye Xiu’s offense.

The situation didn’t change much. Yu Wenzhou had been able to find an opportunity several times, but he had no way of taking back the initiative. Ye Xiu had been able to adjust to Yu Wenzhou’s counter attacks every time, quickly changing his path and staying on the offensive.

The constantly changing combos didn’t seem to go on for very long, but the control and pressure put on by them couldn’t be ignored. Moreover, many attacks were hit in quick succession. However, these attacks weren’t considered as combos by the system, so they didn’t count towards the total.

These attacks may not have been counted towards the combo by the system, but in actual battle, they could be used to chain attacks, which was why players called them “False Combos”. It was possible to avoid false combos, but players couldn’t play perfectly, so they would sometimes fail to dodge these attacks for various reasons.

(TLC: Combos are strings of attacks that cannot be dodged or blocked if the first hit connects. “False combos” are similar to combos, except they can be dodged or blocked, so they are technically not true combos and thus aren’t counted by the system.)

In this match, even though Yu Wenzhou wasn’t completely powerless like Tang Rou or Poplar Beach were, he was still struggling. But even in this situation, the two were still doing two things at once, fighting while chatting. If a normal player was watching on the side, he definitely wouldn’t believe that it was possible to chat with such liveliness in such a high-skill fight.

In the end, the launched Flowing Tree was hit by a Falling Flower Palm and then a Sword Draw. The last sliver of health fell and Yu Wenzhou lost in the end.

“You won.” Yu Wenzhou said.

“Very normal.” Ye Xiu laughed.

“The advantages of an unspecialized really are clear. Plus, you have that mysterious weapon. However, the higher the levels, the weaker they become.” Yu Wenzhou said.

“Yeah….. What do you think the limit is?” Ye Xiu asked.

“To be honest, I don’t think there’s any point discussing unspecialized characters. There are too many difficult requirements that have to be met in order to play them well. First of all, without that weapon in your hand, there’s no way you’d be so oppressive. Next, only you can fully utilize the advantages of an unspecialized. For this specific class, there’s only meaning if these conditions can be satisfied.” Yu Wenzhou said.

“Right now, they’re all satisfied.” Ye Xiu said.

“With all of the conditions you’ve met, I think that at Level 70, the advantages of an unspecialized will still be greater than the lack of high-damage and high-level skills. Remember, this is only if you have a weapon like yours! But let’s say that Glory raises the level cap from Level 70. Level 95. The limit is Level 95. At that level, even if it’s you, unspecialized won’t have any value.” Yu Wenzhou said.

“Woah, you thought the same as me. How unfortunate!” Ye Xiu sighed.

“If this was a bit earlier and you caught up with the Level 50 era, then your unspecialized would be extremely strong. It would have been considered a BUG.” Yu Wenzhou said.

“Right now, it’s not too late yet.” Ye Xiu said.

“However…… After this season, Glory won’t have raised the level cap in three years.” Yu Wenzhou said.

“Yeah….. it might be soon.” Ye Xiu said.

“Level 75? Level 80?…… unspecialized will grow weaker as the other classes gain more skills.” Yu Wenzhou said.

“But it’ll at least be in the acceptable range. Do you think I’ll still be able to play until the day the level cap reaches Level 95?” Ye Xiu said.

“If you only play like this in the tenth server, what isn’t possible?” Yu Wenzhou laughed.

“Ha, you’re right.” Ye Xiu also laughed.

“Another round?” Yu Wenzhou asked.

“No need. I won’t let you see my strength clearly.” Ye Xiu said.

“Did you not use your full strength?” Yu Wenzhou asked.

“Of course, I’m old. I need to take care of myself.” Ye Xiu said.

“Then I guess that’s it!” Yu Wenzhou chuckled and then left the field. After the two characters bumped into each other again outside of the Arena, Ye Xiu said bye and then left.

“What do you think?” Yu Wenzhou turned his head to ask Huang Shaotian.

“He did a total of 21 False Combos.” Huang Shaotian said.

“He really knows what my weaknesses are.” Yu Wenzhou said. Hand speed. This was Yu Wenzhou’s fatal weakness. As a result, in this type of fight, his hand speed was incapable of keeping up with his opponent’s movements. His character would move too slowly, making it so that attacks that could have been avoided weren’t, which in the end, became false combos.

“Yeah.” Huang Shaotian nodded his head and then said, “He knows all the weakness of all his opponents in the Alliance. If I was his opponent, then he wouldn’t have use so many false combos.”

“If he wasn’t an unspecialized, he also wouldn’t be able to put out so many false combos.” Yu Wenzhou said, “If you had been playing under the same circumstances, then how many of those 21 false combos would you have been able to dodge?”

Huang Shaotian stared blankly.

“You should look at the recordings again.” Yu Wenzhou got up and patted Huang Shaotian, “The unspecialized character’s unpredictable and complex style creates these constant false combos…….”

After Yu Wenzhou left, Huang Shaotian returned to in front of his computer. He logged out of the game and opened up the recording app, bringing up the recording of the fight with Yu Wenzhou versus Ye Xiu.

21 false combos, how many could he have dodged?

When he was watching the fight, Huang Shaotian really hadn’t considered this issue. The two had been fighting very quickly, so Huang Shaotian didn’t have time to think of that. Now that he had looked at the recording, Huang Shaotian played it again except this time, he imagine that he was the one playing against Ye Xiu.

If it was him, it would have turned differently here…..

First, he noticed the difference in hand speed. There were a few places that he could have done better. Even though he probably wouldn’t have been able to win against the enormous advantage of an unspecialized, he could have at least played more beautifully than Yu Wenzhou.

But, these 21 false combos……

After counting them out one by one, Huang Shaotian began to sweat.

21 false combos. If he were the one playing, it might not have played out like that. However, when he imagined himself playing, Huang Shaotian discovered that of these 21 false combos, he would have only been able to dodge 4 of them.

4!!!

This was something Huang Shaotian hadn’t expected.

The difference between his hand speed and Yu Wenzhou’s was quite large. Huang Shaotian had originally thought that these false combos sent to Yu Wenzhou were done to bully him, but he now discovered that these 21 false combos wasn’t as simple as taking advantage of Yu Wenzhou’s weakness.

Huang Shaotian recovered and played the recording again.

F*ck!

After watching it again, Huang Shaotian couldn’t help but curse.

3 times!!

The number of false combos he could have dodged was actually three. He had made an oversight on one of them. That false combo looked easy to dodge from a spectator’s perspective, but in the actual battle, Lord Grim had attacked from Flowing Tree’s dead angle. That attack was a sneak attack with a 100% chance of succeeding. Even if it hadn’t hit, the many attacks after it would definitely have hit out a false combo.

For someone so perceptive as him to have made an oversight, that only showed how sneaky and hidden that attack was. It was just that against someone with such a weakness in hand speed like Yu Wenzhou, there was no need to use such a complicated attack.

How many of these tricks was this guy hiding?

Huang Shaotian though. A cold chill went down his spine. He once again studied Lord Grim’s fighting style. He wanted to carefully analyze how many hidden attacks were made.

Soon after, he discovered another terrifying reality.

Even for a God-level character like him, he truly lacked too much experience towards these false combos done by Lord Grim.

Falling Flower Palm followed by a Sword Draw……

In a one on one match, he had never seen such a combo before.

Lord Grim’s numerous combos and false combos, these sort of chaining attacks, could be considered as coordination.

The coordination done by several classes was being done by a single character. The more Huang Shaotian thought, the stronger this feeling.

Flowing Tree’s opponent wasn’t a single person, but rather two, three……. or perhaps even more, but it couldn’t be seen in this match because…… the opponent hadn’t used his full strength!

If he had gone all out, what would the result be? Huang Shaotian was very curious about this question, so he quickly logged into the game.

Chapter 187 – Can’t Find a Chance

In the Heavenly Domain, a very common friend notification rang. However, after looking at the name, many players immediately grew excited.

Troubling Rain!

The character who had come online was impressively Troubling Rain, a god-like character known as the Sword Saint.

No matter how amazing an account was, it came from the game. This was why accounts in the game as well as accounts in the Alliance could be searched. For characters that were liked, who knew how many players asked to be their friend. Some characters directly refused them, while some required them to identify themselves, and a select few directly added them.

Unless the character was the type to directly refuse them, it wasn’t impossible to add a pro God as a friend.

In the game, the number of players who were Troubling Rain’s friends weren’t few. So when his name popped up, many players immediately took note of it. Quite a few bravely sent their greetings to the God.

“Oops, I forgot to hide myself…….” The continuous message prompts made Huang Shaotian’s eyes go blurry, so he hastily logged out.

Because of his special status, his short-lived appearance instantly brought a lot of attention.

Troubling Rain had gone online! This news was already being discussed in the world channel.

A pro-player’s character was being played in game? This type of occurrence wasn’t anything new. In the Heavenly Domain’s Arena, pro-players would frequently play a few rounds. Many normal players had the experience of playing against a pro-level player. However, God-level characters like Troubling Rain truly hadn’t appeared in the Arena for a long time. Pro-players didn’t use the in-game Arena for practice. The game company specially provided them with an environment with which to play in. Apart from this, they also had map editors, setting editors; they could design their own maps with which to practice certain things. The game? These types of top-tier accounts rarely appeared in the game.

While the players were talking about Troubling Rain in the world channel, Huang Shaotian quietly logged into the game, making himself invisible to his friends. Even though many still sent messages, Huang Shaotian calmly acted like he wasn’t there.

But the name on top of his head couldn’t be hidden, and the name Troubling Rain still was capable of causing a lot of wide-eyes. So he went to a small town in a normal server after leaving the Heavenly domain to be away from the prying eyes.

His journey through could have been considered as smooth. Huang Shaotian entered the small town and went directly to the Arena. He set up a room in the Fixed Field. But he began to sweat after opening his friends list.

Troubling Rain and Lord Grim weren’t in the same server. Lord Grim wasn’t in the Heavenly Domain either, so he couldn’t add him as a friend.

Helpless, he could only alt-tab out of the game and open up QQ. He didn’t care whether Ye Xiu really wasn’t on there or if he was faking it and sent him a few messages. However, there was no response.

Just as Huang Shaotian was feeling helpless, he suddenly discovered that Su Mucheng was on, so he immediately sent her a message.

Through this, he was finally able to connect to Ye Xiu. Huang Shaotian waited bitterly for a long time. Su Mucheng finally returned with a reply: “He won’t be playing. He doesn’t have time. He’s about to go dungeon.”

“Dungeon? Which dungeon?” Huang Shaotian asked.

“He’ll probably go to Line Canyon first.” Su Mucheng said.

“F*ck!!” Huang Shaotian felt depressed! What status did he have? How could he be less important than a stupid dungeon like Line Canyon! Fine…… Huang Shaotian had no choice but to admit defeat. To be able to fight with an expert like him, such an opportunity would be extremely hard to come by for a normal player, but to Ye Qiu, this wasn’t anything special.

“Ask him to come fight with me! I’m using my main account! My main account! I’ve opened a Fixed Field, so I won’t be bullying him. Let me see how strong this unspecialized is.” Huang Shaotian chattered.

”

But Su Mucheng automatically replied: “In the middle of a dungeon……”

“Hey hey hey!!!”

“In the middle of a dungeon……”

“Su Mucheng, you have no future! You talk in the same way as him!!! You only need to pass on what I’m saying to him! Did you pass what I said to him?” Huang Shaotian quickly typed out.

“In the middle of a dungeon…….”

“Hey! I do what I want to do, it’s none of your business!” Su Mucheng had clearly been looking at the chat and suddenly replied to Huang Shaotian’s taunts.

No future? Same? Huang Shaotian’s words didn’t make her mad, but they rather suited her quite well.

Huang Shaotian continued to roar, completely displaying his talkative personality. Unfortunately, they couldn’t move Su Mucheng and all he received were “In the middle of a dungeon…..” automatic replies.

Helpless, Huang Shaotian got off his Troubling Rain and went onto Flowing Tree. This account had Lord Grim as his friend, so as soon as he got on he spammed “Hey hey hey hey hey”.

“What?” Ye Xiu calmly replied.

“PK! PK! PK! PK! PK!” Huang Shaotian shouted.

“I’m in a dungeon!” Ye Xiu said.

“What dungeon!! If you still have any pro sense in you, how could running a dungeon be something you should be doing? Hurry up and come to the Arena. You need a high-skilled opponent to help you maintain your condition.” Huang Shaotian said.

“In the middle of a dungeon……”

“You two are so shameful!!!” Huang Shaotian almost flipped the table. He wasn’t easily irritated on stage. But in private, he was more carefree, so there was no need to control his emotions.

“I’m in a dungeon right now. Wait until I’m free!” Ye Xiu said.

Huang Shaotian was helpless. He could only go offline and watch the recording again.

In game, Ye Xiu and the others really were dungeoning.

Line Canyon was a dungeon record they could already try and challenge. This dungeon was a Level 30-33 one. There wasn’t any large five-level equipment or skill difference, so the levels weren’t as significant. It was similar to that time’s Level 25 versus Level 27 run at Boneyard.

Ye Xiu’s five-man team had good equipment and after the addition of Qiao Yifan, they no longer had any weaknesses. They completely had the ability to contest with the elite teams of the big guilds.

And this time, after Blue Brook Guild’s Blue River found out who Lord Grim was, he had already prepared a deal. Now, they were figuring out how to conduct the negotiation. In this dungeon record, the guild who was in the most troublesome position was Tyrannical Ambition.

Blue Brook Guild was their warning.

Blue Brook Guild had tried to compete against Lord Grim for the record, but were stepped on in the end. There didn’t seem to be any hopes in turning that over. Blue Brook Guild’s carefully established power had fallen and for now, they had no way of climbing back up. And for Tyrannical Ambition? The effects from the previous blow to them still remained. The number of players who were applying to their guild was declining, but they still had a chance. Line Canyon was the place where they could prove themselves.

But, Lord Grim….. how were they going to deal with this huge mountain?

After witnessing Blue Brook Guild’s miserable state, Tyrannical Ambition’s guild leader Jiang You decided to bravely go to the Club for help as well.

But when he got to the practice room, he happened to come at a time when the team captain Han Wenqing was reprimanding the team members. Besides his criticizing shouts in the practice room, there were no other sounds. No one dared to speak out, how could Jiang You dare to go up?

Jiang You had waited for the session to end before cautiously moving forward. But once he saw Han Wenqing’s strict glare, Jiang You’s mustered up courage suddenly disappeared. He pretended like he was just passing by and slipped away.

No good……. even if he went to the Club to ask the experts for help, he couldn’t go directly to the captain, Han Wenqing. It’d be better to go look for the vice-captain Zhang Xinjie!

After pacing back and forth outside of the practice room, he finally decided on this.

Zhang Xinjie was also a famous player in the Alliance. As Tyranny’s vice-captain, he wasn’t a person who just offered sympathy after Han Wenqing’s reprimanding. Zhang Xinjie was solemn, strict, and precise. He was the current record-holder in the Alliance for the least number of mistakes on average in a match.

Zhang Xinjie was publicly recognized as more outstanding than any other God-level character in this area, showing just how serious his style was.

For a serious person like him, Jiang You believed that he would have an appropriate solution. At least, he wouldn’t be like Han Wenqing and start shouting at him. Zhang Xinjie was serious, while Han Wenqing was stubborn.

Jiang You left first and prepared to look for a chance. In short, after looking at what happened to Blue Brook Guild, he knew only using their in-game experts wouldn’t be good enough. Jiang You completely recognized this.

In game, the first-string teams in the big guilds were already Level 33. They were currently looking to set the final record for Line Canyon. Even though they knew about the large mountain that was Lord Grim, they also knew that they still had the chance to set a record before the limit was reached. Even if the record wouldn’t last until the very end, they could still appear on TV and earn experience as well as Purple equipment rewards.

Today, Line Canyon’s record had been made with a time of 30:41:12. Afterwards, it hadn’t been broken. But right now, the tenth server were mostly paying attention to that match between Poplar Beach and Chasing Haze. Not many people noticed this dungeon besides the big guilds.

Jiang You put this record in his eyes. If he had experts from the Heavenly Domain come, then they’d definitely be able to break it. But, what about Lord Grim’s team? Where was their limit? What were they doing now? At midnight, when the dungeon entries refreshed, Jiang You quietly pondered.

Chapter 188 – Difficult to Say

“Information from Line Canyon has arrived. Lord Grim and his team went to Line Canyon. That One Inch Ash who set the record with them at Desolate Land the other day is there as well.” After Cold Night received the info, he sent it over to guild leader Jiang You. Jiang You logged into the Elementalist Crowd Lover he used last time and began directing work in the tenth server.

In the afternoon, Jiang You went to the Club, but didn’t get anything done. When he returned, he said he saw Han Wenqing and was too afraid to talk. Cold Night understood him well, extremely well.

He had also had the opportunity to see Han Wenqing with his own eyes. He truly was a person who made your heart chill. If he had been taking a night stroll and ran into him, the other side wouldn’t even have to say anything and he’d give him his wallet……..

“The current record isn’t the limit. If any big guild had their elite experts go all out, then they’d all be able to reach the limit. But looking at the previous records, Lord Grim’s team clearly has the ability to exceed this limit. Although they aren’t yet Level 33, with their skill, they should already be able to compete with us.” Jiang You analyzed.

“Yeah.” Cold Night agreed with this analysis: “If they set an extremely fast record right now, then things would be difficult for us. We’d have no way of taking back the record and it would be too late to negotiate with them. From now on, I don’t think any guild will ask them to substitute in.”

“We won’t, but that might not be true for other guilds. This is the most difficult part.” Jiang You laughed bitterly.

“Others?” Cold Night doubted.

“Our guild needs the dungeon records to show our strength, but some other guilds might not. And for Lord Grim, there’s no difference between earning items from them or us…….”

“But other than our big guilds, who else is able to pay his price?” Cold Night said.

“Four Scarlet Moon Parts….. do you still not understand?” Jiang You said.

Jiang You understood. Lord Grim was willing to set the price at four Scarlet Moon parts. What did that mean? It meant that Lord Grim’s price depended on the buyer. Big guilds might not feel like it was fair, but they had no choice. The initiative was all on the other side’s hands. Being bought with four Scarlet Moon parts by Full Moon Guild was a show of his attitude.

“Would you like me to contact him so we can discuss the records?” Cold Night said.

“Oh? What are you planning on saying?” Jiang You asked.

“Uh, we’re still thinking about the conditions and we hope he’ll stay put for now?” Cold Night said.

“Hm…… you can try it. Let’s see if we can let him drag things out.” Jiang You said.

“Huh……” At this moment, Cold Night suddenly cried out in astonishment.

“What is it?”

“I received a message.” Cold Night said.

“What message? From Lord Grim?”

“No, from Excellent Dynasty.” Cold Night said.

“Excellent Dynasty? What’d they say?” Jiang You was surprised.

“They want to talk with us face to face.” Cold Night said.

Jiang You furrowed his brows. Looking at the two guild’s backgrounds, Excellent Dynasty and Tyrannical Ambition were absolute enemies. This enmity was even greater than the enmity between Tiny Herb and Blue Rain. Tiny Herb’s and Blue Rain’s enmity started from season six playoffs, when Team Blue Rain defeated Team Tiny Herb, while their Tyrannical Ambition and Excellent Dynasty’s enmity originated long before that.

The two teams were both old brands in Glory. They had both fought against each other to be Champions ever since the first season. Their rivalry began there. Excellent Era had won the Championships three years in a row, but in the fourth season, they were finally dethroned by Tyranny. From then on, Excellent Era began going downhill year after year. Tyranny, on the other hand, continued to maintain their strength. However, they hadn’t been able to win their second Championship yet. For this reason, both sides taunted each other. From the Club’s fans to the media, from the matches on-stage to those underneath, their relationship was much tenser than Tiny Herb’s and Blue Rain’s.

Herb Garden’s Plantago Seed and Blue Brook Guild’s Blue River could still add each other as friends and chat with one another, but such a relationship would be very difficult for Tyrannical Ambition and Excellent Dynasty. The reason Cold Night was able to receive the message was because the other side had temporarily added him as a friend.

“Excellent Dynasty is looking for us….. it’s probably related to Lord Grim.” Jiang You said.

“In fact, Excellent Dynasty was the first to begin fighting with Lord Grim.” Cold Night said. Their Tyrannical Ambition hadn’t been in conflict with Lord Grim yet. As for Excellent Dynasty, they had engaged in a large battle against Lord Grim for Frost Forest and Boneyard. From the records, each side had won one battle, but it seemed like Lord Grim had lasted the longest. Everyone had originally been looking forward to seeing Excellent Dynasty act out again, but after being stepped on in Boneyard, there was no other movement from them.

“We can go and see them. When? Now?” Jiang You asked.

“He didn’t say the time.” Cold Night said.

“Then schedule it now! Face to face…… writing method?” Jiang You said.

Writing method meant that even though the two were face to face, they would still type out messages to communicate. Usually, when both sides conducted important meetings, they would use this type of method. The content they typed out would appear above their character’s heads. If the meeting was being recorded, then these could be used as proof.

“The other side wants to talk first.” Cold Night replied.

“No problem. Let’s go and take a look.” Jiang You answered.

“What about Lord Grim?” Cold Night asked.

“Try to contact him and ask!” Jiang You thought for awhile and then spoke.

“Okay…….” Cold Night replied. He had his character move forward and sent a message.

“Brother.”

“Yeah?”

“That, are you able to set a record for Line Canyon tonight?” Cold Night asked.

“Hard to say.” Ye Xiu replied.

This answer made Cold Night surprised. Even if Ye Xiu wasn’t going to set the record, he had expected him to bluff and give them pressure. What type of answer was that?

“What difficulties do you have?” Cold Night asked.

“We met a hidden.” Ye Xiu said.

Tears streamed down Cold Night’s cheeks.

“Hidden BOSS!!!!” When Ye Xiu’s group entered Line Canyon, they received a system notification. Steamed Bun Invasion cried out in joy.

In their team, Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, and Qiao Yifan were all pro-players, so nothing in a little dungeon would surprise them. Tang Rou wasn’t only a new player in Glory, but a new gamer too, so she still didn’t know what was valuable in games. Only Steamed Bun Invasion was both a noob in Glory and an experienced gamer, so he was quite happy about anything valuable in Glory. If not, then why would he bravely gather a bunch of strangers at around Level 20 to fight for the Blood Gunner?

This was why at this moment, seeing this hidden BOSS, only Steamed Bun Invasion expressed his excitement.

“So we finally meet one!” Ye Xiu also followed. Their recent fights with the guilds over the records had gone smoothly, but they weren’t so lucky in other areas. Especially for hidden BOSSes, they hadn’t met one in a few days.

“Illusion Swordmaster Ahong.” Tang Rou looked at the system announcement and read out the hidden BOSS’s name.

“The most difficult BOSS in this dungeon.” Ye Xiu said.

“What features does he have?” Tang Rou asked.

“Did you not look at the guide?” Ye Xiu asked.

“I haven’t.” Tang Rou said bluntly. When she watched the videos in the guides, she never looked at the dungeons. Her research was focused on PvP. She wasn’t too interested in PvE. (Author Note: PvP is player versus player battles. PvE is fighting with monsters, dungeoning, completing missions, etc.)

“The Illusion Sword Master class is a combination of the Berserker and the Blade Master class, so every skill he possesses comes from those two classes. I don’t think there’s anything more that needs to be said. Pay close attention to his left-handed blade.” Ye Xiu said.

“Left-handed blade?”

“Yeah, this BOSS is right-handed, but he also has a short blade at his waist side. While attacking, he might suddenly use his left hand to draw the short blade to perform a sneak attack. This type of attack is called a left-handed blade. There are many different ways he can attack with this. Any of his skills can be used through his left-handed blade, so everyone pay attention!” Ye Xiu said.

When Ye Xiu said everyone, he was actually only talking about Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion. Su Mucheng and Qiao Yifan didn’t need any warning.

Line Canyon’s dungeon terrain was that of a canyon. There were two large cliffs on either side, so players could only move forward. The monsters were similar to those in the leveling area. However, they were elite types, so they did more damage and had more health.

This Illusionary Swordsman Ahong’s background was described as someone who was hiding out in Line Canyon to escape pursuit. As a result, he treated anyone who intruded into the canyon as enemies.

This was what the game described him as. Of course, even if he didn’t actively come and kill players, the players wouldn’t let him go. In general, female players liked the story plot, but Su Mucheng was an old player at Glory, and she had finished the plot enough times to make her want to puke seeing it. Tang Rou wasn’t very interested in the game itself. How could she care about any stories about some NPC? She would compare herself to Ye Xiu everyday to see whether she had improved, how much she had improved, and how much longer until she could crush the guy.

They slaughtered their way through the dungeon with Ye Xiu reminding them the tactics from time to time. The Illusion Swordmaster Ahong didn’t have a fixed spawn point and could appear at any moment.

Sure enough, after clearing a mob of monsters at an intersection, a red-clothed swordsman hurried forward from the intersection. After seeing the five players, he cried out his lines: “That was quick!”

Chapter 189 – Illusion Swordmaster Ahong

Illusion Swordmaster Ahong, red-clothed, red-haired, with a red sheath; there was even a red scar that ran across his face. His two red eyes stared at the five players.

“Pay attention to the Swordmaster’s eyes. The redder his eyes the stronger he’ll be.” Ye Xiu told the new players.

“If you want my life, come at me!!” The Swordmaster was anxious, even more than Steamed Bun Invasion, who was holding a Brick in his hands. The Swordmaster jumped into the air and his sword whirled a gust of air, starting off with a Collapsing Mountain.

“Pay attention! The shockwave from his Collapsing Mountain will be bigger than usual.” Ye Xiu hastily warned.

This meant that you would have to jump high enough to dodge the shockwave.

The shock wave from normal Collapsing Mountains could be dodged by jumping over it. But the Swordmaster’s Collapsing Mountain was different because the height of the hitbox was different, which was why Ye Xiu had warned them so that Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion wouldn’t treat this Collapsing Mountain as normal.

Unfortunately, his warning was a bit too late.

Tang Rou reacted too quickly. Before Ye Xiu was able to finish his warning, she had already jumped up into the air to try and avoid it. And as she jumped, she also had her Soft Mist send a Dragon Tooth over at the Swordsman. Tang Rou was just that type of an aggressive girl.

As for Steamed Bun Invasion, he hadn’t jumped. When he saw the Collapsing Mountain arrive, he hastily ran to outside of the shockwave’s range and then threw a Brick flying over. Steamed Bun Invasion was just that type of a thuggish guy.

When she heard Ye Xiu’s warning, Tang Rou knew that she was in trouble.

She hadn’t jumped at full strength. A perfect jump was to not use a single ounce of strength more or less than what was needed. Her jump to avoid what she thought would be a normal Collapsing Mountain was in an attempt to do this, but unfortunately the Swordmaster’s attack wasn’t normal……

The shock wave from the sword slash emitted a faint red glow as if the slash had created a blood mist. Soft Mist was unable to dodge the shock wave and was hit spiralling into the air.

The BOSS seized this opportunity to follow up and combo. The Swordmaster immediately jumped and used the Blade Master skill Rising Dragon towards Soft Mist.

Even though Tang Rou had strong mechanics, she wasn’t able to stabilize her camera. All she saw on her screen was the camera spinning round and round. Under this situation, she was unable to perform any precise movements. Tang Rou randomly attacked not knowing if she was hitting the target or the air.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim rushed forward. He stabbed forward with his lance and threw out a Circle Swing in order to pull down the Illusion Swordmaster. However, he was met with the unique skill the Illusion Swordmaster possessed: Left-handed blade.

A cold light flashed.

It wasn’t anything flashy. It was thin, quick, and instantly disappeared. But this blade clashed with Lord Grim’s lance and the Circle Swing was smashed to the side.

Bang bang bang. Three gunshots.

At the same time the left-handed blade blocked the Circle Swing, Cleansing Mist shot Anti-Tank Missiles, hitting the BOSS. The three explosions blew the Illusion Swordmaster away. But a BOSS was still a BOSS and so the Anti-Tank Missiles that had a strong knockback effect normally was only capable of shaking the Illusion Swordmaster a little bit. Hence, the Rising Dragon wasn’t interrupted and the sword light flashed up, cutting Soft Mist.

The spiralling Soft Mist spun even faster. Her body smashed into the cliff. The blood from the cut sprayed down from the air. Soft Mist bounced off the cliff before dropping to the ground. It looked as if she had already been defeated. But the instant she hit the ground, she suddenly turned alive and used a Quick Recover to stand back up. In game, as long as the player controlling the character didn’t lose hope, there was no such thing as being seen as dispirited.

The leap of the Illusion Swordmaster’s Rising Dragon was much higher than when the skill was used by players. This was one of the more troublesome reasons about meeting a BOSS. Even though many of the BOSS’s skills came from the in-game skill trees, the effects were different from the players’ and the majority of them had stronger effects than the players’ skills.

The high-up Illusion Swordmaster suddenly pointed his sword while descending and used Falling Light Blade directly towards the closest target, Lord Grim.

Ye Xiu swiped his keyboard and had Lord Grim step to the side. Not waiting for the Falling Light Blade, he drew out a sword from the Thousand Chance Umbrella. A silver light arced into a semicircle. At the same time, a similar arc of light flashed from the opposite side of Lord Grim. The two sword lights weaved together, merging into a brilliant moon.

The one who acted was Qiao Yifan, who had moved at the same time as Ye Xiu. They had used the same skill, the Ghostblade’s knock-up skill, Moonlight Slash.

“Good!” Ye Xiu shouted. The Illusion Swordmaster’s Falling Light Blade was interrupted by these two attacks. The two sword lights slashed across his body in midair, keeping him from falling. Two sword arcs flashed again at the same time, following the same path as the previous Moonlight Slashes. This time, they slashed in the other direction, creating a perfect circle.

Ghostblade Level 20 skill: Full Moonlight Slash.

This skill had a strong blow away effect, but because Qiao Yifan and Ye Xiu were on opposite sides, the two skills counterbalanced each other, keeping the Illusion Swordmaster in place. The sword lights faded. The moment the Illusion Swordmaster hit the ground, a laser flew forward, hitting him square in the stomach and caused him to stumble back a few steps.

This was Cleansing Mist’s Laser Rifle.

“Ice Boundary!” Qiao Yifan had already begun casting the spell when Ye Xiu yelled towards him. Frost formed on the tip of his sword. The Ice Soul created a boundary that spread out. Ye Xiu utilized this opportunity to use Sword Soul and created a Sword Boundary.

The wily Steamed Bun Invasion cheered them on as he ran past them and tossed a handful of sand at the Illusion Swordmaster.

Blind!

The Illusion Swordmaster had clearly lost his sense of direction. He couldn’t find his opponents and walked around in a circle twice. The Ice Boundary’s effect had been set and ice had begun corroding his body. With a crackle, the Freeze effect triggered and the Illusion Swordmaster turned into a large block of ice.

Tang Rou, who had just taken a beating, quickly rushed forward. The instant the Swordmaster was frozen, she chained Double Stab, Dragon Tooth, and Falling Flower Palm together followed by three Magic Chasers that flew out.

After the three skills hit, the Freeze wore off. The Illusion Swordmaster then used Gore Cross. The scarlet Cross didn’t look like two sword lights, rather, they looked like two blood arcs. The Cross flew towards Soft Mist, who immediately leaped back to avoid it. But just as she was about to counterattack, she unexpectedly realized that a smaller Gore Cross was hidden behind the original one . In that instant, Tang Rou saw the left hand of the Illusion Swordmaster move to his waist and realized that the Illusion Swordmaster had used his left-handed blade to use a Gore Cross at the same time. A big one to hide the small one, extremely smart.

The unfortunate Tang Rou was directly hit by the small Gore Cross. When she looked down at her body, fresh blood continued to flow from the cross wound formed by the attack. This Gore Cross had caused a Bleed to take effect. Her bad luck continued again.

The gloomy Tang Rou didn’t dare to advance forward for a second time. She immediately used a health potion and retreated. The Bleed effect from the Illusion Swordmaster was very strong. Her health continued to drop even after using the health potion. Tang Rou began to panic. She didn’t know how low her health would drop to or how to stop it.

“Rest for a bit.” Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim said as he rushed forward from beside her to block the Illusion Swordmaster. Tang Rou immediately relaxed. She believed in Ye Xiu’s judgement and knew that she at least wouldn’t die.

The low-health Tang Rou temporarily became a spectator, while Steamed Bun Invasion continued to act sly. He didn’t dare get too close to the Swordmaster. Sand Toss and Brick became two long-ranged skills, which he used whenever there was a chance to. As a result, the only two who were left to face the Illusion Swordmaster directly were Ye Xiu and Qiao Yifan. Su Mucheng’s Launcher naturally couldn’t rush forward and fight in close-range.

Ye Xiu saw everything. A pro-player was still a pro-player. Whether it was him, Su Mucheng, or Qiao Yifan, none of them had any trouble dealing with the Illusion Swordmaster. The reason Tang Rou was half-dead was because of an old problem of hers: she lacked experience. As for Steamed Bun Invasion, he was currently wandering outside of the team. The usefulness of this type of performance was quite limited for a team.

Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion, actually weren’t very suited to be team players.

Tang Rou was too stubborn and aggressive. Her performance practically revolved with her as the center. Her problem was actually similar to that faced by Sun Xiang in his first match, when he had just joined Excellent era: stubborn individual performance causing the team to come apart.

However, in their current team, there was Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, and Qiao Yifan. Their strength was far greater than Tang Rou’s, so they still had enough strength to suppress this problem. However, as Tang Rou became more and more skilled, this problem would be exposed sooner or later.

As for Steamed Bun Invasion, this guy was too carefree. He had too much of an individual style. As an individual, he might become a player who was impossible to copy, but as a team player, this type of player wouldn’t be able to completely merge because his style was simply too unique.

There were predecessors of this type of player.

Wang Jiexi. Team Tiny Herb’s current captain, Wang Jiexi. His Magician style was the strangest and most graceful style in the Alliance. In the individual competition, Wang Jiexi had an extremely high win rate. But in the team competition, his individual performance was limited. Assimilating this style into the team was a problem Wang Jiexi hadn’t been able to resolve. In the end, he made a sacrifice for the team and changed his style to fit in with the team. It was only because of these changes that Team Tiny Herb was able to become Champions twice in the past three years.

Chapter 190 – The BOSS’s Shadow Steps

Steamed Bun Invasion’s situation was somewhat similar to that of Wang Jiexi’s. However, Wang Jiexi possessed the ability to adjust, while Steamed Bun Invasion probably didn’t know how to do so. After all, even Ye Xiu wasn’t sure how to help him develop. After Wang Jiexi changed, he was still at God-level, but if others did the same thing he did, they might fall to a mediocre level.

A transformation wasn’t something that easy to do. Even though Steamed Bun Invasion was a noob at Glory, he wasn’t a blank slate in other areas of the game. In reality, he had some understanding of what he was doing. In this area, he wasn’t like Tang Rou. Tang Rou truly was a complete blank slate. But it was a pity that this girl’s personality was so stubborn. She had pretty much figured out her own style already and it wasn’t possible to create a large transformation. Ye Xiu could help by instructing her about the game’s mechanics, but he didn’t have the ability to change her personality. Everyone was an adult so their ways of thinking had matured. Tang Rou’s personality wasn’t anything bad either. It just stopped her from becoming a good team player, that was all.

Ye Xiu pondered over this as he watched the two play. But his playing wasn’t slow even though he was multitasking. With ten years of experience, he had experienced all kinds of battles. Many of the things he needed to do were done automatically without too much thought.

Taking the BOSS down wasn’t a problem.

They were a team that could defeat a Level 36 Wild BOSS. If they couldn’t beat a weaker Level 33 hidden BOSS, Illusion Swordmaster Ahong, then they’d be a joke.

The important point was that these types of dungeons could be used as practice for everyone.

Ye Xiu directed the team as he fought casually. His focus was naturally on Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion. Su Mucheng rarely needed Ye Xiu to say anything. As for Qiao Yifan, Ye Xiu hadn’t judged him wrong. He was the complete opposite of Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion. His personality and awareness made him an outstanding team player.

He was adept at observing; he paid attention to the performance of every team player and tried hard to coordinate with each of them.

A part of why Tang Rou’s and Steamed Bun Invasion’s performances weren’t too good was because they were too unfamiliar with the hidden BOSS. After familiarizing themselves with the Illusion Swordmaster’s various skills, the two would gradually assimilate themselves into the team.

Correct, they could still assimilate.

But as their skills continue to grow, their styles would become more and more unique and their conflicts within the team would become greater and greater. This was what Ye Xiu was thinking about right now.

But as of right now, they were still a good team. Under Ye Xiu’s orders, the Illusion Swordmaster was gradually suppressed as he was hit blow after blow under the cliffs.

Lord Grim and One Inch Ash’s “Dual Linking Ghost Boundaries” never broke sothe team was always in a boundary.

Waves of poison arose from Steamed Bun Invasion’s attacks.

Three types of Magic Chasers flew out from Soft Mist.

Explosions erupted from Cleansing Mist’s cannon.

They continued to bombard the Illusion Swordmaster with their skills. Ahong’s eyes grew more and more red, his head was covered in sweat, and his expression grew more and more serious.

“Careful, almost red blood.” Ye Xiu suddenly said.

“What happens when he goes into red blood?” Tang Rou immediately asked. In the beginning, she had suffered quite a bit because she didn’t know what the BOSS’s features were. Tang Rou had learned from her mistakes.

“Shadow Steps.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh? What’s that?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked. He wasn’t like Tang Rou in this area. Tang Rou had helped Chen Guo PK a few times before, so she had seen quite a few high-leveled skills. Even though she might not know the name, “Shadow Steps” had been used in the fight between Poplar Beach and Ye Xiu recently. Chen Guo had even called out the name, so Tang Rou knew what this skill was.

But Steamed Bun Invasion had only played on this account, so he didn’t know of any skills above Level 30.

“It’s an afterimage. There’ll be five soon, one for each of us.” Ye Xiu said. If this were a normal team, then they wouldn’t dare split the team to fight each afterimage one on one. But Ye Xiu’s team was strong, so they dared to fight them directly this way.

“Careful!” Ye Xiu, who had been paying attention to the BOSS’s health the entire time, finally shouted.

The Illusion Swordmaster Ahong’s eyes began to glow red. The white of his eyes could no longer be seen.

“Back!”

Following Ye Xiu’s command, the five characters quickly leaped back. The Illusion Swordmaster roared towards the sky. The red light surrounding his body extravagantly burst outwards. The rocks and grass around him were blown apart and a burst of wind surged down. Fortunately, Ye Xiu’s warning had been quick and the five players retreated fast enough to dodge this attack.

Next, the Illusion Swordmaster twirled his sword in a dance-like motion. His figure blurred and split into five towards them.

What was different from a Blade Master’s Shadow Step was that the Illusion Swordmaster’s Shadow Steps didn’t have any distinction between real and fake. The five were all Illusion Swordmasters. This meant that the players had to fight against five BOSSes at the same time.

If this continued up until the end, then the battle would be impossible to finish. Fortunately, Shadow Steps only lasted for a certain duration. For the Illusion Swordmaster, it was 30 seconds. As long as the players could survive for 30 seconds, then the five afterimages would turn back into one. However, after combining together again, the amount of damage the players had dealt in this battle wasn’t additive, but rather an average. This meant that the actual damage the players dealt was ⅕ the total amount.

This made the battle longer. The Illusion Swordmaster’s Shadow Steps wasn’t a one time use skill. It would continue using it whenever it could until its life was completely gone.

Normal parties would run away during this time. Defense was their priority. They weren’t looking for damage. The damage would only be ⅕ of the total anyways. Once the Illusion Swordmaster merged back into one, the team would then begin attacking again. But Ye Xiu’s team was more heroic. It didn’t matter if the damage was split or not, they would still fight like normal.

The five Illusion Swordmaster afterimages were also very intelligent and each found a target to attack.

The left-rear Illusion Swordmaster sent a Sword Draw at Steamed Bun Invasion, who rolled out of the way. Steamed Bun hadn’t even gotten up yet, when he threw out a Sand Toss at him. Even though the Illusion Swordmaster was a BOSS, it was still blinded for a short while. Steamed Bun Invasion took this opportunity and closed in to whack the back of his head with a Brick. After triggering the Dizzy effect, he Applied Poison onto his weapon. He then used Inject Poison and gave the Illusion Swordmaster a good dose of poison.

The right-rear Illusion Swordmaster hacked forward at Soft Mist with a Collapsing Mountain. Tang Rou met with this attack once again, but instead of retreating, she moved forward and once again, jumped up to attack. Except this time, she calculated the height of the shock wave. She leaped over it and stabbed forward with a Circle Swing. Her arms whirled in a circle and smashed the Illusion Swordmaster onto the ground. She had suffered once before and now she was going to return it all with even more ferocity. Tang Rou was just that type of girl who refused to accept defeat.

The left-front Illusion Swordmaster used Triple Slash directly to close in on Cleansing Mist. Su Mucheng immediately jumped up and blasted out an artillery shell, which exploded and sent herself flying backwards from the recoil. However, this shot wasn’t able to interrupt the BOSS’s Triple Slash. Three sword lights, one after another, chased down Cleansing Mist, but each slash missed Cleansing Mist by just a hair’s breadth. Su Mucheng clearly had everything under control.

Qiao Yifan, on the other hand, took the initiative to close in on the BOSS. After casting an Ice Boundary, he not only hit his own target, but he also turned the one heading towards Lord Grim into an ice block. Even in this type of battle, everyone-for-themselves, if Qiao Yifan found an opportunity to, he would still coordinate with others.

Ye Xiu knew what to do. When Qiao Yifan casted Ice Boundary, he casted a Sword Boundary as well. The two began fighting inside these boundaries. His Thousand Chance Umbrella transformed into the Gun form and sent out Anti-Tank Missiles. The target was Qiao Yifan’s opponent. The three missiles exploded and the Illusion Swordmaster stumbled backwards a few steps. Qiao Yifan made his move right at this moment; he used Moonlight Slash into a Full Moonlight Slash followed by a Ghost Slash. The three slashes sliced forward.

At this moment, he wasn’t feeling happy because he had hit the BOSS, but rather he felt happy because he had coordinated with Ye Xiu.

Under his lead, the God had actively responded to his move, making Qiao Yifan feel he wasn’t alone. Every team member depended on each other and this was what it meant to be teammates. This was an extremely wonderful feeling.

After helping Qiao Yifan block his Illusion Swordmaster, Ye Xiu shook the Thousand Chance Umbrella into the Battle Lance form and use a Sky Strike at the Illusion Swordmaster. The Illusion Swordmaster’s right handed sword continued to attack, while using his left-handed blade to block Lord Grim’s Sky Strike. How could Ye Xiu be tricked by this puny trick? His Battle Lance suddenly retracted. The Illusion Swordmaster’s left-handed blade blocked nothing. The Thousand Chance Umbrella had already turned into two sections that hung on Lord Grim’s arms. He rolled to avoid the right-handed sword. His two arms held the Illusion Swordmaster tightly and Flung the Illusion Swordmaster away.

After using the Grappler skill, he changed the Thousand Chance Umbrella back into a Battle Lance. Ye Xiu was just about to have his Lord Grim follow up, when he suddenly heard two ring ring sounds from outside.

Ye Xiu had lowered the in-game volume to very low because he frequently had to listen for these sounds.

When he heard this, Ye Xiu couldn’t help but curse: “F*ck.”

Having been on night-duty for so many days, he had to bring customers drinks many times. Finally, someone had called for his service at a crucial time.

Ye Xiu’s left hand quickly left the keyboard and connected to the service line. He asked: “What would you like?”

“What?” The first to respond were the four players on the team. Ye Xiu hadn’t taken off his headphones.

“Two Colas.” The customer’s voice came out from the service line soon after.

“Just a second.” Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 191 – I’m In a Hurry

“I’m in a hurry! Hurry up!!” Turning his head, Ye Xiu yelled towards his mic.

Everyone was startled, even Su Mucheng didn’t understand what “Just one second” and then an “I’m in a hurry” right after meant. The cautious Qiao Yifan didn’t dare ask and pondered over what type of strategy “Just one second” and “I’m in a hurry” was.

However, Tang Rou was able to realize what had happened after a short while. Steamed Bun Invasion, on the other hand, obviously didn’t understand. But he would ask what he didn’t know and immediately opened his mouth: “Senior, what do you mean?”

“Hurry up and finish this. I have business to do.” Ye Xiu said. He moved his hands quickly and the in-game Lord Grim began fighting more fiercely. Lunging left, rushing right. He even pulled the afterimage that was supposed to be One Inch Ash’s. Qiao Yifan was greatly startled and found that he wasn’t able to keep up with Lord Grim’s tempo.

But this didn’t make Qiao Yifan discouraged. He understood what was going on: God was going all out. There was still a gap between their skill levels, so he naturally couldn’t keep up. Perhaps the only person who could keep up with this tempo would be a top-tier Phantom Demon in the Alliance like Li Xuan.

“Yifan, set up the boundary.” Ye Xiu shouted.

Qiao Yifan heard this and immediately cast a Sword Boundary.

“Everyone, pull them over here to fight. Steamed Bun, Steamed Bun, pull it over here.” Ye Xiu yelled.

Tang Rou seized the opportunity to use a Falling Flower Palm and blasted the Illusion Swordmaster over. Su Mucheng’s Launcher didn’t have any strong Blow Away effect, so she used an Aerial Fire to come into the Sword Boundary, obtaining the attack buff.

Only Steamed Bun Invasion was left. His Brawler class didn’t have any convenient Blow Away skills, so he circled behind the Illusion Swordmaster and used a Knee Attack. However, the BOSS was quick. How could it be so easy to hit him? As a result, Steamed Bun Invasion leaped left and right sneakily.

Ye Xiu didn’t know whether to laugh or cry: “If you just ran over here, wouldn’t he follow you over?”

“Right!” Steamed Bun Invasion suddenly understood.

“It’s a bit of a mess, no?” After entering the Sword Boundary, Su Mucheng said to Ye Xiu. The five were all in the Sword Boundary facing against five nimble BOSSes. Guaranteeing that none of them would leave the Sword Boundary was a type of training only pro-teams could do. Their team was still far off from that!

“Shadow Steps has ended.” Just as Ye Xiu’s voice fell, the five afterimages of the Illusion Swordmaster blurred again. Instead of four of them disappearing, four of the afterimages swiftly moved towards a single one.

“That one, kill him!” Ye Xiu shouted. His Lord Grim rushed towards the merged Illusion Swordmaster. The instant Shadow Steps ended, the Illusion Swordmaster would show an extremely large opening. Besides taking a beating, he wouldn’t be able to do anything. However, this opening was only an instant, yet Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim as well as Tang Rou, Su Mucheng, and Qiao Yifan were able to seize the opportunity to burst him. Only Steamed Bun Invasion was still dashing towards the Sword Soul, but halfway there, he saw the Illusion Swordmaster behind him zoom past him.

“Oh no!” Steamed Bun Invasion cried. Unfortunately, there was still some distance between himself and the final target, so all he could contribute was a Brick.

“Retreat!” Ye Xiu yelled as Lord Grim moved back. After the Illusion Swordmaster merged into one, the red aura around him exploded out. The people surrounding him leaped back to avoid it. But under this Red Blood status, the Illusion Swordmaster was clearly faster than before. This time, Qiao Yifan was unexpectedly half a step slow and was hit by the red light and instantly shot out into somewhere farther away.

Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist had already stored a Laser Rifle. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion didn’t need Ye Xiu to say anything and rushed forward to attack. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim rushed up as well. Just as he was about to attack, that annoying sound once again ran up from outside of his headphones.

This customer is really annoying…… Ye Xiu sighed. In the end, he turned his head, but discovered that the call had come from a different seat……

They’ve teamed up!

Ye Xiu thought as tears streamed down his cheeks. He controlled Lord Grim, while using his left hand to quickly answer the phone.

“What would you like?” Ye Xiu asked.

“What?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked.

“He’s not talking to you, Steamed Bun.” Tang Rou explained for Ye Xiu.

“Then who is he talking to?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked.

“With Internet Cafe customers!” Tang Rou said.

“Internet Cafe?” Steamed Bun Invasion was still puzzled. Ye Xiu was also extremely gloomy. This time, the customer didn’t directly order and instead slowly asked what brand of cigarettes the Internet Cafe had.

“Yellow Mountain, White Sand, Red Pagoda Mountain, Hibiscus, Nanjing, Red River, One Pen, Yellow Crane Tower, Five Leaves, which one?” Ye Xiu was very familiar with cigarettes! He quickly listed them out. In the end, the customer heard it and fell silent for a long time. He then killed Ye Xiu instantly with one word: “Ah?”

“What do you usually smoke?” Ye Xiu asked helplessly.

“Yellow Mountain.”

“We have it!” Ye Xiu said.

“What type?”

“Red.”

“How much money?”

“22.”

“So expensive.” The other side replied. Ye Xiu’s eyes began to tear up. In any case, there wasn’t any bargaining, so he directly asked: “Do you want it?”

But the customer carefreely brought the question back to his original point: “What else do you have?”

“We have everything. Which one do you want?” Ye Xiu asked. Ye Xiu reckoned that normal people couldn’t ask for anything too weird.

“How much for White Sand?” The customer asked.

“There’s a 6 RMB one, a 10 RMB one, a 13 RMB one.” Ye Xiu said.

“Which type is the 10 RMB one?”

“New Quality.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh…..” The other side seemed to be pondering over it.

This time, Ye Xiu didn’t urge him and focused on the game.

“Careful! He’s about to split!! Pull him back to fight together.” Ye Xiu had been talking with the customer the entire time and the entire team was listening, when he suddenly gave out this warning.

The Illusion Swordmaster blurred and four other Illusion Swordmasters jumped out. But this time, they had planned on gathering together to fight, so the five characters didn’t scatter and directly faced them. The Sword Boundary buffed the team’s attributes and the Ice Boundary made the Illusion Swordmasters to slow down. On the other side, the customer calmly said: “If there’s so many White Sand types, then why’s there only one type for Yellow Mountain?”

Ye Xiu coughed blood: “The New Anhui and Chinese Wind are out.”

“How much for the New Quality?”

“They’re sold out!”

“No problem, I’m just asking.” The customer said.

“16……” Ye Xiu replied helplessly. The customer was the king.

“That’s more expensive than outside!” The customer lamented.

Ye Xiu didn’t reply and continued to play the game. Right now, it was a 5v5. Sword lights, lance blurs, gunshots, the battle was intense.

“Forget it. I don’t need them.” The greatest thing was that the customer had talked for so long, but didn’t buy anything.

Just as he hung up, another sound came. Ye Xiu was about to go mad. The other side asked: “Cola!”

“Just a moment! I’ll be there right away!!” Ye Xiu yelled.

Ye Xiu wasn’t an immortal. It was difficult for him to take care of so many things. This time, the customer had made him move a half a beat slower. The Illusion Swordmaster’s Back Slash unexpectedly hit him and his character was launched into the sky.

Ye Xiu immediately adjusted his camera, but the Illusion Swordmaster had already taken out his sneaky left-handed blade to attack. A Gore Cross followed closely behind the Back Slash and sliced Lord Grim. With an open wound, his life dropped rapidly. The Illusion Swordmaster sheathed his sword and began the animation for Sword Draw.

Ye Xiu immediately moved. The Illusion Swordmaster’s Sword Draw slashed out a cold light, which split Lord Grim into two halves. However, it had hit Lord Grim’s Shadow Clone.

The real body had already flashed to behind the Illusion Swordmaster. Just as he was about to attack, another cold light swooshed towards his body. Ye Xiu wasn’t able to block in time. The sword light sent him flying backwards.

He turned his camera to look. The sword light had come from the Illusion Swordmaster Tang Rou was fighting against. The Sword Draw from that one had flashed towards Ye Xiu.

“So unlucky……” Ye Xiu cursed. His camera was limited in midair, so he hadn’t seen it. The Illusion Swordmaster continued to chase him. Just as it seemed like he would be hit again, Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist suddenly sent an artillery shell in front of Lord Grim, blocking the attack.

“Oh! You’ve got skill!”

“And you need to say that?” Su Mucheng said.

Lord Grim fell to the ground and used Quick Recover. The time won back from the block was enough for Ye Xiu to get back into tempo. With a quick move, he immediately sent the two Illusion Swordmasters, which were targeting Su Mucheng and him, flying.

The battlefield returned back to normal. Everyone had seen Ye Xiu’s muddled performance. After a short moment of silence, Steamed Bun Invasion suddenly asked: “Senior you’re very busy. What do you do?”

“Cafe manager…….” Ye Xiu let out a long sigh.

“Oh, what a coincidence! I also work in an Internet Cafe.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“Oh? You’re also a manager?” Ye Xiu said. It wouldn’t be surprising since Steamed Bun Invasion was able to play the game all-night. If he had a normal job, then playing all-night would be okay from time to time, but Steamed Bun Invasion was doing it everyday.

“No, I’m a security guard.” Steamed Bun Invasion said calmly.

The four others in the team began sweating. He was a Brawler in real life too…..

“Pay attention! It’s about to merge!” Lord Grim didn’t have much life left, but his spirit hadn’t been affected by the interruptions.

“Don’t be polite. Attack! Hurry! Hurry!” Ye Xiu yelled. If the customers continued to disturb himself, then he really might die.

Chapter 192 – Items Lead to Thinking

The instant the Illusion Swordmaster merged into one, the team ferociously assaulted it. They all understood that Ye Xiu was in a difficult predicament and had a rough idea why he was in a hurry.

Under Ye Xiu’s lead, the battle tempo increased. There were often times where they traded blow for blow to deal more damage.

In the Internet Cafe, the customer, who wanted cigarettes, finally decided to buy the 10 RMB White Sand and continued to bother Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu had conquered a challenge and won a difficult battle. He gave the customer the usual reply “Just a second.” The Illusion Swordmaster split and merged until they finally took it down. The service calls began to ring repeatedly again. It was the Cola customer again. He was probably dying of thirst.

“I’m coming! I’m coming!” Ye Xiu gave the customer a reply. He grabbed the Cola and the cigarettes, while taking a quick glance at the items that dropped from the Illusion Swordmaster.

No sword…..

Ye Xiu was a bit disappointed.

He had an item he needed from the Illusion Swordmaster. Scarlet Illusion Blade. This was an Orange weapon for the Thousand Chance Umbrella’s Sword form.

But an Orange weapon was after all, an Orange weapon and wouldn’t drop so easily. Ye Xiu sighed as he delivered the Cola and cigarettes to the customers.

“Let’s see what it dropped!” In game, Steamed Bun Invasion excitedly inspected the items that had dropped. He was the most excited of the players there.

“Can’t use. Can’t use. Can’t use. Materials are for senior……” Steamed Bun Invasion looked at the equipment. He renounced them as he said what he was thinking aloud. The Illusion Swordmaster had dropped three Blue equipment and a few materials —– very normal drops.

“Hm? What’s this?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked. The other three all saw: Line Canyon Map Piece Three.

“Oh. It’s an item needed to open a hidden dungeon.” Qiao Yifan recognized it.

“Hidden dungeon? That sounds very hard.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“Yeah, it’s harder than normal dungeons.” Su Mucheng commented.

“How many times can you run it every day?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked.

“It’s not calculated like that. It requires certain items in order to enter. In theory, as long as you have the items, there’s no limit.” Su Mucheng said.

“Line Canyon Map Piece Three……does that mean we have to gather more of these?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked.

“Yeah, I think it’s four or five.” Su Mucheng wasn’t really familiar with these low-leveled dungeons.

“Four.” Qiao Yifan said. He had done his homework.

At this moment, Ye Xiu had returned. He looked at the items that were waiting to be rolled.

“Oh, a hidden dungeon item!” Ye Xiu sat down and said, after putting on his headphones.

“It seems like it’s a hidden dungeon that hasn’t been run yet.” Su Mucheng checked the dungeon leaderboards.

“It is, but the items aren’t easy to gather! One, two, and three are okay, but the fourth piece is only dropped by the wild BOSS, which only spawns three times a week. It looks like it hasn’t dropped yet.” Ye Xiu said.

“For hidden dungeons are full of hidden BOSSes and wild BOSSes. The drop rate is pretty high too, so running it is quite worth it.” Su Mucheng said.

“Yeah……” How could Ye Xiu not know this? His requirements for this dungeon weren’t easy to get. For example, the Illusion Swordmaster’s Scarlet Illusion Blade or the wild BOSS only drop, Amber Crystal. The big guilds might have these rare materials, but they might not use them as a bargaining chip.

These were all necessary materials that the Clubs needed for researching self-made equipment. If they didn’t have enough of them, how could they just give them out to others? Ye Xiu tried by sending Tyrannical Ambition his materials list, but the other side hadn’t replied yet.

It wouldn’t be easy for them to steal a wild BOSS from the big guilds with their strength. The BOSSes in the hidden dungeons didn’t have anyone that could kill steal them, but in order to enter the hidden dungeon, they had to steal the Line Canyon Map Piece Four from the wild BOSS. No matter how they went about it, it was a dead end.

Ye Xiu pondered over this as everyone split the items. They all just randomly rolled for the equipment. The materials and the Line Canyon Map Piece Three went to Ye Xiu. Whether to sell it or keep it was something he hadn’t decided on yet.

The following dungeons were normal. After finishing their first run, no hidden BOSS appeared in the second and third runs. But on third run, they broke the Line Canyon dungeon record. 30:21:56, beating the former record by around 20 seconds.

The former record wasn’t at the limit because the big guilds were a bit dispirited towards the dungeon records and were mostly doing them for experience and Purple equipment. Set the highest record? With Lord Grim’s existence, they all felt a bit powerless.

Lord Grim crushing Arena experts and breaking dungeon records, the players were already used to these. It was only Full Moon Guild, who gave their congratulations to Lord Grim’s team, under Maple Tree’s lead. It seemed like they were showing off their close relationship with them. That night, the players from the big guilds seemed to have vanished. It was dead silent.

Before this, Tyrannical Ambition’s players still cared for this record, but once the record was broken, Ye Xiu didn’t receive any messages from them and suddenly felt that something wasn’t right. However, he didn’t go and ask them. Actually, Ye Xiu had an urgent need for materials, it was just that he just wasn’t as loud as the other big guilds were for their dungeon records.

After finishing Line Canyon, they went to Desolate Land. Su Mucheng and Qiao Yifan took their leave first. The remaining three continued to level until they were tired and then went to take a break. Tang Rou liked to solo dungeons to practice her mechanics. Steamed Bun Invasion liked to go to the Arena to bully others. Ye Xiu tidied up the materials he had gathered and went to the marketplace. He paid attention to the prices in the tenth server. The prices in the tenth server were still independent. Once players were able to enter the Heavenly Domain, the prices would rapidly decline until they reached the prices of the old servers.

In the market, Ye Xiu was especially mindful of the hidden dungeon items. Sure enough, there were map pieces one, two, and three, but the fourth one wasn’t being sold.

Wild BOSS……

Ye Xiu sighed. Besides the wild BOSSes they could fight earlier than the others like the Fire Witch. They had no way of competing for the same-leveled ones. When the wild BOSSes respawned, the first ones to arrive would be the big guilds. For them, by the time they found out, the BOSS would have been killed already. The reason he was able to steal the Blood Gunner and the Goblin Merchant was because he had been invited by the big guilds. Afterwards, for Desolate Land and Line Canyon, Ye Xiu hadn’t even been able to see the wild BOSSes.

Ye Xiu turned around and went to his warehouse. Everything in there had practically all been earnings he had won from Team Tiny Herb. His warehouse was wealthy and prosperous. He might be able to trade uncommon materials from his warehouse for items he needed such as the Scarlet Stinger with Tyrannical Ambition. Right now, the wild BOSSes were his biggest concern. And as the Thousand Chance Umbrella continued to level, he would need more and more of these rare materials. It would be extremely difficult if he had to gather them all by himself!

If he couldn’t find a way to obtain these materials, then he had no other choice but to rely on the Clubs.

The Clubs understood this. They all had guilds supporting them in the game. The guild’s purpose was to help provide materials for the Club. The materials would then be developed into Silver equipment by the tech team and then turned into strength for achievements. The achievements would bring in media, fan support and better players……

Under this cycle, the big Clubs would grow bigger and bigger. It was difficult for small Clubs to develop.

Club Excellent Era was trying to rise up again and had requirements for their guild Excellent Dynasty as well. However, their development in the old servers had already turned into a standstill. Their prospects at making a breakthrough weren’t large, which was why when the new server opened, the guild leader Chen Yehui had put in large amounts of manpower into it. He himself had personally come to the new server to lead. He had even troubled Liu Hao, a pro-player, to come set the record for a low-leveled dungeon. It was because of his huge burden that he know that things wouldn’t be easy to.

If everything had gone smoothly in the tenth server, the other guilds would have no way of contesting with Excellent Dynasty, who was going all out. However, a Ye Qiu had appeared.

Liu Hao had lost to Ye Qiu.

He had brought his many comrades to fight, but they still lost to Ye Qiu.

However, he had still found a chance amidst Ye Qiu’s dominance in the tenth server. He had to overthrow this mountain because this was where he was going to gamble everything he had. He couldn’t lose.

Chapter 193 – Idiot’s Guide

To outsiders, Ye Xiu was still just as carefree as ever. Even after staying up all night, he never looked tired and nothing ever seemed to irritate him.

To outsiders, they couldn’t tell that he was someone who had encountered difficulties. Even more so, they definitely wouldn’t know whether he had already figured out a solution to this problem.

He made it look like nothing had happened.

Tang Rou didn’t know that Ye Xiu was pondering deeply over this. All she knew was that it was her turn to buy breakfast.

When she returned with breakfast, Ye Xiu had already given his seat to the early-shift employees and was leisurely holding a cigarette in his mouth, waiting for his food to arrive.

After eating breakfast, the two went to their respective rooms to sleep.

At three in the afternoon, they woke up. One went to the front desk to work while the other went looking for an empty computer station to sit at.

Since it was a Saturday, the Internet Cafe’s business was doing exceptionally well. There were, unexpectedly, no open seats in the smoking area. Ye Xiu circled around the Internet Cafe, and in the end, just stood there staring blankly into space for a long time.

“Business is doing well today……” Ye Xiu helplessly returned to the front desk and told his sorrows to Tang Rou.

“As an Internet Cafe employee, you should be happy about that.” Boss Chen walked over.

“Business is doing well today. I’m very happy.” Ye Xiu said with a blank face.

Chen Guo had trained herself. Her ability to restrain herself had gone up. If this had happened a few weeks before, she’d already be shouting and grinding her teeth.

“What are you doing?” Ye Xiu asked Tang Rou.

“I’m looking at guides.” Tang Rou said.

“Aren’t you always looking at guides?” Ye Xiu asked, while taking a glance at her screen.

“Oh? A dungeon guide?” Ye Xiu was surprised. Tang Rou practically never looked at these. The way they ran the dungeons were usually directed by Ye Xiu.

“Yeah…… I’m just skimming over it.” Tang Rou said. Ye Xiu looked more carefully. This girl was currently looking at the introductions to Line Canyon’s three hidden BOSSes as well as the wild BOSS. Clearly, after getting badly beaten by the Illusion Swordmaster yesterday, Tang Rou realized that facing a never-before-seen BOSS was troublesome for her.

“Okay. Looking at the BOSSes is fine, but don’t look at anything else.” Ye Xiu said.

“Hm?”

“Our play style is very different from what is written in the guides.” Ye Xiu said.

“Why is it different?” Chen Guo entered the discussion.

“All DPS, no MT, no healer.” Ye Xiu said.

An all DPS team was a very common matter for Ye Xiu and his squad, but to normal players, especially in the new server, this was something that was rarely seen. Even for the big guilds, when they formed an all DPS team, they often needed experts to substitute for them.

An all DPS team relied on the players’ mechanical skill. Without strong mechanics, a guide wouldn’t help.

“Boss, what level are you on for the whack-a-mole game?” Ye Xiu suddenly asked.

“I only play it for fun. At my age, what’s the point in practicing?” Chen Guo said.

“You could at least improve a bit! If not, then when we get to the Heavenly Domain and look to party up with you, you’ll only be dead weight!” Ye Xiu said.

“……” Chen Guo was speechless. Besides killing him, she had no other thoughts.

“Oh? Who wrote this guide?” Ye Xiu’s attention suddenly snapped back to Tang Rou’s screen. Tang Rou’s newly opened guide was a guide for the Line Canyon hidden BOSS Sandworm.

“Who wrote it?” Tang Rou wasn’t sure. She went to the top of the page and saw the name of the poster: Concealed Light.

“Do you recognize him?” Tang Rou turned her head to ask Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu shook his head. He didn’t recognize the ID.

“What’s so special about this guide?” Chen Guo had also been drawn in and pressed near to look.

“The guide’s very detailed.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh?”

“He’s included the probability of every possible scenario. The process is very detailed. He’s written down every single detail on how to kill the BOSS.” Ye Xiu said.

“No wonder it’s so long…..” Tang Rou said. This guide was several pages long. When she opened it, she jumped up with fright. She hadn’t even looked at the content yet!

“Woah, you’re right…….” Chen Guo looked at it and then immediately discovered that this guide chose five classes, instructed what equipment to use, how to initiate, what moves to use in specific places…….

“It’s practically a video.” Chen Guo thought aloud as she looked.

The three read the entire seven pages, which was probably around twenty thousand words long.

4 minutes 56 seconds.

After thoroughly scouring through the guide, the author had even informed the reader how much time it would take to kill the BOSS, down to the second.

“Is this for real?” Chen Guo didn’t want to believe it. In actuality, she had already begun feeling dizzy after the first page. After that, she stopped reading carefully.

“Not a single mistake…….” Ye Xiu said on the side.

“This……. if it doesn’t allow for any deviation, then doesn’t that mean it doesn’t allow for any mistakes? If there’s a mistake, won’t it all be over?” Chen Guo said.

“That’s right.” Ye Xiu nodded his head, “But if this were for setting the record, there can’t be any mistakes anyways.”

“Are you saying that his strategy is very good for setting a record?”

“That’s not true…… His strategy is very safe, but it isn’t very efficient. However, this might only be because he’s researching a hidden BOSS. For a hidden BOSS, safety is number one. Who cares about efficiency?” Ye Xiu said.

“That’s true.” Chen Guo nodded her head.

“This person has other guides too.” Tang Rou saw the other guides from the author.

Here, Ye Xiu saw the name that the author gave to his guides: Idiot Series.

“It really is an idiot’s guide……” Ye Xiu said. This step by step guide, which provided instructions for everything, down to the small details, didn’t need the people using the guide to use their brain in any way. If they followed the steps, then they’d succeed.

“But it looks like the rating isn’t too good!” Tang Rou looked at the rating and comments.

“It’s probably because of the problem the boss talked about.” Ye Xiu guessed.

“Yeah.” Tang Rou nodded her head.

The comments were mostly mocking him. Just as expected, they were talking about Chen Guo’s problem: No one could ensure that they would be able to follow this type of extremely detailed step by step guide from beginning to end. As a result, everyone saw it as a fraud, as a theory. Since this wasn’t the author’s first guide, below there were comments such as “Another fake.” “Another fantasy fiction.” Practically no one supported the author.

“The guide isn’t wrong…… but the limitations are a bit too much.” Ye Xiu sighed.

“Should we look at his other guides?” Tang Rou moved her mouse around, stopping on different links. Every move stopped on a desired spot. This sister was actually practicing her mechanics even here.

“Let’s look at one!” Ye Xiu said.

Tang Rou opened up another one. This guide was on the other hidden BOSS in Line Canyon, the Scarlet Scorpion Assassin, Sting. The style was the same. From the very begining, the guide chose what classes to use, how to initiate, from beginning to end for several pages.

“Oh? He changed classes?” Ye Xiu was curious. Compared to the previous guide, four of the five classes were different. It was a completely different party set-up. To be able to do such a detailed guide, Ye Xiu had thought that the author had a set five-player team.

When Tang Rou heard Ye Xiu’s surprise, she opened up another guide. At the very start, he chose another completely different team set-up. This guide was for a different hidden BOSS in Desolate Land.

“When were these guides made?” Ye Xiu suddenly asked.

Tang Rou looked at the post time and found that they were all made recently.

“Could he be a player from the new server?’ Ye Xiu felt unsure.

Tang Rou clicked on the author’s name. While taking a looking at his list of works, the Idiot Series, the guides stopped at Line Canyon. This really was the current tenth server pace.

“Log into the game and search for him.” Ye Xiu proposed.

Tang Rou logged into the game. After Soft Mist went online, she looked up the name.

Concealed Light, Male, Level 32, Summoner.

“He really is from the new server.” Tang Rou said.

“But new server doesn’t mean new player, no?” Chen Guo said.

“If he’s not a new player, why would he put so much effort into researching these low-leveled BOSSes?” Ye Xiu said.

“Uh…..” Chen Guo thought, but couldn’t come up with anything.

“Look at this!” Tang Rou suddenly said.

Ye Xiu looked.

The title: The Mystery of the Boneyard 16 Minutes and 24 Second Record!

This record was the one Ye Xiu and his team had set in the tenth server. Hung high up on the leaderboards, the team set-up could be seen.

Battle Mage, Blade Master, Brawler, Launcher, Unspecialized.

Concealed Light had analyzed from these five classes how this record had been made.

From the beginning, he had already analyzed that it couldn’t be done with the usual strategy and that it had to be done by a new strategy.

Then what was this new strategy?

Concealed Light’s analysis wasn’t completely correct, but he was very close.

There was one point that he was wrong about though. Concealed Light clearly didn’t know of Lord Grim’s Thousand Chance Umbrella, so his analysis of the unspecialized character’s role was completely off.

In the end, with the strategy he had designed, he wasn’t able to create the 16 minutes and 24 second record. As a result, he gave Lord Grim and the five characters a set of Orange equipment and confidently said that this was how they did it……

It wasn’t that Concealed Light didn’t know how difficult it was to obtain Orange equipment in the new server at Level 25, but rather, it was that this brother was extremely confident in his analysis and strategy, so by working backwards…… he believed that, although having these five sets of equipment was ridiculous, it wasn’t impossible. But without these equipment, it definitely wasn’t possible to create such a record. As a result, he made such a claim.

The comments below weren’t hard to imagine. They were all practically saying how there was something wrong with the author’s brain.

Towards these comments, Ye Xiu and Tang Rou expressed their approval.

Chapter 194 – A Not So Simple New Player

“This piece of writing makes it sound as if he’s always right.” Ye Xiu concluded.

“Well, he is correct in a few places.” Tang Rou said.

“Actually, if you put in time to do research, it’s not that difficult to come up with such a strategy. It’s just a matter of how much time you are willing to put in.” Ye Xiu said.

“Then do we still need to look at his guides?” Tang Rou asked.

“Let’s look at another BOSS one!” Ye Xiu said.

Tang Rou clicked on the previous Scarlet Scorpion Assassin guide, and just like that, Ye Xiu lied down on his stomach, over the receptionist desk like an idiot, and looked at the idiot’s guide. Tang Rou also looked on, but with her experience, she wasn’t able to read as fast as Ye Xiu. For this type of extremely detailed, step-by-step guide, Tang Rou had a hard time following it. Not long after, she felt like a next page clicking robot.

Chen Guo was actually a bit better in this area. However, she too couldn’t read it any further after a short while. For this type of low-leveled BOSS, even though it was a hidden one, it still wasn’t that difficult. Creating such a complicated guide was a bit excessive.

“What’s there to look at…….” Chen Guo mumbled.

“There isn’t much to look at for the guide.” Ye Xiu affirmed that there wasn’t any value in the guide, “But I wanted to see if he made any mistakes.”

“You’re playing find the fault?” Chen Guo was speechless.

“He he.” Ye Xiu chuckled and then continued to read.

Page after page, the guide totaled around 20,000 words long. Tang Rou and Chen Guo decided to stop reading along and just stared at Ye Xiu, waiting for him to find a mistake.

“There aren’t any mistakes.” Ye Xiu said after reading it.

“You’re still playing?” Chen Guo asked.

“Read another one?” Ye Xiu asked, to which Tang Rou responded by clicking on another link.

“You guys can keep playing!” Chen Guo stretched. She had lost all interest in playing this game.

“Wow!” Just as she turned her head, she heard Ye Xiu cry out in amazement. Chen Guo immediately turned back: “What? What?”

“Different classes.” Ye Xiu said.

“How many times do you need to act amazed?” Chen Guo rolled her eyes. The guide had switched classes before. They had already been amazed once.

“But this time, he doesn’t even include a Summoner. Isn’t he a Summoner?” Ye Xiu said.

“Yeah.” Tang Rou nodded her head. They had verified it earlier: Concealed Light, Level 32 Summoner.

“Does he have multiple accounts?” Chen Guo guessed.

Ye Xiu couldn’t deny such a possibility, so he silently read the guide.

After annihilating the excessive 20,000 word wall of text, Ye Xiu still couldn’t find any mistakes. Even though there were a few places where efficiency wasn’t maximized, they were completely possible, and didn’t contain any mistakes.

During this time, a customer in the smoking area left. Usually, when business is doing so well, the customers had the priority to use the computers, but seeing Ye Xiu’s pitiful appearance, Chen Guo’s heart softened as she waved her hand. Ye Xiu immediately understood her intent and quickly snatched the computer station.

Chen Guo and Tang Rou continued to stare at the walls of text on the computer screen.

Five minutes later……

“Is it interesting?” Chen Guo asked.

“No…….” Tang Rou calmly said. She was tired of reading it.

“Go find two videos to watch!” Chen Guo liked to watch brilliant match videos the most.

“Sure!” Tang Rou agreed. She didn’t feel as if this guide helped her at all. All she wanted to know was each of the BOSS’s features, so she could avoid predicaments, like when she fought against the Illusion Swordmaster. As long as she knew the BOSS’s patterns, Tang Rou believed that she could deal with them relying on her mechanics.

As a result, she closed the Idiot’s Guides and began to find a video to watch, but she suddenly discovered that her screen in Glory had turned entirely grey.

After searching for Concealed Light, she had forgotten to logout. Right now, Soft Mist was lying on the ground. A system notification had popped up asking her if she wanted to revive her character.

“How’d I die?” Tang Rou stared blankly at Chen Guo.

“Were you in the wild?” Chen Guo asked.

“Yeah……”

“You’re too careless.” Chen Guo said. Dying in the wild, whether it be by a random monster or a vicious PKer, was very common.

“Go revive and see what you’ve dropped.” Chen Guo said.

Tang Rou clicked confirm to revive. Her character returned to Congee City in a Critically Ill State. When she opened up her equipment and items, she shook her head: “I didn’t drop anything. Only some money and experience.”

“Those always drop. Check the system log.” Chen Guo said.

“Uh?” Tang Rou unexpectedly didn’t know what that was.

“Here!” Chen Guo took the mouse and clicked it for Tang Rou. The system log recorded her death. She wasn’t killed by a monster, but rather by a player called Breaking Zero.

“Breaking Zero…….” Chen Guo muttered. She opened up the search function and put in the name.

The character was online. A Level 33, male Spellblade.

“Level 33! He’s definitely leveling in Line Canyon. Go and take revenge!” Chen Guo gave the mouse and keyboard back to Tang Rou and commanded her like a general.

“Now?” Tang Rou was unsure.

“Obviously!” Chen Guo nodded her head.

Tang Rou pointed to the side. Chen Guo turned her head and saw a bunch of customers leaning against the front desk, watching the two beauties play the game.

“I’ll go! You take revenge.” Chen Guo went to deal with the customers.

“It’s fine! Who knows if I’ll be able to find him. It’ll be the same if I do it later.” Tang Rou didn’t really care and logged out of the game to take care of the customers.

In the smoking area, Ye Xiu continued to read Concealed Light’s Idiot’s Guides. With the current pace of the new server, there were a total of four dungeons; each one had three hidden BOSSes for a total of twelve. Every one of Concealed Light’s hidden BOSS guides were extremely detailed step-by-step guides that were over 20,000 words long. Even though Ye Xiu read very fast, he still had to read each word one by one. When Chen Guo called for him to eat, he had only finished six of them.

“You’re still reading! I’ll eat first.” Chen Guo was already used to Ye Xiu’s obsession over the game.

“Okay…..”

“Have you found any mistakes?’ Chen Guo asked.

“No.” Ye Xiu shook his head.

“Are you planning on reading them all?” Chen Guo knew that playing find the fault wasn’t a very fun game. It was actually quite tiring.

“We’ll see!” Ye Xiu said.

“Little Tang was killed by someone in the afternoon!” At the dining table, Chen Guo suddenly remembered.

“What happened?” Ye Xiu asked.

“She forgot to logout of the game. Her character was standing in the wild and someone killed her.” The person involved was calmer than Chen Guo.

“The killer was someone called Breaking Zero, a Level 33 Spellblade. If you see him, take note.” However, Chen Guo remembered better than Tang Rou and told him who the murderer was.

“Got it.” Ye Xiu laughed, “If I see him, I’ll definitely kill him.”

“Good.” Tang Rou nodded her head and then asked, “Did you figure out anything from these guides?”

“This person might not have multiple accounts. With how long the new server has been online, I don’t think there’s enough time to understand the details of every single hidden BOSS to such a degree. Right now, I’m doubting whether this author has even killed these hidden BOSSes. He used previous guides and videos as sources to create such an idiot’s guide.” Ye Xiu said.

“No way.” Chen Guo was astonished.

“If what you’re saying is true, then this person is an extremely amazing new player!” Ye Xiu said.

“He used his imagination to write these guides, yet there aren’t any mistakes?” Chen Guo said.

“That’s why I said he’s amazing.” Ye Xiu said.

“I don’t believe it.”

“After I finish eating, there’s still another six I need to look at!” Ye Xiu quickly ate his meal, got up and ran to continue reading the guides.

Guide after guide, Ye Xiu read them without missing a word. The more he read the more he was sure of his judgement. From these guides, he was able to see several not-so-optimal places, which told Ye Xiu that the author had limited in-game experience. These twelve guides were actually just his imaginations after grasping the theory. However, the logic, rationality, and possibilities of these imaginations weren’t simple.

After reading the last guide, Ye Xiu didn’t have any doubts. These twelve guides didn’t have any mistakes in them, however the weaknesses of the author were completely exposed by some of the details. Ye Xiu had already figured out what type of player this Concealed Light was to some extent. He was very interested in this person.

Looking at the time, it was already almost 11 o’clock. It was almost time to change shifts, so Ye Xiu turned off his computer and went to the front desk. During the weekends, there were quite a lot of all-night customers, so the front desk was extremely busy. After Ye Xiu finished, it was 11:30.

Tang Rou went to her usual spot and the two logged into the game. Ye Xiu went online and searched up Concealed Light’s name, but the character wasn’t online. Ye Xiu sent a friend request, but didn’t receive an answer. When he looked at his friends list, Su Mucheng and Qiao Yifan still weren’t online, but Steamed Bun Invasion was. As a result, he sent Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion a message, telling them to gather in front of the dungeon entrance.

“Okay.”

“Got it.”

The two replied. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim immediately left Congee City and headed to Line Canyon.

“Lord Grim has come online! He’s left the city and is now heading towards Line Canyon!”

“Soft Mist has come online! She’s heading towards Line Canyon. Her character is still Critically Ill!”

“Steamed Bun Invasion has left the Arena. He’s now heading out of the city.”

The three didn’t know that their whereabouts were being tracked by others.

11:41

“Desolate Land, coordinates: 1256, 1475. Cleansing Mist has come online.”

11:44

“Desolate Land, coordinates: 1256, 1466. One Inch Ash has come online.”

New information continued to be transmitted.

Chapter 195 – Pursuit From Every Direction

11:50.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was on his way towards Line Canyon. The world was bustling with excitement as the time approached midnight. Quite a few players, like Ye Xiu, were impatiently waiting for the dungeon entries to refresh, and many of them were hurrying along the same road as well.

Ye Xiu had already contacted Su Mucheng and Qiao Yifan. The two had both gone offline at Desolate Land. As soon as they got on, they headed towards Line Canyon and would arrive before those coming from Congee City.

Outside of Congee City was a vast expanse of barren land. Although there were a few Level 30 monsters scattered here and there, it couldn’t be counted as a leveling area. The spawn rate and the concentration of monsters just wasn’t enough to satisfy a player’s leveling needs. Aside from killing them for quests, no player trained here.

After this, the road split into two. The left path led to Desolate Land, while the right led to Line Canyon. When the players reached this point, their levels were obvious at a glance. Those who went left were all Level 30 and under and those who went right were all Level 30 and above. These were the players who were considered high-leveled on the new server.

When Lord Grim reached the fork in the road, he went to the right. Coincidentally, the several players beside him unexpectedly all went to the right as well.

In the front, many players were heading towards Congee City from Line Canyon. During this time, these players, who were heading in opposite directions, bumped into each other.

A total of eight players, four on the left, four on the right, formed a “V” formation.

The players behind him, those who were going along the same route, had unknowingly gathered close to Lord Grim.

Ye Xiu suddenly realized that something wasn’t right and forced Lord Grim to halt.

The several characters next to him instantly halted as well as if they had received orders.

As I thought!

Ye Xiu didn’t think too much and took the initiative to strike first. His left hand gently moved across the keyboard and executed the first move.

These surrounding players didn’t react slowly either. As soon as everyone halted all at once, they knew that they had been exposed.

The mid-ranged characters immediately began their offensive. Bullets and magic bombarded Lord Grim from several directions. Lord Grim was instantly vaporized. Not even a corpse remained.

Shadow Clone Technique!

Lord Grim’s real body had flashed in front of someone towards his right, just before they were able to begin their offensive.

Without any warning, he lifted his lance and attacked.

Right when the Shadow Clone was extinguished, the players blocking the road were blasted away by Lord Grim with a Falling Flower Palm.

Since he was in a melee form, the players had thought that he was planning to take them all at the same time; but their characters suddenly launched into the sky.

Even after being blown away by the Falling Flower Palm, they still hadn’t figured out what had happened.

These flying bodies opened up the way for Ye Xiu.

He had realized that something was wrong earlier than expected, the players wouldn’t have completed their formation. The instantaneous movement from his Shadow Clone Technique was directed towards the weakest part of the not-yet completed encirclement.

The character that had been blown away smashed into one of their allies. Another character, a Sharpshooter, tried to dodge the human meat bullets, as he fired towards Lord Grim in an attempt to stall him.

Ye Xiu saw what he was doing clearly. Lord Grim, who had been rushing forward in a straight line, suddenly moved horizontally, avoiding the string of bullets. He then leapt forward and spun around 180 degrees. His Thousand Chance Umbrella transformed into its Gun Form and let out a storm of bullets, flying away with an Aerial Fire.

With this sudden increase in speed, the bullets and magic missiles that were flying towards Lord Grim missed. After using Aerial Fire, Lord Grim landed right next to the Sharpshooter. The Sharpshooter didn’t react slowly. He lifted his leg and sent a Knee Strike towards him, but midway, he was stomped onto the ground by Lord Grim. However, Ye Xiu had used Punisher one step faster.

“Bang bang” Lord Grim shot twice and then continued to rush forward. Two players, one to his left and one to his right, had caught up and sandwiched him.

On the left was a Berserker. He raised his hands and leapt up high using Collapsing Mountain. Instead of hacking at Lord Grim, he attacked the empty space where Lord Grim was heading towards. Clearly, this attack wasn’t done to do damage, but rather to block Lord Grim from moving forward.

Lord Grim didn’t seem to have noticed him and continued to rush forward, as if looking for his own death. The Berserker was obviously very happy, but the instant his Collapsing Mountain was about to hit, he suddenly saw a cold light flash. Lord Grim drew his sword and accurately Guarded against the Collapsing Mountain.

The Collapsing Mountain looked mighty and powerful, while Guard looked tiny and weak, but the effect of a skill wasn’t always related to its appearance.

“Dong!” A loud sound rang out. The Berserker’s Greatsword clashed with Lord Grim’s sword. The Guard effect activated. A portion of the damage was mitigated and Lord Grim was pushed back by the attack.

This wasn’t something the player on the right had expected. He had originally anticipated for Lord Grim to be blocked by the Collapsing Mountain, but after Lord Grim unexpectedly Guarded, the knock-back effect had caused him to move to a different spot, one right next to him.

The player panicked. How could he be as quick as Ye Xiu, who already had everything planned out? As he was pushed back, his Thousand Chance Umbrella transformed into a Tonfa. As soon as he arrived next to the player, he immediately Flung him. On that side, that Berserker was still in the middle of the recovery animation from using Collapsing Mountain. His shouting ally flew towards him, and the two were sent rolling into a ball.

Ye Xiu didn’t chase them, but rather Lord Grim immediately turned around and ran. A mob of players were roaring at him while chasing him. A Witch was even more active. He rode his Broom and flew quickly. Lord Grim ran a few steps before suddenly turning around and firing, hitting the Witch’s head. Blood blossomed out like the autumn leaves. In this moment of confusion, the Witch crashed into a tree, causing roars of laughter from behind him.

“What are you laughing at!” The Witch, who had crashed into the tree, climbed back up. His tone wasn’t friendly.

Not many paid attention to him. The others continued to chase after Lord Grim.

“Flank! Flank!!” Someone shouted.

“What f*cking flank! How are we supposed to flank with this speed?”

“Is there anyone in that direction? Find someone to block him for a bit.”

“From where? That place isn’t a leveling area.”

“This guy is doing it on purpose. He deliberately went towards a direction where there isn’t anyone positioned.”

“Just chase him. Cut the bullsh*t. We’ll see how far he can run.”

It seemed like a discussion, but also an argument. The mob of players noisily chased like so.

Ye Xiu turned his head to look at the distance. It wouldn’t be hard for him to get away, but looking at how orderly everyone was, he was afraid to just let the matter go.

These characters didn’t have any guild names next to them, but during the fights with a few of them, Ye Xiu had taken note of a few of their IDs. He searched them up as he ran and they were all Level 33 characters.

Currently, in the tenth server, Level 33 characters were practically all elites from big guilds. Even if they didn’t have a guild name next to them, that didn’t mean that they didn’t belong to a guild.

Ye Xiu suddenly thought of Tang Rou’s Soft Mist dying in the afternoon. Was that an unlucky tragedy or an intentional ploy?

Thinking of this, Ye Xiu immediately sent messages to the other members of the team, asking them for their situation.

“Dead…..” Tang Rou replied.

Her Soft Mist had been in a Critically Ill state the entire time. She had planned to recover as she walked over, but how could she know she was being watched?

In a Critically Ill state, all stats would be reduced by 80%. Besides looking for a NPC doctor to treat it, the state could only be removed by waiting for ten minutes.

Tang Rou had believed that the walk from Congee City to Line Canyon would be long enough for her to recover from the Critically Ill State, so she didn’t go and look for a doctor. But with an 80% reduction in stats, how could experienced players not immediately recognize such a chance.

Against such a weakened character, no matter how great of an expert they were facing, there was nothing to fear. Tang Rou was met with attacks from all sides. There wasn’t much resistance she could put up, and she was sent back to the city again. She was still trying to figure out what had happened!

“Ahh! Ahhhh! Why are there people trying to kill me! Boss!!” Steamed Bun Invasion replied in panic.

“Did you die?’ Ye Xiu hastily asked.

“Not yet. I’m running, but they’re still chasing.” Steamed Bun Invasion said. Ye Xiu had predicted that even if Steamed Bun had encountered this type of situation. He would find all sorts of wretched ways to escape.

As for Su Mucheng and Qiao Yifan, he didn’t need to worry about them. The two were both pro-players. They obviously couldn’t stop this group, but running away with their lives should be something they could do. Plus, those two were together.

“Senior, there are people chasing us!” This was Qiao Yifan’s reply.

“Is it Liu Hao again?” Su Mucheng guessed.

“It’s not clear yet. Are you fine? Are you with One Inch Ash?”

“Yeah, we’ve both ran off. The other side has quite a lot of people!” Su Mucheng said.

“How many?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Dozens…..”

“So many! What level are they?”

“From the ones I’ve seen, they’re all Level 33.” Su Mucheng said.

“A single guild shouldn’t have that many Level 33 characters.” Ye Xiu had a feeling that the situation was a lot worse than he had originally guessed.

Chapter 196 – Temporary Alliance

These players were all from the big guilds. This could simply be seen from their levels. However, it was impossible for a single guild to be able to produce so many high-leveled players. How many guilds had acted out? One, two, three, or more? Maybe even all of them?

No matter what the number was, Ye Xiu wouldn’t be surprised. He clearly understood the current plight the big guilds were in; the dungeons records were being held hostage by him, restricting their development in the tenth server. These big guilds weren’t able to rope him in and they definitely weren’t happy, but how could they surrender so easily?

It didn’t matter whether they were making their decisions based on emotion or reason. In such a hopeless situation, it was very common for people to choose the option of simply eradicating the direct cause.

“Don’t leave the city for now. We’re being watched by others.” Ye Xiu told Tang Rou. Only this complete noob might not have experienced this type of fighting and killing in a game.

“Where are you guys?” He then asked Su Mucheng and Qiao Yifan for their whereabouts.

“We’re still in Desolate Land.” Su Mucheng said.

“The enemies might not be limited to just them. There might be backup that will come later. Some of the lower-leveled players may not directly participate in the battle, but they could be messengers. Head towards a place without any players and we’ll look for an opportunity to group.” Ye Xiu messaged.

“Okay, we’ll send you our coordinates from time to time.” Su Mucheng replied.

“Steamed Bun, where are you?” Ye Xiu decided to instruct Steamed Bun Invasion on what to do next.

“I’m at the outskirts of Congee City, near Hades Village.” Steamed Bun Invasion replied.

“Oh? Not bad! You’ve already run there.” Ye Xiu praised. Steamed Bun Invasion, this guy, even though he was a noob at Glory, it seemed like he had played quite a few games before. He had already taken the lead and found an area without many players.

Hades Village was one of the small villages on the outskirts of Congee City. Players would only come here from time to time for a few quests. Besides a few NPCs for quests, one, there weren’t any monsters, and two, there wasn’t good scenery so no one would come here, even if they were bored.

This was the best type of place to escape to. If not, then whether it was a leveling area or a safe area, there would be players from big guilds everywhere. There would be nowhere to hide.

“Yeah, it’s the closest place.” Steamed Bun Invasion’s reply made Ye Xiu realize that he had thought too highly of Steamed Bun Invasion.

“Did you throw them off yet?” Ye Xiu asked.

“I’m looking.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“Be careful.” Ye Xiu said and had Lord Grim look behind him.

The crowd of Level 33 players still hadn’t given up. They were all chasing behind him. On this strip of flat land, there was nowhere to hide. Ye Xiu also needed to find a place similar to Hades Village, so there was where he was heading towards.

“What’s going on?” A voice asked, not from the game. Ye Xiu turned his head and saw Tang Rou was at the front desk looking at him.

“It’s probably players from the big guilds. We took their dungeon records, which is something they care a lot about.” Ye Xiu summarized the situation.

“Because they weren’t able to take the dungeon records, they resorted to this?” Tang Rou looked down on them.

“Who allowed us to be so amazing?” Ye Xiu laughed.

“What do we do now then?” Tang Rou asked.

“Go to the official site and look up the Heavenly Domain guild rankings. Any of the first twenty ranks could be our enemy right now. Take note of their guild names and keep a look out for those names in-game. Walk around in Congee City and try to go to places with fewer players. Also, check if there are any characters following you. Once your Critically Ill State has worn off, look for an opportunity to leave the city unnoticed and I’ll meet up with you.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay.” Tang Rou nodded her head.”

Desolate Land Leveling Area.

After finding out where Cleansing Mist and Once Inch Ash were, quite a few players had joined in on the chase. Some were Level 33 elites, while others were normal, second-rate characters. Even though they hadn’t been required to do so, after knowing about the affair, they voluntarily joined in.

Seeing a destroyed, empty house, Cleansing Mist and One Inch Ash seized the opportunity to rush into it. The number players chasing behind them hadn’t decreased though. There even appeared to be more of them.

Cleansing Mist looked out from the window on the left while One Inch Ash looked out from the window in the rear.

“There’s no one here.” Qiao Yifan called.

“Go.” Su Mucheng had her character run out. The two characters jumped and crouched in mid-air, escaping from the rear window.

There really weren’t any players behind the house, so the two of them took advantage of the fact that their chasers’ view was blocked, and sprinted away. They jumped gently over a dirt wall and when they landed on the ground, they crouched and moved along the wall.

“Over here.” Qiao Yifan carefully paid attention to the surroundings, while leading the way.

“Places with fewer monsters will naturally have fewer players.” Having little confidence in himself, he explained his reasoning towards Su Mucheng.

“Yeah, let’s hurry!” Su Mucheng said. This was her thought as well.

The dirt wall didn’t stretch too far. Even though their sneaky movements would throw off their enemies temporarily, they would definitely be exposed soon. They only hoped that this would earn them enough time to widen the distance between them.

When they reached the end of the wall, the two characters rushed out; one in the front, and one in the back. The two turned their heads to take a look. Their chasers were currently scattered around the outside of the empty house. Clearly, after finding out that they weren’t there, they were looking around for them.

As soon as they exposed themselves, the enemies immediately began chasing again. Cleansing Mist lifted her gun and sent Anti-Tank Missiles towards them. However, they were too far away and they easily dodged it. Su Mucheng obviously wouldn’t stop to fight with them. She continued to run away like crazy.

“Sis Mu, see those four houses ahead? How about we split up?” Qiao Yifan said. He already suspected that Cleansing Mist was Su Mucheng, but he was too afraid to confirm and too afraid to ask. He believed that he was relatively young in their team, so he called them brothers and sisters: Steamed Bun Bro, Sis Mu, Sis Rou, as well as the most honorable senior.

“I’ll take the one on the right.” Su Mucheng said.

“Then I’ll take that one on the left.”

The two said as they entered their respective houses.

“They hid in houses again!!” The chasers behind them angrily shouted.

The size of these empty houses in Desolate Land were all around the same. They were all damaged beyond repair. Some had windows and some had large holes in the wall. In short, there was always more than one exit. When their targets went in and jumped out through the window, they lost sight of them for a quick moment. They had been thrown off several times already by this sort of tactic and the more those two moved, the more energetic they became.

“Spread out! Surround them!” One person yelled.

Except when they heard this command, only a few of them followed it.

“Spread out!” The person roared.

A few others moved, but the majority stood still.

“We don’t all need to spread out, do we? We just need to have some go around and look.” Someone laughed.

Clearly, this crowd didn’t have a single leader.

The plan to get rid of Lord Grim through force had been prepared in advance, but they had only begun gathering after finding out that Lord Grim and his team had come online. The experts from the big guilds simply chose the targets that they happened to be closest to.

This type of temporarily put-together team didn’t have a leader. Even though they all had the same goal, there were still obstacles.

In the alliance Excellent Dynasty had set up, they weren’t asking the guilds to completely unify. They only hoped that the guilds would put out some man power. First, they went to find Tyrannical Ambition because Tyrannical Ambition was in the most desperate situation and naturally wanted a way to resolve the problem.

This was why, even though the two guilds weren’t usually cooperative, Chen Yehui was confident that the force sent by Tyrannical Ambition would be massive.

However, forming an alliance couldn’t just be said and done. It didn’t matter if it was Tyrannical Ambition’s Jiang You, or the tenth server’s Cold Night, they would be suspicious of Excellent Dynasty.

Lord Grim was a mutual enemy of their guilds —- that was a fact, but at this moment, the other guilds should first be waiting to enjoy the show before acting. And the guild that should have been the happiest was Excellent Dynasty.

However, it was Excellent Dynasty that had asked them to form an alliance with them. It was impossible for them to resolve their desperate situation and no matter how much they thought about it, there seemed to be an ulterior motive.

As a result, they probed each other out for almost three hours. During this, Chen Yehui invited several other guilds to participate. Only then did Jiang You and Chen Yehui gradually comply.

In total, there were 7 guilds that joined in. Naturally, they all had an ambition towards dungeon records. Everyone was originally opponents, but currently, they were all set on eliminating their mutual enemy, Lord Grim.

Among this, what surprised Chen Yehui was that Blue Brook Guild had actually decided to reject their temporary alliance.

Chapter 197 – Opposite Direction

Blue Brook Guild was the first guild to think highly of Lord Grim and ask him to help set a record. Naturally, they were also the first guild to try and rope in Lord Grim. For such a talent to appear, as long as the guilds recognized it, none of them would be indifferent.

But now, Blue Brook Guild was the guild that had been damaged the most by Lord Grim. It didn’t matter how they had first met. From Chen Yehui’s eyes, Blue Brook Guild had to be filled with resentment. Their current situation was even worse than Tyrannical Ambition’s current situation. Who would have thought that they would immediately reject his proposal without hesitation?

Their firm attitude made Chen Yehui feel indescribably sour. He felt that Blue Brook Guild’s calm and resolute rejection wasn’t out of impulse or fear, but rather a strategic decision made after much consideration.

“Could they have realized that Lord Grim is Ye Qiu?” Chen Yehui felt uncertain.

Lord Grim was Ye Qiu. This was information that he definitely wouldn’t tell others about. Ye Qiu’s awe-inspiring skill wasn’t the reason. After all this was still just in the game. If five can’t beat you, then I’ll send ten. If ten isn’t enough, then I’ll send twenty. If twenty isn’t enough, then I’ll send a hundred! It didn’t matter how skilled you were, you would eventually be killed from being attacked from all sides.

The reason Chen Yehui was too afraid to tell others of Lord Grim’s identity was because of Ye Qiu’s fame. A God for ten years! How many Glory fans looked up to him as their idol? If this came out, Chen Yehui was afraid that a bunch of experts would run over to Ye Qiu’s side and beg him to take them in as disciples. Especially his Excellent Dynasty, he didn’t dare tell them. Ye Qiu’s fans were even more loyal here.

In the end, he decided not to probe out Blue Brook Guild to see if they knew.

Fortunately, the number of guilds he had gathered was already enough.

This time, not only did he want to exterminate Lord Grim, but he also wanted to take down Ye Qiu’s team. Taking out his anger on Ye Qiu was for his own selfish reasons. Chen Yehui was more concerned about guild matters. If he didn’t take down the team, he had no way of effectively carrying out his plans.

He had already experienced the battle strength of Ye Qiu’s team when they were together. The strength of Lord Grim, Soft Mist, and Steamed Bun Invasion left him in fear, but this time, their forces had an even greater advantage in numbers. They had also surrounded them separately. Everything seemed to be going smoothly. Chen Yehui listened to the reports from those beneath him and also led others to provide further assistance to their troops, but when he got to Desolate Land, he saw the players scattered about, running around with their target’s whereabouts unknown.

“Where are they?” Chen Yehui saw players from his guild and went over to ask them. He ignored the others. Even though he was a guild leader, the others wouldn’t follow his orders. It was even possible for die-hard Tyrannical Ambition players to secretly ambush him. Chen Yehui didn’t doubt this. This alliance was simply to gather players to deal with Lord Grim. There was no intention of becoming friends.

“They went into the houses. The left and right ones.” An Excellent Dynasty player immediately answered.

“Then what are you waiting for? Chase!” Chen Yehui said.

“We have them surrounded…….” The player said helplessly, while looking at the chaotic scene. Right, they were surrounding them…….

“Our people, come here!!” Chen Yehui didn’t attempt to command the entire scene, and only called over his brothers.

Seeing their guild leader, the Excellent Dynasty players gathered together.

“You two stay here. The others come with me.” Chen Yehui had two players stay in position. Positions that the other guilds weren’t covering.

Players had already begun storming into the houses on the left and right.

“They’re not in here!” The players yelled and leapt out of the window. Those who made a mistake wound up getting stuck in the window, causing players from other guilds to laugh at them.

The others who had spread out and surrounded the houses didn’t find any signs of Cleansing Mist and One Inch Ash.

“Hurry, hurry, hurry!!” Everyone shouted and immediately rushed forward, thinking that their targets had taken the chance to widen their distance.

Under their eyes, in the empty house pressed between the house on the left and on the right, Cleansing Mist and One Inch Ash were quietly crouching in a corner.

Cleansing Mist slowly moved to an opening in a wall and took a quick glance outside.

“Ha ha, we’ve fooled them. Just as expected, they got used to us running in the same direction.” Su Mucheng messaged Qiao Yifan.

“They’re not organized well, which was why I believed they would make such a mistake.” Qiao Yifan said. He had noticed their opponent’s disorderly movements and had come up with this plan after consulting with Su Mucheng.

Before, they had used blind spots to escape. Once, twice, thrice, they made an impression on their enemies. As a result, they made a sudden change in this terrain and didn’t continue running. Instead, after passing through the left and right houses, they snuck into the house in the middle.

Everyone hurried past these houses in order to see where the two had run off to.

“Let’s go.” Su Mucheng told Qiao Yifan. They obviously couldn’t stay here forever. When their enemies realized that there was no sign of them, they would definitely look around and find them. The two wanted to use this opportunity to escape in the opposite direction.

Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash immediately moved to entrance to the house, but just as he exposed half of his body, he immediately went back.

“There are players outside……” Qiao Yifan messaged Su Mucheng.

“What?” Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist also went to the entrance.

“Sorry, Sis Mu…….” Most of this escape plan had been proposed by Qiao Yifan. It was a rare moment of confidence, but in the end, he found that there were enemies left behind. Seeing that he had made a mistake, Qiao Yifan immediately felt upset and scared again.

“No problem, rush out!” Su Mucheng said as she moved out from the room. The enemies that had stayed behind were the players Chen Yehui had ordered. In reality, there wasn’t any error in Qiao Yifan’s plan. He just hadn’t thought that backup would arrive at this moment and there just happened to be a guild leader level character like Chen Yehui.

The new players were naturally unaccustomed to their previous pattern. Chen Yehui also had authority over his players. Qiao Yifan’s plan had been formulated throughout their escape, so new players hadn’t been taken into account.

As soon as the two saw Cleansing Mist rush out, they were surprised, but quickly sent messages to everyone. Cleansing Mist’s artillery shells flew over. The two immediately tried to dodge it, but Su Mucheng’s Anti-Tank Missiles were sent in three different directions, so it would have been better to stay still, but it was too late by the time they realized it.

The smoke from the artillery barrage hadn’t yet dissipated when One Inch Ash rushed in front of one of the players and used a Ghost Slash. The player hastily jumped back and dodged it, but One Inch Ash quickly matched it with a Moonlight Slash. The player wasn’t able to react in time and was launched up into the air by the Moonlight Slash. A Full Moonlight Slash followed after the Moonlight Slash, a very common Ghostblade combo. The Full Moonlight Slash caused the player to fly higher into the air. A series of gun fire followed closely after. Cleansing Mist shot up towards the sky with a Gatling Gun. The brother rolled about in the air and took a while before he fell to the ground.

The other player had wanted to help, but was easily knocked to the ground by a few normal attacks from Qiao Yifan. Qiao Yifan raised his sword and cast a Sword Boundary. Cleansing Mist entered it and fired a Laser Rifle and Cannonball. The buffed damage and explosiveness from the Sword Soul added to its might. These two unfortunate players didn’t have any chance of fighting back. If they weren’t rolling around in the sky, then they were rolling around in the dirt. After a short moment, they turned into two corpses.

Chen Yehui received the messages from the two who stayed behind and immediately led his Excellent Dynasty players to return and chase them. The other guild’s players saw this and stared blankly. Without anyone guiding them, they just did what everyone else did and followed along. In the end, when they returned to the rooms, there was no sight of them.

“Where are you?” Chen Yehui asked the two players.

“Where are they?’ The other guilds all asked Chen Yehui.

“Dead…..” Those two’s replies were quick, but Chen Yehui wasn’t able to reply to the other players.

“Everyone split up and search…..” Chen Yehui looked around and then helplessly said. There were quite a few destroyed houses, walls, and holes, and it wasn’t easy to check every one of them.

“F*ck, what are we looking for?” The other guilds’ players didn’t know what had happened and were cursing.

“Those two players hid over here and took the opportunity when we rushed out to kill our two brothers. Right now, we don’t know where they escaped to.” Chen Yehui wasn’t happy either, but had no choice but to explain it to these people.

With this, there was nothing they could complain about. Search!

Everyone split up and searched around, but they didn’t know that Cleansing Mist and One Inch Ash had already returned to the destroyed house and jumped out of the window, playing another game of opposite direction.

Chapter 198 – A Bro at the Bottom of a Well

Outskirts of Congee City: Hades Village. Inside a dried up well. Steamed Bun Invasion stood upright and exposed a small bit of himself in order to take a quick sweep of the surroundings.

Initially, Steamed Bun Invasion had randomly hopped down during his escape. His reason for doing so: because it was close. Unexpectedly, this seldom-visited well gave him a hiding place. Steamed Bun Invasion had bravely begun a game of hide-and-seek with his pursuers.

The originally tranquil village had become a noisy mess because of Steamed Bun Invasion’s intrusion. The NPCs were still calmly following their predetermined routes, but the rampaging footsteps of a dozen players, who were chasing Steamed Bun Invasion, resounded throughout the village. The communication between them also came into Steamed Bun Invasion’s ears from time to time.

Steamed Bun Invasion hastily ducked down and listened intently to the what his pursuers were saying.

“Where’d he go?”

“He can’t have run too far. He has to be in the village.”

“What a cunning guy to run to such a place.”

Some footsteps were far. Some were close. They were clearly looking everywhere. Steamed Bun Invasion was listening and just happened to be pondering whether he should stand up straight to take a quick glance around, when a white light suddenly flashed in front of him and a character appeared. Not waiting for Steamed Bun Invasion to open his mouth, that character cried out in fright: “Who are you?”

“Quiet!” Steamed Bun Invasion hurriedly stopped the person from saying anything more.

“What a coincidence! To think I’d bump into someone in this type of place.” This person had absolutely no idea what was going on and continued talking.

Steamed Bun Invasion heard footsteps coming closer and closer. He didn’t know whether it was because of the noise coming from here. Even though this type of hiding place was difficult to find, if he was found, then it’d be difficult to escape from. Steamed Bun Invasion understood this, so as soon as he heard footsteps coming closer, he wouldn’t take any risks and immediately jump outside to escape.

Just as he was about to jump out, he suddenly heard the guy in front of him shout out loudly: “Huh? Steamed Bun Invasion? Are you the Steamed Bun Invasion in Lord Grim’s team on the dungeon record rankings?”

“Yup, that’s me, but right now, I don’t have time to accept your interview. I’m currently hiding from an intense chase. I’m about to rush out!” Steamed Bun Invasion said with a low voice when he suddenly leapt out from the well. He looked around him and sure enough, people were heading towards the well. Seeing him come out, they immediately shouted: “He’s over here!”

Steamed Bun Invasion didn’t stop. As soon as he landed on the ground, he took off.

“Hey, wait up!” The person in the well yelled and then immediately took off too. However, he didn’t use enough strength and didn’t jump high enough. His character’s two feet hit the side of the well, and he was knocked back into it.

None of the pursuers knew who this guy was, so they also called: “There’s even one waiting to ambush us here!”

“Uh oh! It might be a trap!” Someone said. Some of the players immediately stopped, fearing that there might be hidden troops hiding in the well.

The number of players chasing Steamed Bun Invasion wasn’t as numerous as the number of players chasing Su Mucheng and Qiao Yifan, though because of this, they were more unified. There were a dozens players here, from a total of two guilds and they weren’t mortal enemies like Tyrannical Ambition and Excellent Dynasty either, so there was room for discussion.

In this short moment of hesitation, that brother in the well used enough strength this time and jumped out of it. This character was wearing cloth armor and his hands clutched a magic rod, indicating that he was a Mage. After jumping out of the well, he ignored the pursuers and chased after Steamed Bun Invasion.

Seeing him run, the players realized that it didn’t seem to be an ambush. The chances of one were too small, so they immediately began chasing.

Each of the two guilds had separate leaders, so there wasn’t much confusion. The pursuers chased after him closely. Steamed Bun Invasion hastily glanced around to see if there were any places to hide, like before. Just as he was looking, he heard someone yell from behind him: “Run towards the left.”

The voice sounded a bit familiar. Steamed Bun Invasion didn’t think too much about who had said it and headed towards the left. There wasn’t anything special to the left, only an ordinary straw cottage. Steamed Bun Invasion ran behind the straw cottage and temporarily left his pursuer’s line of sight.

“Jump in from that window.” At this moment, that voice came again. Steamed Bun Invasion searched for the so-called “window” when he realized who the person giving him directions was. It was that bro he met at the bottom of the well.

“You’re a really good guy!” Steamed Bun Invasion said and saw which window the bro was referring to and jumped in. The bro from the bottom of the well quickly caught up and crouched down to jump in like Steamed Bun Invasion. The first time, he crashed into the window sill and fell down. The second time, he crashed again and fell. The third time….. Steamed Bun Invasion was at a loss: “What are you doing!”

“I’m jumping in.” The bro from the well said.

“I really can’t tell.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

The bro from the well understood that he wasn’t skilled enough. His movements weren’t precise enough. After failing three times, he gave up and continued to run left.

“Hey, where are you going?” Steamed Bun Invasion stuck his head out and asked him.

“Put your head back! Add me as a friend and then let’s talk.” The bro from the well ran as he turned his head back to say.

Steamed Bun Invasion pulled back his head and received a system prompt: Concealed Light requests to be your friend.

After accepting the invite, he received a message from Concealed Light: “After 8 seconds, come out through the door.”

Even though Steamed Bun Invasion didn’t know what was going on, he did as he was told. He counted one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, and then ran out of the straw cottage’s door, bumping into Concealed Light, who had just come in from the entrance.

“Over here!” Concealed Light led the way, while Steamed Bun Invasion followed. The two weaved around Hades Village. At first, they could still hear the footsteps and voices of the pursuers, but gradually, the sounds died down and seemed to have returned to the sounds of the NPC’s slow steps and calm village.

“Did we throw them off?” Steamed Bun Invasion glanced around.

“Quiet!” After confirming the situation, it was Concealed Light’s turn to warn Steamed Bun Invasion.

One of Steamed Bun Invasion’s strength was that he was able to listen to other’s suggestions and immediately shut his mouth. At this moment, Concealed Light’s line of sight fell to the Sandstorm Claw that Steamed Bun Invasion was holding, a Brawler weapon.

“Your weapon isn’t an Orange weapon?” Concealed Light suddenly asked.

“Yeah.”

“Why don’t you use one?”

“I don’t have one.”

“What do you mean you don’t have one?”

“It was too expensive. Senior wouldn’t buy it for me.”

The two talked like this with one asking and one replying, but they weren’t on the same page. This Concealed Light was that author of the Idiot’s Series, the Level 32 Summoner, Concealed Light, and was absolutely confident in his judgement. He was certain that Lord Grim’s team all had Orange equipment, but seeing that Steamed Bun Invasion didn’t have one, he refused to believe his judgement was wrong. His intent wasn’t being picked up by Steamed Bun Invasion, who was answering the questions honestly.

“Senior? You mean Lord Grim?” Concealed Light said.

“Yeah! You know him?’ Steamed Bun Invasion was pleasantly surprised.

“I don’t…..” Concealed Light said, but was still confused on how his judgement had been wrong: “How do you not have an Orange weapon?”

“Because we didn’t have enough money.” Steamed Bun Invasion replied as before.

“Their footsteps are coming closer.” Steamed Bun Invasion suddenly heard footsteps.

“Let’s go along this road! We’ll definitely be able to run back to the city before they catch up.” Concealed Light began running forward.

“I’m not going back to the city.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“Then where are you going?”

“I’m getting ready in a bit to meet up with senior.” Steamed Bun Invasion said, “Are you going back to the city? That’s perfect! You can lead them away and I’ll be good then.”

Concealed Light coughed up blood. Shouldn’t he be the one without any problems? He still didn’t know why Steamed Bun was being chased. The only reason he was helping Steamed Bun Invasion was because he was a member of the dungeon record team, one of his researched subjects, a character whose equipment he had deduced.

A luxurious Orange equipped team. This was an unrealistic argument and Concealed Light understood this.

Compared to the other Idiot’s Guides, he spent more time for the Boneyard record. Unfortunately, that was the only conclusion he could come up with. He was absolutely confident, but he just couldn’t convince others of it. He really hoped that he could verify his judgement, but he was never able to.

Even after knowing that Steamed Bun Invasion didn’t have an Orange weapon, Concealed Light refused to give up.

Steamed Bun Invasion’s very casual suggestion to let Concealed Light lead the pursuers away did make him want to cough blood, but he wouldn’t argue over something like this. He turned his head to look at Steamed Bun Invasion and suddenly shouted: “Wow! You’re Level 31 now? You’ve probably switched equipment! You previously used a Level 28 Orange weapon right?”

“Nope. I’ve never used one before.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“Impossible.” Concealed Light was concerned about this.

“Why aren’t you going back to the city! They’re coming closer.” Steamed Bun Invasion was concerned about this.

“They’re not chasing me, so why should I care?” Concealed Light said.

“What? Then why are you running?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked in curiosity.

“……..’ Concealed Light was speechless.

“If you won’t run, then I’ll be running.” Once Steamed Bun Invasion saw that he wasn’t going to lure them away and there was no way he could stay in the same place for too long, he immediately began running again.

“No! No! You can’t go that way!” Seeing where Steamed Bun Invasion was running, Concealed Light blurted out.

Chapter 199 – The Escape Member: Concealed Light

Concealed Light and Steamed Bun Invasion weren’t friends. It was just that when he found that Steamed Bun Invasion had run onto a route where he would be quickly discovered, his auto-correct function activated and autonomously shouted out.

“Okay, then where should I run to?” Steamed Bun Invasion immediately returned.

“Over here.” Concealed Light continued to lead the way.

“Where are you guys meeting up at?” Concealed Light asked. He might as well just send him there.

“I dunno.” Steamed Bun Invasion said bluntly.

Concealed Light seemed to have stumbled on the flat ground. It looked as if he had accidentally pressed the crouch command. In that instant, his finger had clearly touched the wrong key.

“If you don’t know, then where are we running to?” Concealed Light said.

“How should I know? You’re the one leading.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

Concealed Light coughed up blood: “You say a place and I’ll bring you there.”

“Wait! Let me ask!” Steamed Bun Invasion sent a message to Lord Grim.

“Where are you right now?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Hades Village.”

“What? You’re still there? Have you escaped yet?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Not yet.”

“How many pursuers are there?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Uh… let me ask.” Steamed Bun Invasion replied.

Ask? Ye Xiu was confused.

‘Hey, how many players are over there?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked the lead, Concealed Light.

“How should I know? It’s not like they’re chasing me. Maybe a dozen or so!” Concealed Light said.

“A dozen.” Steamed Bun Invasion answered Ye Xiu’s question.

“How’d you find out?” Ye Xiu had a hard time understanding.

“I met a bro at the bottom of a well and he told me.” Steamed Bun Invasion replied.

A bro at the bottom of a well? Ye Xiu was getting more and more confused, but thinking of Steamed Bun Invasion’s brain, he didn’t ask to find out.

“Come to Congee Forest!” Ye Xiu replied.

Glory’s map didn’t only consist of uninterrupted leveling areas. There were also quite a few commonplace transition maps. Similar to the numerous villages scattered around the outskirts of Congee City, these places were mostly used for quests.

Congee Forest was this type of place. Outside of Congee City, it was a forest close to Line Canyon. When there weren’t players there for quests, it was even more empty than those small villages.

“We’re meeting up at Congee Forest.” Steamed Bun Invasion quickly reported to Concealed Light.

“Here!” Concealed Light immediately figured out which direction to go in. Steamed Bun Invasion didn’t say anything further and directly followed behind him.

Concealed Light felt a bit lonely as well as confused.

Isn’t this Steamed Bun Invasion too simple? It’s not like we know each other, how could he just follow along without even asking who I am?

Concealed Light was puzzled over this question, but more importantly: he wanted to obtain approval. Every one of the guides Concealed Light had published had been seen by readers as nonsense, making him feel very angry. His guides were all correct. Why did those people say his guides were unrealistic? Why weren’t they saying their skill wasn’t good enough?

At this moment, he was leading Steamed Bun Invasion away from the pursuers with ease. Yet this Steamed Bun Invasion wasn’t even asking him how he could do it. Concealed Light felt very lonesome. He finally couldn’t take it anymore: “Do you know why we have to run this way?”

“Why?” Steamed Bun Invasion blurted out.

“Because the pursuers are around five coordinates away from us. By going in this direction, the positions of those five coordinates behind us are held by four houses that are blocking their view. If we went that direction you were previously going along, they’d have been able to find you in less than 10 seconds.” Concealed Light happily explained. He was looking forward to Steamed Bun Invasion’s next question. For example: how did you know that they were five coordinates behind.

“Oh.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

Concealed Light’s fingers went astray again. This time it was his right hand. He accidentally left-clicked and he waved his magic rod.

“So you’re saying that the people behind us aren’t able to see where we’re going?” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“Yes! Yes! The following routes I’m going to bring you along will all make the pursuers unable to figure out where we are. This is why we’re able to shrug them off so easily.” Concealed Light said.

“But it looks like there are people in front of us.” Steamed Bun Invasion suddenly said.

“In front?” Concealed Light looked forward but didn’t see anyone.

“I heard footsteps. My 1.5 hearing.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

1.5 hearing……. Concealed Light was confused, but at this moment, just as Steamed Bun Invasion said, a player suddenly jumped out from behind a rock.

“Maybe he’s just passing by…… If he’s with those guys behind us, then our position’s been exposed. From the route those guys will choose to take, we should…….”

“Kill him!” Steamed Bun Invasion had already gone up to kill him.

Sure enough, the person behind the rock wasn’t some passerby. When he saw Steamed Bun invasion, he immediately took out his sword and rushed forward, a Blade Master.

Concealed Light had no choice but to enter the battle as well. As he moved, he began muttering: “Brawlers and Blade Masters have mid-ranged CC skills. Both sides will need some time to close in on each other. Since they will restrict each other, I should summon after going around the Blade Master, to his rear. Brawlers have Brick Buster and Sand Toss, two mid-ranged skilled. If the skills are used one after the other, then he can control the Blade Master for ten seconds. With my movement speed, I can only choose to head towards the 10 o’clock position. Even though I’ll be somewhat close to the Blade Master, there’s a stone wall over there, which can be used to block the Blade Master’s Sword Draw, so I won’t actually be in his attack range. Then, once I get behind the wall, I’ll be behind the Blade Master. First, I’ll summon Thunder Spirit, the Stun effect from the attack can be used to match with the Brawler’s……”

“Hey! What are you muttering?” Steamed Bun Invasion heard Concealed Light whispering something, but couldn’t hear clearly. While he asked, he rushed forward, sending a Brick flying forward.

“F*ck! How can you waste your Brick like that!” Concealed Light saw this scene and immediately shouted.

“So what?” Steamed Bun Invasion replied to him and used the opportunity to close in while the opponent was dodging. This Blade Master wasn’t weak. After dodging the Brick, he drew his sword: “Sword Draw”.

Steamed Bun Invasion rolled to dodge the sword light and reached in front of the Blade Master. He raised his hands and used an Uppercut.

The Blade Master moved back and dodged. He then followed up with a Lunge to counterattack. This guy had clearly spent a few skill points on this skill. This skill no longer made only two stabs, but four.

Four sword lights stabbed forth towards Steamed Bun Invasion. As each one flew forward, Steamed Bun Invasion leapt back. The sword tips flashed in front of him, but never hit. At this moment, Steamed Bun Invasion swung his hand and threw a Sand Toss at him.

Sand Toss was considered a Magic Attack, so the Blade Master’s Guard had no effect, but the low damage skill could be endured as long as he wasn’t blinded.

This Blade Master didn’t dodge this Sand Toss and instead, turned his head towards a different direction. At the same time, he followed up with an attack and a Triple Slash headed towards Steamed Bun Invasion. Just with this skill, it could be seen that this Blade Master wasn’t ordinary.

Concealed Light predicted that the two sides wouldn’t meet each other in close combat for ten seconds, but Steamed Bun Invasion used a Brick and a forward roll to directly close in on the opponent. Concealed Light was still going forward with his original plan, but while he was going around, because of Steamed Bun Invasion’s Sand Toss, the Blade Master’s head suddenly turned to his direction, catching him.

Concealed Light panicked, but saw that the Blade Master’s sword was still aimed at Steamed Bun Invasion.

Steamed Bun Invasion had used this instant to complete his movement. When the Blade Master’s Triple Slash flew past, Steamed Bun Invasion lifted his hand and clawed, clasping onto the Blade Master’s throat, pushing him into the wall.

Knee Strike, Slap, Inject Poison……

Steamed Bun Invasion ignored the Blade Master’s struggling and used the time while the opponent’s defense was reduced from the Strangle to quickly send a few attacks forward.

After the Strangle finished, Steamed Bun Invasion floated to the side of the Blade Master’s body and accurately smashed a Brick into the Blade Master’s head, inducing a Dizzy effect. Steamed Bun Invasion smoothly Applied Poison to his weapon and followed up with a Combo. The Blade Master was trapped against the wall and had no way of escaping. Any place he tried to dodge to was met by a block from Steamed Bun Invasion. The two sides traded health, but clearly, Steamed Bun Invasion had the advantage.

Not long after, Steamed Bun Invasion took down half of the Blade Master’s life and beat the Blade Master into the wall. The Blade Master’s life continued to drop until he fell. Steamed Bun Invasion looked around and saw that Concealed Light was jumping again and again behind a broken-down wall and crashing into it.

“Bro, what are you doing? Are you trying to rape that wall?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked.

Concealed Light was extremely gloomy. He just wanted to jump onto the wall, but the wall was a bit tall and with his jumping strength, he had to grasp the distance and timing in order to succeed. But as he was trying, unknowingly, that Blade Master had already been defeated by Steamed Bun Invasion, yet he still hadn’t jumped onto the wall.

“Hurry up and run. They’re here.” By the time they finished killing the Blade Master, the pursuers finally appeared in their view and were quickly catching up.

Concealed Light didn’t try and fight with the wall anymore and quickly went around it.

“Which way?’ Steamed Bun Invasion asked.

“Uh, over here……” After seeing where those pursuers were coming from, Concealed Light continued to lead the way. Except this time, he was no longer as proud as before.

“You have really weird tastes. What astrological sign are you?” This time, Steamed Bun Invasion took the initiative to ask.

Chapter 200 – PKPKPKPKPKPK

Congee Forest. Ye Xiu told everyone to meet here. At this moment, he was also rushing towards there with his Lord Grim. However, he hadn’t fully thrown off the pursuers yet.

Even though he had fully utilized his abilities and stamina to widen the distance, he had no way of completely breaking away from the pursuers. The other side had many, many players and any random player nearby could be one of their eyes.

Escaping by using the pursuers’ dead angles. Ye Xiu was also using this type of method.

However, as he ran, he suffered from a barrage of trash talk.

“PK! PK! PK! PK! PK!”

Right when it was almost midnight, Huang Shaotian’s Flowing Tree unexpectedly came online and once again began bothering Ye Xiu to fight him in the Arena.

“I’m busy!” Ye Xiu replied firmly.

“You can run dungeons later!!” Huang Shaotian said.

“If you know that I’m going to run dungeons, why don’t you come on earlier?”

“If I come on earlier, are you there? Are you there? Are you there?” Huang Shaotian replied.

“Uh, not today…… tomorrow!” Ye Xiu thought. Today, he had gone to read Concealed Light’s Idiot’s Guides. He really hadn’t been online in the evening and had only come on at 11:30.

“You said it!”

“Yeah.”

“Your word counts!

“Yeah.”

“Okay then!” Huang Shaotian said and then went quiet.

These Gods were both players with frightening hand speed. Ye Xiu chatted while he made his Lord Grim continue running. His speed hadn’t slowed down much.

However after only quietly running for a few minutes, he suddenly received another message. Since he had to pay attention to Su Mucheng and the other team members’ situation, Ye Xiu had to keep his chat box open. But when he looked, he saw that it was Huang Shaotian’s Flowing Tree again: “PKPKPKPKPKPK!!!!!!”

Not waiting for Ye Xiu to reply, another message came: “It’s ‘tomorrow’.” A happy face emoticon even came after this.

Ye Xiu looked at when the message was sent: 00:01:08. He was speechless.

“Hurry up hurry up hurry up. You said ‘tomorrow’. It’s already tomorrow.” Huang Shaotian continued to type.

“Come to Congee Forest.” Ye Xiu replied.

“For what?” Huang Shaotian asked.

“It’s a long story. If you come, you’ll know.”

Congee Forest was completely silent. Huang Shaotian’s Flowing Tree came and looked around, but only saw two players who were leaving after finishing their quests. There wasn’t any sign of Lord Grim.

“I’m here. Where are you?” Huang Shaotian messaged.

“Almost there.”

“Why here?” Huang Shaotian asked.

“PK.”

“F*ck! I’m going to use my main account.” Huang Shaotian shouted.

“Not in the Arena. Real PK in the wild.” Ye Xiu replied.

“You’re four levels higher than me! Aren’t you ashamed of yourself?” Huang Shaotian replied.

“I thought you’d feel ashamed.” Ye Xiu said.

“What should I be ashamed of?”

“Don’t you feel ashamed?”

“Why should I be ashamed?”

“That’s good. As long as you don’t feel ashamed.”

“Hey hey! What are you saying!!” As soon as this message was sent, Huang Shaotian’s Flowing Tree left the forest and saw Lord Grim in front of him, alternating between moving slowly and quickly. He was using the common, pro-player technique for optimizing stamina usage and was running towards him.

Huang Shaotian’s Flowing Tree met up with him and just as he was about to say something, he immediately saw a wave of dust rolling forward not far behind Lord Grim.

“What’d you do?” When Lord Grim reached in front of him, Huang Shaotian asked.

“Didn’t you want to PK? Go up, hero!” Ye Xiu said.

“Are you joking? Do you know who I am? How could I bully normal players!” Huang Shaotian shouted.

“Weren’t you asking why you should be ashamed?’ Ye Xiu asked.

“F*ck. I wasn’t talking about this.” Huang Shaotian felt depressed. He had used ‘tomorrow’ to trick him, which Ye Xiu responded with his own “ashamed” counter.

“Yo, there’s quite a lot of people. What’d you do?” Huang Shaotian looked at the incoming pursuers. There were at least twenty or thirty people. To gather up like this just for a single person, this was rarely seen.

“I set dungeon records.” Ye Xiu said.

Huang Shaotian stared blankly for a bit and then realized what was going on. He laughed out loud: “Serves you right! To let you be so arrogant. To let you be so shameless! What’s your identity? Stealing records from new server players! How shameful!”

“What’s so shameful about that? Right now, I’m just a normal player too. Taking records is normal.” Ye Xiu plainly said, “But you! You probably haven’t seen such a large mob in a while! Are you scared?”

“Tch. How could I go against normal players. I’ll keep my distance from you.” Huang Shaotian said. He really did let his Flowing Tree pull away from Lord Grim a bit. At the moment, a large mob of characters stormed into the forest.

“There’s someone here!!” Quite a few noticed Huang Shaotian’s Flowing Tree.

In this team of pursuers, there was a guild leader level character, Samsara’s tenth server leader, Lonely Drink. He had failed last time to rope in Lord Grim. He had been especially infuriated when the other side used Ctrl+C and Ctrl+V to reply to him. In the current alliance, he was one of the more active members. When he heard where Lord Grim’s and his team’s whereabouts were, he didn’t choose to go to the nearest member, but chose to directly pursue Lord Grim. It couldn’t be denied that the reason was mostly due to his own selfish reasons.

“Flowing Tree…..” Lonely Drink saw this ID. He recited it and felt that it was a bit familiar.

“He’s the one who helped Lord Grim set the Boneyard record!” Someone suddenly shouted in the crowd.

Some shouted out in surprise at Flowing Tree’s appearance. Others were checking the dungeon record rankings. It seemed like Samsara’s players were the calmest. They had a guild leader, and with a leader here, they only had to wait for his orders.

“He’s with Lord Grim. Don’t be polite.” Lonely Drink decided. As soon as Samsara’s people heard their guild leader speak, they immediately rushed forward without hesitation. With people leading the way, the players from the other guilds followed as well. Thirty members suddenly headed towards Flowing Tree together.

“F*ck, what are you doing?” Huang Shaotian was startled. How did he pull in aggro? He immediately had Flowing Tree run further into Congee Forest.

“Don’t let any of them go!” Lonely Drink shouted.

Those that were under him listened to him as well as a few of the players from the other guilds. A mob of players split into two groups; one group went to chase Flowing Tree, while the other group ran towards Lord Grim.

Ye Xi’s response was the same as Huang Shaotian’s. He also had Lord Grim run further into the forest. Flowing Tree wasn’t too far from him and at this moment, he understood what was going on. He began chatting angrily, nonstop. Ye Xiu completely ignored him as if he wasn’t listening.

The two ran someplace and then suddenly split; one left, one right. Right at this moment, the pursuers saw the two split. Lonely Drink didn’t hesitate and chased after Lord Grim. A few players made a suggestion: If there are already people chasing on that side, then we should go to this side! As a result, the remaining players rushed towards Flowing Tree.

Just as they began running, someone shouted: “Wait.”

No one waited. Everyone continued to chase. This person could only run while saying: “I just searched up Flowing Tree. He’s Level 27! Level 27! Why are we be chasing him?”

Everyone heard this. Some players stopped because what he said was true.

Level 27. At this level, the character could only run Boneyard, but that was already past them.

The game progressed this way. The closer they got to the end-game, the early-game records would become less and less valuable. For example, the Frost Forest record. When the players were all Level 20, when the record was set, everyone felt that the team was extremely amazing and that the guild was powerful.

But this “amazing” impression wouldn’t continue being kept. It needed other records to keep up the image and it needed records for dungeons at the peak of the current state of the game. Only these high-leveled dungeons would be noted by players.

At the present state of the game, it would be great to go up on TV for the Line Canyon dungeon records. Even if they weren’t the final holders of the record, it would still be more valuable than setting a new one for Frost Forest. Plus, whoever held the final record could use it as proof of their strength.

All of the experienced players understood this. The reason Chen Yehui was able to create such a movement was because of this. As long as they could kill Lord Grim and his team a few times, they would be able to stall their leveling speed and restrict their development.

As long as they could widen the distance in their levels, future dungeon records would be fought for as usual by the big guilds, and by the time Lord Grim leveled to there, the records would no longer be as valuable. By then, the tenth server players would already be paying attention to higher-leveled dungeons.

By maintaining this type of level difference, it didn’t matter how great Lord Grim’s strength was because the impact he’d have on the big guilds’ development would be greatly reduced.

Chapter 201 – The Trash’s End

Those who understood the situation knew that if Lord Grim was Level 27, they wouldn’t waste their time on him, let alone his little underling.

Level 27, Blade Master.

After a few players confirmed the situation, the torrent of anger immediately dissipated. The majority of them were already getting ready to turn around. The slower players received messages from their friends saying: “Don’t bother with that piece of trash. Hurry up and chase after Lord Grim! Don’t let him escape!”

Trash!!

Huang Shaotian heard this phrase and became furious. Moreover, it seemed to be directed at him. As a pro-player, he had some resistance towards trash talk. However, each player had their own ways of dealing with it. Some ignored it. Some countered it. As one of the experts in the Alliance at trash talking who made the Alliance change the rules solely for him, Huang Shaotian was the latter.

“F*CK!” A roar resounded throughout the forest.

“Whoever said ‘trash’, stand where you are! Let me teach you how to spell ‘trash’.” Huang Shaotian’s Flowing Tree unexpectedly turned around and chased after them.

“Who said it? Who? Who? Where are you running? A bunch of Level 33 players and you’re afraid of a tiny Level 27 Blade Master? If I’m trash, then what are you? Maybe you’re non-recyclable trash? Completely worthless trash? That’s right! I’m talking about you guys! 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 14 pieces of trash running nice and orderly! Are you all lining up waiting to be put in the dumpster? But wait! Did you forget that you were non-recyclable? Have some awareness! You should just dig a hole to bury yourself in there! Stop polluting the environment. Every second you exist…….”

“Shut up!!” Someone finally erupted, a Blade Master as well. But he wasn’t the only one that wanted to jump out, he just happened to be a bit faster. His “Shut up!” temporarily interrupted Huang Shaotian. In this moment of silence, the others who had become riled up took the chance to clear up their anger as well.

“Hm? So it was you? Good. A Blade Master as well. But it does seem like you’re different than normal Blade Masters. Seeing how impatient you are, could you be the legendary…….” Using his voice for the following words wouldn’t bring about the desired reactions, so Huang Shaotian quickly changed to typing. A giant word bubble floated above his head and used the largest 25 size font to write “Trash Master”.

“Trash Master”

“Trash Master”

“Trash Master”

“Trash Master’

……

Huang Shaotian’s hands moved like a blur. In that instant, huge word bubbles piled on top of each other towards the clouds. That Level 33 Blade Master had already gone mad with fury and rushed forward with his sword drawn.

For an expert trash talker like Huang Shaotian, he didn’t need any thinking or feeling to do such a thing. He could even do it even if he was talking to a rock.

He didn’t actually have any malicious intent. It was just something he was used to doing during matches. It was just that in official matches, he could only type in chat box. However, in the game, he could use word bubbles and his own voice to make his trash talk more impactful. How could ordinary players stand such attacks?

In gaming terms, Huang Shaotian’s trash talk wasn’t done through a major summon, but rather through a never ending combo. It made others want to kill him simply because they wanted him to shut up.

Because his verbal attacks had only been directed at one individual, the others felt much better about themselves. After seeing that Blade Master rush forward, they quickly came back to reality.

“We’ll leave this guy to you! We’re going to continue chasing Lord Grim.” Someone yelled this and then ran. There really weren’t many who took this Level 27 player seriously.

The Blade Master didn’t even respond. His attention was clearly, completely focused on Flowing Tree. He raised his sword and initiated with a Berserker’s Collapsing Mountain, showing his intent on chopping Flowing Tree into pieces.

Huang Shaotian continued cursing and appeared very irritated. However, in reality, he was very calm. He didn’t even need to dodge this Collapsing Mountain because the other side was clearly too agitated. The attack had been made too early and wouldn’t hit Flowing Tree.

All in all, this Blade Master was still an elite. Halfway through the animation, he realized that he had messed up. He had used the skill too early and would miss Flowing Tree. He knew that Flowing Tree seemed to understand this, but why was he just standing there doing nothing?

Collapsing Mountain crashed to the ground and the shock wave sent the surrounding grass flying. It had scraped Flowing Tree’s foot, but there was still no movement from him. This attack didn’t inflict any damage onto him.

“Sword Draw!” Huang Shaotian shouted and then used a Sword Draw.

The Blade Master who was still in recovery from the Collapsing Mountain was hit and went flying. If this wasn’t in game, that Blade Master’s head would have been chopped in half like a watermelon.

“Triple Slash!” Huang Shaotian was like a character from a comic, shouting the name of the skill before using it. Flowing Tree slid forward and the first slash hit the flying Blade Master. For the second slash, Flowing Tree suddenly shifted directions and slid diagonally. The second slash hit the Blade Master again. The third slash was the same and the opposing Blade Master, who was about to hit the ground, was lifted into the sky once again.

Huang Shaotian was able to make two directional changes in what was supposed to be a straight-lined Triple Slash. Perhaps many players could do this, but to do so in the minimum three steps while launching the target into the sky —- that was rarely seen.

“Watch my sword! Watch my sword! Lunge! Falling Light Blade! Upward Slash! Sword Draw! Triple Slash…….” Huang Shaotian continued to shout out moves, “Watch my sword!” indicated a normal attack. From the sky to the ground and up to the sky again. Under Huang Shaotian’s continuous attacks, this Blade Master had no way of resisting.

Every time the other side saw a way of getting out, it was already too late. He tapped his keyboard furiously, but every move he made was within the other side’s calculations. He was interrupted again and again……..

Huang Shaotian’s skill shouts caught the attention of the players who went to chase after Lord Grim. Some turned around to glance back and their gaze never moved away afterwards.

It was something they shouldn’t be saying, but it was true. Their ally had been destroyed….. Only the word beautiful could describe the scene.

Flowing Tree only had an ordinary Blue Lightsaber in his hands, but the light that came from it could only be described as extraordinary. Every time the blue light flashed, it would circle back and flash again. The sword’s light connected together as blood continuously splattered from that Level 33 Blade Master’s body, making the scene appear more beautiful and cruel at the same time.

The number of players who stopped to watch, who turned around, and who were dumbstruck grew larger and larger.

They watched and watched and completely forgot about helping their ally. These types of beautiful attacks could only be seen in videos. Real battle? Forget about real battles, even if the opponent was just a wooden log, no one was confident they’d be able to perform such flowing attacks.

“This person’s incredible……”

Finally, someone couldn’t resist blurting this out.

As soon as this was said, everyone returned to reality. Their ally was about to die under their watch.

“Everyone, up!” Someone yelled and everyone moved.

Even though they weren’t very unified, they couldn’t just watch as one of their allies died beneath their eyes. If they didn’t help when they could have, it’d be a bit embarrassing.

“Clerics, where are you? Heal him!” Someone shouted. However, there wasn’t a single Cleric among the fourteen players there.

“Ta ta ta ta ta …….”

Gunfire rang out. A Launcher fired a Gatling Gun and bullets flew towards Flowing Tree in a straight line.

A sword light flashed.

Flowing Tree used Triple Slash again. The Launcher shook his gun and fired towards where he thought Flowing Tree would move to. How could he know that after the first slash, he would change directions and then change again for the third one to go back to his original position? But he had already fired and his bullets hit nothing but air.

“Triangle Triple Slash!” Witnessing this Triple Slash, a few players blurted out the name of this move in astonishment.

Triangle Triple Slash. The move wasn’t too difficult to do. However, different players would have different effects using this skill. Huang Shaotian’s usage of this skill had no faults. That gorgeous sword technique along with this Triple Slash plus his non-stop mouth, everyone understood: the Blade Master in front of them was a great expert. A Level 27 looking down on them. That demeanor seemed like that of a God.

And at this moment, that Blade Master was no longer able to continue under Flowing Tree’s sword. They weren’t able to support him in time.

The Blade Master’s body was hit flying at them and when it reached them, all that was left was a corpse.

“The Trash’s End!” Huang Shaotian shouted out the final move name.

Chapter 202 – Experiencing It Personally

“Incredible, but he’s only Level 27. There’s no need for us to waste our time on him.” Someone said.

This was true. The reason they were chasing after Lord Grim’s team so they could kill them was to force them to waste time to recover their lost experience and put them into a red-lettered state.

In Glory, red-lettered equipment meant that the durability was about to reach zero and needed to be fixed. Being in a red-lettered state was similar to this. After a player’s experience dropped below a certain level, the player would need to re-gain the experience in order to recover his stats.

Although red-lettered characters would not be at a lower level, they would not have the same stats as before. The amount of stats lost depended on how much experience had to be recovered. At the same time, they would also need experience to gain back their skill levels.

The guilds were carrying this type of intent. However, towards Flowing Tree, there was no need to waste their time on him. Flowing Tree was only Level 27. No matter how skilled he was, there was no way he could enter the Level 30 Line Canyon. He was never a threat to them.

Everyone there, whether it was because they still had reason or because they wanted to run away, all realized this. Silently, as if nothing had ever happened, each and every one of them slipped away.

Flowing Tree didn’t go and chase them. He slowly moved back behind a tree and sat down.

No matter how great he was, he had no fighting strength without mana.

With only a Level 25 Blue Lightsaber, his damage output could only be average at best. In addition, he was six levels below his opponent. Even though the level suppression in PVP wasn’t as significant as the level suppression in PVE, the damage reduction was still considerable. Huang Shaotian had used a good 90% of his mana to kill his opponent.

Flowing Tree’s bag was also empty. If the other side had decided to surround and attack him, his only choice would have been to run.

Fortunately, the other side decided to leave. Huang Shaotian didn’t have any objections to this.

From this, it could be seen that Huang Shaotian’s trash talk was something he did consciously. In a situation where he had no fighting strength, he stopped talking.

Without any food or potions, just sitting there only had a slow recovery effect. Recovering in this way, he’d need around 10 minutes.

Where’d those guys go?

Huang Shaotian thought. Flowing Tree looked around and saw a leg sticking out from a tree nearby. Huang Shaotian immediately made Flowing Tree roll backwards. Right as he was about to use Sword Draw, a voice came out from behind the tree: “It looks like we should party up.”

Ye Xiu’s voice. Huang Shaotian let out a sigh.

“Did you throw them off?” Huang Shaotian asked.

“Nope, they’ll be here very soon.”

“I have no mana.” Huang Shaotian said.

Lord Grim rummaged through his pockets and threw some food and potions onto the ground.

“How weak! Carrying so many items.” Huang Shaotian picked them up while mocking Ye Xiu.

“This is called being prepared.” Ye Xiu obviously understood what Huang Shaotian meant. The less weight a character carried, the better. The more skilled you were, the more weight would affect you.

After picking up all the items, Huang Shaotian immediately made Flowing Tree drink a potion to recover his mana.

“They’re here! I’ll be heading off then.” Ye Xiu said

“Protect me for a sec.” Huang Shaotian said.

“Protect you? Are people bothering you?” Ye Xiu said as Lord Grim ran off. Voices saying “Over there!”, “Over there!” came out from the forest. Characters poured out from the trees. Some of the players glanced at Flowing Tree, but completely ignored him and continued to chase after Lord Grim.

“Get me a sword from one of them! This Blue Lightsaber is too disgusting!” Huang Shaotian sent Ye Xiu a message.

“Do you have any common sense? These people are all Level 30. Do you think you can use the equipment they drop?” Ye Xiu replied.

“Tch, so annoying!” Huang Shaotian concealed his low-leveled mistake.

The players madly chased. Swift Run, changing directions, their hands were about to cramp up from making so many movements. On the other hand, the two Gods were chatting.

Flowing Tree drank his potion as he watched his mana recover. Huang Shaotian ignored those players who ignored him. Suddenly, a Blade Master caught his eye. He was moving his camera around like crazy and was trying to find where Lord Grim was. He stood there dumbly for a short moment. He seemed to have sent a message to ask for Lord Grim’s whereabouts and then rushed over in that direction.

This Blade Master was using a Broadsword. The Broadsword had high Physical Attack and even though it had slow Attack Speed, quite a few Blade Masters liked to use it. As one of the top Blade Master experts, Huang Shaotian could obviously use all the different types of swords. Seeing this player’s Broadsword, he immediately ran over: “Hey, Blade Master! You, wait a sec.”

The Blade Master ignored him and continued to run.

“Hey, I’m telling you to wait! You have no manners! Even if you don’t have voice on, I won’t forgive you! How can you not have voice chat on if you’re playing Glory? Can you? Can you? Can you?” Huang Shaotian shouted while waving his sword. That Blade Master seemed to have decided to ignore him and continued to run without even turning his head.

“Isn’t that Broadsword the Strike Sword? A Level 25 Orange weapon, not bad! But with that, you’ll be carrying more weight than me. And let me tell you this, besides a few potions, I don’t have anything else on me! Nothing else! Do you know what this means? This means that even if you stripped yourself, I’d still be able to catch up to you! There’s no point in running. Look, I’ve only said a few words and the distance between us has already pulled closer by quite a bit. So what’s the point in running? Stop and chat with me bro. Do you want to switch weapons? It’s a Level 30 Lightsaber, Blue Grade. Attack Speed of 10. If you use it, you’ll love it! I can guarantee that you’ll like it more than your Broadsword……”

“F*ck you. You’re only Level 27. What Level 30 Lightsaber!!” That Blade Master couldn’t resist lashing back.

“Good. Your observational skills have moved me to tears. You even know that I’m Level 27? Then why are you running? Come here and fight me!”

“Bro, I’ve got no time!” The Blade Master didn’t stop.

“You can only blame yourself. Triple Slash.” Huang Shaotian shouted out the name of the skill and a Triple Slash came out. As a movement skill, he quickly caught up to him. The Blade Master hastily used a Triple Slash as well to hurry forward.

“Ha ha ha ha! Too slow!” Huang Shaotian laughed out loud. The third slash of his Triple Slash hit the back of the Blade Master.

“You’re too careless, bro. With that weight you’re carrying and that type of attack speed, do you think you’d be able to escape my Triple Slash? No use! Now you know how great I am!” Huang Shaotian continued to move his mouth as he chased. This Blade Master had an Orange weapon meaning that he must be an important member of a guild and would be more skilled than the Blade Master that Huang Shaotian had defeated easily…… But, he was still just a normal player. It was still as if an ant was fighting against an elephant.

Even though the Blade Master’s skill wasn’t bad, there was no way he could compete with Huang Shaotian. In addition, he suffered from a back attack at the very start. At this moment, he wasn’t even able to turn his camera around in time, when he began getting comboed. Seeing how none of his allies were nearby, the Blade Master was afraid that he might die there. Even worse, he didn’t even have time to curse before he died. His enemy was hacking at him while chatting non-stop, annoying as hell.

These people wouldn’t necessarily think of Huang Shaotian when they saw this type of chattering Blade Master.

Normal players only recognized Huang Shaotian from match recordings and was their idol, especially for Blade Masters. From a spectator’s view, they would think that Huang Shaotian’s trash talk was beautiful, especially when his opponent would mess up in rage. Fans would all laugh.

And now, personally experiencing such an attack, the only feeling in their hearts besides annoyance was annoyance. This type of feeling was completely different from what they felt when they watched Huang Shaotian do it.

Under these two attacks, the Blade Master was quickly unable to hang on. Sword light twisted across his body and his health continued to drop. But at this moment, he was already no longer in the mood to care about all this. Why am I not dead yet? These were his thoughts.

His wish seemed to have come true.

When his health hit rock-bottom, the other side’s attacks stopped. The Blade Master heaved a sigh of relief, the torture was finally over!

The screen turned gray and the camera zoomed out, no longer in a first-person point of view. And like a ghost that had floated out of its body, he watched as his corpse fell from the air.

“F*ck!!” The Blade Master suddenly cursed. Unfortunately, when his character died, voice would no longer be transmitted out.

He watched as the Broadsword in his hands also fell.

“Wow, what good luck! I just kill some random guy and he drops an Orange weapon? The game really is different after not playing for so long! It wasn’t easy saving up so much luck.” Huang Shaotian was still chattering.

“Let me borrow this. I’ll give it back when I’m done.” Huang Shaotian picked up the Level 25 Orange Strike Sword and a word bubble popped out from his head. He knew that even though the other side couldn’t hear him, he could still see the word bubble. His corpse was still there, so he hadn’t yet revived back to the city!